TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Eighth	O
and	O
Last	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROCAS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1730	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
VIII	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
YEAR	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Ivy-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXX	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
15th	O
,	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
1730	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fourth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
BROCAS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Raymond	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Raby	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Say	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hows	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Dovey	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Templeman	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dollar	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ayliffe	I-pers
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Timbrel	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
David	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
6	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Whitlock	I-pers
and	O
another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taking	O
the	O
Sugar	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hogshead	O
upon	O
Botolph	O
's	O
Wharf	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
heartly	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Disherman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallow	B-place
's	I-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bargout	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Gateway	O
of	O
Chester-Key	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Bickerstaff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
70	O
l.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
hired	O
Servant	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Month	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
his	O
Steward	O
)	O
and	O
himself	O
a	O
Master	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
(	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
Servant	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
paid	O
the	O
70	O
l.	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
use	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
use	O
,	O
but	O
unhappily	O
going	O
into	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
where	O
some	O
Men	O
were	O
Gaming	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
losing	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
Felony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Texton	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Zachary	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Kerk	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
Forster-Lane	B-place
about	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
three	O
Men	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
clapp	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
put	O
their	O
Hands	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
demanded	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Rings	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denying	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
a	O
few	O
Steps	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
thought	O
himself	O
out	O
of	O
Pistol-shot	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
turning	O
again	O
,	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Horne	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
running	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
them	O
;	O
two	O
ran	O
into	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
up	O
a	O
turning	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Evidences	O
agreed	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Person	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
themselves	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
having	O
gotten	O
away	O
;	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Merrey	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Chick-Lane	B-place
about	O
Twelve	O
or	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
over-against	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Kennel	O
;	O
that	O
without	O
either	O
speaking	O
a	O
Word	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
standing	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
in	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
kneel	O
'd	O
upon	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
Hand	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Money	O
chink	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
struggled	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
held	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
several	O
Blows	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
there	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
exactly	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
see	O
how	O
I	O
am	O
beat	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Brunskel	I-pers
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Gulliford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
hearing	O
an	O
outcry	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Dennis	B-pers
Cormick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
14	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Netherton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
holding	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Horse	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
his	O
Coat	O
to	O
move	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Arabella	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Ryden	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
into	O
Dobson	B-place
's	I-place
Brandy-shop	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Old-Bailey	I-place
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
down	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Brandy	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
came	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Collibery	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Lodger	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Shirt	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Shirt	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
necessitated	O
,	O
did	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Chair-Woman	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
open	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Christ-Church	I-place
,	I-place
Spittle-Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
85	O
Yards	O
of	O
Camblet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
45	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Rosetto	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Spear	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
present	O
October	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Spear	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
Morning	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
hearing	O
an	O
out-cry	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
Robb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
under	O
a	O
Bed	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
turn	O
a	O
Throwing-Mill	O
in	O
his	O
Father-in-Law	O
's	O
Work-shop	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
putting	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
under	O
a	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
examined	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
taken	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
the	O
Warehouse-Door	O
being	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
carried	O
them	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
carried	O
them	O
out	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
two	O
Pieces	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
whole	O
six	O
were	O
too	O
heavy	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Shoes	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
calling	O
his	O
Fellow-Prentice	O
,	O
she	O
run	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
old	O
Master	O
's	O
(	O
deceas	O
'd	O
)	O
Bed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
slipt	O
in	O
privately	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Night	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
her	O
Sister	O
having	O
Lock	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
call	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
have	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
for	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
that	O
Morning	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Upon	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Lydia	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Artillery-Ground	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Sconces	O
,	O
11	O
Pictures	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
two	O
Stows	O
,	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
and	O
Chairs	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Pyson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
-	O
Cox	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
entrusted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
pawn	O
Goods	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
pawned	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
converted	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
use	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Nailor	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Westburn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Norton-Falgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Bays	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Abigail	B-pers
Godson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Westcoat	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
29	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
6000	O
Nails	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boards	O
which	O
the	O
latter	O
swore	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Possession	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Persons	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
Years	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
69	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Knot	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Coat	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Audley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Coat	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
having	O
taken	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
giving	O
the	O
Box	O
a	O
push	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
into	O
her	O
Coat	O
that	O
was	O
pinned	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
11	O
She	O
ep	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
lost	O
the	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
found	O
the	O
Skins	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
's	O
a	O
Felt-monger	O
,	O
in	O
Barnaby-street	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
Bloomsbury-Market	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Evidences	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
of	O
that	O
Nature	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
had	O
committed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Sheep	O
of	O
a	O
Drover	O
near	O
the	O
five	O
Mile	O
Slad	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Mother	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
had	O
always	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Home	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
got	O
into	O
ill	O
Company	O
,	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
her	O
common	O
Practice	O
to	O
come	O
Home	O
and	O
get	O
what	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
desir	O
'd	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
Transported	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
her	O
coming	O
to	O
an	O
ill	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
received	O
his	O
Wages	O
at	O
the	O
Pay-Table	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Billing	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
drank	O
two	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
missing	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
sending	O
for	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
no	O
Body	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
that	O
being	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
she	O
pulled	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
other	O
Evidences	O
of	O
their	O
drinking	O
two	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Gin	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
her	O
having	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
hold	O
in	O
pledge	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
for	O
having	O
carnal	O
Conversation	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
refusing	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Woman	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
Half	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
deny	O
'd	O
his	O
giving	O
the	O
Watch	O
on	O
any	O
such	O
Account	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Alexander	B-pers
Dowrrg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Night	O
Cellar	O
,	O
near	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
where	O
,	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
light	O
him	O
Home	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
Cellar	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
telling	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
neither	O
Silver	O
nor	O
Brass	O
;	O
that	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lent	O
him	O
three	O
Pence	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
drawing	O
the	O
Liquor	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
standing	O
by	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
he	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
slipt	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
feeling	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
Cellar	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
at	O
the	O
Brandy-shop	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Candlesticks	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Anne	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
being	O
alive	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
5	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Filings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Lewen	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
taking	O
Notice	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
suspecting	O
them	O
,	O
watch	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Hat	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
immediately	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edith	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalen	I-place
,	I-place
Mill-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
Robert	O
Wood	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
Alderman	O
Biller	O
's	O
Office	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
speaking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Alderman	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Hatch	O
to	O
be	O
shut	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
at	O
Alderman	O
Billers	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
threw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
among	O
the	O
People	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
one	O
South	O
,	O
that	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
none	O
himself	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Loin	O
of	O
Lamb	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Goose	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
a	O
dead	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hen	O
,	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
lurk	O
about	O
Newgate-Market	O
,	O
a	O
Person	O
suspecting	O
her	O
,	O
watched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Goose	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
Stall	O
,	O
seiz	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
different	O
Things	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
six	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Dressing-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Girl	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Work-house	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
there	O
but	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Fitzer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Coffee-Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Isles	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
gotten	O
a	O
Key	O
that	O
would	O
open	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
fifty	O
Guineas	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
at	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
five	O
Guineas	O
,	O
by	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
three	O
Guineas	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
tax	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
stripp	O
'd	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
laid	O
a	O
Purse	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Draw	O
upon	O
a	O
Shelf	O
by	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
with	O
nothing	O
but	O
his	O
Shirt	O
on	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
as	O
before	O
related	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hitchin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
the	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Liberty	I-place
of	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
having	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
mend	O
two	O
Cane	O
Chairs	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bringing	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
having	O
been	O
telling	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
dropt	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Guinea	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Guinea	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Guinea	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
his	O
Pay-Master	O
Serjeant	O
might	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
deduct	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pay	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Devil	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Guinea	O
in	O
his	O
damn	O
'd	O
Guts	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
appear	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
likewise	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Guinea	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Pay-Master	O
Serjeant	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Crawford	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
always	O
deny	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Guinea	O
in	O
his	O
damn	O
'd	O
Guts	O
.	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Albermarl	O
,	O
Colonel	O
Hamilton	O
,	O
and	O
Captain	O
Southly	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sully	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Aaron	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Trebent	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Derry	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Weight	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
Staining	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lock	O
,	O
212	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
26	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bridgen	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
four	O
Hand-Saws	O
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
Tools	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
as	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sanger	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Tools	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
some	O
Buildings	O
in	O
Mark-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Tools	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
in	O
Billiter-Lane	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Belmosset	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Common	O
Passage	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Rose	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
passing	O
through	O
Rose-Alley	O
about	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
assaulted	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
12s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
were	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
Robbed	O
him	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
very	O
plainly	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
just	O
under	O
the	O
Lamp	O
,	O
that	O
Belmosset	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Rogers	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Minutes	O
in	O
Robbing	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
having	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bloody	O
Condition	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Caffey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
Dwelling	O
in	O
Hand-Alley	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
standing	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bled	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
wash	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
Home	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
also	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Caffey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
How	O
it	O
came	O
about	O
that	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
committed	O
so	O
long	O
since	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
not	O
prosecuted	O
till	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
passing	O
near	O
the	O
Hog-House	O
in	O
Church-Lane	O
,	O
he	O
seeing	O
four	O
Men	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Road	O
from	O
Stepney	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
dare	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
Notice	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Body	O
ready	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
towards	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
turning	O
suddenly	O
into	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
got	O
some	O
Intelligence	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
apprehending	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
accidentally	O
saw	O
Rogers	O
in	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
Belmosset	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
taking	O
Rogers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
describing	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Belmosset	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
several	O
such	O
Persons	O
pass	O
by	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
Belmosset	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
had	O
Robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
Robbed	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
invalidate	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Valiant	O
Trooper	O
,	O
over-against	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
he	O
pulling	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hat	O
which	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
pawned	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
5s	O
.	O
3d	O
.	O
a	O
Piece	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hillendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ravishing	O
and	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
spin	O
.	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Will	O
and	O
Consent	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
Home	O
from	O
a	O
Meeting	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
That	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
Discourse	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
he	O
dragged	O
her	O
down	O
Kingston-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
she	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
caught	O
her	O
bold	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
from	O
Ear	O
to	O
Ear	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
endeavour	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
all	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
holding	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
held	O
her	O
so	O
long	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
almost	O
strangled	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
neither	O
Voice	O
nor	O
Strength	O
;	O
that	O
thus	O
dragging	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
main	O
Road	O
into	O
Kingston-Lane	B-place
,	O
he	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
grassy	O
Place	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
a	O
rising	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Head	O
lying	O
among	O
the	O
Bushes	O
,	O
and	O
punch	O
'd	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Stomach	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
Breath	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
carnal	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
-	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
she	O
did	O
resist	O
and	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
She	O
did	O
cry	O
out	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
struggled	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
able	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
stopping	O
her	O
Breath	O
,	O
by	O
holding	O
her	O
Throat	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
hard	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Power	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
nor	O
strive	O
any	O
longer	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
repeated	O
Oaths	O
threatened	O
to	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
from	O
Ear	O
to	O
Ear	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
How	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
?	O
she	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
Wet	O
within	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
an	O
Hundred	O
Miles	O
off	O
,	O
threatening	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
from	O
Ear	O
to	O
Ear	O
.	O
-	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
no	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Field-Heath	O
,	O
not	O
much	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
off	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Hillendon	O
under	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Disorder	O
,	O
complaining	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
dragged	O
into	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
modest	O
sober	O
Girl	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
Home	O
at	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
she	O
complain	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
Violence	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
almost	O
choak	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
resisted	O
to	O
the	O
utmost	O
of	O
her	O
Power	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
almost	O
choaked	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
her	O
Breath	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
her	O
Daughter	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
led	O
into	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
scarce	O
speak	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fainted	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
gave	O
her	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
to	O
recover	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
How	O
old	O
her	O
Daughter	O
was	O
?	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
She	O
was	O
18	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
going	O
between	O
Hillendon	O
and	O
Uxbridge	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
neither	O
Dark	O
nor	O
Light	O
,	O
but	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
see	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
hear	O
several	O
shrieks	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
saw	O
no	O
Body	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
the	O
found	O
of	O
some	O
Person	O
treading	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
no	O
Body	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Hillendon	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
How	O
far	O
he	O
was	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Fact	O
is	O
said	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
committed	O
?	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
He	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
150	O
Yards	O
.	O
Another	O
Evidence	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
time	O
mention	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
towards	O
that	O
Place	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
after	O
this	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
attended	O
with	O
Convulsion	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
Ill	O
for	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Tumour	O
in	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
might	O
be	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
pinching	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
grew	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
hard	O
Swelling	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
break	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Uproar	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Door	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
led	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Persons	O
,	O
Men	O
and	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
dragg	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
Kingston-Lane	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
ravish	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
the	O
Question	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
round	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Clothes	O
were	O
not	O
dirty	O
;	O
others	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dirty	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
rainy	O
Day	O
,	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
till	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
and	O
Kingston-Lane	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
dirty	O
Lane	O
,	O
others	O
said	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Lane	O
was	O
passable	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
however	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
rising	O
places	O
in	O
it	O
that	O
were	O
dry	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
at	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
of	O
that	O
Day	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Throat	O
was	O
sore	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
full	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Beavis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
145	O
Guineas	O
,	O
15	O
Broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
3	O
twenty	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
,	O
a	O
4	O
Pistole	O
Piece	O
,	O
two	O
Watches	O
,	O
divers	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gillum	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
Uncle	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
while	O
his	O
Uncle	O
was	O
abroad	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
it	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Bassishaw	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
174	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
7l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shorey	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Ward	I-place
of	I-place
Farringdon	I-place
Within	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Coningsby	B-pers
Kerwood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Gill	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
presently	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Spoon	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ruffiter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Union	B-place
Coffee-house	I-place
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Pegs	O
where	O
Gentlemen	O
hang	O
their	O
Cloaks	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Cloak	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Peg	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursued	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Cloak	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
but	O
pleaded	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
disorder	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
when	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Cornwall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Fletcher	O
's	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
punch	O
on	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
his	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
rose	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Foot	O
slipping	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
the	O
start	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
hurt	O
his	O
Foot	O
,	O
got	O
clear	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Latimer	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Watch	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
following	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
privately	O
taking	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Stephen	B-pers
Mallard	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Danbury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hammersmith	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
intrusted	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
absent	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pace	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Wig	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
very	O
probably	O
lose	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
deposing	O
several	O
Circumstances	O
that	O
rendered	O
it	O
improbable	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
take	O
the	O
Wig	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
3	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
being	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
and	O
Phillis	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
Miller	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
Lane	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Boar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Tankard	O
was	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Rabbit-loft	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Hole	O
between	O
the	O
Floor	O
and	O
the	O
Cieling	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Communication	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Trap-Door	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
House	O
,	O
into	O
that	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
also	O
having	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Foster-Lane	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Mare	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
sen.	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
left	O
a	O
Trunk	O
of	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Clark	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
Willis	O
;	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
upon	O
Clark	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Confession	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Willis	O
's	O
having	O
any	O
concern	O
in	O
the	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Clark	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
seign	O
have	O
fix	O
'd	O
that	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
producing	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
accidentally	O
meeting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
Clark	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Rechoning	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Petticoats	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
41	O
s.	O
which	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
he	O
telling	O
Wills	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Clothes	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
pawn	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
borrowing	O
more	O
than	O
35	O
s.	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
fetch	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
rather	O
than	O
have	O
the	O
Trouble	O
of	O
doing	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
(	O
Clark	O
)	O
6	O
s.	O
more	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
Promise	O
of	O
paying	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
Wills	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
Clark	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
steal	O
6	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
that	O
was	O
pinned	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bower	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Linen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
taking	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Thatcher	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
Susannah	B-pers
Addison	I-pers
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
there	O
found	O
himself	O
stripp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
naked	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
Robbed	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
getting	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
Susannah	O
Addison	O
,	O
she	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Billers	O
confess	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
Robbed	O
.	O
Susannah	O
Addison	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Sea-Coal-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Fleet-Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
drank	O
Drams	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
left	O
him	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
heard	O
him	O
cry	O
out	O
he	O
was	O
starv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
sitting	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
almost	O
naked	O
,	O
having	O
nothing	O
on	O
but	O
his	O
Breeches	O
and	O
Stockings	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
coming	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Clothes	O
,	O
saying	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
hid	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
in	O
the	O
Shoes	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Sarah	O
Dyer	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Susannah	O
Addison	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hether	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
searching	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
did	O
there	O
find	O
the	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
hidden	O
under	O
some	O
Rubbish	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Vanghan	I-pers
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Addison	O
were	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
Clothes	O
,	O
Shoes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
on	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
that	O
are	O
common	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
but	O
one	O
Door	O
to	O
two	O
Houses	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
that	O
Condition	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
some	O
Clothes	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
also	O
deny	O
'd	O
her	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
They	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Matter	O
depending	O
purely	O
on	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Addison	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Tisdel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
1000	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Linen	O
Rags	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
,	O
and	O
Iron	O
and	O
Leaden	O
Weights	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
;	O
which	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Robert	B-pers
Stader	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	I-place
Spittle-Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stader	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-Chapel	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
8	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Bengall	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Sydenham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
That	O
Robert	O
Stader	O
being	O
a	O
Covenant	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
carrying	O
away	O
Bobbins	O
of	O
Silk	O
a	O
Nights	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
Work	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
got	O
the	O
Silk	O
wound	O
off	O
,	O
did	O
bring	O
back	O
the	O
empty	O
Bobbins	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
Bobbins	O
delivered	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
throw	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
finding	O
a	O
Bale	O
of	O
Silk	O
fall	O
short	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
three	O
full	O
Bobbins	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stader	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Father	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hen	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hen	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Garden	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
four	O
others	O
were	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hen	O
was	O
then	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Fowls	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
good	O
gound	O
for	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
no	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Macguy	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Dalloon	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Macguy	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Jane	B-pers
Dalloon	I-pers
being	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
away	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
carried	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
married	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Suits	O
of	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
her	O
new	O
Husband	O
's	O
being	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Ellis	B-pers
Tuner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Duroy	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cheshire	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
Intent	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Arabella	B-pers
Lewden	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Starling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Swanson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-Chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Scully	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Jury	O
not	O
thinking	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sufficient	O
,	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
Convict	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Katharine	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Burdier	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
meeting	O
Katherine	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Hay	O
Market	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
one	O
Austin	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Monmouth-Court	O
,	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
bringing	O
in	O
Geneva	O
,	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
laying	O
his	O
Watch	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
Cannon	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Rachel	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
October	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
16	O
Guineas	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
.	O
Prichard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
Drunk	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
since	O
absconded	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
to	O
their	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Old	O
Bedlam	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
pulling	O
out	O
his	O
Money	O
for	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Sleeve	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
but	O
a	O
Halfpenny	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
leaving	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
lost	O
16	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
coming	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
living	O
near	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanting	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
his	O
Friend	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Guinea	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
take	O
Care	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Matter	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
lose	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
take	O
Care	O
how	O
he	O
went	O
a	O
Whoring	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
alledge	O
nothing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
his	O
Friend	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
,	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Guinea	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
who	O
got	O
the	O
16	O
Guineas	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lovet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
taking	O
two	O
Bags	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
Lovet	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
was	O
Lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Scrutore	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
some	O
Person	O
had	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Sash-Window	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
the	O
Blind	O
being	O
thrown	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
complaining	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Little	O
,	O
his	O
next	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
at	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
through	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
Yard	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
said	O
out	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
disturb	O
the	O
Family	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
knowing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
knowing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
discharg	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Silver	O
was	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
some	O
Hampstead	O
Coachmen	O
,	O
made	O
enquiry	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
apprehended	O
her	O
drinking	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bag	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Silver	O
was	O
lying	O
under	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sat	O
;	O
that	O
enquiring	O
of	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
paid	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
change	O
;	O
that	O
sh	O
e	O
did	O
afterwards	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Guinea	O
was	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
the	O
Night	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
with	O
some	O
Coachmen	O
to	O
a	O
Night-Cellar	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
spend	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Punch	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Little	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
through	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Service	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Pales	O
that	O
parted	O
his	O
Yard	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
being	O
broken	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
(	O
as	O
is	O
suppos	O
'd	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
22	O
s.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
left	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
examined	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
Remainder	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
Punch	O
over-against	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
conceal	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
Money	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
divers	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
85	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fenwick	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
made	O
fast	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
his	O
Wife	O
waked	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
or	O
Bustling	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
listened	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
hearing	O
any	O
Noise	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Sleep	O
again	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
his	O
Servant	O
John	B-pers
Trotman	I-pers
told	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
Robb	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Beaufet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Corner-Cupboard	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
Back-Parlour	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
seldom	O
went	O
into	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Window	O
open	O
;	O
but	O
observing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
no	O
force	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
used	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
guess	O
'd	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
Family	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
his	O
Footman	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Maids	O
,	O
but	O
enquiring	O
among	O
their	O
Friends	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
honest	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Proof	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
committed	O
to	O
Prison	O
,	O
but	O
permitted	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
And	O
having	O
advertis	O
'd	O
his	O
Plate	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Intelligence	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
,	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
searching	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
Letter	O
sent	O
by	O
C	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
directed	O
,	O
To	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
,	O
Glover	O
,	O
in	O
Guy's-Court	O
,	O
in	O
Vinegar-Yard	O
,	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
these	O
Words	O
.	O
Dear	O
Tom	O
,	O
Let	O
me	O
see	O
you	O
at	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
to	O
Morrow	O
Morning	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Postern-Spring	O
,	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
C	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
That	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
the	O
Linen	O
found	O
in	O
Rivers	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
at	O
the	O
White-Horse-Inn	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Girst	I-pers
;	O
that	O
Rivers	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
Shirts	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Burket	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
The	O
Shirt	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
of	O
Rivers	O
's	O
Back	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Girst	I-pers
had	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shirts	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lace	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Rivers	O
's	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Grub	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Pawn-Broker	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
Rivers	O
brought	O
him	O
56	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Plate	O
about	O
1	O
or	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
13	O
l.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
his	O
Landlord	O
and	O
Landlady	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
Wine	O
Vault	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Girst	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
on	O
Friday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
a	O
Letter	O
came	O
directed	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
by	O
Noon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
went	O
with	O
Rivers	O
to	O
meet	O
C	O
-	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Candle	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
having	O
drank	O
there	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
a	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
C	O
-	O
said	O
to	O
Rivers	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
bring	O
some	O
Body	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Rivers	O
ask	O
'd	O
C	O
-	O
whether	O
he	O
should	O
bring	O
him	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
bring	O
him	O
as	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Rivers	O
(	O
both	O
Lodging	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
)	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
following	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
with	O
the	O
Door	O
a	O
jarr	O
,	O
peeping	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
C	O
-	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Beaufet	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Candle	O
burning	O
in	O
a	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
C	O
-	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Carpet	O
on	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Napkins	O
and	O
Linen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Buroe	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Lac	O
'd	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
serch	O
'd	O
the	O
Tea	O
Equipage	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Silver	O
Canisters	O
,	O
and	O
Rivers	O
bundled	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
Rivers	O
carried	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Rivers	O
's	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Guys-Court	O
in	O
Vinegar-Yard	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Chairman	O
,	O
and	O
Rivers	O
having	O
pawn	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
Oxford	O
,	O
carrying	O
the	O
Plate	O
thither	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
at	O
the	O
Inn	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
C	O
-	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
about	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
Rivers	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
himself	O
could	O
have	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
?	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Rivers	O
brought	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
shree	O
Castors	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
without	O
a	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Girst	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
C	O
-	O
came	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
,	O
if	O
two	O
Men	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Rivers	O
and	O
Girst	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
C	O
-	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
C	O
-	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Rivers	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
to	O
C	O
-	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
their	O
Verdict	O
in	O
Special	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dewd	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Devedy	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Meercliff	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
uttering	O
and	O
vending	O
one	O
Deer-Skin	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
stamp	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
counterfeit	O
Stamp	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forg	O
'd	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
feloniously	O
offering	O
to	O
Sale	O
6	O
Sheep	O
skins	O
,	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
counterfeit	O
Stamp	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
Stamp	O
to	O
be	O
Counterfeit	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
sell	O
one	O
Deer-skin	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Stamp	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Matth.ias	B-pers
Knegg	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Machieg	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isabel	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gwin	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
and	O
harbouring	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vanderwest	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
2	O
,	O
3	O
,	O
or	O
4	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Matthias	B-pers
Knegg	I-pers
at	O
Mrs.	O
Eaton	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
Tavern	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Diamond	O
Ear	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Eaton	O
's	O
Ears	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
said	O
Matthias	O
Knegg	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Robbed	O
by	O
her	O
of	O
his	O
Rings	O
,	O
that	O
Sullivan	O
being	O
too	O
quick	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Lambert	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
Matthias	B-pers
Knegg	I-pers
went	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
Rings	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
Sullivan	O
,	O
she	O
absconding	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Sullivan	O
was	O
Lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
German	O
,	O
Matthias	O
Knegg	O
,	O
came	O
several	O
times	O
about	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Harvey	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
for	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
attending	O
upon	O
Sullivan	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
walking	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
she	O
held	O
out	O
her	O
Fingers	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
had	O
she	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
div	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
Fingers	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
soon	O
leave	O
England	O
;	O
but	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Pockets	O
that	O
ever	O
she	O
had	O
picked	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
name	O
like	O
the	O
German	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
knocks	O
in	O
them	O
that	O
had	O
even	O
her	O
Fingers	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Sullivan	O
said	O
she	O
wished	O
Moll	O
Harvey	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
the	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
her	O
,	O
Liberty	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Lebat	I-pers
desired	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Knegg	O
should	O
take	O
up	O
Sullivan	O
for	O
stealing	O
his	O
Ear-rings	O
by	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Lambert	O
;	O
but	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
came	O
with	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
rescued	O
her	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Ear-rings	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Brien	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Obrien	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jane	B-pers
Kidd	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Ruby	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
other	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Garnet	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
about	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
over-against	O
the	O
Savoy-Gate	B-place
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
five	O
Men	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
which	O
came	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Rings	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
their	O
Faces	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
Day-light	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
believe	O
that	O
Obrien	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
Bernard	O
Fink	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
to	O
Rob	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Warrington	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
having	O
Robb	O
'd	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
before	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
Gentlewomen	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Obriens	I-pers
and	O
Hugh	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
put	O
Pistols	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
deliver	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
two	O
Ladies	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pockets	O
,	O
they	O
flung	O
the	O
Pockets	O
away	O
into	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
distributed	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
wore	O
on	O
their	O
Fingers	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Windsor	O
;	O
that	O
Johnson	O
had	O
a	O
Ring	O
with	O
one	O
Stone	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Sparks	O
round	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Brian	O
had	O
a	O
Ruby	B-pers
Ring	I-pers
with	O
2	O
Sparks	O
on	O
each	O
Side	O
;	O
and	O
Morris	O
had	O
a	O
green	O
Stone	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
lost	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
to	O
Windsor	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Saturday	O
about	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Ring	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
Johnson	O
's	O
Wife	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
this	O
Evidence	O
)	O
had	O
two	O
Guineas	O
for	O
his	O
Share	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
that	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
sold	O
for	O
three	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Warrington	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
Robbing	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
three	O
Soldiers	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
presenting	O
their	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
threatning	O
to	O
shoot	O
them	O
through	O
the	O
Head	O
if	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
molest	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
turned	O
down	O
a	O
turning	O
by	O
the	O
Savoy	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
denying	O
their	O
being	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
he	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
almost	O
all	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
near	O
Brook's-Market	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
at	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
Robb	O
'd	O
three	O
Gentlemen	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Poplet	O
came	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pursue	O
some	O
Rogues	O
that	O
had	O
Robb	O
'd	O
at	O
Hockley	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
;	O
that	O
arriving	O
at	O
Windsor	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
Morris	O
and	O
Bryan	O
in	O
Prescot-Street	O
,	O
just	O
going	O
into	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
that	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
that	O
seizing	O
them	O
,	O
Morris	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
were	O
at	O
Datchet	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
sent	O
Poplet	O
to	O
Datchet	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
-	O
Poplet	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Datchet	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
Assistance	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
,	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Landlord	O
deny	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Warrington	O
,	O
Johnson	O
and	O
Fink	O
all	O
in	O
Bed	O
together	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
Breeches	O
under	O
the	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and-two	O
Pistols	O
loaded	O
lay	O
between	O
the	O
Breeches	O
and	O
the	O
Bolster	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
apprehended	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Rings	O
upon	O
their	O
Finger	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
those	O
were	O
the	O
Rings	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
Robb	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Fink	O
and	O
Warrington	O
;	O
and	O
Obrien	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Evidences	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
Obrien	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
at	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hasper	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Obrien	O
invited	O
him	O
to	O
Supper	O
that	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
his	O
Birth-day	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
from	O
10	O
to	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
be	O
same	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Ferrers	O
Obrien	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
Month	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Obrien	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Merry-making	O
,	O
till	O
