TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1731	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
1	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXI	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
AND	O
ON	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
Thursday	O
,	O
Friday	O
,	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
9th	O
,	O
10th	O
,	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
1731	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Page	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Standish	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ilston	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jemmit	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Heron	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Shackerly	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hewlet	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
,	O
Oshaston	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Crafton	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Shouter	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
fixing	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
and	O
Christian	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
2	O
Girls	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Cockburn	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
a	O
Gilt	O
Metal	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
3	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Shew	O
Glass	O
at	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
afterwards	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Cockburn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
on	O
her	O
Information	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Creature	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
Apprentice	O
by	O
the	O
Parish	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
that	O
sells	O
Fish	O
and	O
Pork	O
,	O
and	O
Butter	O
and	O
Eggs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
so	O
one	O
Night	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
into	O
Gracechurch-street	O
,	O
who	O
should	O
I	O
meet	O
but	O
Sue	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
,	O
Chrissy	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Beck	B-pers
Cockburn	I-pers
;	O
and	O
so	O
says	O
Save	O
,	O
Lord	O
!	O
Bess	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
!	O
where	O
are	O
ye	O
going	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
why	O
then	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
ye	O
little	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
e'en	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Markham	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
3	O
of	O
us	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
while	O
Sue	B-pers
Bean	I-pers
went	O
over	O
and	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Shew	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Beck	O
Cockburn	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Snuff	O
Boxes	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
away	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
Ballad-singing	O
Jack	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
He	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
first	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Whitlow	I-pers
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
ready	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
trust	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Radford	O
's	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
lye	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
came	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
Jack	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
Radford	O
will	O
buy	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
you	O
stand	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
sees	O
you	O
,	O
she	O
wo	O
n't	O
meddle	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
we	O
to	O
Jack	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
by	O
your	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
Bargain	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
So	O
away	O
goes	O
Jack	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
he	O
comes	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
tells	O
us	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
we	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
get	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
goes	O
again	O
and	O
brings	O
us	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
now	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
odd	O
half	O
Guinea	O
for	O
my	O
Pains	O
:	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
we	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
little	O
too	O
hard	O
with	O
us	O
then	O
,	O
we	O
think	O
6	O
s.	O
is	O
pretty	O
well	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
gave	O
him	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
share	O
the	O
rest	O
among	O
our	O
selves	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Whereof	O
,	O
says	O
Jack	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
make	O
a	O
Noise	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
go	O
by	O
your	O
selves	O
and	O
share	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
except	O
you	O
'll	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
a	O
Fire	O
with	O
a	O
whole	O
Peck	O
of	O
Coals	O
and	O
a	O
Faggot	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
we	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
Love	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
to	O
venture	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
meeting	O
with	O
my	O
Mistress	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
left	O
Jack	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
Door	O
to	O
divide	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
quarrelled	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
whereof	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Markham	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Radford	O
's	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Bess	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
'em	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stockwell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Cornhall	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
300	O
Weight	O
of	O
Beef-Suet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
his	O
Mistress	O
,	O
Alice	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Hazard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Undershaft	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Crape	O
Hatband	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
in	O
Lime-street	B-place
;	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
wo	O
n't	O
you	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
Present	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
Present	O
of	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
stood	O
talking	O
together	O
a	O
little	O
friendly	O
,	O
I	O
catched	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
this	O
Hatband	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Hatband	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
called	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
thinking	O
it	O
proper	O
to	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
indicted	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Hatband	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
wrongfully	O
accused	O
of	O
the	O
Guinea	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
18	O
d.	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
cut	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
fell	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Proof	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pearl	O
Trunk	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
6	O
China	O
Cups	O
and	O
Saucers	O
,	O
1	O
Muslin	O
,	O
2	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
1	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Jemima	B-pers
Pemmell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Sister	O
in	O
Long	O
's	O
Ward	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
's	I-place
Hospital	I-place
.	O
The	O
Trunk	O
(	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
in	O
it	O
)	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
where	O
a	O
Patient	O
lay	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Helper	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
to	O
carry	O
off	O
the	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Possession	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Martha	B-pers
Robingon	I-pers
being	O
Alive	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Body	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
two	O
Marriages	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
laid	O
Claim	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
lawfully	O
married	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
convicted	O
of	O
a	O
second	O
Marriage	O
before	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lugroof	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Sunbury	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
feloniously	O
slaying	O
William	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
by	O
Beating	O
,	O
bruising	O
,	O
and	O
casting	O
him	O
Headlong	O
down	O
a	O
Cellar	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Fall	O
he	O
received	O
one	O
mortal	O
Fracture	O
in	O
the	O
crown	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
(	O
both	O
Bargemen	O
)	O
were	O
wrestling	O
together	O
(	O
not	O
in	O
Malice	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
to	O
try	O
their	O
Strength	O
)	O
at	O
the	B-place
Magpye	I-place
in	I-place
Sunbury	I-place
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
down	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Fall	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
his	O
Head	O
against	O
a	O
Butt	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
fractured	O
his	O
Scull	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
immediately	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
accidental	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
1	O
Moidore	O
,	O
1	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wayman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Whitnell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
help	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Wayman	O
on	O
his	O
Horse	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
at	O
Kilburn	O
,	O
about	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
Green	O
Purse	O
with	O
Gold	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rush	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Wayman	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
Kilburn	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
black	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
stone	O
Dead	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
Watch	O
(	O
't	O
was	O
then	O
past	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
)	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
but	O
no	O
Purse	O
,	O
nor	O
Gold	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
murdering	O
and	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Wayman	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Purse	O
away	O
for	O
fear	O
it	O
should	O
betray	O
him	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
Dead	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
rattled	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
as	O
leave	O
it	O
for	O
another	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
from	O
London	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Hounslow-Whelm	O
,	O
beyond	O
Paddington-Hill	O
,	O
between	O
Five	O
and	O
Six	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Miles	O
farther	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
Dead	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
guggled	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
;	O
and	O
how	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
could	O
you	O
leave	O
your	O
Fellow-Dumb-Creature	O
in	O
that	O
Condition	O
?	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Purse	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
threw	O
the	O
Purse	O
on	O
the	O
Dunghill	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Dunghill	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Stanmore	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
Drunk	O
,	O
but	O
raising	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
Dead	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
a	O
few	O
Yards	O
further	O
,	O
I	O
kick	O
'd	O
a	O
Purse	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
emptied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Dunghill	O
;	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Magnes	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
19	O
Yards	O
of	O
broad	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
having	O
lost	O
several	O
Quantities	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Cloth-worker	O
,	O
and	O
frequently	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
Shop	O
to	O
fetch	O
Cloth	O
to	O
be	O
dress	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
set	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
place	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
superfine	O
Broad	O
Cloth	O
,	O
wrapt	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
far	O
before	O
he	O
oblig	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
begged	O
hard	O
for	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
protected	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Crime	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Guilty	O
of	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
strictly	O
examined	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
several	O
Parcels	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
-	O
Wynn	O
,	O
a	O
Piece-broker	O
,	O
behind	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Mayhew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Watch	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
waked	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
both	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
won	O
it	O
at	O
Cards	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
but	O
bringing	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
pounds	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Right	B-pers
Honourable	I-pers
James	I-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Athol	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Green	O
,	O
about	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
coming	O
up	O
Surrey	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
with	O
Sheet-Lead	O
on	O
their	O
Backs	O
;	O
he	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Green	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Lead	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Boat	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
The	O
Boat	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Manister	I-pers
of	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
that	O
Night	O
at	O
the	O
Strand-Bridge	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Lead	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Athol	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Nurse	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
the	O
Feathers	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
)	O
and	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Spoons	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
being	O
drunk	O
,	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
'em	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
Mistress	O
keeps	O
a	O
Bawdy-House	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
up	O
to	O
Gentlemen	O
to	O
earn	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
she	O
refused	O
,	O
her	O
Mistress	O
swore	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
her	O
Soul	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
prosecute	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Fothergill	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Fothergan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
8	O
Razors	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
Shillings	O
,	O
5	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mantle	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Hargrove	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Saddles	O
and	O
4	O
Bridles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Old	O
Rags	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
50	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Old	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Batt	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
December	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Patrick	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Bed	O
Curtains	O
,	O
2	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
3	O
Sheets	O
,	O
1	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
1	O
Cloak	O
,	O
3	O
Gowns	O
,	O
1	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Caran	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Carny	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
(	O
in	O
Mill-Yard	O
,	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
;	O
)	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Crab	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
a	O
Box-Iron	O
,	O
a	O
Plate	O
,	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Colly	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
let	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	B-pers
Colly	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Askew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
Yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
Linen	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hitchingman	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
plain	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Wainscot	O
Quarter	O
[	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
]	O
Leaves	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Master	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
December	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
my	O
Master	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Master	O
's	O
)	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
10	O
Leaves	O
of	O
Wainscot	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Walford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Moidores	O
,	O
1	O
Broad-Piece	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Katharine	B-pers
Windham	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Mary	O
Brooks	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Ann	O
Walsord	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
against	O
her	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Templeman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
's	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Francis	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hickson	I-pers
,	O
by	O
beating	O
and	O
bruising	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
Blows	O
and	O
Bruises	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
Blow	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
but	O
two	O
Blows	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
Blow	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Breast	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
on	O
receiving	O
which	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
his	O
Coach-Box	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
his	O
Coach	O
standing	O
in	O
Rank	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
along	O
driving	O
a	O
Whitster	O
's	O
Cart	O
with	O
Linen	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
pass	O
without	O
crossing	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
crossing	O
his	O
Cart-Wheel	O
accidentally	O
brush	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
hind	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coach	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
damn	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
came	O
off	O
the	O
Coach-box	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Provocation	O
,	O
struck	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Blows	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stirred	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
his	O
Coach-box	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
betwixt	O
his	O
Coach	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
passing	O
the	O
Cart	O
Wheel	O
brush	O
'd	O
the	O
hind	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coach	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
damning	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Blows	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
trembling	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
to	O
guard	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
once	O
offering	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
turning	O
up	O
the	O
white	O
of	O
his	O
Eyes	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Cart	O
,	O
in	O
crossing	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
brush	O
'd	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coach	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
off	O
his	O
Coach-box	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Blows	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
Hands	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
one	O
Blow	O
.	O
The	O
Street	O
was	O
pretty	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
whole	O
Transaction	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Middleton	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Desire	O
of	O
some	O
Persons	O
,	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Head	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
sign	O
of	O
his	O
receiving	O
his	O
Death	O
by	O
the	O
Fall	O
;	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Mark	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
opening	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
several	O
Contusions	O
in	O
the	O
Thorax	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
coagulated	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Vessels	O
broke	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
were	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
against	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
my	O
Coach	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
gross	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
first	O
.	O
I	O
drew	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Stand	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Benskin	I-pers
.	O
In	O
crossing	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
the	O
Cart	O
Wheel	O
hitch	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
jamm	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
Coach-Wheel	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Jerk	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
strike	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
often	O
,	O
or	O
which	O
struck	O
first	O
.	O
But	O
since	O
the	O
Accident	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Slap	O
o	O
'	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hoper	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Blows	O
with	O
as	O
much	O
Vehemence	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
retreated	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
too	O
hard	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
last	O
Blow	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
over	O
the	O
Channel	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boston	I-pers
.	O
Several	O
Blows	O
pass	O
'd	O
betwixt	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
retreated	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Yards	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
.	O
Several	O
Blows	O
were	O
given	O
by	O
both	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coachman	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
in	O
Rank	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
Deceased	O
through	O
betwixt	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Deceased	O
turn	O
'd	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
the	O
Wheel	O
run	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coach	O
Wheel	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
off	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Blows	O
follow	O
'd	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Rouse	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Drouse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coventry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Bird	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
a	O
Pastry-Cook	O
)	O
about	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
eighteen	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
Pies	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Bell-Savage	O
Inn	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
,	O
with	O
Change	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
the	O
Pies	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Change	O
,	O
as	O
supposing	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
Change	O
at	O
the	O
Inn	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tap-house	O
at	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
that	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Pies	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
returning	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
Coventry	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Gate-way	O
,	O
My	O
Lad	O
,	O
says	O
Coventry	O
,	O
have	O
ye	O
brought	O
the	O
Pies	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
find	O
no	O
body	O
that	O
wants	O
'em	O
.	O
O	O
!	O
says	O
Coventry	O
,	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
wrong	O
Place	O
;	O
they	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
that	O
House	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Inn-Yard	O
)	O
but	O
have	O
you	O
brought	O
Change	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
Change	O
at	O
the	O
Inn	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Pics	O
,	O
says	O
Coventry	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
every	O
House	O
hereabouts	O
for	O
Change	O
,	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
some	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
went	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
related	O
what	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
Coventry	O
.	O
The	O
Family	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
Coventry	O
pointed	O
to	O
were	O
Customers	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
the	O
less	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
sent	O
again	O
with	O
Change	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
a	O
Caution	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
Change	O
,	O
or	O
Pies	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
half	O
Guinea	O
.	O
In	O
returning	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bird	O
;	O
What	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
ha	O
n't	O
ye	O
carried	O
the	O
Pies	O
yet	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
back	O
for	O
Change	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Pies	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
'em	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
'em	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
'em	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
up	O
comes	O
Coventry	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Change	O
.	O
You	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
but	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
half	O
Guinea	O
first	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Coventry	O
fumbled	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
suddenly	O
gave	O
the	O
Boy	O
a	O
Punch	O
on	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
then	O
kept	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
led	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
several	O
Streets	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
looking	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
till	O
thinking	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
she	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Pies	O
in	O
Gillspur-street	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
catch	O
me	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
He	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Paternoster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Darvan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Linen	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Linen	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
were	O
left	O
from	O
a	O
Ground-Room	O
in	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Laundry	O
at	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
We	O
suppose	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Sash	O
was	O
lifted	O
up	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
Waistcoats	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
Mark	B-pers
G.	I-pers
R	I-pers
.	O
under	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Surrey	O
County-Goal	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Callicant	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Nowland	O
,	O
was	O
apprehended	O
(	O
for	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Northook	O
)	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
our	O
Goal	O
.	O
And	O
hoping	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
'Go	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Cranes	O
'	O
in	O
Castle-Lane	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
enquire	O
'	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Ram	O
lives	O
,	O
Paternoster	O
and	O
Darvan	O
'	O
lodge	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
in	O
her	O
'	O
House	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
find	O
'em	O
there	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
'	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
behind	O
Green	O
's	O
Free-school	O
,	O
and	O
'	O
if	O
you	O
miss	O
of	O
'em	O
there	O
too	O
,	O
desire	O
the	O
People	O
'	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
Mr.	O
'	O
Morris	O
the	O
Shoe-maker	O
lives	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
often	O
'	O
meet	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Paternoster	O
is	O
a	O
young	O
'	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
bald	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
wears	O
a	O
fair	O
'	O
Wig	O
,	O
an	O
out-side	O
light	O
Drab	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
'	O
great	O
Cape	O
,	O
his	O
under	O
Clothes	O
are	O
Snuff-colour	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
sometimes	O
blue	O
Grey	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
'	O
with	O
Black	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Crimson	O
'	O
String	O
.	O
Darvan	O
is	O
a	O
young	O
Lad	O
near	O
19	O
'	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
pretty	O
well	O
set	O
,	O
wears	O
a	O
light	O
'	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
new	O
Hat	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Loop	O
and	O
'	O
Button	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
grey	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
work	O
'd	O
'	O
Waistcoat	O
;	O
and	O
sometimes	O
an	O
olive-colour	O
'd	O
'	O
Suit	O
.	O
Each	O
of	O
'em	O
wears	O
a	O
small	O
Diamond-Ring	O
.	O
'	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
Directions	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Cranes	O
in	O
Castle	O
Lane	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Ogilby	I-pers
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ram	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
her	O
if	O
her	O
Lodgers	O
were	O
within	O
,	O
went	O
directly	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
push	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Chamber-Door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
'em	O
in	O
Bed	O
.	O
We	O
secur	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Their	O
Hats	O
,	O
Wigs	O
,	O
Clothes	O
,	O
Watches	O
and	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Persons	O
,	O
answer	O
'd	O
Callicant	O
's	O
Description	O
;	O
and	O
yet	O
with	O
horrible	O
Oaths	O
and	O
Imprecations	O
they	O
protected	O
at	O
first	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
nor	O
heard	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Woman	O
as	O
Callicant	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Drawers	O
we	O
found	O
these	O
7	O
Holland	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
mark	O
'd	O
G	O
R	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Crown	O
at	O
top	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Crowns	O
is	O
partly	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
above	O
20	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Mens	O
and	O
Womens	O
,	O
Silk	O
,	O
Thread	O
and	O
Worsted	O
;	O
some	O
Womens	O
Linen	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Sorts	O
of	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
bought	O
the	O
Mens	O
Apparel	O
for	O
their	O
own	O
wearing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Womens	O
Clothes	O
were	O
their	O
Wives	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
same	O
Goods	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
them	O
these	O
Wires	O
roll	O
'd	O
up	O
thus	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Foot	O
long	O
,	O
when	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Hook	O
at	O
one	O
End	O
.	O
They	O
seem	O
very	O
proper	O
to	O
draw	O
Goods	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
when	O
they	O
lie	O
too	O
far	O
within	O
a	O
Room	O
to	O
be	O
reach	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
only	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ogilby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
same	O
Things	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Possession	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ram	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Castle-Lane	O
,	O
(	O
some	O
call	O
it	O
Cabbage-Lane	O
)	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
my	O
Lodgers	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
the	O
Shoe-maker	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
Gentlemen	O
's	O
Sons	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
700	O
l.	O
left	O
'em	O
by	O
their	O
Godmothers	O
.	O
They	O
kept	O
pretty	O
good	O
Hours	O
.	O
But	O
one	O
Night	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
6	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
huff	O
'd	O
'em	O
for	O
staying	O
out	O
so	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
'em	O
one	O
day	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
with	O
those	O
Wives	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
went	O
a	O
fishing	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	B-pers
,	I-pers
J	I-pers
.	I-pers
Darvan	O
.	O
We	O
do	O
n't	O
deny	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
our	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
we	O
brought	O
'em	O
there	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ram	O
could	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
without	O
our	O
Key	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
one	O
Night	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Room	O
washed	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
Key	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ram	I-pers
.	O
That	O
was	O
only	O
once	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
by	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Did	O
we	O
deny	O
you	O
the	O
Key	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Ram	I-pers
.	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Peterson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Paternoster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Darvan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Suits	O
of	O
Laced	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
2	O
Cambrick	O
Heads	O
and	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
2	O
Muslin	O
Hoods	O
,	O
7	O
Mobs	O
,	O
several	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lingard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
Window	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Lingard	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
A	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
carried	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
advertiz	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
brought	O
'em	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Room	O
(	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
some	O
Account	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Trial	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
Paternoster	O
have	O
some	O
wet	O
Linen	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
hide	O
behind	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
Who	O
does	O
that	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
her	O
Headclothes	O
.	O
Your	O
Wife	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
took	O
'em	O
from	O
him	O
)	O
does	O
your	O
Wife	O
wear	O
such	O
Linen	O
as	O
this	O
?	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Linen	O
;	O
here	O
's	O
14	O
Pieces	O
of	O
'em	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
On	O
reading	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
I	O
carried	O
this	O
Linen	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Sheppard	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Among	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Diamond	O
Pen	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
cut	O
Glass	O
.	O
Paternoster	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Linen	O
was	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ogilby	I-pers
.	O
He	O
said	O
then	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
Cork-cutter	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ram	I-pers
.	O
She	O
that	O
went	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
liv	O
'd	O
near	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
all	O
our	O
Clothes	O
and	O
Watches	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
can	O
prove	O
we	O
bought	O
,	O
and	O
honestly	O
paid	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
we	O
hope	O
we	O
shall	O
have	O
'em	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Louisa	B-pers
Thornwitz	I-pers
,	O
[	O
a	O
Girl	O
]	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Lodging	O
let	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
very	O
plain	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Cornelia	B-pers
Thornwitz	I-pers
,	O
[	O
Mother	O
of	O
Louisa	B-pers
Thornwitz	I-pers
]	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
Yards	O
of	O
Damask	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
6	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Damask	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
fixing	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
,	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isabel	B-pers
Sack	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shield	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Mary	B-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Clothes	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
3	O
Cravats	O
,	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Spatterdashes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Chapel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chapel	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Place	O
in	O
the	O
Oxford	O
Coach	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
to	O
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
it	O
behind	O
.	O
About	O
Hillington	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lutwych	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
the	O
One-ey	O
'd	O
Boy	O
that	O
has	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
from	O
Oxford	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
try	O
'd	O
at	O
Oxford	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
still	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
into	O
Town	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
behind	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
behind	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Bondstreet	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
running	O
with	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
bade	O
the	O
Coachman	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
to	O
pursue	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
slip	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn	O
Play-house	O
,	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
pick	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Bulgress	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Daltman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
1	O
Silver	O
Medal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
13	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Great	B-place
Russel-Street	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Montague	I-place
House	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
about	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Medal	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Directors	O
of	O
the	O
Hand-in-Hand	O
Fire-Office	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
Director	O
has	O
such	O
a	O
Medal	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
shewing	O
of	O
which	O
to	O
the	O
Fire-men	O
,	O
they	O
know	O
his	O
Authority	O
,	O
and	O
readily	O
observe	O
his	O
Orders	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
demanded	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
not	O
delivering	O
readily	O
,	O
he	O
stoop	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Chain	O
,	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
his	O
Pistol-Hand	O
;	O
we	O
struggled	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
stepp	O
'd	O
back	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
my	O
Sword	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
down	O
Queen-street	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Medal	O
and	O
13	O
Shillings	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Moon-light	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
such	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dolman	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Patten-maker	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
's	O
(	O
a	O
Butcher	O
)	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
Boy	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
somebody	O
robbing	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
under	O
Montague	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
stept	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hanger	O
in	O
t'other	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
drive	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
off	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
Hanger	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
kick	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
several	O
others	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Ale	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
Shillings	O
and	O
this	O
Medal	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
Pistol	O
was	O
brought	O
thither	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
charged	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
with	O
Sparrow-shot	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
much	O
Hurt	O
if	O
it	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Broughill	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
over-against	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
's	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Boy	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Dolman	O
running	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
close	O
,	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Heels	O
as	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
a	O
Corner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
,	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
and	O
a	O
Medal	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Outcry	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
flat	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Hanger	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dolman	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
reel	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
forward	O
,	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Dolman	O
kick	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
his	O
Pistol	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
13	O
s.	O
this	O
Medal	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Bag	O
of	O
Gunpowder	O
.	O
Israel	O
Pain	O
,	O
a	O
Chairman	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
their	O
Assistance	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
down	O
together	O
.	O
-	O
Holder	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
Heart	O
over-against	O
where	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Two	O
Boys	O
gave	O
the	O
Alarm	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
said	O
(	O
since	O
his	O
Commitment	O
)	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
if	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
They	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Medal	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
(	O
his	O
Father	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
several	O
Persons	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
3	O
Sheets	O
,	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
15	O
Napkins	O
,	O
7	O
Aprons	O
,	O
1	O
Calamancoe	O
Gown	O
,	O
7	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
1	O
large	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
2	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
1	O
Strainer	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tongs	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Pen	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
1	O
Tortoise-shell	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
;	O
and	O
1	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Parishioners	B-pers
of	I-pers
Christ-Church	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Sexton	O
of	O
Christ-Church	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Vestry-House	B-place
in	I-place
Butcher-Hall-Lane	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
way	O
thro	O
'	O
to	O
the	O
Church	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
attended	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Shew	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
I	O
soon	O
heard	O
that	O
my	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
among	O
the	O
old	O
Clothes	O
Shops	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Savages	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
offer	O
my	O
Calamancoe	O
Gown	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
.	O
When	O
my	O
Husband	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Show	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
too	O
about	O
Twelve	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
One	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Doors	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Hospital	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Patrick	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
and	O
another	O
Man	O
walking	O
to	O
and	O
for	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
for	O
two	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
Stairs	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Patrick	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
follow	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Patrick	O
and	O
another	O
go	O
into	O
Christ-Church	O
Vestry	O
[	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
]	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
youngest	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Door-way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
Patrick	O
)	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
follow	O
'd	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fench	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Patrick	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
Savages	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
to	O
fell	O
some	O
old	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
Things	O
among	O
'em	O
like	O
what	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
left	O
Descriptions	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
while	O
I	O
detain	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
People	O
came	O
afterwards	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Patrick	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Manmouth-street	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Trevors	I-pers
.	O
[	O
This	O
William	B-pers
Trevors	I-pers
was	O
then	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Trial	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
was	O
found	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Trevors	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Patrick	O
crying	O
old	O
Clothes	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
him	O
this	O
Gown	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
then	O
?	O
Trevors	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Patrick	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
Trevors	O
was	O
a	O
most	O
notorious	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Patrick	O
's	O
Gang	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
last	O
Sessions	O
he	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
Dog	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
when	O
Patrick	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
against	O
Robert	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Patrick	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Linen	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Blague	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Calamancoe	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Adderly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Blague	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
2	O
Gowns	O
and	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Savages	O
,	O
the	O
Golden	O
Key	O
,	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fench	I-pers
,	O
Savages	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
Goods	O
to	O
sell	O
with	O
those	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Durant	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopt	O
them	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Savages	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fench	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
that	O
Coat	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Adderly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
These	O
Shoes	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
Lodging	O
,	O
in	O
Abel	O
's	O
Buildings	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
all	O
these	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Trevors	I-pers
.	O
Trevor	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
very	O
true	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Partners	O
stole	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
notwithstanding	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Trevor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Nowls	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Gibson	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloth-Coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
examined	O
separately	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
my	O
Room	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
from	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Door	O
wrench	O
'd	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Trevor	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Then	O
Trevor	O
's	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
'	O
That	O
John	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
'	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
'	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Pall-mall	O
,	O
'	O
one	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
one	O
opposite	O
Stocks-Market	O
,	O
'	O
one	O
at	O
the	O
Dog	O
Tavern	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
,	O
'	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
acquitted	O
;	O
two	O
in	O
Thomas-Street	O
,	O
and	O
'	O
one	O
in	O
a	O
Lane	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	O
,	O
these	O
three	O
'	O
in	O
one	O
Day	O
;	O
one	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
one	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
Door	O
of	O
St.	O
'	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
'	O
.	O
This	O
last	O
is	O
that	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
indicted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
outer	O
Door	O
opens	O
into	O
an	O
Entry	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
4	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Entry	O
dirty	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Bustle	O
above	O
,	O
when	O
presently	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Nowland	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
Trevor	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
he	O
past	O
by	O
me	O
so	O
quick	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
leisure	O
to	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
Nowland	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
5	O
Minutes	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
Who	O
that	O
Man	O
was	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
?	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
a	O
fat	O
Man	O
.	O
And	O
who	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
her	O
Name	O
is	O
Elizabeth	O
-	O
a	O
-	O
What	O
d	O
'ye	O
call	O
her	O
?	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
think	O
of	O
her	O
Name	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
lately	O
married	O
a	O
Weaver	O
.	O
There	O
's	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
lives	O
here	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
Door	O
and	O
his	O
Drawers	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
-	O
Cranwell	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
to	O
Patrick	O
Nowland	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
quest	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Durant	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
There	O
I	O
met	O
Trevor	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
brought	O
in	O
just	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
soon	O
after	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Description	O
agreed	O
with	O
that	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Nowland	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
left	O
out	O
in	O
Trevor	O
's	O
Information	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Trevor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
when	O
I	O
gave	O
in	O
my	O
Information	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
's	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
I	O
confess	O
'd	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
along	O
the	O
Horse-Market	B-place
in	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
,	O
when	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
3	O
Men	O
.	O
Cole	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
clapping	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
!	O
your	O
Money	O
!	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
16	O
Shillings	O
and	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
Pain	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
3d	O
Man	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Horses	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
them	O
plainly	O
by	O
the	O
Lights	O
in	O
the	O
Shops	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
the	O
Houses	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
No	O
.	O
Being	O
fetch	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
then	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
verily	O
believed	O
that	O
you	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
positive	O
then	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
fully	O
recollected	O
my	O
Memory	O
.	O
P	O
-	O
J	O
-	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Pain	O
stood	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
while	O
Cole	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
Door	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
as	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
took	O
more	O
he	O
sunk	O
it	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
together	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Oads	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Goat	O
in	O
Black-Boy-Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
.	O
Pain	O
.	O
He	O
swears	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
when	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Coach	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
false	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
but	O
a	O
Stick	O
.	O
-	O
Oads	O
.	O
P	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
together	O
;	O
they	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
Pain	O
is	O
a	O
Beef	O
Carrier	O
,	O
and	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Jumbo	O
.	O
-	O
Bistow	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Parker's-Lane	O
.	O
Cole	O
and	O
P	O
-	O
lodged	O
together	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
for	O
2	O
Sailors	O
.	O
-	O
French	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Cross-Lane	O
.	O
P	O
-	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Pain	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
but	O
a	O
short	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
I	O
-	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Sea	O
.	O
What	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
him	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Cooper	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
first	O
about	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
P	O
-	O
being	O
apprehended	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
Friends	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pointer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Musician	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Fidler	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Pain	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
Play-fellows	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
a	O
Night	O
or	O
two	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
P	O
-	O
and	O
Cole	O
had	O
drawn	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
apply	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
catch	O
them	O
.	O
Cole	O
.	O
This	O
Fidler	O
keeps	O
a	O
House	O
to	O
entertain	O
Pick-pockets	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
P	O
-	O
and	O
Cole	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
Moor-fields	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Watch	O
at	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Fidler	O
directed	O
me	O
.	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
P	O
-	O
brought	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Pain	O
and	O
the	O
Fidler	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Jury	O
gave	O
their	O
Verdict	O
against	O
Pain	O
,	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
force	O
a	O
Smile	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
all	O
of	O
ye	O
!	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
receive	O
Sentence	O
,	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
Pardon	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
his	O
Rashness	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
when	O
he	O
utter	O
'd	O
those	O
Expressions	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Anne	B-pers
Kendall	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Bermudas	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Kendall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Anne	O
Kendall	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
crossing	O
Holbourn	B-place
from	O
the	O
Little-Turn-Stile	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
2	O
other	O
Men	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
that	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
me	O
a	O
punch	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
with	O
a	O
Link	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
Thing	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
stuck	O
like	O
Pitch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Hat	O
.	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
recover	O
'd	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
lose	O
my	O
Hat	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
in	O
Sight	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
ty	O
'd	O
my	O
Hat	O
fast	O
upon	O
my	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
so	O
hard	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Ribbon	O
about	O
my	O
Neck	O
.	O
So	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
Hat	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
mine	O
is	O
a	O
Bermudas	O
Hat	O
,	O
lined	O
with	O
blue	O
Silk	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
so	O
easily	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
in	O
my	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
losing	O
'em	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
2	O
s.	O
besides	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Priddam	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
my	O
Hat	O
!	O
my	O
Hat	O
!	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
pass	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Presently	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
String	O
about	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
accus	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
Robbing	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
black	O
Hat	O
under	O
his	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
her	O
's	O
was	O
a	O
Bermudas	O
Hat	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
blue	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pitch	O
'd	O
her	O
Face	O
with	O
a	O
Link	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
two	O
Yards	O
found	O
this	O
Bermudas	O
Hat	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
presently	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
his	O
two	O
Companions	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bladen	I-pers
.	O
As	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
cross	O
'd	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
Men	O
attack	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
cry	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
thrust	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
Hat	O
off	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
ran	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
was	O
only	O
in	O
Rognery	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
Fun	O
with	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
by	O
pulling	O
and	O
hauling	O
her	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
letting	O
her	O
slipdown	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
thrust	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Faircloth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
meant	O
no	O
begun	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
fear	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
hurt	O
will	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Hat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Cow	O
's	O
Face	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
came	O
in	O
Drunk	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
pawn	O
'd	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
for	O
some	O
Liquor	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
now	O
she	O
swears	O
that	O
I	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
2	O
s.	O
)	O
But	O
neither	O
Mrs.	O
Fowler	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
nor	O
her	O
Man	O
,	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Cow	O
's	O
Face	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
And	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
.	O
And	O
me	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
2	O
s.	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
two	O
Companions	O
were	O
three	O
notorious	O
Rogues	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
draw	O
them	O
no	O
more	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
turn	O
'd	O
'em	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
said	O
by	O
the	O
Man	O
or	O
the	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Cow	O
's	O
Face	O
is	O
no	O
Evidence	O
on	O
either	O
side	O
,	O
except	O
they	O
were	O
here	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
themselves	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Relations	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
a	O
Weaver	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Parents	O
are	O
honest	O
industrious	O
People	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Proposal	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
his	O
two	O
Companions	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Council	O
was	O
see	O
'd	O
to	O
move	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Constable	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
prove	O
the	O
Fact	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
Case	O
shall	O
I	O
be	O
in	O
?	O
I	O
shall	O
get	O
nothing	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
act	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
Fact	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
fix	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
Justice	O
Hilder	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
on	O
a	O
violent	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
robbed	O
by	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
knocked	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
an	O
Information	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
consulted	O
together	O
about	O
going	O
to	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Crank	O
and	O
Pace	O
,	O
his	O
two	O
Companions	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Constable	O
declin	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Wood	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Prentice	O
.	O
I	O
beat	O
him	O
once	O
about	O
not	O
taking	O
to	O
his	O
Business	O
readily	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
over	O
to	O
his	O
Brother	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
till	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Trade	O
for	O
a	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
believ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Fanny	B-pers
Finnick	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
Sitting	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Hand	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Silk	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
into	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
Quarter	O
past	O
Six	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
Mistress	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
an	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
shuffling	O
the	O
Silk	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Silk	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
Information	O
in	O
Expectation	O
of	O
being	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Justice	O
Du	O
Veil	O
.	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obstinate	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
three	O
Persons	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
since	O
been	O
try	O
'd	O
and	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
a	O
Bill	O
was	O
found	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
prov	O
'd	O
too	O
late	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Mosely	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
along	O
Southampton-Row	B-place
in	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Norman	O
clapp	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
more	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
Rogers	O
came	O
on	O
my	O
Right-side	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
18	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
about	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
more	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
where	O
's	O
your	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
Breeches	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
Norman	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
ye	O
stay	O
for	O
?	O
Go	O
along	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
ye	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
moved	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
Yards	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
afterwards	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
th	O
e	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
as	O
they	O
attempted	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
in	O
Bell-Alley	O
,	O
Coleman-street	O
.	O
Norman	O
confess	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
from	O
above	O
a	O
hundred	O
;	O
several	O
of	O
whom	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
as	O
they	O
attempted	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
in	O
Bell-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
a	O
Cane	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
advis	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
another	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Grand-Jury	O
for	O
London	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Norman	O
's	O
Confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
was	O
read	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
'	O
That	O
on	O
'	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Rogers	O
,	O
and	O
Hunter	O
,	O
'	O
stopt	O
a	O
Man	O
near	O
Pancras	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
'	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
9d	O
.	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
'	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
'	O
himself	O
and	O
Rogers	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
'	O
of	O
8s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
'	O
the	O
20th	O
following	O
,	O
attempted	O
to	O
rob	O
another	O
'	O
Man	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
)	O
in	O
Little-Bell-Alley	O
,	O
'	O
in	O
which	O
Fact	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
'	O
George	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Packer	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
Rogers	O
is	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
served	O
me	O
5	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Servant	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Coronation-Day	O
,	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
beat	O
and	O
bruised	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
asham	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
News	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cockle	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Rogers	O
(	O
his	O
Master	O
being	O
my	O
Packer	O
)	O
has	O
done	O
Business	O
for	O
me	O
these	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
had	O
scarce	O
over	O
less	O
than	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
1000	O
l.	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Power	O
almost	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
wrong	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
100	O
or	O
200	O
l.	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
Cause	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
Rogers	O
with	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
frequent	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Farthing	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woolcott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Duffell	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
fifteen	O
pence	O
half-penny	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Duffell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
Well-Close-Square	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Turning	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
near	O
a	O
Lamp	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
him	O
full	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Bar	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
Prentice	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
Man	O
behind	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
was	O
then	O
beating	O
the	O
Hour	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Fear	O
;	O
but	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
hardly	O
gone	O
3	O
Steps	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Blows	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
fifteen	O
pence	O
half-penny	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
there	O
.	O
With	O
scuffling	O
and	O
struggling	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
good	O
Luck	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
Watch	O
in	O
my	O
Fob	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
(	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
)	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sandford	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
dress	O
'd	O
my	O
Head	O
.	O
In	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Sandford	O
again	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Trouble	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
Watchman	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Fellows	O
run	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
that	O
Man	O
was	O
the	O
Captain	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
went	O
a	O
thieving	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Justice	O
Philips	O
's	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
directly	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
then	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
confused	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Hemorrhage	O
,	O
and	O
dress	O
'd	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
Street-Robbers	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Lamp	O
in	O
Well-Close-Square	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
fifteen	O
pence	O
half-penny	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
beating	O
the	O
Round	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
Fellows	O
rioting	O
and	O
singing	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
playing	O
the	O
Rogue	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
hard	O
Stroke	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
forward	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
Hat	O
or	O
Wig	O
.	O
He	O
begg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hinds	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Salt	O
Petre	O
Bank	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
Fellows	O
near	O
the	O
Square	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
is	O
named	O
-	O
Perkins	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
is	O
call	O
'd	O
Nice	O
Neddy	O
.	O
Standing	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Blow	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
Hat	O
or	O
Wig	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carly	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
himself	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Nice	O
Neddy	O
,	O
and	O
Will	O
Woolcott	O
,	O
and	O
Ned	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
all	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Thing	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
three	O
pence	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pease	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
'Prentice	O
.	O
He	O
serv	O
'd	O
me	O
three	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
receiv	O
'd	O
and	O
paid	O
Money	O
for	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
and	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
(	O
Cooper	O
's	O
Work	O
)	O
among	O
the	O
Merchants	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
wrong	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
till	O
lately	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
drawn	O
away	O
by	O
wild	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Trick	O
of	O
lying	O
out	O
o	O
'	O
Nights	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Petty	O
Treason	O
,	O
in	O
Coining	O
two	O
False	O
and	O
Counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
Pewter	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
base	O
Metal	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Likeness	O
of	O
the	O
Lawful	O
Coin	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
King	O
George	O
the	O
First	O
's	O
Shilling	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
deceive	O
and	O
defraud	O
one	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Subjects	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Late	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
drunk	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Hampstead	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
Gingerbread	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Pench	O
Bowl	O
and	O
Two	O
Blue	O
Posts	O
,	O
in	O
Russel-Street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
bad	O
Shilling	O
to	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Gingerbread	O
.	O
Honest	O
Friend	O
,	O
says	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
(	O
looking	O
on	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
bending	O
it	O
between	O
his	O
Teeth	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
Good	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
another	O
such	O
a	O
Piece	O
you	O
might	O
be	O
brought	O
into	O
Trouble	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
more	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Gingerbread	O
;	O
says	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
another	O
Shilling	O
in	O
your	O
Hand	O
that	O
looks	O
like	O
a	O
Bad	O
One	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
bade	O
him	O
try	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
like	O
the	O
former	O
.	O
By	O
this	O
time	O
several	O
People	O
were	O
got	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Du	O
Veil	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
Examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
'Change	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Man	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
who	O
return	O
'd	O
him	O
those	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
pence	O
half-penny	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
grant	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
that	O
Victualler	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
press	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
Truth	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
vain	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
then	O
brought	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
those	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
more	O
,	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
intended	O
to	O
make	O
fix	O
in	O
all	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
defraud	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
them	O
off	O
for	O
Good	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Fortunatus	O
's	O
Wishing	O
Cap	O
with	O
'em	O
,	O
to	O
divert	O
his	O
Fellow-Servants	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Child	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
Evening	O
.	O
(	O
Fortunatus	O
's	O
Wishing	O
Cap	O
is	O
a	O
Thing	O
that	O
Jugglers	O
show	O
Tricks	O
with	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain-maker	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
Servant	O
,	O
minded	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
intrusted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
Deficiency	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
hearing	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
for	O
Coining	O
Tools	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
Counterfeit	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
perceived	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
struck	O
,	O
but	O
cast	O
in	O
Sand	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
talk	O
about	O
a	O
Wishing-Cap	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Currier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
Witess	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cast	O
the	O
Shillings	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
privately	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Fortunatus	O
's	O
Wishing	O
Cap	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
him	O
talk	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
before	O
about	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
having	O
a	O
Gold	O
Button	O
to	O
match	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
take	O
that	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
the	O
Shillings	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Flask	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
took	O
this	O
Tool	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
frequently	O
used	O
in	O
our	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
the	O
Edges	O
of	O
the	O
Shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Flasks	O
are	O
two	O
Iron	O
Frames	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
kind	O
of	O
Sand	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
we	O
make	O
the	O
Impression	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Fellow-Prentice	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
cast	O
the	O
two	O
Shillings	O
for	O
making	O
a	O
Wishing	O
Cap	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
above	O
a	O
Year	O
before	O
.	O
Several	O
others	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
like	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appearing	O
a	O
silly	O
boyish	O
Trick	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Kenneday	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Table-cloths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Tow	I-pers
,	O
in	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Oggars	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Odgers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-Chapel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Eggs	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Earthen	O
Pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
;	O
which	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Charles	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
[	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
]	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Drawer	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
fix	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Brass	O
Weights	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
Mordecai	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
Duvries	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
,	O
in	O
Forging	O
an	O
Acceptance	O
to	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
drawn	O
on	O
Peter	O
Victorin	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Merchant	O
,	O
for	O
450	O
l.	O
Sterling	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
Defraud	O
the	O
Governour	B-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Bank	I-pers
of	I-pers
England	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	B-pers
Victorin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
publishing	O
the	O
said	O
forged	O
Acceptance	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
fraudulent	O
Design	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
1731	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
having	O
opened	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
proceeded	O
to	O
call	O
their	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
Charge	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carnthers	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Servant	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
several	O
Bills	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
discounted	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
near	O
1000	O
l.	O
among	O
which	O
this	O
Bill	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Victorin	O
,	O
for	O
450	O
l.	O
was	O
one	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Bill	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
]	O
Stockholm	O
,	O
30	O
June	O
,	O
1731	O
.	O
450	O
l.	O
Sterl	O
.	O
Two	O
Months	O
after	O
Date	O
pay	O
this	O
my	O
first	O
,	O
per	O
Exchange	O
,	O
to	O
Johan	B-pers
Good	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Order	O
,	O
Four	O
Hundred	O
and	O
Fifty	O
Pounds	O
,	O
Sterling	O
.	O
Andries	O
Millern	O
.	O
Accepted	O
12	O
July	O
,	O
1731	O
.	O
Payable	O
at	O
Messrs.	O
Knight	O
and	O
Jackson	O
.	O
Pet	O
.	O
Victorin	O
.	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Acceptance	O
very	O
narrowly	O
,	O
suspected	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Committee	O
.	O
They	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
other	O
Bills	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
other	O
Officers	O
of	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
us	O
several	O
times	O
within	O
two	O
Months	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
Bills	O
discounted	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
all	O
honourably	O
paid	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Banker	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Victorin	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
often	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
this	O
Acceptance	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
several	O
Bills	O
on	O
him	O
drawn	O
from	O
Stockholm	O
,	O
but	O
remember	O
none	O
drawn	O
by	O
Andries	O
Millern	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Correspondent	O
,	O
or	O
even	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
such	O
Person	O
in	O
being	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Bill	O
drawn	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Kireman	O
at	O
Stockholm	O
,	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Victorin	O
,	O
for	O
200	O
l.	O
'T	O
is	O
endors	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
accepted	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Victorin	O
himself	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Word	O
Accepted	O
,	O
he	O
writes	O
Accep	O
with	O
a	O
d	O
at	O
top	O
;	O
for	O
Payable	O
,	O
Pay	O
with	O
le	O
at	O
top	O
;	O
for	O
Messieurs	O
,	O
Mess	O
with	O
rs	O
at	O
top	O
;	O
and	O
signs	O
Pet	O
.	O
for	O
Peter	O
.	O
All	O
