TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
1732	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARBER	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1732	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILFORD	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Chapter-House	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARBER	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Page	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bullsink	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Norroy	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Skip	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
,	O
Bennet	B-pers
Metcalf	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gubell	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Winnell	I-pers
,	O
Josias	B-pers
Johannet	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Dobbinson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Durnford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rayne	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lutmar	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Clear	I-pers
,	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Speed	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Sealy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Manteel	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
and	O
one	O
Yard	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Barnard	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
November	O
3	O
.	O
B.	O
Townsend	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
hearing	O
of	O
it	O
afterwards	O
,	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Papers	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Howard	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
in	O
Bell-Savage	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
If	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
my	O
Shop	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
to	O
buy	O
Half	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Muslin	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
take	O
away	O
a	O
Manteel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Velvet	O
?	O
She	O
answered	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
the	O
Velvet	O
into	O
a	O
Hood	O
.	O
Milliscent	B-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Townsend	O
's	O
Shop	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
She	O
ask	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
Muslin	O
;	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
Candles	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
some	O
.	O
She	O
wanted	O
Half	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
we	O
were	O
disputing	O
about	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
another	O
Customer	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
my	O
back	O
to	O
serve	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
For	O
the	O
Manteel	O
with	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
pinn	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
lay	O
ready	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
had	O
bespoke	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
coming	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
both	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Velvet	O
of	O
about	O
a	O
Yard	O
with	O
a	O
Slope	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Townsend	O
so	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
Nov.	O
11.	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Howard	O
's	O
.	O
She	O
readily	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Manteel	O
and	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Velvet	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
tore	O
the	O
Slope	O
of	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Velvet	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
burnt	O
the	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
confess	O
'd	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
on	O
me	O
by	O
Surprize	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Bath	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Muslin	O
?	O
M.	O
Nicholas	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Cloaths	O
had	O
I	O
on	O
?	O
M.	O
Nicholas	O
.	O
A	O
short	O
Mob	O
and	O
a	O
wash	O
'd	O
Gown	O
;	O
you	O
was	O
clean	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
tight	O
Girl	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Lodger	O
November	O
4.	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
Things	O
in	O
security	O
for	O
her	O
Lodging	O
till	O
her	O
Uncle	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Scoley	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Magdalen	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Night-Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
April	O
30	O
.	O
1731	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
above	O
a	O
Year	O
in	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Holms	O
and	O
his	O
Mother-in-Law	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Scoley	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
continued	O
about	O
3	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
not	O
missing	O
any	O
thing	O
then	O
)	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
Col.	O
Armstrong	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holms	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
missing	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
traced	O
her	O
to	O
Col.	O
Armstrong	B-pers
's	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
to	O
escape	O
,	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
broke	O
her	O
Thigh	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Holms	O
's	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Scoley	O
's	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gown	O
in	O
the	O
Bog-House	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
stole	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Hospital	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
accordingly	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
Directions	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Swanson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
lb	O
.	O
15	O
Ounces	O
of	O
sewing	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Ferrers	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Shop	O
.	O
Nov.	O
27	O
.	O
John	O
Ferrers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
Blowbladder-Street	B-place
,	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
Goods	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
chasser	O
with	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
setting	O
them	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
farthest	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
leaning	O
with	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Maid	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
Goods	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
)	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
white	O
Balladine	O
Silk	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Wrapper	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
a	O
Yard	O
or	O
two	O
farther	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
my	O
Man	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Silk	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
weigh	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
seemed	O
very	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Devil	O
egg	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
Evidence	O
was	O
corroborated	O
by	O
the	O
Maid	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Susan	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Night-Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kivax	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Linen	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gofforth	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Richard	B-pers
Albridge	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Alder	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
in	O
length	O
2	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
depth	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
last	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
in	O
his	O
Rage	O
the	O
said	O
Percival	O
,	O
and	O
stabbing	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
Weapon	O
drawn	O
,	O
nor	O
having	O
first	O
stricken	O
the	O
said	O
Aldridge	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
Percival	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
my	O
Brother	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Basketman	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Market	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
spreading	O
some	O
Butter	O
upon	O
a	O
Roll	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
spread	O
one	O
Piece	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
begun	O
to	O
spread	O
the	O
other	O
Piece	O
:	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Piece	O
that	O
was	O
butter	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Wo	O
n't	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
this	O
?	O
And	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Mouth	O
in	O
jest	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
eat	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
bite	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
retreated	O
and	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
Tub	O
of	O
Blood	O
that	O
stood	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
Dead	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
that	O
be	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
no	O
Blood	O
?	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Guts	O
hang	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Didier	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
sew	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Work-House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
-	O
Parker	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
took	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bread	O
and	O
Butter	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
a	O
little	O
back	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
fell	O
over	O
a	O
Blood-Tub	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Market	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stab	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
-	O
Boswell	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
spread	O
half	O
a	O
Roll	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Bulk	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
over	O
a	O
Tub	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
clapping	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Belly	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
Then	O
get	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Knife	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
dirty	O
at	O
the	O
Point	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
smelt	O
of	O
nothing	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Nurse	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Work-house	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
near	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
Misfortune	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
playing	O
the	O
Rogue	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
about	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Bread	O
and	O
Butter	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
fell	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
forward	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stab	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Belly	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
half	O
spread	O
my	O
Roll	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
:	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
save	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
let	O
's	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
hungry	O
.	O
No	O
you	O
sha'n't	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
punch	O
'd	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
how	O
in	O
struggling	O
,	O
while	O
my	O
Knife	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
beat	O
me	O
about	O
.	O
So	O
and	O
please	O
your	O
Worship	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
be	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
my	O
Bread	O
and	O
Butter	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
Harm	O
done	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Percival	O
,	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
when	O
it	O
begun	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
spreading	O
the	O
Butter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
his	O
Knife	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
struggling	O
till	O
then	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Words	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
laid	O
no	O
Hands	O
on	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Stab	O
was	O
given	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
endeavour	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
Bread	O
and	O
Butter	O
?	O
Percival	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
Butcher	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
poor	O
foolish	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Boys	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
Game	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
play	O
Tricks	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
'em	O
black	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
him	O
about	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
throw	O
him	O
out	O
into	O
a	O
Kennel	O
to	O
wash	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
provoked	O
or	O
fall	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
at	O
such	O
Usage	O
;	O
so	O
far	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
from	O
them	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
into	O
a	O
Corner	O
and	O
laugh	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
always	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
often	O
been	O
trusted	O
by	O
me	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
observ	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
a	O
spiteful	O
revengful	O
Temper	O
in	O
him	O
,	O
let	O
what	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
done	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
as	O
vile	O
a	O
Lad	O
as	O
any	O
about	O
the	O
Market	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
idle	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
his	O
Knot	O
and	O
Basket	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
loiter	O
about	O
and	O
sleep	O
upon	O
Bulks	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Butchers	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Market	O
gave	O
the	O
like	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
on	O
the	O
First	O
and	O
Third	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
William	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Bromley	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sodder	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Lefevre	I-pers
and	O
Comp	O
.	O
Octob	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
leaden	O
Pump	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
January	O
4	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
8.	O
Henry	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
and	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Cecil	I-pers
,	O
November	O
16	O
.	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
.	O
I	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Dog-house	O
Bar	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
warm	O
himself	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
Cart	O
to	O
Edmonton	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
cold	O
.	O
He	O
beg	O
'd	O
an	O
old	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
Notice	O
that	O
those	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
were	O
very	O
bad	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
till	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
Door	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Supper	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
on	O
Windmill-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
Supper	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
:	O
Next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Taylor	O
came	O
to	O
mend	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
overnight	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
a	O
brass	O
Box	O
in	O
the	O
Side-Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
for	O
my	O
Breeches	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
my	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Searching	O
farther	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
old	O
Shoes	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
tied	O
with	O
Packthread	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
was	O
split	O
in	O
two	O
.	O
The	O
Shoes	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Next	O
Week	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Cellar-Door	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Stone	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
thrust	O
the	O
wooden	O
Bolt	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Hat	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
for	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
Breeches	O
in	O
Turnbull-Street	O
for	O
a	O
1s	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
those	O
Places	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
my	O
Shoes	O
upon	O
his	O
Feet	O
.	O
-	O
Thompson	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Coleman-street	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Warrant	O
out	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
pilfer	O
'd	O
some	O
Things	O
while	O
he	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Sims	O
.	O
He	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
Cellar-door	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
Stone	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cecil	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
keep	O
the	O
Dog-house-Bar	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Graves	O
,	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
Huntsman	O
.	O
My	O
Breeches	O
did	O
hang	O
up	O
where	O
I	O
did	O
lye	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
Zick	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
vorced	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
leave'n	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
have	O
got	O
'en	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Go	O
and	O
look	O
on	O
'em	O
.	O
Cecil	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
these	O
be	O
they	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
zafely	O
zwear	O
to	O
'n	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
9.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Pigot	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Alice	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Sarah	I-pers
Laverstitch	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bunny	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding-hood	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Caps	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Low	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Willet	I-pers
,	O
October	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Beesly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Dishes	O
and	O
seven	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
December	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
4	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Towel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
6	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
13.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stew-pan	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Burdus	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14	O
,	O
15.	O
Barbary	B-pers
Hewsly	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Arthur	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
Value	O
4l	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
Oct.	O
15	O
.	O
A.	O
Murphey	O
,	O
near	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Hewsly	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
near	B-place
the	I-place
End	I-place
of	I-place
Short's-Gardens	I-place
in	I-place
Drury-Lane	I-place
,	O
push	O
'd	O
me	O
against	O
a	O
Wall	O
,	O
slipt	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
struggled	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Chain	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Key	O
and	O
Seal	O
through	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Companion	O
Jones	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
as	O
loud	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
still	O
kept	O
hold	O
of	O
Hewsly	O
.	O
Jones	O
returned	O
presently	O
,	O
swore	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
her	O
foolish	O
Bitch	O
for	O
staying	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
more	O
Noise	O
she	O
'd	O
make	O
me	O
hold	O
my	O
Tongue	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watch	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Hewsly	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Cook's-Shop	O
buying	O
a	O
Bit	O
of	O
Meat	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
Gown	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
House	O
he	O
stript	O
us	O
stark	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
about	O
us	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
our	O
own	O
.	O
Murphey	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
till	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
first	O
surprized	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
or	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
searched	O
slightly	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
stript	O
stark	O
naked	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
on	O
her	O
indeed	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
Jones	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
2	O
Watchmen	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cook	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Garvy	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
and	O
Spread-Eagle	O
in	O
Prince's-street	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
downright	O
sober	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
merry	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
them	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
quitted	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
by	O
the	O
Lamp-light	O
.	O
Jones	O
,	O
He	O
search	O
'd	O
me	O
from	O
Top	O
to	O
Toe	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
16.	O
Hester	B-pers
Hogdon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
a	O
Dith	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Winch	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
17.	O
Rowland	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
60lb	O
.	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
Value	O
.	O
44	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Will	B-pers
.	I-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
24	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Brass	O
Ingots	O
,	O
Value	O
28l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
16	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
19.	O
Susan	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
Yards	O
of	O
Red	O
Sarcenet	O
,	O
Value	O
50s	O
.	O
and	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Straw	O
colour	O
'd	O
Sattin	O
,	O
Value	O
50s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
Nov.	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Jane	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Value	O
20s	O
.	O
a	O
Lutestring	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Crimson	O
Poplin	O
Cloak	O
,	O
Value	O
20s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Peers	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
1	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Peers	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
and	O
Coat	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
black	O
Silk	O
,	O
a	O
Lutestring	O
Gown	O
and	O
Coat	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
grey	O
Silk	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
flower	O
'd	O
damask	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Apparel	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
lock	O
'd	O
and	O
corded	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Pearson	O
's	O
Garret	B-pers
Mr	I-pers
.	O
Pearson	O
kept	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
by	O
Smithfield	B-place
Bars	I-place
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
about	O
a	O
12	O
Month	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Box	O
in	O
his	O
Garret	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
thence	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
when	O
having	O
Occasion	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Things	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
to	O
fetch	O
'em	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Pearson	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Box	O
corded	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
as	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
somebody	O
has	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
seem	O
'd	O
as	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
Fact	O
:	O
This	O
gave	O
us	O
Occasion	O
to	O
suspect	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Lid	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
without	O
unlocking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
drawn	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
out	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
at	O
three	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hamlin	O
's	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
She	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
hang	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
used	O
us	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
Law	O
allowed	O
us	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Pearson	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Prison	O
for	O
another	O
Offence	O
.	O
When	O
Mrs.	O
Peers	O
mist	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
this	O
Wench	O
has	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
her	O
aside	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
She	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
readily	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
hop	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
broke	O
any	O
Lock	O
,	O
but	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Lid	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
drawn	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-brokers	O
;	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
them	O
till	O
we	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
him	O
from	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
these	O
Goods	O
worth	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Peers	O
.	O
About	O
10l	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
at	O
once	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Pearson	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
carried	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
three	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
September	O
12	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
promised	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
merciful	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Pearson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
did	O
Wrong	O
.	O
You	O
ought	O
not	O
by	O
Promise	O
of	O
Favour	O
to	O
draw	O
Persons	O
into	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
those	O
Confessions	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
their	O
Lives	O
.	O
When	O
Confessions	O
are	O
obtained	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
,	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
but	O
little	O
Weight	O
with	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Pearson	O
,	O
We	O
have	O
no	O
Desire	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
her	O
Life	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
But	O
if	O
the	O
Jury	O
should	O
find	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
40s	O
.	O
at	O
any	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hamlin	I-pers
,	O
Pawn-broker	O
.	O
These	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
3	O
times	O
;	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
Parcel	O
I	O
lent	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
15	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
30s	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
Tickets	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
looks	O
very	O
ill	O
in	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
to	O
receive	O
such	O
valuable	O
Goods	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
without	O
examining	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
By	O
her	O
Appearance	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
imagine	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
These	O
People	O
know	O
if	O
they	O
bought	O
Goods	O
under	O
such	O
suspicious	O
Circumstances	O
at	O
an	O
under	O
Rate	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
liable	O
to	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
as	O
Receivers	O
of	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
think	O
to	O
evade	O
the	O
Law	O
by	O
lending	O
a	O
Trifle	O
upon	O
'em	O
to	O
Persons	O
who	O
they	O
are	O
pretty	O
sure	O
will	O
never	O
come	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
doubt	O
not	O
but	O
in	O
these	O
Cases	O
they	O
know	O
too	O
well	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
are	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
in	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
equally	O
punished	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
's	O
denying	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
when	O
Persons	O
of	O
Credit	O
came	O
to	O
demand	O
them	O
,	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
knavish	O
Appearance	O
.	O
Officer	O
!	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Court	O
till	O
the	O
Jury	O
have	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
had	O
the	O
Confidence	O
to	O
tell	O
us	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
not	O
worth	O
above	O
14s	O
.	O
more	O
than	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
cost	O
above	O
30	O
l.	O
Mrs.	O
Pearson	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
and	O
thrust	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
The	O
Parliament	O
were	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
pretend	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
.	O
He	O
abused	O
us	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
gross	O
Manner	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
willing	O
to	O
prosecute	O
this	O
Man	O
?	O
It	O
will	O
be	O
doing	O
Justice	O
to	O
your	O
Country	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baily	O
.	O
As	O
your	O
Lordship	O
pleases	O
.	O
Hamlin	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
serve	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
[	O
a-part	O
]	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baily	O
.	O
Rememember	O
how	O
you	O
serv	O
'd	O
us	O
.	O
[	O
a-part	O
]	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Officer	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
Hamlin	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
!	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
can	O
find	O
sufficient	O
Bail	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Baily	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
entered	O
into	O
Recognizances	O
to	O
prosecute	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
at	O
next	O
Sessions	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Oct.	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
drew	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
4	O
.	O
Drew	O
Drury	O
.	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
polish	O
Silver	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Silver	O
for	O
above	O
a	O
Year	O
past	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
my	O
Method	O
to	O
weigh	O
my	O
Silver	O
up	O
every	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
the	O
Quantity	O
in	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
constantly	O
miss	O
'd	O
every	O
Week	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
,	O
40	O
,	O
50	O
,	O
or	O
60	O
Shillings	O
worth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Work	O
;	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
my	O
Boys	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
pretty	O
deal	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
tumble	O
it	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
Why	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
him	O
and	O
call	O
me	O
?	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
Nov.	O
4	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
my	O
Boys	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
hide	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Closet	O
with	O
a	O
Window	O
that	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
)	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
be	O
mealy	O
mouth	O
'd	O
now	O
,	O
because	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
near	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
comes	O
,	O
play	O
your	O
Rogues	O
Tricks	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
about	O
as	O
you	O
do	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
may	O
suspect	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Basket	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Post	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Boys	O
began	O
to	O
play	O
their	O
Tricks	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
run	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
this	O
stept	O
to	O
the	O
Basket	O
,	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
immediately	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
will	O
hardly	O
came	O
down	O
till	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
e'en	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Boys	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
sit	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Chamber	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
work	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Robin	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
work	O
for	O
you	O
this	O
Week	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
settle	O
Accounts	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
you	O
for	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Boys	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
getting	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
search	O
him	O
and	O
welcome	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
.	O
Sure	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
Eyes	O
did	O
not	O
deceive	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
presently	O
my	O
Boys	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Silver	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Bit	O
.	O
He	O
begg	O
'd	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
do	O
so	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
[	O
This	O
Deposition	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
Boys	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Drury	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
take	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Basket	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
And	O
had	O
you	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
me	O
before	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
sworn	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
P.	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
Plot	O
laid	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
C.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
too	O
.	O
P.	O
Another	O
Man	O
having	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
speaking	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
laid	O
this	O
Trap	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
that	O
good	O
Principle	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
no	O
Body	O
live	O
but	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
trusted	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silver	O
.	O
C.	O
Without	O
Weight	O
or	O
Tale	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Drury	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
C.	O
Then	O
you	O
were	O
accountable	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
P.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Hankercher	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Plot	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
common	O
to	O
lose	O
40	O
or	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
my	O
Master	O
has	O
had	O
more	O
Silver	O
than	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Drury	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
sometimes	O
make	O
a	O
Mistake	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
always	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
November	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
,	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Loyzada	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
S.	O
Loyzada	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Castle-Yard	B-place
in	I-place
Houndsditch	I-place
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
House	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
about	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
Casement	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Coffee-pot	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
I	O
beat	O
my	O
Round	O
at	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
safe	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
there	O
with	O
my	O
Comrade	O
,	O
a	O
Fellow	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Candle	O
for	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
?	O
What	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
To	O
light	O
me	O
home	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
bit	O
;	O
but	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
loose	O
Chap	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
he	O
went	O
the	O
contrary	O
way	O
.	O
Thinks	O
I	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
some	O
Roguery	O
in	O
hand	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
Watchman	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
.	O
He	O
turn	O
'd	O
down	O
Castle-Yard	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
brother	O
Watchman	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
softly	O
after	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Casement	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Kitchen-window	O
unhung	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Street-door	O
with	O
the	O
Candle	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
You	O
Rogue	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
did	O
I	O
lend	O
you	O
the	O
Candle	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
?	O
With	O
that	O
he	O
flung	O
the	O
Candle	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
to	O
the	O
Gate	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
this	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Plate	O
ty	O
'd	O
before	O
him	O
thus	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Wrapper	O
.	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
struggled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Rogue	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turn	O
down	O
Woolpack-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
down	O
Angel-Alley	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Thorow-fare	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
is	O
Woolpack-Alley	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Door	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
through	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
's	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
old	O
ruined	O
Houses	O
and	O
Rubbish	O
in	O
that	O
Alley	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
hid	O
himself	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
we	O
set	O
a	O
Watch	O
against	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
towards	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Says	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
a	O
Man	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
he	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Stew-pan	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
Hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
run	O
down	O
Woollpack-Alley	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
a	O
Watch	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
Castle-Alley	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
one	O
said	O
to	O
Owen	O
;	O
There	O
's	O
a	O
Man	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
he	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
!	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
Place	O
when	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
t'other	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
Way	O
home	O
thought	O
to	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
Woollpack-Alley	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
the	O
Door	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Watchman	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Who	O
goes	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Friend	O
:	O
Says	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
Here	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
Who	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
Says	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
so	O
,	O
says	O
Owen	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
examin	O
'd	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
a	O
Reed-maker	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
satisfy	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
somebody	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
here	O
two	O
Sessions	O
ago	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
*	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Word	O
for	O
my	O
Appearance	O
.	O
*	O
In	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Vide	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
VII	O
.	O
Part	O
II	O
.	O
Page	O
223.	O
William	B-pers
Byrom	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Corbet-Court	O
,	O
Spittle-Fields	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
Mr.	O
James	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Double	O
Chair	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Crowd	O
about	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
asked	O
Owen	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
he	O
first	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
?	O
And	O
,	O
says	O
Owen	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Constable	O
proffered	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
's	O
Word	O
for	O
his	O
Appearance	O
,	O
but	O
somebody	O
saying	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
such	O
Security	O
,	O
Owen	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
I	O
only	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
swore	O
it	O
positively	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
such	O
Word	O
as	O
believe	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
25	O
,	O
26.	O
John	B-pers
Nethercliff	I-pers
and	O
Solomon	B-pers
Carlisle	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Hammer	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
Sept.	O
4	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Carlisle	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Nethercliff	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
John	B-pers
Norcot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
pint	O
Mug	O
,	O
Value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Oct.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
Joseph	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Stocker	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
420	O
iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Laurence	B-pers
Victorin	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Hayford	I-pers
,	O
November	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Mary	B-pers
Paulin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Napkins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Shales	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Shales	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
's	O
,	O
Nov	O
.	O
19	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
30.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Chalmers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
333	O
Yards	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
Value	O
105	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
24	O
Yards	O
of	O
Printed	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
45	O
Yards	O
of	O
Damask	O
,	O
Value	O
16	O
l.	O
and	O
26	O
Yards	O
of	O
striped	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fermer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Fermer	I-pers
.	O
And	O
please	O
your	O
Loard-ship	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
intule	O
the	O
Country	O
upon	O
proud	O
prassing	O
Basiness	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
the	O
Frasner	O
to	O
car	O
of	O
my	O
Loadings	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
And	O
because	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Poaverty	O
,	O
I	O
taud	O
him	O
he	O
mat	O
mack	O
use	O
of	O
my	O
Bad	O
and	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
danno	O
'	O
gi	O
'	O
him	O
Laberty	O
to	O
maddle	O
wi	O
'	O
my	O
Geuds	O
that	O
were	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
Chast	O
of	O
Drawers	O
in	O
the	O
Cloaset	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
greet	O
Paircel	O
of	O
Lannen	O
there	O
.	O
But	O
whan	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
it	O
was	O
aw	O
gone	O
!	O
The	O
deel	O
a	O
Bit	O
was	O
thare	O
last	O
!	O
Ye	O
Raug	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
ha	O
'	O
roab	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Maidam	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
bag	O
your	O
Pairdon	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
Nasassity	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Nasassity	O
!	O
ye	B-pers
Raug	I-pers
you	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
Nasassity	O
cou	O
'	O
ye	O
ha	O
'	O
to	O
tack	O
aw	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
?	O
cou	O
'	O
no	O
'	O
ye	O
be	O
contanted	O
wi	O
'	O
a	O
lattle	O
?	O
I	O
'll	O
tap	O
ye	B-pers
Justice	I-pers
,	O
troath	O
will	O
I	O
.	O
How	O
goat	O
ye	O
the	O
Locks	O
oppen	O
ye	B-pers
Raug	I-pers
?	O
Why	O
Maidam	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Machine	O
in	O
my	O
Poaket	O
;	O
a	O
crooked	O
Iron	O
.	O
Wan	O
na	O
'	O
it	O
haird	O
to	O
tack	O
aw	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
ye	B-pers
Raug	I-pers
ye	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
And	O
than	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
doad	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
round	O
the	O
Room	O
over	O
and	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
bag	O
'd	O
of	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
tack	O
awaw	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
wi	O
'	O
my	O
Gends	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Pan	O
and	O
Ank	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
saw	O
much	O
sauld	O
,	O
saw	O
much	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
much	O
gamed	O
awa	O
'	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
particular	O
Goods	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Fermer	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Shute	O
of	O
Table-Linnen	O
,	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Pianted	O
Lnnen	O
,	O
and	O
piece	O
of	O
striped	O
Hoaland	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
intanded	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
Brewer	O
wi	O
'	O
gm	O
he	O
wad	O
accept	O
'em	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
wanno	O
'	O
tack	O
'em	O
.	O
Than	O
there	O
was	O
saxteen	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Hoaland	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Shutes	O
of	O
Damask	O
Table-Linnen	O
.	O
The	O
Value	O
of	O
'em	O
aw	O
was	O
better	O
than	O
105	O
Punds	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
intrust	O
me	O
with	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
?	O
F.	O
Naw	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
avery	O
Thing	O
from	O
ye	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
House	O
were	O
those	O
Goods	O
left	O
?	O
F.	O
In	O
Edward	B-pers
White	I-pers
's	O
House	O
in	O
Yoark-Buildings	O
.	O
P.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
trust	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
Linnen	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomson	O
the	O
Brewer	O
in	O
Charles-Court	O
?	O
F.	B-pers
Margaret	I-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
my	O
Chair-woman	O
,	O
carried	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Douglas	O
brought	O
'em	O
back	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Fermer	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Rainbow	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Villers-street	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
none	O
but	O
he	O
in	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
and	O
nothing	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
to	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Chairs	O
and	O
Bed	O
:	O
The	O
rest	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Parcel	O
to	O
the	O
Brewer	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Fermer	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Douglas	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
Brewer	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
entrusted	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
left	O
in	O
his	O
Room	O
.	O
P.	O
Did	O
I	O
or	O
Mrs.	O
Fermer	O
desire	O
you	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
back	O
?	O
D.	O
Neither	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
own	O
Account	O
,	O
without	O
Orders	O
from	O
any	O
.	O
You	O
told	O
me	O
your	O
self	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
every	O
thing	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
P.	O
I	O
shall	O
prove	O
the	O
Contrary	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
printed	O
and	O
striped	O
Holland	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Feriner	O
's	O
Order	O
,	O
to	O
clear	O
the	O
Brewer	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
Douglas	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Orders	O
.	O
P.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
the	O
Brewer	O
,	O
in	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
's	O
Hands	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
mentions	O
,	O
tells	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
those	O
Goods	O
which	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
,	O
were	O
intrusted	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
prove	O
that	O
Letter	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Writing	O
?	O
P.	O
She	O
has	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
F.	O
Let	O
me	O
see	O
the	O
Letter	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
wanno	O
'	O
deny	O
my	O
aun	O
Hand	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Writing	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
send	O
in	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Clerk	O
reads	O
]	O
.	O
Greases-Greases	O
?	O
F.	O
Naw	O
Sir	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
no	O
'	O
Greases	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
Gravesend	O
.	O
You	O
canno	O
'	O
read	O
my	O
Hand-writing	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
see	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
read	O
it	O
my	O
Sal	O
'	O
.	O
She	O
reads	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
following	O
is	O
a	O
true	O
Copy	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Thomison	O
Bruer	O
in	O
hog	O
lean	O
by	O
tyburn	O
road	O
greases	O
Septmbr	O
the	O
18	O
.	O
1732	O
.	O
MR	O
thomison	O
I	O
heave	O
been	O
at	O
Londin	O
and	O
heas	O
brogt	O
eaney	O
lytell	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
ther	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
setell	O
in	O
*	O
dr	O
Scotland	O
wher	O
I	O
am	O
loved	O
and	O
known	O
I	O
heave	O
lost	O
my	O
all	O
with	O
peepoll	O
runing	O
a	O
way	O
in	O
my	O
det	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
standing	O
of	O
all	O
that	O
as	O
I	O
allwais	O
promised	O
to	O
doo	O
you	O
juistis	O
I	O
doo	O
beyond	O
pouer	O
I	O
heave	O
ordered	O
you	O
ten	O
pounds	O
woorth	O
of	O
nerey	O
pritey	O
goods	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
to	O
you	O
by	O
woon	O
mr	O
cheambers	O
and	O
upon	O
your	O
full	O
discarg	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
shall	O
de	O
liver	O
you	O
the	O
goods	O
Scotland	O
in	O
Six	O
months	O
after	O
deat	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
full	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
own	O
you	O
for	O
you	O
know	O
your	O
a	O
Count	O
is	O
not	O
Just	O
and	O
by	O
your	O
receat	O
I	O
can	O
prone	O
the	O
Seam	O
but	O
how	O
ever	O
be	O
that	O
as	O
it	O
will	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
eabell	O
to	O
do	O
mor	O
then	O
I	O
+	O
ckean	O
and	O
beliue	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
mercy	O
great	O
uellow	O
for	O
you	O
I	O
wood	O
not	O
heave	O
given	O
my	O
self	O
this	O
trubell	O
so	O
if	O
you	O
pleas	O
to	O
acept	O
of	O
this	O
you	O
may	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
you	O
me	O
let	O
aloo	O
I	O
wish	O
euerey	O
body	O
wood	O
pay	O
me	O
as	O
weel	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
heave	O
such	O
loses	O
as	O
I	O
heave	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
from	O
Sr	O
your	O
most	O
hombell	O
Sernen	O
Johana	B-pers
Fermer	I-pers
*	O
Dear	O
.	O
+	O
Can	O
The	O
Goods	O
I	O
heaue	O
ordered	O
you	O
is	O
this	O
,	O
l.	O
s.	O
d.	O
one	O
Shout	O
++	O
of	O
syn	O
demisk	O
teabell	O
lyning	O
at	O
4l	O
.	O
the	O
Shout	O
,	O
4	O
00	O
0	O
++	O
One	O
Suit	O
.	O
24	O
yeards	O
syn	O
prented	O
lyning	O
at	O
3	O
and	O
6	O
pens	O
per	O
yeard	O
is	O
4	O
04	O
0	O
a	O
leven	O
yeards	O
Striped	O
holland	O
at	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
pens	O
per	O
yeard	O
is	O
1	O
16	O
8	O
for	O
too	O
gallins	O
neat	O
brandy	O
0	O
18	O
0	O
in	O
all	O
is	O
10	O
18	O
8	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
her	O
begun	O
by	O
our	O
coming	O
both	O
in	O
one	O
Ship	O
from	O
Scotland	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
great	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
do	O
me	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
expected	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
her	O
some	O
in	O
return	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
ow	O
'd	O
a	O
pretty	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
a	O
way	O
to	O
pay	O
off	O
all	O
her	O
Creditors	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
leave	O
Goods	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Scotland	O
,	O
would	O
send	O
them	O
word	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
in	O
full	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
ow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Discharge	O
they	O
might	O
,	O
otherwise	O
they	O
might	O
get	O
their	O
Money	O
how	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
Thus	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hayward	O
,	O
a	O
Wine	O
Merchant	O
,	O
with	O
15l	O
.	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
70l	O
.	O
He	O
thinking	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Scotland	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
to	O
act	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
15	O
l.	O
in	O
full	O
for	O
the	O
70	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
compounded	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Avery	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
ow	O
'd	O
20	O
l.	O
for	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
upon	O
this	O
Account	O
that	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
lye	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
her	O
Creditors	O
enquired	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Scotland	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
a	O
Trick	O
.	O
Before	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
for	O
Necessaries	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
want	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
Goods	O
enough	O
in	O
her	O
Closet	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
dispose	O
of	O
upon	O
Occasion	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
Keys	O
.	O
F.	O
Naw	O
Sir	O
I	O
last	O
my	O
Keys	O
in	O
my	O
Drawers	O
.	O
P.	O
She	O
trusted	O
the	O
Keys	O
and	O
Goods	O
too	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
Care	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
very	O
familiar	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
many	O
a	O
Time	O
.	O
F.	O
Upon	O
my	O
Oath	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
why	O
,	O
does	O
your	O
Loardship	O
think	O
I	O
was	O
lye	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
Jackanapes	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
?	O
The	O
Goods	O
I	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hayward	O
and	O
the	O
Brewer	O
,	O
was	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
.	O
P.	O
Here	O
's	O
Mr.	O
Grub	O
,	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
will	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Grub	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
Woman	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
A	O
Piece	O
of	O
these	O
Goods	O
was	O
pledg	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
her	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
Character	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
cheat	O
or	O
defraud	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
me	O
false	O
Plate	O
for	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
20	O
l.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
F.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Lady	O
Cassells	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
her	O
Dining-room	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
deceiv	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
you	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bovin	I-pers
.	O
Before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
writ	O
any	O
Letter	O
till	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
free	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
many	O
a	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
hereupon	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
hum	O
'd	O
and	O
haw	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
and	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
more	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Drawers	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
ho	O
Violence	O
done	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
says	O
they	O
were	O
open	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
with	O
a	O
Pain	O
in	O
his	O
Ear	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Days	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
something	O
to	O
eat	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Porringer	O
and	O
Spoon	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
every	O
Thing	O
.	O
-	O
Douglas	O
,	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
nothing	O
but	O
dirty	O
Sheets	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Towel	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
never	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Fermer	O
,	O
why	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
Goods	O
to	O
his	O
Care	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
untold	O
Gold	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
several	O
Things	O
that	O
intimated	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Question	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lain	O
in	O
a	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
say	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
prosecuted	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
say	O
now	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
her	O
Husband	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
Man	O
but	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Cheat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
for	O
deluding	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Examination	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
P.	O
And	O
she	O
had	O
deluded	O
me	O
too	O
.	O
She	O
's	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
a	O
vile	O
Character	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
Lawyer	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drew	O
up	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
promis	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
sign	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
King	O
in	O
my	O
behalf	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pails	O
,	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Calloway	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
16	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Iron-hoops	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spade	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
16	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
.	O
32.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Boards	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Fordham	I-pers
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
33.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Rum	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Odell	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
34.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
28	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
35.	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
80	O
l.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
72	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36.	O
John	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cure	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
Suit	O
of	O
Point-lace	O
Head-clothes	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
Cambrick	O
laced	O
Heads	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Mantle	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cure	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Pint	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
.	O
and	O
2	O
Table-cloths	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
12	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
George	O
Cure	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Hay	B-place
Market	I-place
against	I-place
the	I-place
Opera-House	I-place
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
Nov.	O
12	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
my	O
Maid	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Walnut-tree	O
of	O
my	O
Scritore	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Lock	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
open	O
'd	O
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
said	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
cracking	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Who	O
's	O
there	O
?	O
My	O
Wife	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
Lace	O
in	O
a	O
Band-box	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
and	O
Manteel	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
over-night	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Shutter	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen-Window	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
down	O
and	O
set	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Casement	O
left	O
open	O
.	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
be	O
easy	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Thief	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
Directions	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Newton	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Particulars	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
examined	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
just	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
had	O
given	O
Orders	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
advertised	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Things	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Hat	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Friend	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
this	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
that	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
against	O
the	O
Opera-House	O
.	O
-	O
Garbet	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
last	O
up	O
but	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
were	O
safe	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Shutter	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Window	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Hinges	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Casement	O
(	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Sash	O
Casement	O
)	O
stood	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
several	O
things	O
before	O
my	O
Master	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Way	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Watchman	O
of	O
Maiden-lane	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
gone	O
past	O
One	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
leaning	O
on	O
a	O
Post	O
,	O
speaking	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
Watchman	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ast	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
white	O
Bundle	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
2	O
or	O
three	O
Doors	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
much	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
then	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
begun	O
to	O
creep	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
run	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
Cecil-street	O
he	O
run	O
into	O
that	O
Watchman	O
's	O
Arms	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Bundle	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Newton	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
he	O
was	O
shewn	O
the	O
same	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Watchman	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
Coat-Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
a	O
Chissel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mohawk-Knife	O
with	O
a	O
Saw	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Cure	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
my	O
Knife	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Pruning-Knife	O
.	O
Ellis	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
Bullet	O
and	O
some	O
Powder	O
too	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Cure	O
saw	O
the	O
Bundle	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
but	O
the	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Cure	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
Sarah	O
Wall	O
's	O
.	O
Ellis	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Beadle	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Faithfull	I-pers
,	O
Beadle	O
.	O
A	O
Link-man	O
found	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Way	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
through	O
Maiden-lane	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Southampton-street	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Godfrey	O
's	O
(	O
the	O
Chymist	O
's	O
)	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
.	O
The	O
Pistol	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
that	O
Place	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
ready	O
loaded	O
and	O
cock	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
screw	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ball	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
fitted	O
it	O
exactly	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Friends	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
(	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
)	O
till	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
enquired	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
somebody	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
What	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
why	O
6	O
d.	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
agreed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Pall-Mall	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
trouble	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
any	O
farther	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Opera-House	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
Shove	O
as	O
I	O
past	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
that	O
for	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
No	O
offence	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Who	O
's	O
that	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
?	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
we	O
fell	O
into	O
Discourse	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
his	O
Sister	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
those	O
odd	O
things	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Thames-Street	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
Hold	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
few	O
other	O
odd	O
Things	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
take	O
'em	O
all	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
into	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
other	O
Things	O
he	O
might	O
thrust	O
in	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
having	O
come	O
from	O
home	O
without	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
bad	O
me	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
formerly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Master	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
afterwards	O
has	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Since	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
I	O
lost	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Kinsey	I-pers
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clapham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Woodison	I-pers
were	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
that	O
Sunday	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
till	O
past	O
a	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Hat	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
37.	O
William	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Martha	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Rich	O
.	O
Plummer	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Bib	O
,	O
a	O
Pincushion	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
Farthing	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
,	O
Decem	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Hackney	O
to	O
Newington	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stopt	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
I	O
should	O
deliver	O
.	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
!	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
save	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
3	O
d.	O
Farthing	O
.	O
That	O
wo	O
n't	O
do	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
give	O
me	O
something	O
else	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
's	O
Knife	O
,	O
struck	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
took	O
my	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
Assistance	O
coming	O
in	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
within	O
two	O
Fields	O
where	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
!	O
I	O
hearken	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Voice	O
.	O
I	O
jump	O
'd	O
over	O
a	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
He	O
saw	O
me	O
coming	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Bundle	O
towards	O
her	O
and	O
run	O
.	O
I	O
proceeded	O
after	O
him	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
once	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
till	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
Shoemaker	O
's	O
Knife	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
begg	O
'd	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bracey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Hurst	O
were	O
binding	O
Faggots	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter-in-law	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
Henry	O
run	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
!	O
I	O
jump	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Ditch	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
youngest	O
got	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
from	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
towards	O
her	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
2d	O
Man	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
do	O
the	O
like	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
next	O
to	O
Brook-House	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
2	O
Men	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
Garden	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
Jerry	O
and	O
John	O
run	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Hurst	O
run	O
the	O
foremost	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
Hurst	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Hedge-Bill	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
3d	O
.	O
Farthing	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Jerry	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Partner	O
went	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
Woman	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Thief	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Bundle	O
up	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
Child-bed	O
Linen	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
38.	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Serge	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Sagathy	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Poplin	O
Gown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
30	O
.	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Violin	O
,	O
a	O
Case	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
Dear-skin	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
Sheets	O
of	O
Manuscript	O
Musick	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Festing	I-pers
.	O
Decem	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Thomas	O
More	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Pettit's-Court	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Hanaway-Street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
last	O
Instant	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
some	O
Body	O
open	O
'd	O
my	O
window	O
Shutter	O
,	O
push	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
By	O
delivering	O
written	O
Papers	O
to	O
some	O
Gentlemen	O
Pawnbrokers	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Noon	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
that	O
this	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
Warrant	O
from	O
The	O
Right	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
,	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
behind	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
this	O
Gown	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
indicted	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
He	O
pledged	O
this	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
Decem	O
.	O
4	O
this	O
Advertisement	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
acted	O
like	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
find	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
all	O
like	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
that	O
was	O
here	O
Yesterday	O
.	O
-	O
Miller	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
Cloak	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gown	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
beside	O
a	O
Turn-up-Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Gown	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
was	O
Se'nnight	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
several	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Deacon	O
's	O
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
from	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
till	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
except	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
Girl	O
came	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
would	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
and	O
found	O
William	B-pers
Hampton	I-pers
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Cloak	O
and	O
a	O
Gown	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Bundle	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
for	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
2	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
consented	O
.	O
Hampton	O
is	O
now	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
here	O
.	O
[	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
to	O
every	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Defence	O
]	O
The	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
*	O
William	O
Hampton	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
swore	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
she	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
below	O
.	O
John	O
Noon	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
seldom	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
Stanhope-street	O
,	O
and	O
sells	O
old	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
Tea	O
pots	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
odd	O
Things	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
his	O
Girl	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
any	O
Body	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
my	O
Oath	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Landlord	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
good	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Festing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Violin	O
,	O
and	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Sheets	O
of	O
Manuscript	O
Music	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Seat	O
of	O
my	O
Parlour	O
Window	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
5	O
Guineas	O
Reward	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
John	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
(	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Stanhope-street	O
)	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Violin	O
and	O
Bow	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Case	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
the	O
Papers	O
.	O
John	O
Noon	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
this	O
Violin	O
and	O
Bow	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
for	O
6s	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
from	O
Gold-Smith	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
-	O
Miller	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Warrant	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
stood	O
behind	O
a	O
Partition	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
out	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
,	O
give	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
left	O
it	O
here	O
took	O
the	O
Papers	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Deacon	O
's	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
word	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
(	O
not	O
Will	O
.	O
Hampton	O
)	O
wanted	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
Men	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
playing	O
upon	O
this	O
Fiddle	O
;	O
they	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
'em	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
to	O
Mr	O
Noon	O
for	O
6s	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Father	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
from	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Fiddle	O
.	O
He	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
in	O
Chick	O
lane	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
another	O
Man	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
my	O
Father	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
the	O
Thief	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
.	O
E.	O
Giles	O
found	O
the	O
Musick	O
Papers	O
in	O
this	O
Man	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
swore	O
positively	O
to	O
these	O
Particulars	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
39.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Katharine	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
2	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
Oct.	O
12	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
40	O
,	O
41.	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Macloughlane	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Purse	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
88	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Nov.	O
2	O
.	O
Henry	O
Green	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Brother	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
fourscore	O
and	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
.	O
W.	O
M.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
but	O
68	O
Guineas	O
you	O
old	O
Rogue	O
you	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
but	O
68	O
Guineas	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
88	O
Guineas	O
and	O
4	O
half	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
my	O
Lodgers	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
to	O
that	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Partition	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
see	O
all	O
over	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Pretence	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
had	O
a	O
poor	O
Brother	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Northamptonshire	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
dubitons	O
that	O
my	O
Husband	O
should	O
give	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
to	O
this	O
poor	O
Brother	O
,	O
I	O
hided	O
the	O
Purse	O
with	O
90	O
Guineas	O
in	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
Child	O
's	O
Bed	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
walking	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
might	O
see	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
through	O
the	O
Slit	O
in	O
the	O
Wainscot	O
:	O
Then	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
his	O
Brother	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
By	O
and	O
by	O
,	O
one	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
that	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Boy	O
up	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
something	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
W.	O
M.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
then	O
?	O
Ann	O
Green	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
W.	O
M.	O
P.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
enquire	O
into	O
your	O
Character	O
.	O
Ann	O
Green	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
got	O
Moll	O
Harvey	O
of	O
your	O
side	O
,	O
so	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
care	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
.	O
(	O
Aged	O
16	O
)	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
Tom	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
this	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
comes	O
in	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
the	O
Bundle	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
pretty	O
Feather-bed	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
turned	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
Money	O
being	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
tell	O
my	O
Mother	O
they	O
would	O
certainly	O
come	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
these	O
two	O
end	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Allomby	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Novemb	O
.	O
one	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
next	O
Door	O
that	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
of	O
near	O
an	O
100	O
Guineas	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
.	O
You	O
wicked	O
Wretch	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
take	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
?	O
She	O
denied	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Gold	O
about	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
his	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
7	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Latham	I-pers
,	O
Coachman	O
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
W.	O
M.	O
from	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
in	O
Blackman-street	O
,	O
to	O
Islington	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Head	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
drive	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Moll	O
Harvey	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
68	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Watch	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
'em	O
again	O
.	O
Moll	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
and	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
his	O
Watch	O
:	O
He	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
Money	O
too	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
Warrant	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
drive	O
to	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
's	O
.	O
But	O
Moll	O
Harvey	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
saying	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
there	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
drive	O
to	O
Justice	O
Lambert	O
's	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Justice	O
Lambert	O
called	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
asked	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
withdraw	O
.	O
W.	O
M.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
Moll	O
Harvey	O
,	O
nor	O
her	O
House	O
neither	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
stands	O
pretty	O
near	O
you	O
however	O
.	O
-	O
Banford	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Cow	O
and	O
Calf	O
Ale-house	O
by	O
Islington	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Murphey	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
so	O
?	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
Man	O
,	O
Woman	O
,	O
nor	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
any	O
Gold	O
about	O
me	O
it	O
is	O
yours	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
in	O
a	O
Housewife	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
:	O
So	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
who	O
enquired	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Macloughlane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Robbery	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
W.	O
M.	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
5	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
studded	O
Watch	O
.	O
He	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
dirty	O
,	O
his	O
Shirt	O
Sleeve	O
was	O
torn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
some	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Coachman	O
who	O
brought	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mall	O
Harvey	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Watchman	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
River	O
Company	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Chamberlain	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Banford	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Cow	O
and	O
Calf	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
there	O
that	O
Day	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Irish	O
Brogue	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
Ireland	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
?	O
He	O
answered	O
me	O
in	O
Irish	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
North	O
of	O
Ireland	O
,	O
near	O
Dundee	O
.	O
Sure	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
:	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Name	O
?	O
My	O
Name	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
is	O
Will	O
.	O
Maclonghlane	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
come	O
from	O
of	O
France	O
.	O
Parlezvous	O
Francois	O
,	O
says	O
I.	O
Ouy	O
Monsieur	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
could	O
speak	O
so	O
much	O
French	O
as	O
I	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
no	O
Matter	O
whether	O
he	O
could	O
or	O
not	O
:	O
The	O
Court	O
do	O
n't	O
want	O
to	O
hear	O
how	O
many	O
Scraps	O
of	O
French	O
and	O
Irish	O
you	O
can	O
repeat	O
.	O
-	O
Davis	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
He	O
says	O
his	O
Name	O
is	O
Will	O
.	O
Maclonghlane	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
Name	O
in	O
the	O
Warrant	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
I	O
kick	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
against	O
a	O
Jack-Chain	O
.	O
He	O
began	O
to	O
struggle	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
You	O
Rogue	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
Resistance	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
hang	O
you	O
in	O
this	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
save	O
Jack	B-pers
Catch	I-pers
the	O
Labour	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
wrong	O
Man	O
,	O
honest	O
Will	O
.	O
Macloughlane	O
!	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
not	O
William	O
Macloughlane	O
,	O
but	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
aside	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
another	O
Box	O
.	O
Countryman	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
Irish	O
)	O
I	O
wonder	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
hard	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
5	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Watch	O
from	O
me	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
)	O
.	O
Give	O
me	O
the	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
keep	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
the	O
Silver	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chamberlain	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
Assistance	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
Davis	O
step	O
out	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
W.	O
Macloughlane	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Damn	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
Name	O
is	O
not	O
John	O
Howard	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
aside	O
with	O
Davis	O
.	O
Davis	O
beckon	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
over-heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Gold	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
the	O
Silver	O
.	O
He	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
but	O
sensible	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Murphy	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
(	O
the	O
Cow	O
and	O
Calf	O
)	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
Islington	O
for	O
the	O
Air	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
Lodging	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
eat	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
fetch	O
her	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
some	O
Stakes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
Man	O
,	O
Woman	O
,	O
or	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Gold	O
about	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
Green	O
's	O
.	O
Upon	O
search	O
they	O
found	O
7	O
Guineas	O
in	O
her	O
Hussy	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Maclonghlane	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
Howard	O
.	O
5	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
studded	O
Watch	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
offer	O
'd	O
Davis	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Silver	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
H.	O
Green	O
.	O
They	O
never	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
My	O
House	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Parker's-Lane	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
that	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
Murphy	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Name	O
is	O
not	O
Murphy	O
but	O
Maclonghlane	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
is	O
my	O
Husband	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jurick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
marry	O
'd	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Jurick	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
recollect	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Allbollon-Eve	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Wedding	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
Husband	O
here	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Trial	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
they	O
married	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
At	O
a	O
Lady	O
's	O
House	O
beyond	O
Red-Lion-Square	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
They	O
supt	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
;	O
and	O
Green	O
keeps	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
too	O
.	O
C.	O
By	O
whom	O
were	O
they	O
married	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Roman	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
.	O
They	O
are	O
Roman	B-pers
Catholicks	I-pers
.	O
C.	O
In	O
what	O
Room	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Garret	O
.	O
Green	O
said	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
hang	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
Green	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
damn	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
them	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
more	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sherrit	I-pers
.	O
Green	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jurick	O
's	O
Room	O
(	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
hang	O
them	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
more	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Soams	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Green	O
's	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
A	O
Soldier	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
nothing	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Green	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
searched	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
affronted	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
no	O
more	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
H.	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
neither	O
searched	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
saw	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
Brother	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
Nor	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
'em	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
before	O
I	O
mist	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
Isabella	O
Soams	O
can	O
prove	O
that	O
Green	O
has	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Soldier	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Soams	O
is	O
your	O
Name	O
?	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
gone	O
by	O
that	O
Name	O
?	O
Isabella	O
Eaton	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
12	O
Month	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
try	O
'd	O
you	O
here	O
by	O
another	O
Name	O
.	O
Eaton	O
.	O
Very	O
like	O
you	O
might	O
try	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
another	O
Name	O
too	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
if	O
you	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
Innocent	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
came	O
here	O
for	O
my	O
Crimes	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Passions	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Two	O
Blue-Posts	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
William	B-pers
Macloughlane	I-pers
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
's	O
Servants	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
20	O
Guineas	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
by	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
Day	O
as	O
Green	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
Green	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
here	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
16	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Tell	O
him	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
next	O
time	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
I	O
affronted	O
him	O
by	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
now	O
I	O
understand	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
'll	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
Soldier	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
him	O
5	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
that	O
ago	O
?	O
Eaton	O
.	O
Six	O
Weeks	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
Weeks	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Eaton	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
keep	O
an	O
Almanack	O
in	O
my	O
Head	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
That	O
Soldier	O
is	O
still	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
5	O
Guineas	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Eaton	O
.	O
And	O
says	O
Green	O
,	O
send	O
Billy	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
find	O
the	O
Soldier	O
,	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
I	O
'll	O
