TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
1732	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Eighth	O
and	O
last	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1732	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Raymond	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Hickman	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Caleb	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Benbridge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blakesly	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Court	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Glanister	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Tilder	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
Gabel	B-pers
Fogar	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Richard	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stick	O
of	O
Logwood	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
watch	O
some	O
Logwood	O
on	O
Porters-Key	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
this	O
Stick	O
of	O
Logwood	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Porters	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Keys	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
.	O
A	O
Constable	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
carrying	O
the	O
Logwood	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
only	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Pile	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Pile	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Knot	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
his	O
Foot	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
Logwood	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
had	O
rectified	O
the	O
Pile	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
Notice	O
how	O
the	O
Sticks	O
Lay	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
Stick	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Pile	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
Load	O
from	O
Stocks-Market	O
to	O
Tower-Wharf	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
over	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
I	O
stopt	O
at	O
the	O
Pile	O
of	O
Logwood	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Sticks	O
fell	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
its	O
Place	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
Cox	O
came	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
2.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
of	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
.	O
George	O
Bond	O
.	O
Between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
blue	O
grey	O
Stockings	O
,	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
Paper	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
were	O
just	O
a	O
dozen	O
pair	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
wanted	O
a	O
different	O
Colour	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
took	O
down	O
another	O
Paper	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
about	O
the	O
Price	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
another	O
pair	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
her	O
to	O
double	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
that	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
again	O
to	O
reach	O
another	O
Parcel	O
.	O
She	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
several	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
liking	O
the	O
Price	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
2	O
pair	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
found	O
one	O
pair	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
pair	O
in	O
the	O
Lining	O
of	O
her	O
Gown	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pairs	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
other	O
pair	O
at	O
another	O
Hosiers	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
whether	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
William	B-pers
Sherrington	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
September	O
11	O
.	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Ellock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Major	O
(	O
a	O
Barber	O
)	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
he	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Strangury	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
backwards	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Wig	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
He	O
soon	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
stood	O
talking	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
the	O
Wig	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
Middle-Row	O
in	O
Holbour	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
3d	O
Wig-shop	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Horn	O
who	O
keeps	O
that	O
Shop	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
5	O
Minutes	O
since	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Horn	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
Wig	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
towards	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Winethen	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
agreed	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mistrust	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
.	O
He	O
gets	O
his	O
Bread	O
by	O
making	O
up	O
Wigs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Major	O
's	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
needs	O
think	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
wonder	O
'd	O
how	O
the	O
Devil	O
came	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Wig	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wire-Grate	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Strutton	I-pers
,	O
September	O
17	O
.	O
P.	O
Strutton	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Stall-Grate	O
about	O
5	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
exposed	O
to	O
Sale	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Newsham	I-pers
's	O
.	O
E.	O
Newsham	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
,	O
betwixt	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
Grate	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
't	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
doubt	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Coming	O
late	O
from	O
Work	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Grate	O
near	O
the	O
Dust-hole	O
,	O
going	O
into	O
Postern-Row	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Ticket-Porter	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Waterside	O
near	O
5	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
intrusted	O
in	O
landing	O
and	O
housing	O
Merchants	O
Goods	O
both	O
by	O
Day	O
and	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Complaints	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
bound	O
for	O
his	O
Honesty	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
so	O
mean	O
an	O
Action	O
.	O
Other	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
5.	O
Martha	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Queenhith	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
Head-cloaths	O
lac	O
'd	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Blandy	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Fellow-Servant	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Blandy	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Tobacconist	O
,	O
on	O
Breadstreet-hill	B-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
on	O
Friday	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
my	O
Mistress	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Epsom	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Headcloaths	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Box	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Brocas	O
;	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Headcloaths	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Check	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Joanna	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
September	O
6	O
.	O
Joanna	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Great	B-place
Ambry	I-place
[	I-place
Almonry	I-place
]	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
watch	O
my	O
Door	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
Upstairs	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
up	O
long	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
seems	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Check	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Woman	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Check	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Gregoire	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Shop	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Checks	O
?	O
The	O
Woman	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
call	O
the	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Moment	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Check	O
I	O
sent	O
2	O
Boys	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
my	O
Eye	O
on	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
John	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Quart-Pots	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
September	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
studded	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
27	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
at	O
a	O
Cook's-shop	O
in	O
Chare	B-place
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
your	O
Company	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
that	O
brought	O
me	O
Victuals	O
and	O
Drink	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sit	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
Room	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
so	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
as	O
People	O
sit	O
in	O
to	O
eat	O
their	O
Victuals	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
near	O
you	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
None	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Landlady	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
House	O
together	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
Minutes	O
.	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
there	O
above	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
in	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Fish-skin	O
Case	O
,	O
studded	O
with	O
Silver	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
Door	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
pledge	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
my	O
Barrow	O
of	O
Oysters	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
wanted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
should	O
make	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
say	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
it	O
's	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nail	O
'd	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
make	O
my	O
self	O
for	O
ever	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
find	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
trust	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
think	O
she	O
meant	O
by	O
nailing	O
?	O
Peirce	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
understand	O
those	O
Newgate	O
Words	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Keeper	O
!	O
Can	O
you	O
inform	O
the	O
Court	O
?	O
Keeper	O
.	O
Not	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
People	O
can	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
ask	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
one	O
says	O
it	O
signifies	O
stealing	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
Nailing	O
,	O
is	O
likewise	O
used	O
metaphorically	O
to	O
signify	O
,	O
securing	O
,	O
taking-hold-of	O
,	O
or	O
apprehending	O
.	O
e.g	O
.	O
Tom	O
Beck	O
says	O
of	O
John	O
Davison	O
,	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
himself	O
that	O
Peter	O
Buck	O
was	O
nail	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
.	O
Vide	O
,	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
4.	O
pag	O
.	O
104	O
.	O
Peirce	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
,	O
her	O
Landlady	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Betty	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
wrong	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Landlady	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Minutes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
something	O
to	O
eat	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
cold	O
Flank	O
Beet	O
,	O
or	O
hot	O
Leg	O
of	O
Beef	O
.	O
He	O
chose	O
Leg	O
of	O
Beef	O
;	O
he	O
stay	O
'd	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
Watch	O
!	O
Watch	O
!	O
John	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
down	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
safe	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Smithfield	O
with	O
a	O
ha'perth	O
of	O
Plumb-pudding	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
bit	O
?	O
With	O
all	O
my	O
Heart	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
since	O
you	O
are	O
so	O
civil	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
you	O
drink	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Gin-shop	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
much	O
like	O
this	O
Liquor	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
go	O
somewhere	O
else	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
treat	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Ale	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Landlady	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
stands	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Crown	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
leave	O
you	O
my	O
Watch	O
in	O
Pledge	O
till	O
I	O
bring	O
you	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
proffer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
half	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
keep	O
it	O
longer	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
wou	O
'd	O
come	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
Mary	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
too	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Transportation	O
but	O
last	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
'T	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
my	O
self	O
indeed	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
Sea	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Time	O
being	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
she	O
swore	O
bitterly	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
swore	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
had	O
then	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
had	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Shilling	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Upon	O
Condition	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
customly	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Woman	O
a	O
Shilling	O
upon	O
such	O
an	O
Account	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
not	O
she	O
insist	O
upon	O
a	O
Crown	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
John	B-pers
Cantrell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
28	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
10.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dear	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Georges	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Hens	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Wilfred	B-pers
Oldridge	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
11.	O
William	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
Books	O
,	O
Value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Duncan	B-pers
Macqueen	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Sept.	O
26	O
.	O
Duncan	O
Macqueen	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Attorney	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
for	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
17	O
Books	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
'em	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
search	O
some	O
Booksellers-shops	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
;	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Law	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
others	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
these	O
five	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
part	O
of	O
those	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
Brown	O
on	O
Fines	O
;	O
Brown	O
's	O
Practice	O
of	O
th	O
e	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
Retorna	O
Brevium	O
;	O
The	O
Compleat	O
Sheriff	O
;	O
and	O
Nelson	O
's	O
Lex	B-pers
Maneviorum	I-pers
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Marsh	O
that	O
those	O
Books	O
were	O
stolen	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
?	O
He	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
'em	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
driven	O
to	O
Necessity	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
to	O
raise	O
Money	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Marsh	O
that	O
I	O
sold	O
'em	O
for	O
your	O
use	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
got	O
for	O
them	O
was	O
laid	O
out	O
in	O
Necessaries	O
for	O
your	O
House	O
;	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
at	O
the	O
Chandler's-Shop	O
,	O
for	O
no	O
Body	O
would	O
trust	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
have	O
since	O
moved	O
off	O
your	O
Goods	O
by	O
Night	O
.	O
Macqueen	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
pawning	O
the	O
Seal	O
and	O
moving	O
off	O
by	O
Night	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
true	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
but	O
indifferent	O
Circumstances	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
And	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
you	O
trod	O
upon	O
my	O
Toes	O
,	O
and	O
whisper	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
easy	O
.	O
Macqueen	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
tender	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
House-keeper	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
good	O
repute	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Macqueen	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
other	O
Books	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Millan	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Millan	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
Book	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Anchor	O
and	O
Vine	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
;	O
Macqueen	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
Macqueen	O
threatened	O
to	O
prosecute	O
me	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
a	O
Girl	O
on	O
some	O
Message	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Girl	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
strange	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
still	O
harbour	O
a	O
Man	O
whom	O
he	O
pretended	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
his	O
Books	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Millan	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
no	O
harm	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
trust	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
12	O
,	O
13.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Evershet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Brass	O
Locks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
Keys	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
16	O
Brass	O
Screws	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
Brass	O
Box	O
Staples	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Borlace	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Sept.	O
19	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
in	O
Malborough-Street	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
had	O
a	O
House	O
to	O
be	O
Lett	O
,	O
in	O
Great-Marlborough-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Turner	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
having	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
take	O
one	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Painters	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Londall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Son-in-law	O
were	O
doing	O
the	O
Painter	O
's	O
work	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
's	O
Back-house	O
.	O
There	O
's	O
a	O
Garden	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Back-house	O
and	O
the	O
Fore-house	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Fore-house	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
they	O
might	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
my	O
Son	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
something	O
comes	O
upon	O
my	O
Mind	O
,	O
that	O
these	O
are	O
not	O
honest	O
Men	O
,	O
is	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
loose	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
they	O
can	O
take	O
away	O
?	O
There	O
's	O
nothing	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Brass	O
Locks	O
that	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Chain	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
running	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
Son	O
,	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
down	O
from	O
a	O
Scaffold	O
12	O
Foot	O
high	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
running	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
God	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
Locks	O
!	O
we	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Tyburn-Road	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Theif	O
!	O
stop	O
Red-Coat	O
and	O
Blue-Coat	O
.	O
They	O
run	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
turning	O
a	O
Corner	O
,	O
they	O
dropt	O
a	O
Bag	O
with	O
the	O
Locks	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
soon	O
after	O
taken	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Holdsworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Father-in-law	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
down	O
Poland-Street	O
,	O
in	O
Tyburn-Road	O
.	O
They	O
run	O
into	O
Chappel-Street	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Corner	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Locks	O
fall	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
Turner	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Stanton	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
George	B-pers
Alehouse	I-pers
Door	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Chappel-Street	O
.	O
Eversbet	O
run	O
down	O
a	O
Coach-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
2	O
Brass-Locks	O
on	O
the	O
Dunghill	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Red-Coat	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Little-House	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
search	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Hay-Loft	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
at	O
the	O
George	B-pers
Door	I-pers
,	O
when	O
Turner	O
came	O
running	O
along	O
in	O
a	O
Blue	O
Rug-Coat	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Bag	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
I	O
quitted	O
my	O
Horse	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Stanton	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
swear	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Locks	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
And	O
these	O
are	O
all	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
's	O
Locks	O
.	O
The	O
Defence	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
Painters	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
some	O
People	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
reading	O
the	O
Bill	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
they	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
too	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
might	O
and	O
welcome	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
let	O
'em	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Coventry	I-pers
,	O
Painter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
have	O
both	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
trusted	O
in	O
Gentlemen	O
's	O
Houses	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Complaints	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14	O
,	O
15	O
,	O
16.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Coxen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Yates	O
for	O
stealing	O
with	O
Abigal	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
a	O
Linen	O
Wallet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
21	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
Richardson	O
and	O
Coxon	O
for	O
receiving	O
(	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
I	O
sell	O
Stockings	O
about	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Barnet-Market	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Cloth-man	O
,	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
in	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
together	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
and	O
her	O
Sister	O
Abigal	O
Freeman	O
liv	O
'd	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
this	O
Shop	O
.	O
They	O
owed	O
me	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
being	O
so	O
near	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
call	O
for	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
the	O
Cloth-man	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
my	O
Wallet	O
of	O
Stockings	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
They	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
over-joy	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Abigal	O
bid	O
her	O
Sister	O
Betty	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
full	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
may	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
send	O
for	O
one	O
Pot	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
had	O
2	O
Pots	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
so	O
late	O
I	O
drank	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Women	O
follow	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
about	O
10	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
come	O
to	O
some	O
Mischief	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Wallet	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Doors	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
use	O
any	O
Violence	O
,	O
or	O
threaten	O
you	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
your	O
Wallet	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
great	O
Harry	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
there	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
me	O
a	O
Mischief	O
.	O
He	O
ha	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
great	O
Harry	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
The	O
biggest	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
-	O
Harry	O
-	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
-	O
Richardson	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
else	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Joseph	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
out	O
upon	O
Bail	O
;	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sneesby	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
indicted	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
since	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
Abigal	O
Freeman	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
's	O
gone	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Betty	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Baker	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Baker	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
That	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
forget	O
his	O
Name	O
-	O
stay	O
-	O
't	O
is	O
Cock	O
-	O
Cock	O
-	O
Coxon	O
-	O
Isaac	B-pers
Coxon	I-pers
.	O
Coxon	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
then	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
then	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
you	O
there	O
afterwards	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
light	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Candle	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Glimpse	O
of	O
Day-Light	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
Wallet	O
when	O
the	O
Women	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
how	O
many	O
Pair	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
7	O
Pair	O
of	O
fine	O
Hose	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
me	O
in	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Pair	O
prime	O
cost	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Were	O
your	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
went	O
up	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
soon	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
set	O
Eyes	O
on	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
afterwards	O
,	O
except	O
these	O
a	O
Pair	O
and	O
an	O
odd	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
near	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Fellow	O
to	O
the	O
odd	O
One	O
,	O
which	O
Sneeshy	O
had	O
sold	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
some	O
Body	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
because	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
sick	O
a-Bed	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Body	O
but	O
her	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
2	O
Men	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
stood	O
there	O
with	O
my	O
Knife	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
I	O
would	O
stick	O
the	O
next	O
Man	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
or	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Foxley	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
beating	O
2	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
call	O
,	O
Watch	O
!	O
Watch	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
2	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Men	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
gone	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
himself	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
beating	O
the	O
Hour	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
and	O
an	O
odd	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
about	O
50	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
good	O
earnest	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Betty	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Sister	O
Nab	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Baker	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
least	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
Men	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Stockings	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
.	O
Harris	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Stockings	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Fellow	O
to	O
the	O
odd	O
one	O
that	O
Sneeshy	O
sold	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
ha'porth	O
of	O
Small	O
Beer	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Deptford	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
Beadle	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
at	O
11	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
a	O
proper	O
Officer	O
,	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
obey	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
2	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
2	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
the	O
Hemp-dresser	O
and	O
the	O
Baker	O
;	O
but	O
Sneeshy	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Richardson	O
had	O
got	O
off	O
;	O
however	O
we	O
took	O
Richardson	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
2	O
Hours	O
afterwards	O
.	O
For	O
he	O
coming	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
told	O
us	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
,	O
damn	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Jail	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Jail	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
indeed	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
too	O
hard	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Dog	O
kept	O
him	O
under	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sorrow	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
poor	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
gone	O
aside	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
under	O
a	O
Colour	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
appear	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Defence	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Yates	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
has	O
nothing	O
to	O
lay	O
to	O
my	O
Charge	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
was	O
only	O
out	O
of	O
kindness	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Coxon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watch	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charged	O
me	O
.	O
Henry	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
,	O
in	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Betty	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
2	O
Women	O
and	O
2	O
Men	O
,	O
so	O
suddled	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
neither	O
go	O
no	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
lose	O
any	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
lost	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
'em	O
drinking	O
together	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
Men	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
a	O
Distiler	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
my	O
living	O
honestly	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
you	O
and	O
Sneesby	O
that	O
jumpt	O
out	O
at	O
Window	O
.	O
Richardson	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
us	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
left	O
you	O
both	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
got	O
out	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
watch	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
were	O
both	O
gone	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
being	O
drunk	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
but	O
one	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
17.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sneesby	I-pers
was	O
[	O
next	O
Day	O
]	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wallet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
21	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
Women	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Wallet	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
P	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Richardson	O
and	O
Matthews	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Richardson	O
escaped	O
out	O
at	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
never	O
find	O
who	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
till	O
last	O
Sessions	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
Matthews	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
odd	O
one	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Deptford	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
,	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
dropt	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
Beadle	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Round	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
Foxly	O
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Betty-Yates	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
thrown	O
the	O
Stockings	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watch	O
would	O
meet	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
stept	O
on	O
several	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
drop	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Remainder	O
which	O
was	O
2	O
pair	O
and	O
an	O
odd	O
one	O
he	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
at	O
Deptford	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
these	O
other	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
and	O
an	O
odd	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
Islington	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
.	O
This	O
odd	O
one	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
odd	O
one	O
which	O
he	O
sold	O
at	O
Deptford	O
are	O
Fellows	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
in	O
Islington	O
with	O
Long	O
Harry	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
Betty	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Abby	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
were	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
together	O
.	O
Long	O
Harry	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
and	O
Harry	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
together	O
.	O
Then	O
Abigal	O
Freeman	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
lying	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
secure	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
then	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
sure	O
you	O
ha	O
n't	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
safe	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
a	O
Hatter	O
in	O
Newtoner's-Lane	O
.	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
neither	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
nor	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
below	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
2	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
were	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
with	O
my	O
Penknise	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
rest	O
from	O
going	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lobb	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Lobb	I-pers
.	O
We	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
10	O
Weeks	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
civil	O
,	O
sober	O
Man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
18	O
,	O
19.	O
Abigal	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
she	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wallet	O
and	O
21	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
About	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
Abigal	O
Freeman	O
and	O
Betty	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
for	O
7	O
s.	O
which	O
my	O
Wife	O
had	O
lent	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
lived	O
hard	O
by	O
us	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
What	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
says	O
Abigal	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
heartily	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
drank	O
once	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
Women	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Wallet	O
of	O
Stockings	O
under	O
pretence	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
robbed	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
robb	O
'd	O
or	O
robb	O
'd	O
not	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
London	O
this	O
blessed	O
Night	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
carried	O
my	O
Wallet	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Upstairs	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
Harry	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Sam	O
Sneeshy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Goods	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
thrown	O
out	O
at	O
Window	O
,	O
as	O
Sam	O
Sneeshy	O
told	O
me	O
afterwards	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Woman	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
and	O
the	O
Men	O
said	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
should	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
stay	O
till	O
Morning	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
behave	O
your	O
self	O
in	O
a	O
friendly	O
Way	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
without	O
making	O
any	O
Complaints	O
of	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
No	O
farther	O
than	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
never	O
buss	O
'd	O
her	O
Lips	O
,	O
nor	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
nor	O
touch	O
'd	O
her	O
Flesh	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
there	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
staid	O
watching	O
without	O
the	O
Door	O
3	O
Hours	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
11	O
till	O
2	O
.	O
Nicholson	O
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Betty	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Room	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
we	O
saw	O
Coxon	O
there	O
too	O
.	O
We	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
which	O
of'em	O
he	O
charged	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
All	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Cage	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
4	O
a-Clock	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
we	O
met	O
Richardson	O
.	O
He	O
begun	O
to	O
rifle	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
damn	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Cage	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
we	O
made	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Abigal	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
along	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
brought	O
hither	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
Defence	O
.	O
Abigal	O
Freeman	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
about	O
Dusk	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
undressing	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
for	O
one	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
another	O
.	O
We	O
sat	O
drinking	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
near	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Chandler's-Shop	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
suddled	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
Night	O
and	O
lie	O
in	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
lie	O
with	O
my	O
Sister	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
Upstairs	O
.	O
Coxon	O
and	O
Richardson	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
Richardson	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
join	O
'd	O
together	O
for	O
a	O
full	O
Pot	O
of	O
Two-penny	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
'em	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
11	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
till	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
waked	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
along	O
Islington	O
a	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
I	O
met	O
Betty	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
;	O
't	O
is	O
very	O
dark	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
pray	O
be	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
she	O
invited	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
shall	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
again	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
amends	O
for	O
your	O
Civility	O
in	O
taking	O
care	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
To-Morrow	O
's	O
Sunday	O
,	O
sure	O
you	O
'll	O
have	O
some	O
time	O
to	O
spare	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
engag	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
n	O
come	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
I	O
promiss	O
'd	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
on	O
Monday	O
Evening	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
staid	O
there	O
sometime	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
Lodging	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
lye	O
at	O
her	O
Sister	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
Abigal	O
.	O
Abigal	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
was	O
a-bed	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
fast	O
asleep	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
at	O
all	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
Abigal	O
?	O
[	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
Harris	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
sit	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
just	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
20.	O
Ann	B-pers
Holliwell	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hollomay	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Feckner	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
l.	O
August	O
14	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
Frederick	O
Feckner	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
whereupon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deliver	O
'd	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
testifying	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
personally	O
serv	O
'd	O
with	O
Notice	O
of	O
Tryal	O
.	O
The	O
Affidavit	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
again	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
be	O
Estreated	O
.	O
21	O
,	O
22.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bygrave	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
he	O
for	O
stealing	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Seal	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
October	O
17	O
.	O
and	O
she	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
23.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Pelletier	I-pers
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
24.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gabriel	I-place
Fenchurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
October	O
7	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Buttolph	I-place
's	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Gun	O
Barrel	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Guns	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
27	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
27.	O
John	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
and	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tallow	O
,	O
Value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jasper	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
26	O
.	O
Jasper	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Tallowchandler	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
was	O
my	O
Journeyman	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
at	O
Work	O
;	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Beard	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
had	O
stopt	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
some	O
Tallow	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Man	O
's	O
Wife	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Tallow	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
your	O
Tallow	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Cellar	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
acting	O
in	O
Obedience	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
28.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstans	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
7	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
Value	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
4	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
Shaving	O
Cloths	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
September	O
16	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
.	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Chairwoman	O
at	O
my	O
Chambers	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
Temple	O
;	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
several	O
odd	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
suspect	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
happen	O
'd	O
one	O
Day	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Shirt	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
7	O
new	O
ones	O
which	O
cost	O
me	O
about	O
30	O
s.	O
a-piece	O
but	O
3	O
Weeks	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
some	O
were	O
soul	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
at	O
Washing	O
.	O
This	O
put	O
me	O
upon	O
a	O
farther	O
Search	O
,	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
7	O
Shirts	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
and	O
2	O
Tea-spoons	O
,	O
several	O
Neck-cloths	O
,	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
light	O
my	O
Fire	O
,	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
her	O
closely	O
;	O
she	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
Sake	O
do	O
n't	O
ruin	O
me	O
!	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
Shirts	O
,	O
my	O
Neckcloths	O
,	O
my	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
Spoons	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
tempted	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
more	O
Things	O
than	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
deliver	O
me	O
the	O
Shirts	O
to	O
wash	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
order	O
'd	O
you	O
either	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
get	O
wash	O
'd	O
any	O
Shirts	O
since	O
those	O
7	O
were	O
made	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nelthorp	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
By	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
's	O
Order	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Jarvis	O
's	O
the	O
Pawn-brokers	O
on	O
Newstreet-hill	O
to	O
fetch	O
out	O
4	O
Shirts	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
2	O
Guineas	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
,	O
but	O
understanding	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
likewise	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Guineas	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
to	O
fetch	O
that	O
out	O
too	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
her	O
own	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Jarvis	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Presence	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
Direction	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
.	O
And	O
these	O
4	O
Shirts	O
are	O
para	O
of	O
those	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Nelthorp	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
too	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
four	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
's	O
Neckcloths	O
and	O
2	O
of	O
his	O
Shaving	O
Cloths	O
in	O
Black-Fryars	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
at	O
what	O
House	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
This	O
white	O
Callico	O
Waistcoat	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
me	O
Yesterday	O
Morning	O
(	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
)	O
by	O
Jarvis	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
enter	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Books	O
to	O
her	O
Name	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Weller	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Shaving	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Towels	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
Suit	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
deliver	O
me	O
the	O
Shirts	O
to	O
wash	O
?	O
Weller	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
1	O
Shirt	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Ink	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Weller	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
1	O
Shirt	O
indeed	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
ink	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Ink	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
:	O
Besides	O
,	O
you	O
said	O
you	O
knew	O
of	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
that	O
had	O
not	O
yet	O
been	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
name	O
them	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
you	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
disown	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
pretends	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Tea-spoons	O
too	O
,	O
because	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
cleaning	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
Weller	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
Tea-spoons	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
home	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Day	O
before	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
missing	O
we	O
had	O
had	O
Peas	O
for	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
Use	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
Night	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
often	O
did	O
when	O
my	O
Master	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
treated	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
as	O
likely	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Spoons	O
as	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
Spoons	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
name	O
any	O
Spoon	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
but	O
spoke	O
in	O
general	O
Terms	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
pawn	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
own	O
that	O
I	O
stole	O
them	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
.	O
You	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
away	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Burker	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
his	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Towels	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
have	O
Patience	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
.	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
pawn	O
'd	O
'em	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
your	O
Pardon	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
of	O
a	O
Husband	O
that	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
swell	O
'd	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Poison	O
that	O
my	O
Husband	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
miscarry	O
'd	O
and	O
was	O
like	O
to	O
dye	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
this	O
Condition	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
Wages	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
back	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
stop	O
it	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
.	O
She	O
indeed	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
her	O
Wages	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
due	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
having	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Reason	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
here	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
they	O
are	O
gone	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
take	O
your	O
Tryal	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
you	O
desir	O
'd	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
off	O
till	O
to	O
Day	O
,	O
because	O
your	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
called	O
up	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
desired	O
his	O
Tryal	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
off	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
all	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
hired	O
to	O
swear	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
29.	O
Mary	B-pers
Trotman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
13	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
September	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Atwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mallard	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31.	O
Richard	B-pers
Rippon	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
Plains	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Carpenters	O
.	O
Tools	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
Frances	B-pers
Macclean	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Bellady	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Stock	O
Buckle	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Tortoiseshell	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bellady	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
is	O
my	O
Fellow-Servant	O
;	O
my	O
Mistress	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
sing	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Gown	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Smith	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Charles	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Waiters	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Bagnio	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
James's-Street	I-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
sing	O
at	O
our	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mistress	O
used	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Six-pence	O
or	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
One	O
Night	O
she	O
came	O
when	O
it	O
rain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
Victuals	O
and	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
together	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
up	O
before	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Snuff-Box	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
Night	O
in	O
a	O
Brandy	O
shop	O
in	O
Wychstreet	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
Things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Pinch	O
of	O
Snuff	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
Box	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
Present	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Gown	O
too	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Waiter	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
more	O
Money	O
than	O
that	O
Gown	O
was	O
worth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Candle	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Maids	O
too	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
his	O
Buckles	O
at	O
John	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Stanhope-street	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
'em	O
in	O
pawn	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
Jane	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
Curtains	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Duvain	I-pers
,	O
September	O
9	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
35	O
,	O
36.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
aged	O
15	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
aged	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
,	O
aged	O
11	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pauls	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brain	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
10b	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
Sept.	O
15	O
.	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Watchman	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
my	O
Cellar-door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
Sutton	O
in	O
my	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bag	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
mine	O
)	O
upon	O
the	O
Cellar-stairs	O
with	O
about	O
10	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
such	O
a	O
Quantity	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Casks	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Cellar-door	O
was	O
made	O
fast	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
?	O
Brian	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
Sutton	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
James	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
thrust	O
back	O
the	O
2	O
Bolts	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
the	O
Shutter	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
attempted	O
it	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Sutton	O
said	O
may	O
affect	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Mason	O
and	O
Abraham	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Sutton	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blackmore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bodice	O
,	O
a	O
Stomacher	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
3	O
Mobs	O
,	O
2	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blackmore	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
3	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
2	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
August	O
1	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
And	O
.	O
37.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
and	O
harbouring	O
them	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
they	O
had	O
committed	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
And	O
.	O
38.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blackmore	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Sept.	O
6	O
.	O
And	O
39.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Pembrook	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Sept.	O
6	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Blackmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shakesby's-Walk	B-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
waking	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
Window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
So	O
having	O
no	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
Shakesby-Walk	O
with	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
on	O
but	O
my	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
mad	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
without	O
finding	O
the	O
Thieves	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
afterwards	O
upon	O
another	O
.	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
confest	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ovington	I-pers
.	O
When	O
Sutton	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Brian	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Will	O
Abraham	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
break	O
that	O
Cellar-Window	O
open	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Abraham	O
and	O
Mason	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
stood	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
while	O
Sutton	O
got	O
into	O
Blackmore	O
's	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
out	O
a	O
Box	O
and	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
carried	O
to	O
Pembroke	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
open	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Sutton	O
gave	O
the	O
Bodice	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
sold	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Childrens	O
Shoes	O
for	O
4	O
d.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
Brooks	O
and	O
Pembroke	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
Brooks	O
a-bed	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
unwilling	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
on	O
these	O
Bodice	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
Pembroke	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Gin-shop	O
hard-by	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Boys	O
having	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Closet	O
to	O
hide	O
themselves	O
in	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
enquired	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Closet	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
Pembroke	O
smoking	O
a	O
Pipe	O
.	O
This	O
Handkerchief	O
too	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
Brooks	O
.	O
E.	O
Blackmore	O
.	O
This	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Bodice	O
,	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Ovington	O
.	O
Sutton	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
stole	O
any	O
Goods	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Grandmother	O
Pembroke	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
neglected	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
Sirral	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
bring	O
me	O
Goods	O
as	O
you	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
I	O
can	O
maintain	O
you	O
in	O
Idleness	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
Sutton	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
Fact	O
?	O
Ovington	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
when	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Boys	O
confess	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
all	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
40.	O
Richard	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
5	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
14	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
2	O
Swords	O
,	O
a	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
a	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pint-pot	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Cover	O
,	O
a	O
Copper-pot	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Horn	O
Box	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Ham	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
;	O
5	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
;	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bermudes	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Halwell	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
6	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
41	O
.	O
42.	O
Mary	B-pers
Horsenail	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Amy	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Marshall	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Table	O
cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
,	O
a	O
Horn	O
Box	O
,	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
4	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bermudas	O
Hat	O
;	O
and	O
Griffin	O
for	O
receiving	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Entrance	O
was	O
made	O
at	O
a	O
Back	O
Cellar-window	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
fast	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
the	O
Grate	O
wrench	O
'd	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
This	O
Window	O
leads	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
my	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
recollected	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
what	O
Particulars	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
drew	O
up	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
sufficient	O
Number	O
of	O
them	O
printed	O
and	O
dispersed	O
about	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
by	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Goods	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Advertisements	O
with	O
the	O
Particulars	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
this	O
Inst	O
.	O
September	O
,	O
1732	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Dorrington-street	O
,	O
Cold-Bath	O
Fields	O
,	O
near	O
Sir	O
John	O
Oldcastle	O
's	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
this	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
thence	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Arm	O
and	O
Sword	O
for	O
the	O
Crest	O
,	O
the	O
Mouth	O
a	O
little	O
worn	O
.	O
One	O
Pair	O
of	O
large	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
in	O
a	O
Kind	O
of	O
Square	O
or	O
Diamond	O
Cut	O
.	O
One	O
Pair	O
of	O
small	O
ones	O
,	O
with	O
square	O
Bottoms	O
.	O
One	O
large	O
odd	O
one	O
,	O
with	O
round	O
Knobs	O
.	O
One	O
Copper	O
Coffee-Pot	O
.	O
One	O
large	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
both	O
clean	O
scower	O
'd	O
.	O
Two	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
little	O
melted	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
.	O
One	O
Pewter	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
.	O
One	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
all	O
marked	O
either	O
with	O
HCE	O
or	O
the	O
Arm	O
and	O
Sword	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
One	O
Soop	O
Plate	O
a	O
little	O
melted	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
.	O
One	O
Water	O
Plate	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Cover	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Four	O
Shifes	O
,	O
one	O
mark	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Breast	O
with	O
M.C	O
.	O
Four	O
white	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
colour	O
'd	O
ones	O
.	O
One	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
one	O
Flaxen	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Irish	O
Cloth	O
mildew	O
'd	O
at	O
one	O
End	O
.	O
If	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
pawn	O
'd	O
or	O
sold	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
desired	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
Party	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
Notice	O
as	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
three	O
Guineas	O
Reward	O
.	O
P.S	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
likewise	O
one	O
Mourning	O
Sword	O
,	O
one	O
Lacquer	O
'd	O
Sword	O
,	O
one	O
Boy	O
's	O
Hat	O
;	O
a	O
salted	O
Ham	O
,	O
quite	O
white	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
hung	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
small	O
Leg	O
in	O
pickle	O
.	O
A	O
Bermudas	O
Hat	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
red	O
Silk	O
,	O
a	O
narrow	O
Brim	O
,	O
and	O
Hat-band	O
curiously	O
wrought	O
with	O
Bugles	O
and	O
Silk	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
.	O
A	O
Copper-pot	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
refresh	O
your	O
Memory	O
by	O
looking	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
in	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carrey	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
5	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
a	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
14	O
Plates	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
Water	O
plate	O
,	O
4	O
Shifts	O
,	O
7	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Pait	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Swords	O
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
falted	O
Ham	O
,	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Pork	O
in	O
Pickle	O
,	O
a	O
Bermudas	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
,	O
a	O
Copper-pot	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
3	O
Guineas	O
Reward	O
for	O
stopping	O
them	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
these	O
Advertisements	O
being	O
left	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Askew	O
(	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
)	O
's	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
following	O
.	O
with	O
this	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Amy	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
.	O
Mason	O
,	O
alias	O
Davis	O
,	O
alias	O
Griffith	O
,	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
rried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
,	O
she	O
impeach	O
'd	O
Marshall	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
the	O
2	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Marshall	O
's	O
Wife	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
King	I-pers
John	I-pers
,	O
who	O
goes	O
for	O
Mason	O
's	O
Husband	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
published	O
fresh	O
Advertisements	O
+	O
for	O
Apprehending	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
2	O
Guineas	O
on	O
his	O
being	O
secured	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
more	O
on	O
his	O
Conviction	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Parker	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
2	O
Guineas	O
as	O
promised	O
.	O
King	O
John	O
immediately	O
confess	O
'd	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Marshal	O
had	O
robbed	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
too	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
Year	O
ago	O
+	O
London	O
,	O
September	O
30	O
,	O
1732	O
.	O
Whereas	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
King	I-pers
John	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Blacksmith	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
Others	O
(	O
now	O
in	O
Custody	O
)	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
Houshold	O
Goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
said	O
Griffin	O
is	O
a	O
short	O
,	O
square	O
,	O
well-set	O
Man	O
,	O
about	O
Thirty-five	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
much	O
pitted	O
with	O
the	O
Small-pox	O
,	O
round	O
Vizage	O
,	O
his	O
Hair	O
short	O
,	O
thick	O
,	O
and	O
curling	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
Brown	O
,	O
his	O
common	O
Apparel	O
a	O
striped	O
Flanel	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Leather-Apron	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
wears	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
seldom	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
generally	O
a	O
Snuff-colour	O
'd	O
Camblet	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
most	O
Part	O
open	O
and	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
several	O
Disguises	O
;	O
sometimes	O
he	O
appears	O
like	O
a	O
Countryman	O
,	O
a	O
Sailor	O
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Whoever	O
Apprehends	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
shall	O
receive	O
Five	O
Guineas	O
Reward	O
,	O
two	O
upon	O
Surrender	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
remaining	O
Three	O
on	O
Conviction	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Dorrington-street	O
,	O
Cold-Bath-Fields	O
.	O
H.	O
CAREY	O
.	O
N.B	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
seen	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
neatly	O
Drest	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
new	O
Suit	O
of	O
Light-colour	O
'd	O
Cloth	O
,	O
or	O
Drugget	O
.	O
If	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
reasonable	O
Charges	O
shall	O
be	O
allow	O
'd	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Griffin	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
Sword	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
.	O
He	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
spoon	O
of	O
Amy	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
Search	O
was	O
made	O
;	O
for	O
upon	O
the	O
second	O
Search	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
two	O
Swords	O
in	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
examin	O
'd	O
very	O
strictly	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
this	O
Iron	O
Hand-crow	O
too	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
Griffin	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Marshall	O
wrench	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Grate	O
of	O
my	O
Cellar-window	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Askew	I-pers
.	O
Amy	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Crest	O
answering	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
3	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
Amy	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
Cow-cross	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Swain	O
,	O
knew	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Swain	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
Mason	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
Cow-cross	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
Barber	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
secure	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
however	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
Spoon	O
.	O
R.	O
Marshall	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
Griffin	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
Spoon	O
?	O
Askew	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
King	O
John	O
.	O
Dick	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
Watch	O
had	O
gone	O
12	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
we	O
wrenched	O
the	O
Wooden	O
Bat	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar-window	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
open	O
the	O
2	O
Bolts	O
,	O
and	O
risted	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Marshall	O
took	O
this	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
ye	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Spoon	O
?	O
John	O
.	O
By	O
this	O
Mark	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
John	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
as	O
many	O
Things	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
carry	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
Brass	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Who	O
's	O
there	O
?	O
And	O
so	O
we	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
2	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Hung	B-pers
Beef	I-pers
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
Dick	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hung	B-pers
Beef	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
boiled	O
the	O
Pork	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
John	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
else	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
?	O
John	O
.	O
A	O
Box	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
a	O
Tea-pot	O
,	O
4	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
11	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
other	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
Water-plate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
Writing	O
round	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
read	O
.	O
We	O
put	O
the	O
Pewter	O
and	O
Brass	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Dick	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
comes	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
a-bed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
Amy	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
then	O
my	O
Wife	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
neglecting	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
on	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
my	O
Wife	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
break	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
.	O
A	O
Juryman	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
were	O
disturbed	O
by	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
crying	O
,	O
Who	O
's	O
there	O
?	O
how	O
came	O
Marshall	O
to	O
venture	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
?	O
John	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Things	O
without	O
Side	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
a	O
doors	O
the	O
last	O
Time	O
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
knew	O
how	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
her	O
afraid	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Spoon	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
Wife	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
Wife	O
?	O
John	O
.	O
Amy	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
's	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
I	O
married	O
her	O
at	O
Cripplegate	O
Church	O
.	O
R.	O
Marshall	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
another	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Children	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Murdock	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Swain	O
having	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Askew	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
Amy	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
to	O
Swain	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
but	O
little	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
But	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
,	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
Mason	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
about	O
20	O
Times	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
lives	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
commit	O
you	O
.	O
While	O
his	O
Mittimus	O
was	O
making	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
where	O
Mason	O
was	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
secured	O
Dick	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
backwards	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
Trunk	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
told	O
us	O
,	O
these	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
this	O
Bermadas	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Table-cloth	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
more	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
R.	O
Marshall	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
(	O
by	O
Direction	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Marshall	O
's	O
Landlord	O
)	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Distress	O
upon	O
Marshall	O
's	O
Goods	O
for	O
Rent	O
.	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Shift	O
,	O
mark	O
'd	O
M.	O
C.	O
And	O
remembring	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
's	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
Shifts	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
suspected	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
search	O
more	O
narrowly	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Wig-box	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
Candlesticks	O
and	O
this	O
Pewter	O
Cover	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
loaded	O
Pistol	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
this	O
other	O
Pair	O
of	O
Candlesticks	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
the	O
Dresser	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
Stairs	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Ham	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
:	O
Here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Harrison	O
.	O
This	O
Bermudas	O
Hat	O
is	O
mine	O
It	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
.	O
Her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Name	O
is	O
Henry	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
And	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Hat	O
belongs	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Halliwell	I-pers
my	O
Lodger	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Shift	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
more	O
and	O
4	O
Aprons	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Amy	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
were	O
married	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
acted	O
under	O
the	O
Power	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
their	O
Husbands	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Richard	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
43.	O
Richard	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
44.	O
Mary	B-pers
Horsenail	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
45.	O
Amy	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
he	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robe	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
Bolsters	O
,	O
2	O
Blankets	O
.	O
18	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
6	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
1	O
China	O
Canister	O
,	O
2	O
China	O
Tea	O
cups	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Tea-spoon	O
,	O
2	O
Copper	O
Tea-kettles	O
,	O
1	O
Copper	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
1	O
Copper	O
Chocolate-pot	O
,	O
3	O
Sauce-pans	O
,	O
1	O
Porringer	O
,	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
6	O
Knives	O
,	O
6	O
Forks	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robe	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
August	O
31	O
,	O
1731	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
And	O
Mary	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
two	O
China	O
Cups	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
;	O
and	O
Amy	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
1	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robe	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
of	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
was	O
a	O
Twelve-Month	O
,	O
News	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
furnish	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intention	O
of	O
sending	O
my	O
Children	O
thither	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
Condition	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Doors	O
all	O
forced	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Furniture	O
was	O
carried	O
off	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
's	O
House	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
Search	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
Distress	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Richard	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
Rent	O
due	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
the	O
Landlord	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
China	O
Cups	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Robe	O
swears	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prizmore	I-pers
.	O
And	O
these	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Richard	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Newnham	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Table-cloth	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Amy	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
or	O
her	O
Sister	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Table	O
cloth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
.	O
One	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
latter-end	O
of	O
August	O
was	O
a	O
12	O
Month	O
,	O
Dick	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
Gun	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Garden-house	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
China	O
Decanister	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Cover	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
Doors	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
our	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
rumaged	O
the	O
House	O
from	O
Top	O
to	O
Bottom	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
Bedding	O
and	O
Pewter	O
,	O
and	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
else	O
we	O
could	O
come	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
Dick	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
sold	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
The	O
Bed	O
and	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Blankets	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Worth	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Thornton	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
Dish	O
and	O
5	O
Plates	O
of	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
,	O
thinking	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
claims	O
them	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
Mr.	O
Robe	O
's	O
Dishes	O
and	O
Plates	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
Plates	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
fell	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
sold	O
a	O
Featherbed	O
and	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Worth	O
upon	O
Saffron-Hill	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Worth	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Broker	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Green	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Marshall	O
's	O
,	O
were	O
sell	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Marshall	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
kept	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Cow-cross	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
Scot	O
and	O
Lot	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
Credit	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Body	O
would	O
have	O
disputed	O
to	O
have	O
bought	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
Bed	O
for	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
afford	O
to	O
give	O
more	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Sale	O
at	O
Islington	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
this	O
Bed	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
allow	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
40	O
s.	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
would	O
give	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
R.	O
Marshall	O
.	O
This	O
Griffin	O
has	O
been	O
reckon	O
'd	O
a	O
Thief	O
for	O
these	O
5	O
and	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
brought	O
so	O
many	O
People	O
into	O
Trouble	O
only	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Green	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
sell	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
Pretence	O
he	O
brought	O
these	O
Goods	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Holloway	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Green	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Worth	O
's	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
2	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Rich	O
.	O
Marshall	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
46.	O
John	B-pers
Booker	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Matselon	I-place
,	I-place
alias	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Collet	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
near	O
the	O
Nag's-Head-Inn-Gate	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Funeral	O
pass	O
by	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
stood	O
close	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
betwixt	O
their	O
Heads	O
.	O
Says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
hand	O
on	O
Burying	O
.	O
I	O
wonder	O
whether	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Maid	O
or	O
a	O
Batchelor	O
.	O
Those	O
are	O
fine	O
Srutcheous	O
;	O
do	O
but	O
look	O
,	O
Madam	O
!	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
car	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
turning	O
about	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Penknife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Pocket	O
was	O
cut	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
Fingers	O
in	O
the	O
Slit	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pulling	O
out	O
my	O
Snuff-box	O
.	O
I	O
actually	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
You	O
Rogue	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
Box	O
!	O
Damn	O
your	O
Eyes	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
speak	O
such	O
another	O
Word	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
sacrifice	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
several	O
Times	O
on	O
the	O
Stomach	O
.	O
I	O
still	O
held	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
threw	O
something	O
over	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
your	O
Box	O
,	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
still	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
Penknife	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
self	O
in	O
a	O
Puddle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
Box	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
twisting	O
himself	O
about	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
into	O
a	O
Court	O
;	O
telling	O
the	O
People	O
he	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Bailiff	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
begging	O
them	O
to	O
hide	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Cave	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
sitting	O
down	O
at	O
a	O
Table	O
opposite	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
begun	O
to	O
use	O
better	O
Language	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
Bitch	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
Madam	O
;	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
my	O
Life	O
away	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
these	O
Words	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Collet	O
.	O
I	O
question	O
whether	O
they	O
did	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
leaned	O
over	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
whisper	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
first	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
mistaken	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
wrong	O
Person	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Collet	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
you	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
damned	O
my	O
Eyes	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Nag's-Head	O
Gate	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Funeral	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Bromley	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Burying	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
but	O
view	O
it	O
well	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Collet	O
was	O
standing	O
against	O
an	O
Oyl-Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
stood	O
close	O
before	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
Left-hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
this	O
Clasp-pen-knife	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
on	O
it	O
thus	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Collet	O
