TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
1732	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1732	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probyn	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fortescue	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eden	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mazarine	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Aubin	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Petty	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Grainger	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dag	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rex	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Littlewood	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Ann	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barter	I-pers
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
John	O
Barter	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
Coach-maker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
by	O
Cavendish-Square	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
Sev'n-night	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
;	O
but	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
a-miss	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Side-pocket	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
2	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
brought	O
up	O
by	O
another	O
Creature	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Piece	O
for	O
'em	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Third	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
but	O
a	O
Penny	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Crown	O
but	O
2	O
Minutes	O
before	O
Missing	O
my	O
Watch	O
too	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
a	O
coming	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
do	O
as	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
Watchman	O
away	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
getting	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Watchman	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
made	O
shift	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
fuddled	O
?	O
Barter	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
a	O
Judge	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
the	O
Watch	O
again	O
?	O
Barter	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Surprize	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Watchman	O
in	O
a	O
Surprize	O
too	O
?	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
search	O
her	O
?	O
Barter	O
.	O
Lord	O
bless	O
you	O
!	O
she	O
kick	O
'd	O
and	O
beat	O
the	O
Watchman	O
and	O
Constable	O
like	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
in	O
Pawn	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-brokers	O
to	O
inquire	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Barter	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
advis	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
play	O
the	O
Devil	O
with	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
Wife	O
to	O
Frasier	O
who	O
was	O
hang	O
'd	O
in	O
Chains	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
twice	O
cast	O
for	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Man	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Grosvenor-Square	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
,	O
do	O
and	O
welcome	O
;	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
will	O
then	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
be	O
familiar	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
haul	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
would	O
serve	O
his	O
turn	O
,	O
truly	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
needs	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
he	O
has	O
sworn	O
this	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
his	O
Watch	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
Shilling	O
about	O
me	O
when	O
the	O
Watchman	O
search	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
good	O
House-keepers	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
thinking	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
Vile	O
and	O
Wicked	O
as	O
to	O
swear	O
this	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
sent	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
's	O
Jenny	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
a	O
vile	O
Slut	O
!	O
that	O
has	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
since	O
her	O
own	O
Husband	O
was	O
hang	O
'd	O
in	O
Chains	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
given	O
this	O
Fellow	O
Money	O
to	O
pick	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
me	O
Transported	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
way	O
;	O
O	O
Conscience	O
!	O
Conscience	O
!	O
do	O
but	O
look	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
and	O
see	O
how	O
he	O
blushes	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
2.	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-Watch	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
in	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kingland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
-	O
Willet	O
at	O
a	O
Skettle-Ground	O
in	O
Moor-lane	B-place
,	O
*	O
Morris	O
and	O
Kingland	O
were	O
try	O
'd	O
last	O
Sessions	O
and	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
now	O
acquitted	O
Green	O
.	O
*	O
Session's-Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
V.	O
Page	O
142	O
3.	O
William	B-pers
Faucett	I-pers
,	I-pers
[	I-pers
Fosset	I-pers
]	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass-Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
and	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Shop	O
,	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s.	O
an	O
Apron	O
val	O
.	O
18d	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver-Buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
2	O
a-Clock	O
on	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
end	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
take	O
Dimensions	O
for	O
making	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
drinking	O
new	O
Rum	O
and	O
other	O
Liquors	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
others	O
till	O
past	O
a	O
11	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
down	O
in	O
Denmark-street	B-place
in	I-place
Ratcliffe	I-place
High-way	I-place
,	O
I	O
fell	O
fast	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
wake	O
till	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
I	O
wonder	O
'd	O
where	O
about	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
my	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Stockings	O
,	O
my	O
Blue	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Hat	O
.	O
But	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
bethought	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Body	O
had	O
found	O
me	O
a-sleep	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
undress	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
barefooted	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
towards	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
any	O
idle	O
Person	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
9	O
that	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
Friend	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Ludlow	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
in	O
Upper-Shadwell	O
,	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
her	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
John	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
the	O
Watchman	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
Stockings	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
go	O
along	O
barefooted	O
.	O
From	O
Bridewell	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
again	O
before	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
then	O
had	O
my	O
Apron	O
on	O
:	O
He	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
nothing	O
but	O
Swore	O
and	O
Curs	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
Bandy	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
.	O
Watchman	O
in	O
Upper-Shadwell	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
beating	O
my	O
Rounds	O
at	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
in	O
West-Garden	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
vine	O
Hat	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
What	O
dost	O
thee	O
do	O
here	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Why	O
I	O
want	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
one	O
?	O
Where	O
didst	O
thee	O
get	O
such	O
a	O
vine	O
Hat	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Why	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
again	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
goes	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
comes	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
calls	O
vor	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
however	O
thee	O
didst	O
come	O
by	O
this	O
Hat	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
thee	O
didst	O
get'n	O
,	O
the	O
Devil	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
but	O
sure	O
thy	O
Husband	O
never	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
to	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
zays	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
his	O
Zhoes	O
and	O
Ztockings	O
too	O
in	O
my	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
leave	O
'em	O
all	O
with	O
you	O
till	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
.	O
Zo	O
she	O
pull'd'n	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took'n	O
and	O
throwd'n	O
by	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
hardly	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
she	O
.	O
Zo	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
vor	O
'em	O
about	O
2	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
zays	O
I	O
,	O
thee	O
must	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
thee	O
didst	O
come	O
by'n	O
bevore	O
I	O
let	O
thee	O
have'n	O
again	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
zee	O
a	O
Man	O
coming	O
along	O
bare-vooted	O
,	O
and	O
bare-leg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
a	O
Hat	O
.	O
Hoy	O
!	O
hoy	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
Plague	O
beest	O
thee	O
,	O
that	O
thee	O
runs	O
naked	O
a	O
that'n	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
the	O
Things	O
that	O
Prisoner	O
lest	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
he	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ludlow	I-pers
.	O
About	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
o	O
'	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
these	O
Buckles	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
gave	O
'em	O
her	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
stol'n	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Headborough	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
by	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
claimed	O
the	O
Buckles	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
them	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
a-sleep	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
my	O
Nosegays	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
Ratcliff-Highway	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
dark	O
Entry	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
his	O
Will	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
pawn	O
his	O
Buckles	O
for	O
7s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
obliging	O
her	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
took	O
'em	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
'em	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
so	O
much	O
upon	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sell	O
'em	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
by	O
striking	O
him	O
and	O
throwing	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Blows	O
and	O
Fall	O
,	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
several	O
mortal	O
Bruises	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Sides	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
Boy	O
s	O
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
They	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
playing	O
together	O
at	O
Buff-at-the-Bear	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
caught	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
lie	O
down	O
and	O
be	O
the	O
Bear	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
others	O
buffeted	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
occasion	O
'd	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
he	O
challeng	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Box	O
him	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Long	O
field	O
by	O
the	O
Burying	B-place
Ground	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Pancras	I-place
.	O
They	O
met	O
,	O
fought	O
fair	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
striking	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
an	O
unlucky	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
it	O
broke	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Blood	O
Vessels	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
Robert	B-pers
Element	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shadwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Coniers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Looking	O
glass	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
3	O
Caps	O
,	O
four	O
Towels	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pillow	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Coniers	I-pers
:	O
Two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Stocks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
JamesRule	B-pers
:	O
Two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
3	O
Aprons	O
,	O
4	O
Caps	O
,	O
2	O
Suits	O
of	O
Pinners	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
Girdle	O
and	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
April	O
17	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Dallison	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
First	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Coniers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New-Gravel-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
wash	O
Linen	O
for	O
my	O
Livelihood	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
small	O
Morsel	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
shut	O
my	O
Window-shutter	O
which	O
was	O
within	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
barr	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
this	O
little	O
wooden	O
Bar	O
[	O
about	O
an	O
Inch	O
square	O
]	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
left	O
at	O
Home	O
to	O
lock	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
understand	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
and	O
my	O
other	O
Lodger	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
at	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Door	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Kitchen-Casement	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
little	O
Bar	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Riding-Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Linen	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Rule	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Cox	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Parker	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Looking-glass	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Fleming	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Cox	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Coniers	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
she	O
waked	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Linen	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Jack	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
and	O
Jack	B-pers
Longmore	I-pers
and	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
in	O
Well-street	O
;	O
but	O
Osborn	O
and	O
Longmore	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
'em	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
a	O
Yard	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
little	O
Deal	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
and	O
a	O
Riding-Hood	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
some	O
Towels	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pocket	O
which	O
had	O
two	O
Keys	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
Ten	O
a	O
Clock	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
there	O
was	O
Linen	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Maux	O
's	O
,	O
lodging	O
in	O
Church-Lane	O
,	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
We	O
kept	O
a	O
Shirt	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
Aprons	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
She	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
brought	O
us	O
18	O
s.	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
sunk	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Street-Robbery	O
with	O
Osborn	O
,	O
Tripland	O
,	O
and	O
Longmore	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Coniers	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
her	O
the	O
Keys	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Laurence	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
We	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Ale	O
house	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
Country	O
Bob	O
(	O
a	O
Name	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
)	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
'd	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
him	O
to	O
Fleming	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
bang	O
that	O
Rogue	O
Fleming	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
for	O
betraying	O
me	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
'll	O
carry	O
me	O
before	O
Justice	O
Philips	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
'll	O
admit	O
me	O
for	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Fleming	O
has	O
not	O
put	O
this	O
Burglary	O
into	O
his	O
Information	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
inform	O
against	O
him	O
and	O
others	O
for	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Hats	O
on	O
the	O
Thames	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Facts	O
.	O
Indeed	O
,	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
hanged	O
for	O
a	O
Fool	O
,	O
for	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
so	O
soon	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
to	O
Brentford	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
under	O
a	O
Brick-kiln	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
my	O
Thigh	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Fleming	O
ca	O
n't	O
hurt	O
me	O
for	O
any	O
Thing	O
but	O
this	O
one	O
Fact	O
of	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
New-Gravel-Lane	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
Friend	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
dye	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
any	O
Man	O
living	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dallison	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
that	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
lay	O
in	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
placed	O
betwixt	O
the	O
two	O
Beds	O
,	O
to	O
hide	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
About	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
finding	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
open	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
waked	O
us	O
.	O
Our	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
fo	O
und	O
him	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
Coat	O
,	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
Stockings	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
before	O
Justice	O
Giffard	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
your	O
Room	O
?	O
Dallison	O
.	O
Very	O
odly	O
.	O
About	O
3	O
Weeks	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
lying	O
asleep	O
upon	O
a	O
Bulk	O
in	O
Bloomsbury-market	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Shirt	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Some	O
Boys	O
pinn	O
'd	O
a	O
Paper	O
to	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
setting	O
Fire	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
burnt	O
his	O
Back-side	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Son	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
well	O
.	O
Tho	O
'	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
been	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
but	O
little	O
Hurt	O
by	O
what	O
the	O
Boys	O
did	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
chief	O
Damage	O
before	O
,	O
by	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
Brick-kiln	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dallison	I-pers
corroborated	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Dallison	O
's	O
Son	O
that	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
me	O
shamefully	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
please	O
I	O
can	O
shew	O
you	O
the	O
Marks	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Dallison	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
owed	O
me	O
a	O
Grudge	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
7	O
,	O
8	O
,	O
9.	O
John	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
Valentine	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
150	O
Brass	O
Patterns	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Bell-metal	O
Mortar	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Skelthorn	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
June	O
30	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Skelthorn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Founder	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
about	O
150	O
Brass	O
Patterns	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Melting-House	O
in	O
King's-Head-Court	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Shoe-Lane	I-place
.	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
without	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
somebody	O
within	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Charley	I-pers
,	O
had	O
agreed	O
to	O
rob	O
Mr.	O
Skelthorn	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
promised	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
.	O
Between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
his	O
Brother	O
Valentine	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
Val	O
.	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Melting-house	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Patterns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bell-Metal	O
Mortar	O
.	O
We	O
packed	O
'em	O
up	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
our	O
Pockets	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
our	O
Laps	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
under	O
our	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
Harry	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
greatest	O
Part	O
to	O
Winterton	O
,	O
an	O
Ironmonger	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
Parcel	O
to	O
a	O
Brasier	O
by	O
Smithfield-Bars	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
Mortar	O
to	O
one	O
Simon	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
somewhere	O
about	O
Barbican	O
,	O
for	O
15	O
d.	O
Halfpenny	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Val	O
.	O
Robins	O
went	O
into	O
Beach-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
to	O
a	O
Nail-maker	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
worth	O
to	O
a	O
Spoon-maker	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
(	O
26	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
Halfpenny	O
)	O
all	O
we	O
made	O
of	O
that	O
Night	O
's	O
Work	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Skelthorp	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Brocas	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
fell	O
on	O
their	O
Knees	O
,	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
persuaded	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
Winterton	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bid	O
them	O
bring	O
whatever	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hobert	I-pers
.	O
All	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Scrape	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
'em	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
John	O
Robins	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
Robins	O
,	O
and	O
Henry	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
,	O
11.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Charley	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Dangerfield	I-pers
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
July	O
2	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
Hampstead	B-place
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Men	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Field	O
from	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
going	O
to	O
Pancras	B-place
.	O
The	O
first	O
clap	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
surrounded	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
3	O
s.	O
or	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Hat	O
.	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
five	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rhodes	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Goat	O
in	O
Black-Boy	O
Alley	O
,	O
Chick	O
lane	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
towards	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn-lane	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Path	O
;	O
between	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
and	O
Pancras	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
.	O
Charley	O
and	O
Dangerfield	O
stood	O
by	O
with	O
Sticks	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
:	O
Val	O
.	O
Robins	O
took	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
Sarret	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Barret	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
next	O
Field	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
went	O
a	O
contrary	O
Way	O
.	O
We	O
lay	O
under	O
a	O
Hedge	O
till	O
break	O
of	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Shore	O
ditch	O
;	O
I	O
forget	O
the	O
Sign	O
.	O
where	O
we	O
drank	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Pots	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
eat	O
some	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Arthur	O
and	O
eat	O
some	O
Beans	O
and	O
Bacon	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
9	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rhodes	O
's	O
in	O
Black-Boy-Alley	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Skittles	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Pawn	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
John	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
and	O
Charley	O
carried	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
they	O
got	O
5	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
Charley	O
bought	O
a	O
Pistol	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Bartlett	O
's	O
Buildings	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
Rob	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
of	O
out	O
going	O
out	O
on	O
such	O
an	O
Account	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
hearing	O
distinctly	O
,	O
desir	O
'd	O
that	O
Norman	O
might	O
repeat	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
without	O
varying	O
in	O
any	O
Circumstance	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Waker	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Atley	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
asked	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
mistrust	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
3	O
Hours	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
Mr.	O
Atley	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
Dangerfield	O
in	O
Field-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Turn-again-Lane	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
we	O
would	O
help	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Wood-Street	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
others	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rhodes	O
's	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
.	O
We	O
mist	O
of	O
'em	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
Partridge	O
(	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Barns	O
and	O
Fink	O
)	O
who	O
came	O
from	O
Norman	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
the	O
3	O
Compasses	O
in	O
Tottenham	O
Court-Road	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
but	O
met	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
John	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
Valentine	O
and	O
Barret	O
and	O
Norman	O
,	O
but	O
Country	O
Jo	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
the	O
former	O
three	O
to	O
Dangerfield	O
in	O
Wood-Street	O
Compter	O
;	O
but	O
Norman	O
being	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
our	O
Way	O
thither	O
,	O
Country	O
Jo	O
past	O
by	O
us	O
.	O
Jo	O
,	O
says	O
Norman	O
what	O
,	O
wo	O
n't	O
ye	O
speak	O
to	O
us	O
?	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
too	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Brocas	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
Norman	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Be	O
as	O
particular	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
about	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
.	O
Waker	O
.	O
Barret	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
Norman	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
any	O
such	O
Fact	O
before	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
Robins	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
before	O
Barret	O
.	O
Country	O
Jo	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
never	O
concerned	O
in	O
any	O
Robbery	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Norman	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Robbery	O
before	O
he	O
knew	O
Norman	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
Dangerfield	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
)	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Barret	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Dangerfield	O
.	O
Nor	O
I	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
stealing	O
the	O
Brass	O
Patterns	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
convicted	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Most	O
of	O
Waker	O
's	O
Evidence	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Claxon	I-pers
.	O
In	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
Barret	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
.	O
Barret	O
.	O
You	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
turn	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Claxton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
speak	O
it	O
as	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
alledg	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
to	O
their	O
Reputation	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
12.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
9	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13	O
,	O
14.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
,	O
June	O
17	O
.	O
John	O
Willoughby	O
.	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
Walker	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
about	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
o	O
'	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
in	O
Hanging	B-place
Sword-Alley	I-place
.	O
The	O
other	O
brought	O
up	O
a	O
Flask	O
and	O
a	O
Glass	O
;	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
1/4	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
;	O
but	O
Walker	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
first	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
said	O
Bishop	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
you	O
shall	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
flung	O
her	O
Arms	O
round	O
my	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
buffing	O
on	O
me	O
like	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Then	O
Nill	O
Walker	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
hard	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
.	O
While	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
with	O
t'other	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
let	O
go	O
her	O
Hold	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
that	O
Hand	O
to	O
my	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Hand	O
she	O
reach	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
Bishop	O
who	O
presently	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Then	O
says	O
Nell	O
,	O
what	O
does	O
he	O
make	O
a	O
Noise	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
but	O
2	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
for	O
the	O
Maid	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
toward	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
Landlady	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
2	O
men	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
who	O
help	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
o	O
'	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
about	O
3	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
but	O
8	O
Pence	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
lost	O
3	O
Pounds	O
.	O
Nell	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Fellow	O
came	O
by	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
me	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
14	O
d.	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
to	O
his	O
Honour	O
,	O
and	O
oblige	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
things	O
upon	O
Trust	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
deal	O
with	O
none	O
but	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
could	O
make	O
me	O
a-handsome	O
Present	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
Bishop	O
to	O
have	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
nothing	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
I	O
'm	O
a	O
Christian	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
no	O
more	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
than	O
2	O
Groats	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
swears	O
he	O
lost	O
3	O
l.	O
But	O
he	O
's	O
an	O
Irishman	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
consider	O
his	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
he	O
will	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
to	O
borrow	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
trust	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
Shilling	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Play-House-Yard	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
15	O
,	O
16.	O
James	B-pers
Emerton	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Frances	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Frances	O
his	O
Wife	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchers	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
(	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Dawcett	I-pers
in	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
Emerton	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dawcett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
Long	O
Lane	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Emerton	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
damn	O
your	O
Soul	O
too	O
much	O
you	O
Dog	O
!	O
is	O
it	O
fit	O
that	O
any	O
Rogue	O
should	O
knock	O
my	O
Teeth	O
out	O
?	O
and	O
now	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
swear	O
my	O
Life	O
away	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
too	O
.	O
Dowatt	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
they	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
needs	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
for't	O
F.	O
E.	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
tried	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
speak	O
one	O
Word	O
till	O
my	O
Husband	O
is	O
clear	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
,	O
[	O
she	O
stamps	O
about	O
till	O
her	O
Cap	O
falls	O
off	O
]	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
put	O
my	O
Cap	O
on	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
a	O
Rogue	O
.	O
D.	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
say	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
White	B-place
Horse	I-place
in	I-place
Chick	I-place
Lane	I-place
.	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
self	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
they	O
stript	O
me	O
by	O
main	O
Force	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
F.	O
E.	O
Ah	O
you	O
Dog	O
!	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
for	O
your	O
Sake	O
.	O
D.	O
And	O
then	O
one	O
said	O
to	O
t'other	O
.	O
Let	O
's	O
murder	O
him	O
.	O
F.	O
E.	O
You	O
lie	O
,	O
Sirrah	O
,	O
you	O
lie	O
,	O
you	O
Hang-in-Chains	O
Rogue	O
.	O
D.	O
So	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
her	O
Husband	O
)	O
stopt	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Collar	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Watch	O
go	O
by	O
past	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
help	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
with	O
much	O
a	O
do	O
I	O
forc	O
'd	O
my	O
Way	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
naked	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
F.	O
E.	O
O	O
you	O
damnation	O
Rogue	O
.	O
D.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
but	O
be	O
easy	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Price	I-pers
Watchman	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
beating	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
12	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
as	O
naked	O
as	O
ever	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
except	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
Robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Emerton	I-pers
.	O
Here	O
's	O
another	O
Hang-in-Chains	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
;	O
ar	O
n't	O
you	O
asham	O
'd	O
of	O
yourself	O
you	O
Rogue	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
run	O
up	O
the	O
Alley	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Church-lane	O
.	O
F.	O
Emerton	O
.	O
You	O
lie	O
you	O
Dog	O
.	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
James	B-pers
Emerton	I-pers
was	O
standing	O
leaning	O
upon	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Clothes	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
every	O
thing	O
but	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
his	O
Buckles	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Emerton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
before	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Emerton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
met	O
this	O
Man	O
in	O
g	O
lane	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Eye	O
was	O
cut	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
by	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Morefields	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
to	O
wash	O
his	O
Eye	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
wash	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
Gin	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
Water	O
and	O
wash	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
that	O
too	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
th'other	O
Woman	O
,	O
shall	O
I	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
'em	O
.	O
They	O
2	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
my	O
Husband	O
comes	O
home	O
dead	O
drunk	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
this	O
Fellow	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
t'other	O
Woman	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
has	O
sent	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
for	O
cutting	O
his	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
he	O
swears	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
vile	O
Rogue	O
for	O
his	O
Pains	O
;	O
and	O
Will	O
.	O
Balt	O
a	O
Runner	O
of	O
Newgate	O
knock	O
'd	O
this	O
Tooth	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
Alderman	O
Brocas	O
's	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Dear	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
Consideration	O
;	O
do	O
what	O
you	O
will	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
let	O
all	O
Punishment	O
be	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
clear	O
my	O
Husband	O
;	O
do	O
n't	O
hang	O
him	O
whatever	O
you	O
do	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Wife	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
29	O
Yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
24	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
183	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
Value	O
15	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
June	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
Isabella	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gwyn	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
a	O
Broad	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
Mother	O
at	O
the	O
Dutch	O
Ware-house	O
against	O
Durham-Yard	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
Night	O
I	O
met	O
Isabella	O
Eaton	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Half-Moon-Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
2	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy	O
shop	O
(	O
kept	O
by	O
one	O
Soamn	O
)	O
in	O
Red-Lion-street	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Citron-Water	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
paid	O
1	O
s.	O
Eaton	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lye	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
refusing	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
same	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
to	O
the	O
Greyhound-Inn	B-place
in	I-place
Drury-Lane	I-place
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Eaton	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
so	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
Bed	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
lye	O
with	O
me	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
suspecting	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Design	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
counting	O
it	O
,	O
parted	O
the	O
Gold	O
from	O
the	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Gold	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
a	O
Broad-piece	O
and	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
into	O
my	O
Right-side	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
down	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
(	O
not	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
lay	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
Business	O
she	O
had	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
?	O
But	O
she	O
got	O
her	O
Hand	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
for	O
feeling	O
on	O
the	O
out-side	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
some	O
Money	O
within	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
Gold	O
was	O
safe	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
Eaton	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
going	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
.	O
This	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
searching	O
my	O
Pocket	O
within-side	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
only	O
2	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Sixpences	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
my	O
Gold	O
:	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
'em	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
owned	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
Money	O
(	O
but	O
not	O
how	O
much	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
except	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
'em	O
two	O
Guineas	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
would	O
return	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
say	O
how	O
they	O
got	O
it	O
?	O
G.	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
Eaton	O
was	O
very	O
outrageous	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Landlord	O
prevented	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Moll	O
Harvey	O
came	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Riot	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
Bell	O
Eaton	O
escaped	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
produced	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
no	O
more	O
Gold	O
about	O
you	O
,	O
than	O
what	O
you	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
?	O
G.	O
A	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sral	O
Gra	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Greyhound-Inn	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Bll	O
Eaton	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
little	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
.	O
Says	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
ye	O
want	O
two	O
Beds	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
Offence	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Pint	O
with	O
my	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
some	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
up	O
together	O
.	O
When	O
that	O
Pint	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
We	O
will	O
have	O
my	O
Pint	O
now	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
.	O
Says	O
Eaton	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
is	O
more	O
generous	O
than	O
to	O
let	O
you	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
paid	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
to	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
ca	O
n't	O
I	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
welcome	O
,	O
says	O
my	O
Mistress	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
a	O
Porter	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
(	O
as	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
)	O
who	O
came	O
directly	O
.	O
They	O
sat	O
down	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
another	O
Pint	O
.	O
By-and-by	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
knocking	O
above	O
Stairs	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
for	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Water	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
filled	O
a	O
Bottle	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatch	O
'd	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Go	O
up	O
,	O
saysmy	O
Mistress	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
why	O
she	O
stays	O
;	O
and	O
tell	O
her	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
never	O
suffer	O
such	O
Doings	O
,	O
as	O
for	O
two	O
Women	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
one	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
Practice	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
my	O
Mistress	O
wonder	O
'd	O
she	O
staid	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
a-bed	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
Your	O
Husband	O
wants	O
ye	O
.	O
Let	O
him	O
go	O
Home	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
tell	O
ye	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a-bed	O
,	O
and	O
wo	O
n't	O
come	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Young	B-pers
Woman	I-pers
,	O
what	O
d	O
'ye	O
want	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
my	O
Mistress	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
such	O
Things	O
,	O
as	O
two	O
Women	O
to	O
one	O
Man	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
Gold	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Side-pocket	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
Says	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
served	O
in	O
this	O
Manner	O
by	O
two	O
Women	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
sit	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
shall	O
be	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
About	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
my	O
Master	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Eaton	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Chamber-door	O
softly	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
coming	O
out	O
.	O
Hey	O
!	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
two	O
Woman	O
a	O
creeping	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
hearing	O
this	O
,	O
got	O
from	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
forced	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
Eaton	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Disturbance	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
out	O
o	O
'	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
prevented	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
several	O
Slaps	O
o	O
'	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Very	O
well	O
,	O
Madam	O
!	O
I	O
sha	O
n't	O
strike	O
you	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
split	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
kept	O
her	O
from	O
getting	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
Constable	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
came	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Money	O
by	O
your	O
Candle	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Guineas	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Broad-piece	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
?	O
Grant	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Gold	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
Sort	O
.	O
He	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
hold	O
it	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
counting	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Voice	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
say	O
,	O
We	O
own	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
shall	O
never	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
except	O
you	O
'll	O
give	O
us	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eland	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Greyhound-Inn	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Russel-street	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
last	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
about	O
six	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Eaton	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
were	O
making	O
a	O
Riot	O
,	O
and	O
disturbing	O
his	O
Lodgers	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
charg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Broad-piece	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
'em	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
'em	O
to	O
their	O
Choice	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
or	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
up	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
chose	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
'em	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Eaton	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
be	O
spent	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
carry	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Du	O
Veil	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
her	O
Terms	O
,	O
she	O
catch	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
Case-Knife	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
stick	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
avoided	O
the	O
Blow	O
;	O
and	O
by-and-by	O
Moll	O
Harvey	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Mob	O
of	O
I	O
believe	O
an	O
Hundred	O
Pick-pockets	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Riot	O
about	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
Eaton	O
escaped	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
stir	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
no	O
Crime	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
faitly	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
old	O
Acquaintance	O
.	O
G.	O
A.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
Face	O
before	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
before	O
Justice	O
Dn	O
Veil	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
in	O
Red-Lion-street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
say	O
so	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
About	O
a	O
Week	O
ago	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
Lett	O
none	O
under	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
her	O
Husband	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
her	O
Character	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Soams	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
in	O
Red-Lion-street	O
.	O
So	O
o	O
'	O
Friday	O
Night	O
one	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
lye	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Soams	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
she	O
and	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Soams	O
if	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
receive	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
pulled	O
some	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
Perhaps	O
you	O
are	O
afraid	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
no	O
Money	O
.	O
Whereof	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
says	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Now	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
give	O
me	O
enough	O
to	O
fetch	O
my	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
very	O
much	O
against	O
my	O
Desire	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
sent	O
a	O
Paper	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
ruin	O
my	O
Husband	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Cabinet-maker	O
)	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Whitney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
Soams	O
's	O
o	O
'	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
9	O
,	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tiff	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
free	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swears	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
drank	O
a	O
Dram	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Whitney	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
drank	O
Punch	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
kiss	O
'd	O
and	O
embraced	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
soudly	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
Woman	O
about	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
this	O
Woman	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
If	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
Money	O
to	O
fetch	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
a	O
Broad-piece	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
enough	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
did	O
she	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
enough	O
?	O
Whitney	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
with	O
that	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
observe	O
the	O
Pieces	O
so	O
particularly	O
?	O
W.	O
I	O
stood	O
pretty	O
near	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
W.	O
No	O
.	O
C.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
find	O
you	O
out	O
then	O
?	O
W.	O
She	O
heard	O
of	O
me	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Soams	O
's	O
.	O
C.	O
Are	O
you	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
constant	O
Customers	O
?	O
W.	O
No	O
:	O
But	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Business	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
We	O
often	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
drink	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drinks	O
at	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
Customers	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brings	O
Customers	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
live	O
very	O
sociably	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Soams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
in	O
Red-Lion-street	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
o	O
'	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Dram	O
a-piece	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
sate	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Tiff	O
of	O
Punch	O
.	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
We	O
wo	O
n't	O
sit	O
here	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
.	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
often	O
promised	O
to	O
fetch	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
,	O
And	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
sha	O
n't	O
want	O
Money	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Moidore	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
all	O
?	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Broad-piece	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
which	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
enough	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
her	O
more	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
's	O
one	O
of	O
Moll	O
Harvey	O
's	O
Bail	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Husband	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
had	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
pass	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
?	O
Was	O
you	O
never	O
reputed	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
Husband	O
?	O
Soams	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
S.	O
Grant	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
my	O
Mistress	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
Wife	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
pretty	O
much	O
at	O
her	O
Beck	O
,	O
however	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gines	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Soam	O
's	O
'so	O
'	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
Dear	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
Inn	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Night	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
above	O
her	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
promise	O
her	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
And	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
promised	O
me	O
Money	O
many	O
a	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
is	O
only	O
out	O
of	O
Spite	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
along	O
with	O
Bill	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Mary	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bladwell	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Galliot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Gasper	I-pers
Grace	O
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
John	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Ickenham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Osmond	I-pers
,	O
May	O
13	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Osmond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ickenham	B-place
Parish	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Uxbridge	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
before	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Horse	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Field	O
;	O
in	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
)	O
offering	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Paul	O
of	O
Dartford	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
Deptsord	O
Bride	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
in	O
Ickenham	O
Parish	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
another	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Name	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
the	O
Letter	O
by	O
Mistake	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acquainted	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Contents	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Paul	O
.	O
A	O
Farrier	O
in	O
Dartford	O
asking	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
Alehouse	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
Says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
value	O
this	O
Horse	O
at	O
12	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
a	O
Journey	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
some	O
Horse	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
that	O
will	O
serve	O
my	O
Turn	O
I	O
'll	O
rap	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
pitch	O
'd	O
upon	O
a	O
little	O
serub	O
Horse	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
this	O
little	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
Guineas	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
Earnest	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Custom	O
of	O
our	O
Neighbourhood	O
to	O
require	O
Vouchers	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
bought	O
a	O
Horse	O
of	O
a	O
Stranger	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
could	O
bring	O
no	O
Vouchers	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
knew	O
no	O
Body	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Horse	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Harrow	O
on	O
the	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
now	O
have	O
sold	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
Bexley-Heath	O
of	O
3	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Shilling	O
left	O
to	O
bear	O
his	O
Charges	O
.	O
On	O
farther	O
Talk	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
Shuffled	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
several	O
Stories	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Buck	O
in	O
our	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
sold	O
a	O
Horse	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
'd	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Buck	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
did	O
buy	O
a	O
Horse	O
of	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
Bristol-Causeway	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
afterwards	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
Horse	O
was	O
stol'n	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
who	O
having	O
examin	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Deptford-Bridewell	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rundal	I-pers
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
saw	O
the	O
Horse	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
away	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Taibot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
Horse	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
a	O
black	O
Cart	O
Gelding	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
drove	O
him	O
3	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
One	O
John	B-pers
Brocks	I-pers
a	O
Farmer	O
,	O
at	O
Maidenhead	O
,	O
met	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
between	O
Kensington	O
and	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Horse	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
Rochester-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
22.	O
John	B-pers
Gillet	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mouth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Maxey	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dionis	I-place
Back-Church	I-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
April	O
9	O
.	O
John	O
Maxey	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Lime	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
*	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
)	O
standing	O
at	O
Pewterer	O
's	O
Hall-Gate	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
at	O
the	O
Rummer	O
Tavern-Door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
both	O
their	O
Faces	O
plainly	O
by	O
the	O
Lamp	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Cullum-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
Crouch	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
to	O
my	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
Crouch	O
shook	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
nothing	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
perceiving	O
that	O
Crouch	O
did	O
not	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Danm	O
you	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
come	O
along	O
.	O
Says	O
Crouch	O
,	O
He	O
holds	O
me	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
let	O
go	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
they	O
both	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
last	O
Monday	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
described	O
him	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Crouch	O
,	O
alias	O
Yarmouth	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions-Paper	O
,	O
p.	O
139.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
my	O
Door	O
o	O
'	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Description	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
damn	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
,	O
on	O
an	O
Information	O
for	O
robbing	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
Crouch	O
's	O
Company	O
but	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
Crouch	O
will	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
if	O
you	O
send	O
for	O
him	O
from	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
23.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
(	O
with	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Plumridge	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
Joshua	B-pers
Lumm	I-pers
in	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloth-Coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
*	O
Plumridge	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Cole	O
and	O
Pain	O
who	O
were	O
capitally	O
Convicted	O
in	O
Doceer	O
last	O
,	O
see	O
his	O
Tryal	O
in	O
the	O
Session-Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
I.	O
Pag	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Desire	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
him	O
were	O
examin	O
'd	O
a-part	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Lumm	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Alderman	O
Parsons	O
:	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
June	O
18th	O
near	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
3	O
Men	O
in	O
Stepney-Fields	B-place
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
collar	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
my	O
Shirt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gathers	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
push	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
cut	O
me	O
across	O
the	O
Throat	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
want	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
then	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
Broomsticks	O
,	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pathway	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
they	O
dragg	O
'd	O
me	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
Yards	O
aside	O
;	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
leaning	O
me	O
against	O
a	O
Bank	O
,	O
took	O
19	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
piece	O
of	O
Span	O
sh	O
Silver	O
,	O
worth	O
about	O
4	O
d.	O
halfpenny	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches-Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
left	O
6	O
d.	O
behind	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
pull	O
'd	O
my	O
Coat	O
off	O
,	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Gloves	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Coat-Pocket	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
several	O
Knocks	O
with	O
Broomsticks	O
to	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
up	O
my	O
Hand	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
defend	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
my	O
Arm	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
swell	O
'd	O
next	O
Day	O
with	O
the	O
Blows	O
:	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
cut	O
my	O
Wrist	O
,	O
my	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Ears	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
several	O
other	O
Cuts	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
threatened	O
to	O
tie	O
me	O
Neck	O
and	O
Heels	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
listed	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
run	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Wounds	O
drest	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
well	O
yet	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
;	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Plumridge	O
committed	O
this	O
Robbery	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Winniat	O
's	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Mutton	O
and	O
Turnips	O
for	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Bowls	O
of	O
Punch	O
after	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Winniat	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Countryman	O
;	O
but	O
Winniat	O
is	O
since	O
absconded	O
.	O
Between	O
9	O
and	O
o	O
at	O
Night	O
Plumridge	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Caraway	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
all	O
together	O
to	O
Whitechappel-Fields	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
Plumridge	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
across	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
Stabs	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Case-knife	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
from	O
Winniat	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
give	O
the	O
Stabs	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
afterwards	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Broomstick	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
10	O
th	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
we	O
dragg	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Bankside	O
;	O
Plumridge	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
pull	O
him	O
over	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
19	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
examin	O
'd	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Pocket-Piece	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
Silver	O
like	O
a	O
Sixpence	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
mine	O
.	O
Lumm	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
no	O
Hat	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
.	O
Buck	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
senseless	O
with	O
the	O
Blows	O
and	O
Wounds	O
:	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Plumridge	O
took	O
his	O
Wig	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Remembrance	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
since	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
We	O
stript	O
his	O
Coat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
and	O
wear	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
first	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
murder	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
begg	O
'd	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
ye	O
serve	O
a	O
Man	O
so	O
villainously	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
sure	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
such	O
vile	O
Men	O
as	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
!	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
spare	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
I	O
listed	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
run	O
for	O
his	O
Life	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Plumridge	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
to	O
kill	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
made	O
'em	O
easy	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
are	O
the	O
2	O
Cuts	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
came	O
on	O
foot	O
to	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
Coach	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pember	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Pindar	O
of	O
Wake-field	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
together	O
.	O
Pember	O
married	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Sisters	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
by	O
the	O
Church	O
in	O
Old	O
Bedlam	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
spent	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
and	O
Plumridge	O
went	O
to	O
Cow-Cross	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Coat	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Ralph	B-pers
Dohson	I-pers
's	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
Night	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
voluntarily	O
surrender	O
'd	O
myself	O
to	O
Justice	O
Rohe	O
the	O
same	O
Week	O
(	O
but	O
I	O
forget	O
the	O
Day	O
)	O
and	O
gave	O
Information	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
immediately	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Men	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Plumridge	O
in	O
Old	O
Bedlam	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
myself	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
Warrant	O
out	O
against	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
surrender	O
'd	O
?	O
Buck	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Judge	O
's	O
Warrant	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
surrender	O
'd	O
upon	O
no	O
other	O
Account	O
than	O
the	O
Pricks	O
of	O
Conscience	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
happened	O
it	O
then	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
surrender	O
sooner	O
?	O
Buck	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Company	O
without	O
his	O
suspecting	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
Wig	O
powder	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pointing	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Men	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
to	O
surrender	O
myself	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Plumridge	O
?	O
Buck	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
5	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
Plumridge	O
10	O
Months	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
became	O
acquainted	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rhodes	O
's	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Black-Boy-Alley	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Poulterer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
Plumridge	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
'em	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
enquire	O
into	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Buck	O
.	O
My	O
Character	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
enough	O
known	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
Moon	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
at	O
Madam	O
Lawley	O
's	O
at	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hare	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Horns	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
several	O
other	O
Places	O
:	O
And	O
then	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
Mules	O
and	O
Asses	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
to	O
sell	O
Earthen-ware	O
,	O
till	O
within	O
these	O
3	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
my	O
Sister	O
in	O
Black-Boy-Alley	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
his	O
Sisters	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
for	O
picking	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
Bill	O
was	O
found	O
Ignoramus	O
.	O
Buck	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
my	O
Sisters	O
kept	O
a	O
Brandy	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
t'other	O
kept	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
the	O
Pindar	O
of	O
Wakefield	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
have	O
both	O
met	O
with	O
Losses	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
have	O
left	O
off	O
Trade	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Cooper	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
Liquors	O
and	O
Earthen-ware	O
,	O
Buck	O
,	O
and	O
Plumridge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Dorcheste	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Perry	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pomber	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lately	O
kept	O
the	O
B	O
Tree	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
the	O
Pindar	O
of	O
Wakefield	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
since	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Buck	O
,	O
and	O
Plumridge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Fire	O
,	O
nor	O
Candle	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
dry	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
Buck	O
,	O
You	O
know	O
the	O
way	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
fetch	O
up	O
some	O
bottle	O
Ale	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
3	O
Bottles	O
.	O
I	O
groped	O
about	O
for	O
a	O
Mug	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
it	O
readily	O
,	O
they	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bottle	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
3	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Pump	O
to	O
wash	O
themselves	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
lay	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
5	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Window-shutter	O
,	O
saw	O
their	O
Cloaths	O
which	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Linen	O
were	O
very	O
bloody	O
:	O
Plumridge	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Towel	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
wash	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Coats	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
more	O
bloody	O
than	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
you	O
'll	O
spoil	O
your	O
Coat	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
dry	O
Brush	O
;	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
rub	O
the	O
Blood	O
off	O
his	O
own	O
Coat	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
Buck	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Brush	O
,	O
and	O
clean	O
'd	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
Says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Buck	O
,	O
You	O
ca	O
n't	O
go	O
to	O
London	O
in	O
that	O
Coat	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
pickle	O
:	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
in	O
my	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
the	O
Coat	O
here	O
till	O
dry	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
'em	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
that	O
bloody	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
the	O
Coat	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
playing	O
Rogue	O
with	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
it	O
myself	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
we	O
all	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
Buck	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Coat	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
'em	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
long	O
they	O
staid	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Buck	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
Fellow	O
Plumridge	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
fighting	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
rescue	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
manage	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
were	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
overselves	O
.	O
Now	O
we	O
are	O
afraid	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
take	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
enquire	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
name	O
any	O
particular	O
Fact	O
,	O
concerning	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
he	O
should	O
turn	O
Evidence	O
?	O
Pember	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
London	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
Stepney	O
Fields	O
of	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
abused	O
.	O
This	O
made	O
me	O
suspicious	O
of	O
these	O
three	O
Men	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
that	O
Night	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
Buck	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
frequented	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
came	O
in	O
drunk	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
They	O
stay	O
'd	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
towards	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
they	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Coat	O
that	O
Buck	O
and	O
Plumridge	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
Cow-Cross	O
;	O
they	O
swore	O
and	O
curs	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Names	O
;	O
you	O
're	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
Rogne	O
as	O
I	O
,	O
says	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
Heart	O
,	O
says	O
th'other	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
drew	O
their	O
Knives	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wrested	O
Buck	O
's	O
Knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
Buck	O
sell	O
into	O
a	O
dry	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
without	O
a	O
Coat	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Buck	O
and	O
Plumridge	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
resolute	O
,	O
and	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
their	O
Compliance	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
another	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Buck	O
came	O
Home	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
Bed	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
sat	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Sister	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
your	O
Wife	O
?	O
Pember	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
too	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
be	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
Buck	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
consulted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Brock	O
,	O
Mr.	O
James	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pointing	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
about	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Buck	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
came	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Wife	O
suspecting	O
my	O
Design	O
,	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
Brother	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
timely	O
Notice	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
and	O
Mr.	O
James	O
in	O
London	O
at	O
6	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
to	O
detain	O
Plumridge	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Pointing	O
waited	O
at	O
several	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
catching	O
Buck	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
came	O
that	O
Way	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
mist	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
we	O
stay	O
'd	O
till	O
8	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
Plumridge	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Drury	O
lane	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
two	O
Street	O
Robbers	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
two	O
other	O
Men	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Buck	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Mob	O
being	O
rais	O
'd	O
by	O
that	O
Attempt	O
,	O
those	O
2	O
were	O
committed	O
for	O
breeding	O
a	O
Riot	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
being	O
Thursday	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
that	O
Way	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
happening	O
to	O
see	O
Buck	O
's	O
eldest	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
I	O
dog	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
White-Hart	O
in	O
*	O
Baldwin	O
's	O
Gardens	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drinking	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
Cards	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
express	O
'd	O
some	O
uneasiness	O
that	O
Buck	O
stay	O
'd	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
for	O
Buck	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
under	O
Pretence	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Wig	O
powder	O
'd	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
But	O
one	O
Mr.	O
How	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
the	O
Reason	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
Mr.	O
How	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Writ	O
against	O
you	O
for	O
9	O
l.	O
which	O
you	O
owe	O
your	O
Father-in-Law	O
Thorowton	O
Bocklingson	O
for	O
Board	O
.	O
O	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
's	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
mind	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
sung	O
us	O
a	O
Song	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
a	O
Coach	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
driving	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Father-in-Law	O
's	O
in	O
Rose-street	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
we	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
Richard	B-pers
Pointing	I-pers
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Street	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Information	O
of	O
Buck	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
turn	O
'd	O
as	O
Pale	O
as	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
Sure	O
Peter	O
Buck	O
would	O
never	O
serve	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
carried	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Cross	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Confession	O
.	O
*	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pointing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
Pember	O
and	O
How	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
them	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
2	O
Sugar-Loaves	O
Ale-house	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
on	O
Buck	O
's	O
Information	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
Pointing	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Buck	O
had	O
informed	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
in	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
(	O
not	O
Ba'dwin	O
's	O
Gardens	O
)	O
in	O
Drury	O
lane	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
and	O
Buck	O
and	O
Pember	O
with	O
Buck	O
's	O
Sister	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
another	O
Box	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Buck	O
made	O
an	O
Excuse	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
get	O
his	O
Wig	O
powder	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Sister	O
said	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
hungry	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
Pigeon	O
Pye	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
Thing	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
Pember	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
left	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
play	O
'd	O
a	O
Game	O
or	O
2	O
at	O
Cards	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
wondred	O
that	O
Buck	O
stay	O
'd	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
uneasy	O
.	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
9	O
l.	O
due	O
to	O
his	O
Father-in-Law	O
for	O
Board	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
Buck	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
some	O
Time	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
know	O
where	O
Buck	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
coming	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
carrying	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
were	O
afraid	O
of	O
raising	O
a	O
Mob	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
known	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
a	O
Street	O
Robber	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
gone	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
Pointing	O
following	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Minutes	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hutson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Winniat	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Because	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
Buck	O
say	O
,	O
We	O
robb	O
'd	O
Man	O
yesterday	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Wig	O
.	O
C.	O
Why	O
,	O
was	O
Buck	O
mad	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
publickly	O
?	O
H.	O
He	O
spoke	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
vapoueing	O
way	O
.	O
C.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hear	O
him	O
?	O
H.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
then	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Buck	O
dine	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
?	O
H.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
very	O
positive	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Winniat	O
's	O
but	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Days	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
C.	O
Did	O
you	O
carry	O
in	O
any	O
Punch	O
after	O
Dinner	O
?	O
H.	O
Yes	O
,	O
2	O
Bowls	O
.	O
C.	O
Did	O
they	O
eat	O
together	O
?	O
H.	O
Yes	O
,	O
c.	O
And	O
drink	O
together	O
?	O
H.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
.	O
C.	O
That	O
's	O
not	O
the	O
Question	O
.	O
H.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drank	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
and	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
C.	O
You	O
shuffle	O
!	O
did	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
one	O
Company	O
?	O
H.	O
To	O
my	O
thinking	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
C.	O
Was	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
?	O
H.	O
Another	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
Dinner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
C.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
they	O
stay	O
?	O
H.	O
Till	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
c.	O
Did	O
they	O
go	O
away	O
both	O
together	O
?	O
H.	O
I	O
think	O
so	O
.	O
c.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Plumridge	O
?	O
Did	O
the	O
third	O
Man	O
drink	O
Punch	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
H.	O
They	O
two	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
9	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
our	O
Shop	O
was	O
then	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Carraway	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
stay	O
no	O
longer	O
than	O
just	O
to	O
drink	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
out	O
.	O
C.	O
And	O
could	O
not	O
you	O
have	O
said	O
this	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
without	O
shuffling	O
?	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
Master	O
?	O
H.	O
Gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
C.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
?	O
H.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
.	O
C.	O
And	O
when	O
do	O
you	O
expect	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
H.	O
His	O
Sister	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
expected	O
him	O
next	O
Monday	O
Night	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
3	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
apprehended	O
Buck	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
Buck	O
surender	O
'd	O
himself	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Fathwall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
last	O
Witness	O
Richard	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
informed	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
Buck	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
committed	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
'em	O
both	O
.	O
But	O
Buck	O
's	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
present	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
fetched	O
one	O
Brock	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
with	O
others	O
and	O
beat	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Pots	O
at	O
us	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
Buck	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
Buck	O
turned	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Pember	O
again	O
.	O
Buck	O
's	O
Sister	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
to	O
Captain	O
Giffard	B-pers
's	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
late	O
(	O
being	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
)	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Harry	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
we	O
took	O
Buck	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Scotch	O
Arms	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
Buck	O
in	O
my	O
Hands	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Sister	O
and	O
Brock	O
the	O
Bailist	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
rushed	O
in	O
and	O
rescued	O
them	O
before	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
They	O
raised	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
to	O
sighting	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
charged	O
us	O
with	O
breeding	O
a	O
Riot	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
We	O
were	O
informed	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
that	O
2	O
Street-Robbers	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Scotch	O
Arms	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
seized	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Brock	O
and	O
his	O
Gang	O
came	O
and	O
rescued	O
'em	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
unfortunate	O
as	O
to	O
drink	O
in	O
Buck	O
's	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Buck	O
and	O
Pember	O
both	O
are	O
Persons	O
of	O
the	O
vilest	O
Character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
the	O
City-Marshal	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
found	O
Buck	O
in	O
ill	O
House	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
Debson	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
warn	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
keep	O
away	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Gallows	O
.	O
Pember	O
's	O
Wife	O
is	O
as	O
bad	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
;	O
she	O
's	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
present	O
Pember	O
himself	O
has	O
no	O
visible	O
Way	O
of	O
Livelihood	O
.	O
Brock	O
and	O
James	O
make	O
it	O
their	O
Business	O
to	O
take	O
Rogues	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prickmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Pember	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
no	O
I	O
'll	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
any	O
further	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
lives	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Buck	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Barnet	O
Finks	O
and	O
Yates	O
's	O
Information	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lester	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
'	O
Prentice	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
a	O
Poulterer	O
by	O
Trade	O
.	O
And	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
fed	O
Ducks	O
at	O
his	O
Father-in-Law	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
'em	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Trade	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
no	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Father-in-Law	O
keeps	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Rose-street	O
in	O
Newgate-market	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
good	O
Repute	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lawman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
Hundreds	O
of	O
Pounds	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Farthing	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
Ducks	O
of	O
him	O
within	O
these	O
three	O
Weeks	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
were	O
at	O
Liberty	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
:	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
100	O
l.	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
any	O
Man	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
being	O
ill	O
in	O
February	O
and	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
during	O
her	O
Illness	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
often	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
and	O
pay	O
30	O
,	O
40	O
,	O
or	O
50	O
l.	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
keep	O
my	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
always	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Thorowton	O
Pocklington	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
these	O
18	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Father-in-Law	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
Money	O
to	O
buy	O
Ducks	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
fatted	O
up	O
and	O
sold	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
denied	O
him	O
Money	O
when	O
he	O
wanted	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
rob	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
Charge	O
with	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Neighbours	O
appeared	O
in	O
his	O
behalf	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
24.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cornoch	I-pers
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Rooksby	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
June	O
3d	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
Susan	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gowns	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
27.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Gill	B-pers
Hyat	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
28.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Antony	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
June	O
25th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Cambell	I-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
the	O
