TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
,	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
1732	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1732	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
CHILD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Raymond	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Penton	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Crlin	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
,	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Piggot	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Driver	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burkett	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodyer	I-pers
,	O
Felix	B-pers
Boulton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wolch	I-pers
,	O
Eli	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Allen	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Aveline	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Carleton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Cheeses	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
April	O
10	O
.	O
Owen	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
Cheeses	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop-window	O
in	O
Middle-Row	B-place
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
.	O
There	O
's	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
Yard	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
and	O
Night	O
my	O
Husband	O
went	O
thither	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
Occasions	O
,	O
and't	O
please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
one	O
Hole	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
somebody	O
was	O
upon	O
t'other	O
,	O
whereof	O
he	O
omes	O
running	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
tells	O
me	O
the	O
Story	O
.	O
Now	O
you	O
must	O
know	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
thinks	O
I	O
this	O
may	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rogues	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
the	O
Wind	O
blew	O
(	O
my	O
Candle	O
out	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
Tugg	O
'd	O
the	O
Boy	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Cheeses	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
What	O
Business	O
that	O
was	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
up	O
steps	O
a	O
little	O
whissling	O
Creature	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
Damn	O
your	O
Eyes	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
none	O
of	O
yours	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
Husband	O
fetch	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Boy	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Boy	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
Cheeses	O
from	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Middle-Row	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Winniat	O
the	O
Brandy-man	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
half	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
my	O
Pains	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
2.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Corals	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Banbrear	I-pers
,	O
March	O
27	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Service	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
two	O
Spoons	O
,	O
one	O
Coral	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ring	O
to	O
Mary	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Coral	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chesterman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Saul	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Wiseman	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
Night	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
by	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Orders	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Drops	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Read	O
in	O
Burr-street	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
homeward	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Virginia-street	B-place
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Men	O
leaning	O
over	O
the	O
Rail	O
of	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Moon-light	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Moon	O
was	O
at	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
little	O
clouded	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
them	O
clearly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
when	O
presently	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
repeated	O
their	O
Blows	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
received	O
2	O
contused	O
Wounds	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
fractur	O
'd	O
my	O
Skull	O
.	O
Then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
my	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
examin	O
'd	O
all	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
get	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
because	O
in	O
the	O
Posture	O
I	O
lay	O
my	O
Knees	O
were	O
bent	O
under	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
no	O
Money	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
bye	O
Place	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
groaning	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
somebody	O
open	O
'd	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
beat	O
me	O
again	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
escaped	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
that	O
bid	O
you	O
stand	O
?	O
and	O
you	O
said	O
No	O
.	O
Wiseman	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
no	O
such	O
Question	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
if	O
I	O
took	O
your	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
?	O
and	O
you	O
said	O
No	O
.	O
Wiseman	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
now	O
that	O
you	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Minart	I-pers
,	O
Exciseman	O
.	O
About	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
my	O
Duty	O
in	O
Ratcliffe-Highway	O
,	O
about	O
40	O
Yards	O
from	O
Virginia-street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
3	O
Men	O
running	O
different	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
towards	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shady	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
suddenly	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
meant	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
easily	O
vindicate	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
soon	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
very	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Justice	O
Phillips	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Robbery	O
stifly	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
Business	O
he	O
had	O
near	O
Virginia-street	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
one	O
Will	O
Fleming	O
at	O
the	O
Hercules-Pillar	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
lies	O
anquitt	O
contrary	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
shut	O
up	O
this	O
Twelve	O
month	O
.	O
Somebody	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Parsons	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Smallcoal	O
men	O
*	O
.	O
This	O
Instrument	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Saw	O
that	O
will	O
cut	O
an	O
Iron-bar	O
,	O
another	O
is	O
a	O
Sharp	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
a	O
Tool	O
that	O
they	O
call	O
a	O
Mobock	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
so	O
impudent	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
Hat	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
two	O
contused	O
Wounds	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Number	O
3.	O
pag	O
.	O
89	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
Instrument	O
is	O
for	O
no	O
use	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
cut	O
Cock-spurs	O
with	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Cock-fighting	O
Tool	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sturmy	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Person	O
that	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Dress	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
now	O
?	O
Sturmy	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Sailor	O
's	O
Dress	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Check	O
Shirt	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
These	O
Men	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
threatning	O
Letter	O
by	O
the	O
Penny-Post	O
.	O
For	O
Mr.	O
Wiseman	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
,	O
a	O
Surgun	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
Old	O
Gravel	O
lane	O
,	O
Rattlif	O
High	O
way	O
.	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Our	O
Friend	O
is	O
now	O
starving	O
in	O
Prison	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
gets	O
out	O
we	O
shall	O
take	O
a	O
noportuniti	O
for	O
revenge	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
ar	O
favourable	O
in	O
your	O
Evidense	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
save	O
his	O
life	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
shall	O
le	O
willin	O
to	O
forgive	O
you	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
dyes	O
the	O
Decil	O
fly	O
away	O
with	O
us	O
soul	O
and	O
body	O
if	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
shoot	O
you	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Eksize	O
man	O
that	O
stopt	O
him	O
we	O
will	O
steal	O
his	O
head	O
of	O
before	O
he	O
is	O
much	O
older	O
which	O
you	O
may	O
tell	O
him	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
favourable	O
you	O
will	O
prevent	O
any	O
mischief	O
from	O
coming	O
to	O
you	O
both	O
.	O
By	O
God	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
resolushon	O
of	O
.	O
Number	O
2	O
]	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
this	O
Letter	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
his	O
2	O
Accomplices	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
allow	O
'd	O
in	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
Hang	O
me	O
if	O
it	O
cost	O
a	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
,	O
because	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
for	O
an	O
Anatomy	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Justice	O
Philips	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
can	O
set	O
that	O
Matter	O
to	O
rights	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
did	O
indeed	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
endeavour	O
.	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Body	O
for	O
an	O
Anatomy	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
himself	O
so	O
remarkable	O
,	O
by	O
bestowing	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Small-coal	O
Men	O
upon	O
the	O
Parsons	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
4.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
8d	O
.	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
my	O
Work	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	B-place
,	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Alms-Houses	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
met	O
you	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
pay	O
you	O
heartily	O
,	O
for	O
telling	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
about	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
that	O
Harry	B-pers
Whitesides	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
,	O
*	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
short	O
Stick	O
,	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
kneeling	O
upon	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
took	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cap	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
them	O
both	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
Tom	O
Beck	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
sell	O
upon	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
fill	O
'd	O
my	O
Mouth	O
full	O
of	O
Mud	O
,	O
and	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
right	O
Buttock	O
;	O
see	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Wound	O
in	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
Money	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Whitesides	O
below	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
this	O
Fellow	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
scandalous	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
picking	O
Pockets	O
along	O
with	O
Peter	O
Buck	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
be	O
suffer	O
'd	O
to	O
vilify	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Character	O
thus	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
easy	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
such	O
things	O
of	O
any	O
other	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
do	O
you	O
no	O
Service	O
,	O
for	O
whatever	O
you	O
say	O
without	O
proof	O
,	O
will	O
pass	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
can	O
bring	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
in	O
validate	O
his	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
hear	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
Peter	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
was	O
nail	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
;	O
nail	O
'd	O
,	O
is	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
false	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
Buck	O
's	O
Company	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
well	O
known	O
that	O
I	O
work	O
hard	O
for	O
an	O
honest	O
Livelihood	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
work	O
'd	O
these	O
4	O
Years	O
at	O
Thomas	B-pers
Corks	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
Cellar	O
under	O
John	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Sadler	O
's	O
)	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
just	O
beyond	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cheshire-Cheese	O
and	O
Pump	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
's	O
Harry	B-pers
Whitesides	I-pers
will	O
give	O
your	O
Lordship	O
a	O
Character	O
of	O
this	O
Man	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Witness	O
against	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
Convicted	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
can	O
not	O
then	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
very	O
great	O
with	O
Sarah	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
that	O
bought	O
the	O
Parson	O
's	O
Scarf	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
swore	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
+	O
he	O
has	O
bore	O
me	O
a	O
Spight	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
But	O
one	O
Day	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
Black-Eye	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
Damn	O
me	O
,	O
Tom	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
how	O
d	O
'ye	O
think	O
the	O
Bitch	O
Whittle	O
has	O
serv	O
'd	O
me	O
?	O
She	O
has	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
Black-Eye	O
,	O
and	O
Damn	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
a'nt	O
,	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
a	O
Smack	O
will	O
do	O
you	O
any	O
good	O
it	O
's	O
at	O
your	O
Service	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Smack	O
is	O
an	O
Oath	O
)	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
hardly	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
swears	O
now	O
.	O
+	O
See	O
the	O
Sessions-Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
P.	O
92	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
prove	O
all	O
this	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
's	O
Burton	O
who	O
now	O
lies	O
in	O
Newgate	O
for	O
a	O
Fine	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
prove	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Let	O
Burton	O
be	O
brought	O
hither	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
So	O
far	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
stood	O
without	O
the	O
Grate	O
,	O
he	O
fill	O
'd	O
his	O
Shoe	O
with	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
[	O
Enter	O
Burton	O
.	O
]	O
Court	O
.	O
Here	O
!	O
Burton	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
treat	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
any	O
Gin	O
?	O
-	O
Burton	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
talking	O
together	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Grate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fill	O
'd	O
his	O
Shoe	O
with	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
says	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
enquired	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
very	O
sick	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
likely	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
but	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
Robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
5.	O
Peter	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Marriot	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
6	O
Pictures	O
,	O
value	O
51s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Marriot	O
Hudson	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
April	O
.	O
Marriot	O
Hudson	O
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
Covent-Garden	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Pictures	O
,	O
an	O
d	O
came	O
into	O
Chelsea-Fields	B-place
between	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Fields	O
,	O
laid	O
say	O
Pictures	O
down	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
Stile	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
walked	O
very	O
fast	O
the	O
same	O
Way	O
over	O
the	O
second	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Third	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
staid	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
seiz	O
'd	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
out	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
a	O
Word	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Pictures	O
off	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
bid	O
me	O
pull	O
off	O
my	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Shoes	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
my	O
Cap	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
walk	O
'd	O
off	O
together	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
I	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
Joseph	O
White	O
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dunea	I-pers
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
Men	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
fight	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
near	O
Hide-Park	O
Corner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Pictures	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
threw	O
down	O
their	O
Bundles	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
to	O
a	O
heap	O
of	O
great	O
Stones	O
,	O
they	O
there	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
pelted	O
us	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
more	O
People	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
to	O
their	O
Heels	O
again	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
up	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
Chairman	O
near	O
Devonshire-House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
down	O
Half-Moon-Street	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
Pictures	O
off	O
your	O
Head	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
held	O
me	O
so	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
turn	O
my	O
Head	O
just	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
loosed	O
his	O
hold	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
go	O
from	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Pictures	O
under	O
your	O
Arm	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Duneau	O
from	O
Buckingham	O
House	O
towards	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Boy	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
'and	O
enquiring	O
the	O
Reason	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
gone	O
towards	O
Hide-Park	O
Corner	O
.	O
We	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
fight	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Pictures	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
some	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
Each	O
of	O
them	O
threw	O
down	O
his	O
Parcel	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
great	O
Stones	O
at	O
us	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
stand	O
their	O
Ground	O
long	O
.	O
We	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
too	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Chairman	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Pictures	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Duncan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
vas	O
valking	O
vid	O
from	O
Buckingham	O
Garden	O
at	O
de	O
Pimlico	O
,	O
vare	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
vark	O
togader	O
,	O
and	O
ven	O
ve	O
come	O
into	O
de	O
Shelsea-Field	O
,	O
dare	O
ve	O
see	O
dis	O
Boy	O
,	O
vid	O
noting	O
in	O
de	O
Varld	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
but	O
von	B-pers
Shart	I-pers
,	O
and	O
vid	O
no	O
Shoe	O
upon	O
his	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
vas	O
make	O
a	O
de	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
de	O
very	O
much	O
cry	O
;	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
say	O
,	O
Vat	O
he	O
de	O
mater	O
vid	O
you	O
Boy	O
?	O
Be	O
you	O
mad	O
?	O
Vy	O
you	O
run	O
vidout	O
von	B-pers
Shoe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
vou	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
dis	O
cry	O
?	O
O	O
,	O
he	O
say	O
,	O
dare	O
vas	O
2	O
Rogue	O
bust	O
a	O
new	O
dat	O
take	O
avay	O
mine	O
Pictuer	O
,	O
and	O
mine	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
mine	O
Va	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
boat	O
mine	O
Shoe	O
,	O
and	O
den	O
da	O
run	O
dat	O
avay	O
.	O
So	O
ve	O
all	O
tree	O
make	O
a	O
de	O
run	O
after	O
dem	O
.	O
Vite	O
vas	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
den	O
de	O
Boy	O
vas	O
second	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
vas	O
de	O
turd	O
Man	O
.	O
But	O
ven	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
de	O
Hide-Park	O
Than	O
,	O
I	O
vas	O
out	O
of	O
bret	O
,	O
and	O
coud	O
run	O
no	O
I	O
no	O
see	O
de	O
Preeloner	O
vid	O
de	O
Picteur	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
running	O
without	O
Shoes	O
or	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Here	O
they	O
are	O
!	O
Who	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
The	O
Men	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
stopp	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Heap	O
of	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
us	O
.	O
Then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
ran	O
down	O
Half-Moon-Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
out-ran	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Joseph	B-pers
White	I-pers
running	O
before	O
the	O
Boy	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Cale	I-pers
were	O
within	O
a	O
100	O
Yards	O
of	O
Half-Moon-Street	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
8	O
,	O
when	O
White	O
came	O
running	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
2	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
2	O
Men	O
stopp	O
'd	O
a	O
while	O
to	O
throw	O
Stones	O
at	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
forward	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
again	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
down	O
Half-Moon-Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Cale	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
ran	O
too	O
fast	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
some	O
Ditches	O
towards	O
May-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
escap	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
shop	O
when	O
White	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
Men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
had	O
Pictures	O
in	O
Frames	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
They	O
threw	O
down	O
their	O
Things	O
near	O
a	O
Heap	O
of	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
Stones	O
at	O
those	O
that	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
first	O
threw	O
the	O
Shoes	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ran	O
off	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Chairman	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Stratton-Street	O
,	O
by	O
Devonshire	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
40	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
next	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
several	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
too	O
;	O
Jones	O
and	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
after	O
a	O
Fellow	O
that	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
when	O
they	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
that	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
came	O
first	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Field	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
met	O
me	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Pictures	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Half-Moon-Street	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
6.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wentland	I-pers
Wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wentland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
,	O
7	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mackeg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
1	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
Penny	O
,	O
8	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Quarter	O
Portugal	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
19	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
Henry	O
Parker	O
.	O
That	O
same	O
Ann	O
Wentland	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
as	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
Bit	O
of	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
Time	O
did	O
she	O
pick	O
you	O
up	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
Day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
saying	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
Bit	O
of	O
Victuals	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Moll	O
Harvey	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cock	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
drank	O
Beer	O
and	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
eat	O
some	O
Fish	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
6	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
Paid	O
it	O
,	O
this	O
Jade	O
saw	O
my	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
10	O
Pounds	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
stood	O
up	O
to	O
light	O
my	O
Pipe	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
lighting	O
my	O
Pipe	O
,	O
she	O
whipt	O
the	O
Bag	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
Harvey	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
.	O
Harvey	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Bag	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Jade	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Harvey	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
,	O
Countryman	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
your	O
Bag	O
:	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
Five-pence	O
Halfpenny	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
naughty	O
Piece	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
[	O
A	O
Leaden	O
Medal	O
the	O
Size	O
of	O
a	O
Half-Crown	O
.	O
]	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Harvey	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bag	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Wentland	O
give	O
the	O
Bag	O
to	O
Harvey	O
as	O
she	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Steps	O
,	O
and	O
Harvey	O
brought	O
it	O
directly	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
For	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
with	O
my	O
Sheep	O
at	O
3	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Sales-man	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Ailsbury	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
to	O
Smith-field	O
Mondays	O
and	O
Fridays	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
returned	O
Thousands	O
of	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
such	O
Cattle	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
a	O
bad	O
Accident	O
Thing	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
work	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
Family	O
.	O
Wentland	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
Man	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
and	O
3	O
more	O
Men	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
5	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Parker	O
.	O
They	O
Arrested	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
false	O
Action	O
for	O
30	O
l.	O
to	O
hinder	O
my	O
coming	O
to	O
Prosecute	O
,	O
as	O
this	O
Man	O
knows	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
.	O
After	O
Harvey	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
Sister	O
,	O
el	O
Eaton	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Arabella	B-pers
Gwyn	I-pers
,	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Arrested	O
in	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
There	O
stands	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
Arrested	O
him	O
.	O
Harvey	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
the	O
Money	O
at	O
the	O
Barley-Mow	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
Tub-woman	O
for	O
stealing	O
it	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Paydon	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wentland	I-pers
was	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Black-Lion	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
,	O
from	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
St.	O
Patrick	O
's	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
away	O
Salt-Fish	O
and	O
Potatoes	O
to	O
my	O
Customers	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Scoyles	I-pers
.	O
We	O
were	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Ann	B-pers
Wentland	I-pers
there	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
be	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Four	O
.	O
Wentland	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Harvey	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Miles	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Coach-man	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
betwixt	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Barley-Mow	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Burkitt	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Unicorn	O
Brew-House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
a	O
Pail	O
of	O
Beer	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
that	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
he	O
crossed	O
the	O
Way	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Barley-Mow	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Red	O
Lion-Street	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
over	O
Night	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
came	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stockwell	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
17th	O
,	O
or	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
which	O
(	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
)	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
last	O
Night	O
of	O
fifty	O
Pounds	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
some	O
House	O
near	O
Red-Lion-Street	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nevill	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
On	O
St.	O
Patrick	O
's	O
Day	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
at	O
Harvey	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
broke	O
her	O
Windows	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Gifford	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
advised	O
them	O
to	O
agree	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
Friends	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
from	O
thence	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Company	O
till	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Harvey	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Wentland	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
8.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Fosset	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Block-Tin	O
Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tay	I-pers
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Tay	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday-Night	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Grace-Church-Street	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
away	O
about	O
2	O
on	O
Sunday-Morning	O
.	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Corbet-Court	B-place
,	O
where	O
my	O
Master	O
lives	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
all	O
a-Bed	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
going	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
for't	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Fob	O
.	O
I	O
resisted	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Buckle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shoe	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
swear	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
that	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Pocket	O
?	O
Tay	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
Matthias	B-pers
Gainsboroug	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Corbet-Court	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Servant	O
having	O
work	O
'd	O
hard	O
on	O
Easter-Eve	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
but	O
staying	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
I	O
shut	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
giving	O
some	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
ragged	O
Dress	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
who	O
knew	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Brocas	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Servant	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Corbet-Court	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
9.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wentland	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Winkland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Saxon	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
July	O
23	O
.	O
John	O
Saxon	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Leaden-Hall-street	B-place
,	O
just	O
by	O
Creed-Church	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
steps	O
up	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
whips	O
her	O
Arms	O
round	O
me	O
;	O
My	O
Dear	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
wo	O
n't	O
you	O
be	O
loving	O
and	O
kind	O
?	O
Ye	O
Bitch	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
mistaken	O
in	O
your	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
'm	O
not	O
for	O
your	O
Turn	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
hardly	O
spoke	O
,	O
when	O
another	O
Woman	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Hip	O
!	O
when	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
it	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
resist	O
,	O
or	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
knock	O
you	O
down	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
the	O
2d	O
Woman	O
began	O
to	O
rifle	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
2	O
Half-Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
O	O
you	O
wicked	O
Man	O
!	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
swear	O
so	O
falsly	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
above	O
60	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
did	O
an	O
ill	O
Thing	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Saxon	O
.	O
I	O
swear	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Truth	O
:	O
He	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
searching	O
my	O
Pockets	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
lose	O
my	O
Life	O
as	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
little	O
Light	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
Watch	O
!	O
Watch	O
!	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Women	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Watch	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
about	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Waterside	O
:	O
He	O
presently	O
took	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
among	O
the	O
Ships	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
lost	O
Sight	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Compter-Gate	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
But	O
some	O
how	O
or	O
other	O
he	O
found	O
Means	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
whether	O
by	O
precuring	O
common	O
Bail	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
what	O
other	O
Means	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
But	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
where	O
his	O
Lodging	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
overtook	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Leadenball-street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
now	O
to	O
go	O
upon	O
your	O
Defence	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
Opportunity	O
for	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
you	O
have	O
given	O
their	O
Evidence	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
Questions	O
to	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
now	O
propose	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Pray	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
?	O
Saxon	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
you	O
threatned	O
to	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
Resistance	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
wicked	O
forsworn	O
Wretch	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
60	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Beadle	O
.	O
A	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
2	O
Men	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
some	O
Assistance	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
they	O
had	O
heard	O
was	O
some	O
where	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
2	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
Saxon	O
swears	O
this	O
against	O
me	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
myself	O
before	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
a	O
Word	O
clandestinely	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
wretched	O
to	O
swear	O
my	O
Life	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
Lucre	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Door	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
transported	O
my	O
Wife	O
for	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
bang	O
me	O
;	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
rap	O
[	O
swear	O
]	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Bechive	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	O
.	O
Mills	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
found	O
what	O
we	O
came	O
about	O
,	O
Now	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
God	O
send	O
that	O
neither	O
you	O
nor	O
your	O
Families	O
may	O
ever	O
prosper	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
O	O
you	O
vile	O
Rogue	O
!	O
Sixty	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
!	O
Robert	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
that	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
placed	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
Door	O
to	O
secure	O
[	O
prevent	O
]	O
his	O
Retreat	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
Now	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
transported	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
come	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
Life	O
too	O
;	O
for	O
my	O
Life	O
lies	O
in	O
your	O
Hands	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
O	O
you	O
vile	O
Rogue	O
!	O
O	O
good	O
God	O
!	O
above	O
Sixty	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
!	O
the	O
Lord	O
forgive	O
you	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
all	O
for	O
the	O
Reward	O
and	O
Lucre	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
whole	O
Truth	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
saved	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
Leadenball	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Watchman	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
Cold	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
coughing	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
towards	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
knew	O
my	O
Cough	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
my	O
Husband	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
this	O
Man	O
charges	O
me	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
2	O
Half-Guineas	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sees	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
catches	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
charge	O
you	O
too	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
we	O
all	O
were	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Constable	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
other	O
Woman	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
says	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
this	O
Man	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
?	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
nothing	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
go	O
about	O
their	O
Business	O
.	O
With	O
all	O
my	O
Heart	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
were	O
discharged	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
met	O
me	O
afterwards	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
Board	O
an	O
India-man	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
,	O
who	O
sent	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
saved	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
lewd	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
six	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
me	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sixty	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
and	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
Man	O
will	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
committed	O
the	O
least	O
Crime	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
dye	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
committed	O
any	O
Crime	O
,	O
may	O
I	O
never	O
be	O
received	O
into	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Heaven	O
.	O
As	O
God	O
is	O
my	O
Saviour	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
innocent	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
might	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Fright	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
Lordship	O
wo	O
n't	O
let	O
me	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
old	O
Age	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
my	O
Relations	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Siney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
30	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
hard	O
on	O
the	O
Thames	O
in	O
heaving	O
Coals	O
and	O
Balla	O
st	O
,	O
till	O
within	O
these	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
no	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ay	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
works	O
hard	O
a-Days	O
is	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
robbing	O
a-Nights	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
more	O
need	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
Rest	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Southernwood	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
16	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
fellow	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
then	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pardoe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
25	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
Work	O
hard	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
excused	O
from	O
saying	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
10.	O
James	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Razors	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
by	O
whom	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
Midnight	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
'em	O
these	O
2	O
Razors	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
2	O
Razors	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
2	O
Razors	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
11	O
,	O
12.	O
James	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	O
Perry	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Suit	O
,	O
Value	O
35	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckskin	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
6	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Favin	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	O
Perry	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
Edward	O
Favin	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
About	O
9	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
for	O
some	O
Tools	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
my	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
talking	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Gate	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
fast	O
within	O
side	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
back	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
the	O
Rogues	O
from	O
one	O
Place	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Grass-Farm-Wood	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Upon	O
Phillips	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckskin	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Wig	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Favin	I-pers
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Hurst	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
that	O
were	O
mine	O
.	O
Phillips	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
Edward	O
Favin	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
Daniel	O
Perry	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
staid	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Doors	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Key	O
at	O
his	O
Daughter	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
.	O
About	O
9	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
middle	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Window-Frame	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Lock	O
of	O
my	O
Chest	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
for	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Miles	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
Grass-Farm-Wood	O
,	O
with	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
say	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Favin	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Hurst	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
let	O
in	O
Phillips	O
.	O
Barnard	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Phillips	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
shoot	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
came	O
any	O
farther	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
still	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
fir	O
'd	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Groin	O
(	O
with	O
small	O
Shot	O
)	O
8	O
of	O
the	O
Shot	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
beat	O
me	O
and	O
bruis	O
'd	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
under	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
's	O
Hands	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
not	O
yet	O
quite	O
recovered	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
dy	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
after	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
.	O
13.	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
80	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14	O
,	O
15	O
,	O
16.	O
Ann	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
April	O
1st	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
17	O
,	O
18.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bugbear	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Arres	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stanmore	B-place
Magna	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cogdell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Feb.	O
23d	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Evidence	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
19.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
female	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Office	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
suffocated	O
,	O
March	O
11	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Morning	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
complain	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Twitching	O
in	O
her	O
Stomach	O
with	O
the	O
Cholick	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
afterwards	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Gilman	O
,	O
my	O
Landlady	O
(	O
for	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
Old-street-Square	O
)	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
directly	O
down-stairs	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
5	O
Minutes	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
seeing	O
some	O
Disorder	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
That	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
the	O
Vault	O
something	O
had	O
forc	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
for	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
half	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
her	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Leg	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
Leg	O
;	O
for	O
in	O
the	O
Surprize	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
hardly	O
knew	O
what	O
was	O
what	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Midwife	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
dangerous	O
Way	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
cut	O
off	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
bad	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
Time	O
to	O
undress	O
her	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
this	O
Disaster	O
happen	O
'd	O
?	O
She	O
could	O
hardly	O
speak	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
As	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
saved	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Notice	O
of	O
my	O
Labour	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
the	O
Cholick	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
sat	O
there	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
oe	O
Pain	O
;	O
a	O
forcing	O
Pain	O
that	O
brought	O
down	O
the	O
Child	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
Disorder	O
and	O
Surprize	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stir	O
my	O
self	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
have	O
saved	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
usual	O
for	O
Women	O
to	O
have	O
such	O
hasty	O
Labours	O
?	O
Midwife	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
not	O
common	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Instances	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
under	O
my	O
Care	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
?	O
Midwife	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whose	O
Child	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
examined	O
her	O
?	O
Midwife	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
after	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
swooning	O
away	O
and	O
dying	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
speak	O
before	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
likely	O
the	O
Child	O
should	O
come	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
?	O
Midwife	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
up	O
and	O
wash	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Marks	O
or	O
Bruises	O
?	O
Midwife	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
clear	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
full	O
grown	O
?	O
Midwife	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dikes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Midwife	O
when	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
we	O
wash	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Tub	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
provided	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
one	O
Shirt	O
in	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
Pain	O
like	O
the	O
Cholick	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Necessary-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
Pain	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
Child	O
into	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
stir	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Help	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Vault	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Place	O
no	O
Body	O
heard	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
lawfully	O
marry	O
'd	O
14	O
Years	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
often	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
several	O
Times	O
within	O
this	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rimons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
married	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
several	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
Child	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Child-bed	O
Linen	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
her	O
Name	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
driven	O
to	O
great	O
Necessities	O
by	O
a	O
wicked	O
base	O
Rogue	O
of	O
a	O
Husband	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Eastman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
this	O
other	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Child-bed	O
Linen	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
by	O
her	O
Directions	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
20.	O
Richard	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bodicoat	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
,	O
each	O
for	O
25	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
Susanna	B-pers
Calfe	I-pers
or	O
Bearer	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Bank	O
Note	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Waldo	I-pers
,	O
or	O
Bearer	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Susanna	O
Calfe	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
16	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Reading-glass	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Spanish	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
Value	O
36	O
s.	O
half	O
a	O
Broad-piece	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
16	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Calfe	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
16.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Calfe	I-pers
.	O
In	O
February	O
last	O
I	O
took	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Collier	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Chappel-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Collier	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
and	O
boarded	O
there	O
for	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
paid	O
her	O
but	O
for	O
6	O
Weeks	O
;	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
poor	O
,	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
honest	O
.	O
Sometime	O
after	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Collier	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
her	O
my	O
Judgment	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Collier	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
spare	O
Money	O
enough	O
to	O
buy	O
so	O
much	O
Tea	O
as	O
she	O
spoke	O
of	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
6l	O
.	O
of	O
my	O
Dividend	O
.	O
You	O
sha	O
n't	O
want	O
Money	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
lend	O
you	O
5	O
l.	O
You	O
lend	O
me	O
5	O
l.	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
You	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
pretend	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
50	O
l.	O
By	O
God	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
damn	O
'd	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
.	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
was	O
the	O
Day	O
agreed	O
on	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Tea	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
in	O
Order	O
;	O
my	O
Desk	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
sore	O
Room	O
on	O
the	O
Ground-floor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
Box	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
weigh	O
'd	O
about	O
80lb	O
.	O
in	O
my	O
Bed-Chamber	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
Desk	O
I	O
had	O
16	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Spanish	O
Piece	O
of	O
36s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Broad-piece	O
of	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Pocket-Book	O
that	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Huxley	O
's	O
Mortgage	O
,	O
a	O
Reading-glass	O
,	O
2	O
Wills	O
of	O
mine	O
(	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
Duplicate	O
)	O
and	O
a	O
Paper	O
on	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Memorandum	O
of	O
the	O
Numbers	O
and	O
Value	O
of	O
3	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Box	O
were	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Huxley	O
's	O
Mortgage	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Writings	O
of	O
my	O
Family	O
and	O
Hereditary	O
Estate	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
3	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
.	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
my	O
Desk	O
and	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Keys	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Collier	O
about	O
Noon	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
my	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
infirm	O
Gentlewoman	O
were	O
left	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Child	O
look	O
very	O
much	O
disorder	O
'd	O
and	O
frighted	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
my	O
Box	O
of	O
Writings	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
'Scrutore	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
this	O
be	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
may	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
to	O
look	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
impossible	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
any	O
Body	O
could	O
get	O
over	O
these	O
Palisades	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cross	O
this	O
wide	O
Airey	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
.	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
spend	O
your	O
Time	O
in	O
considering	O
which	O
Way	O
your	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
you	O
may	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
in	O
your	O
Box	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
Three	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
lose	O
no	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
let	O
's	O
go	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
and	O
give	O
Notice	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
'Scrutore	O
for	O
the	O
Memorandum	O
of	O
those	O
Bills	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Paper	O
was	O
gone	O
too	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crouch	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Numbers	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
Notes	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
Name	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
remember	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
payable	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Walde	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
forgot	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
Bond	O
for	O
the	O
former	O
2	O
Notes	O
.	O
In	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
Son	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
wait	O
for	O
me	O
without	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
should	O
stay	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
in	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
to	O
desire	O
my	O
Son	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
without	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
tell	O
my	O
Son	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
returned	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
my	O
Business	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Son	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
disordered	O
to	O
sleep	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
officions	O
in	O
offering	O
his	O
Service	O
to	O
set	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
doubt	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
hear	O
of	O
my	O
Writings	O
again	O
.	O
And	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
my	O
Friend	O
Mr.	O
Ashton	O
,	O
an	O
Attorney	O
in	O
Surry	O
street	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
his	O
Advice	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
(	O
't	O
was	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
)	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
forbear	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
Palisades	O
.	O
Lord	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
an	O
easy	O
Matter	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
here	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Hands	O
upon	O
the	O
Rails	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
Offer	O
to	O
jump	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
away	O
without	O
getting	O
over	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Never	O
fear	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
for	O
by	O
God	O
I	O
'll	O
help	O
you	O
to	O
your	O
Writings	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
restain	O
from	O
Tears	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
why	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
left	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
be	O
so	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
receive	O
some	O
Money	O
next	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
lend	O
you	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
l.	O
if	O
you	O
want	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
poor	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
consulted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Ashton	O
,	O
my	O
Suspicion	O
encreas	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
must	O
play	O
cunning	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Box	O
of	O
Writings	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
of	O
far	O
more	O
Value	O
to	O
me	O
than	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Notes	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
draw	O
up	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
for	O
the	O
News-Papers	O
:	O
He	O
wrote	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
it	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
because	O
Mrs.	O
Collier	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
proper	O
to	O
mention	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
drew	O
up	O
another	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
need	O
of	O
advertising	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
for	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
will	O
but	O
follow	O
Discipline	O
(	O
those	O
were	O
his	O
Words	O
)	O
I	O
'll	O
find	O
your	O
Box	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
Son	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
looking	O
after	O
the	O
Writings	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
upon	O
the	O
hunt	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
talk	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
very	O
high	O
Terms	O
,	O
they	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
200l	O
.	O
You	O
talk	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
!	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
who	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
Nay	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
no	O
naming	O
of	O
Names	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
would	O
get	O
your	O
Box	O
again	O
you	O
must	O
follow	O
Discipline	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
provok	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
of	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
Warrant	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
this	O
Letter	O
by	O
the	O
Petty-Post	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
by	O
comparing	O
the	O
Hand	O
with	O
these	O
Advertisements	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
)	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
written	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Letter	O
may	O
be	O
read	O
.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
,	O
reads	O
.	O
For	O
Md	O
Calfe	O
at	O
Ms	O
Collars	O
in	O
Chappel	O
street	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Chappel	O
.	O
Mad	O
WEE	O
are	O
a	O
sett	O
of	O
young	O
gentelmen	O
who	O
are	O
oblidged	O
to	O
live	O
by	O
our	O
wits	O
into	O
whose	O
bads	O
[	O
hands	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
]	O
yor	O
papers	O
are	O
fallen	O
and	O
as	O
our	O
dependans	O
is	O
on	O
fortune	O
tacke	O
especall	O
care	O
not	O
to	O
slighther	O
favors	O
least	O
she	O
resent	O
it	O
therefore	O
Madm	O
hope	O
youl	O
excuese	O
our	O
not	O
coming	O
into	O
yours	O
and	O
yor	O
frind	O
barves	O
way	O
of	O
thnking	O
[	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
Word	O
or	O
two	O
not	O
legible	O
]	O
yt	O
70	O
poundsworth	O
of	O
yor	O
Bank	O
noats	O
are	O
of	O
no	O
signification	O
to	O
any	O
person	O
who	O
hati	O
the	O
charge	O
thereof	O
except	O
yor	O
self	O
no	O
Madm	O
plesase	O
to	O
know	O
we	O
are	O
merchantilin	O
men	O
and	O
know	O
theare	O
worth	O
so	O
well	O
yt	O
should	O
be	O
loath	O
to	O
give	O
[	O
here	O
are	O
two	O
other	O
Words	O
not	O
legible	O
]	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
1000	O
worth	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
morgages	O
settelements	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
petty	O
things	O
not	O
worth	O
mentioning	O
we	O
bily	O
esteme	O
now	O
Mad	O
as	O
you	O
know	O
on	O
what	O
prisipeice	O
we	O
stand	O
hope	O
youl	O
not	O
think	O
our	O
demands	O
exorbitant	O
which	O
are	O
as	O
follows	O
viz	O
.	O
to	O
maeke	O
that	O
70	O
pounds	O
200	O
gineys	O
one	O
which	O
condition	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
restorde	O
every	O
paper	O
and	O
parchment	O
without	O
exposition	O
or	O
deminition	O
nithar	O
is	O
it	O
fit	O
yt	O
all	O
ye	O
world	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
perusall	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
so	O
the	O
Calfe	O
Likwise	O
and	O
other	O
utensils	O
shall	O
be	O
restoared	O
which	O
if	O
not	O
prevented	O
soon	O
will	O
be	O
metamorphosed	O
for	O
pleas	O
to	O
know	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
Idolatars	O
If	O
this	O
proposal	O
be	O
not	O
with	O
dont	O
send	O
yr	O
frind	O
harve	O
to	O
seek	O
our	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
comes	O
on	O
any	O
othar	O
condition	O
or	O
pre-whatsoever	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
hazared	O
of	O
his	O
one	O
from	O
yor	O
humbel	O
sarvantes	O
the	O
sones	O
of	O
fortune	O
.	O
from	O
our	O
office	O
in	O
taserd-mallan	O
street	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Calfe	I-pers
.	O
On	O
receiving	O
this	O
Letter	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
stop	O
to	O
the	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Box	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
promis	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
I	O
sent	O
so	O
Mrs.	O
Collier	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
.	O
She	O
appear	O
'd	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
uneasy	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Letter	O
here	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
sent	O
me	O
Yesterday	O
;	O
pray	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
read	O
two	O
Words	O
wrong	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
Merchantilin	O
,	O
I	O
read	O
Merchandizing	O
,	O
and	O
Principle	O
for	O
Precipice	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
no	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
second	O
was	O
wrong	O
,	O
the	O
Word	O
should	O
be	O
Precipice	O
;	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
they	O
stood	O
in	O
great	O
Danger	O
,	O
for	O
its	O
a	O
dangerous	O
thing	O
to	O
help	O
People	O
to	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
that	O
deal	O
that	O
way	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
cautious	O
in	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
was	O
hang	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
you	O
would	O
do	O
them	O
any	O
hurt	O
:	O
No	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
why	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
to	O
satisfy	O
them	O
that	O
they	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
advise	O
you	O
to	O
withdraw	O
your	O
Bond	O
in	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
searching	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
we	O
begun	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
every	O
Place	O
upwards	O
till	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
look	O
up	O
and	O
see	O
a	O
Trap-door	O
to	O
the	O
Cock-lost	O
(	O
the	O
Space	O
between	O
the	O
Garret	B-pers
Cieling	I-pers
and	O
the	O
Roof	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
braveBox	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
my	O
Heart	O
leap	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Word	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
glad	O
I	O
was	O
that	O
nothing	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
ammer	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
w	O
hich	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
using	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Pattison	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Shavings	O
he	O
found	O
my	O
Will	O
with	O
the	O
Codicil	O
,	O
this	O
Reading	O
Glass	O
,	O
my	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
the	O
Memorandum	O
of	O
my	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Papers	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
'Sciutore	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Silver	O
Coffee-pot	O
that	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Calf	O
engraven	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
the	O
Calf	O
they	O
mean	O
in	O
the	O
Letter	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
say	O
.	O
It	O
would	O
soon	O
be	O
metamorphos	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
no	O
Idolaters	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
gone	O
and	O
left	O
your	O
Bureau	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
home	O
very	O
airy	O
at	O
12	O
or	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
not	O
thank	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
locking	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
your	O
Absence	O
?	O
S.	O
Calf	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
one	O
Night	O
about	O
10	O
from	O
Dr.	O
Harris	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
frighted	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Wits	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
leave	O
your	O
Bureau	O
unlock	O
'd	O
?	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
unlok	O
'd	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
your	O
Room	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
think	O
what	O
Business	O
I	O
had	O
there	O
;	O
nor	O
I	O
neither	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
except	O
you	O
went	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
two	O
Weeks	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
lock	O
the	O
Coffee-Pot	O
in	O
that	O
Box	O
?	O
S.	O
Calfe	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
always	O
put	O
there	O
when	O
not	O
in	O
use	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
charged	O
your	O
Sons	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
particular	O
your	O
younger	O
Son	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
this	O
Villain	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
he	O
that	O
has	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
?	O
S.	O
Calfe	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
bid	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
you	O
never	O
charged	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
this	O
Fact	O
?	O
And	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
could	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
Writings	O
?	O
S.	O
Calfe	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
did	O
say	O
so	O
of	O
my	O
Sons	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
to	O
amuse	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
recover	O
my	O
Writings	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
suspect	O
(	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
)	O
that	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
say	O
that	O
your	O
Son	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
of	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Money	O
?	O
S.	O
Calf	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
too	O
saucy	O
and	O
refractory	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
only	O
said	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
strange	O
how	O
the	O
Ring	O
should	O
be	O
gone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
told	O
me	O
you	O
was	O
afraid	O
your	O
Son	O
would	O
rob	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
your	O
Throat	O
?	O
And	O
have	O
you	O
not	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
?	O
S.	O
Calfe	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
is	O
but	O
a	O
Boy	O
of	O
19	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
indeed	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
apt	O
to	O
be	O
pretty	O
saucy	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
behaved	O
himself	O
one	O
Night	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
become	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
bear	O
his	O
Insolence	O
no	O
longer	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
turn	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
again	O
,	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
open	O
since	O
you	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
you	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
your	O
self	O
?	O
S.	O
Calfe	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Calfe	I-pers
.	O
About	O
Noon	O
my	O
Mamma	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Collier	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Collier	O
had	O
Orders	O
for	O
her	O
Maid	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
Two	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Maid	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Mamma	O
was	O
Sick	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
immediately	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
best	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
go	O
by	O
all	O
means	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
my	O
Mamma	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
but	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
Two	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Gentlewoman	O
at	O
Home	O
.	O
My	O
Mamma	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
Home	O
at	O
Hour	O
past	O
Three	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Collier	O
's	O
Maid	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
(	O
she	O
came	O
Home	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Mamma	O
's	O
Apartment	O
in	O
a	O
dismal	O
Condition	O
,	O
the	O
Windows	O
were	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Curtains	O
drawn	O
;	O
the	O
Desk	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Chips	O
of	O
it	O
lay	O
about	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
below	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
imagine	O
how	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
Room	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
Thieves	O
were	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
We	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
every	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
see	O
no	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
pray	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
me	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
still	O
afraid	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
alone	O
)	O
till	O
my	O
Mamma	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
like	O
Sailors	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
my	O
Mamma	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
my	O
Mamma	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
before	O
my	O
Mamma	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
using	O
a	O
Hammer	O
to	O
knock	O
up	O
a	O
Brass	O
Nail	O
to	O
hang	O
the	O
Brush	O
on	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Hammer	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
my	O
Mamma	O
's	O
Box	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Cock-lost	O
,	O
that	O
Hammer	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Mamma	O
came	O
Home	O
between	O
Four	O
and	O
Five	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
Mrs.	O
Collier	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Cock-lost	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Box	O
that	O
weighed	O
I	O
believe	O
near	O
a	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Hammer	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Calfe	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Silver	O
Coffee	O
Pot	O
,	O
three	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Writings	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
looking	O
among	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Shavings	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
reading	O
Glass	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Writings	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
,	O
Feb.	O
17.	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
about	O
the	O
Writings	O
?	O
And	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
they	O
talk	O
high	O
,	O
they	O
demand	O
100	O
or	O
200	O
Pounds	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
who	O
demanded	O
.	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Calfe	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
Four	O
and	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Grocer's-Alley	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Jewry	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
Mother	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
Son	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
pray	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
till	O
I	O
come	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
waited	O
an	O
Hour	O
in	O
the	O
Bank-Yard	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
my	O
Mother	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
me	O
go	O
without	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
Writings	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Mortgage-Deed	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Huxley	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Bank	O
Notes	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
Account	O
my	O
Mother	O
was	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Would	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
Notes	O
have	O
gone	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
order	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stopp	O
'd	O
?	O
J.	O
Calfe	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
my	O
Mother	O
had	O
a	O
Mortgage-Deed	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Huxley	O
's	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
imagine	O
how	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
among	O
the	O
other	O
Writings	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
my	O
Mother	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
how	O
the	O
Scrutore	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
too	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Rag-Fair	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
Writings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
getting	O
the	O
Writings	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
advertis	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
People	O
said	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Advertisement	O
put	O
out	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Owner	O
would	O
hardly	O
ever	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
because	O
People	O
had	O
been	O
stopp	O
'd	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
brought	O
home	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
22.	O
John	B-pers
Clew	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Laurence	I-place
King	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Aldermanbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wallnut-tree	O
Canister-Box	O
,	O
with	O
3	O
Canisters	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hesketh	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
Richard	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Billinsgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sheldrick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Bermudas	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Box-Iron	O
and	O
3	O
Heaters	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Morden	I-pers
,	O
December	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26	O
,	O
27.	O
Henry	B-pers
Whitesides	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Foster-Lane	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hatband	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
Paul	B-pers
Fellows	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Bryant	B-pers
Ambler	I-pers
,	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Bryan	O
Ambler	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
behind	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
forward	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Boy	O
struggling	O
with	O
Scott	O
(	O
the	O
least	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Scott	O
had	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
while	O
another	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Hat	O
.	O
Maurice	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
Scott	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
?	O
and	O
Whitesides	O
was	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
Scott	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
the	O
Flap	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
lift	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
Whitesides	O
snatch	O
'd	O
a	O
Hat	O
off	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Scott	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
stopt	O
Scott	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
Whitesides	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
a	O
Shop	O
where	O
Whitesides	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Hatband	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
Band	O
for	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
tell	O
his	O
Companions	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Haberdasher	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
notice	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
next	O
Day	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Shop	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
Hat	O
of	O
Harry	B-pers
Whitesides	I-pers
o	O
'	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
.	O
Scott	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
ask	O
what	O
was	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Whitesides	O
.	O
Whitesides	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
run	O
along	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
away	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
as	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
David	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bloomsbury	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Philip	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
a	O
Cullinder	O
,	O
a	O
Bason	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30	O
,	O
31.	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Washing	O
Tubs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hitchins	I-pers
,	O
March	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32	O
,	O
33.	O
John	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Martin	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
500	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waxham	I-pers
,	O
being	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Freehold	O
,	O
March	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
Showland	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
with	O
Elliot	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Ford	I-pers
)	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
Theo	O
.	O
Eades	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
beat	O
and	O
bruis	O
'd	O
all	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
by	O
3	O
Persons	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
)	O
who	O
met	O
me	O
near	O
the	O
Brewhouse	O
on	O
Saffron-Hill	B-place
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
They	O
abused	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Rustical	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Saffron-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
there	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
2	O
Hours	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
Robbery	O
in	O
committing	O
?	O
Eades	O
.	O
Five	O
or	O
Six	O
Minutes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
no	O
Body	O
come	O
by	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Eades	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Keen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
383	O
.	O
The	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
was	O
within	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
Coach	O
that	O
Morning	O
about	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
with	O
it	O
till	O
after	O
a	O
11	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
sober	O
Lad	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
swear	O
an	O
Oath	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Hodge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
About	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
Coach	O
in	O
Basingball-Street	O
,	O
the	O
Number	O
was	O
383	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
driven	O
to	O
Ratcliff-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
9	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
set	O
down	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Boy	O
that	O
drove	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
Night	O
and	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
Ratcliff-Cross	O
from	O
Saffron-Hill	O
?	O
K.	O
Hodge	O
.	O
About	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Miles	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Birkham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Coach	O
for	O
these	O
2	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
drove	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Courtman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
on	O
Saffron-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
fighting	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
maul	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
last	O
Night	O
at	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
;	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
by	O
whom	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Harry	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Warrant	O
out	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
That	O
Lad	O
was	O
formerly	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Harry	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	O
d	O
'ye	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
nor	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
neither	O
;	O
yet	O
afterwards	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
Brooks	O
,	O
and	O
Brooks	O
shewing	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
thought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Lad	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chevers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
'T	O
is	O
hard	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
this	O
Boy	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
know	O
3	O
Persons	O
at	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
help	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
give	O
me	O
6	O
Guineas	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
clear	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Here	O
,	O
Eades	O
,	O
what	O
light	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
?	O
Eades	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Moon-light	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
cloudy	O
?	O
E.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Keen	I-pers
.	O
It	O
had	O
rain	O
'd	O
all	O
Day	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
rain	O
at	O
Night	O
?	O
Keen	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
It	O
rain	O
'd	O
all	O
Day	O
as	O
if	O
Heaven	O
and	O
Earth	O
had	O
come	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Night	O
was	O
cloudy	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Moon	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
serv	O
'd	O
the	O
Warrant	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
parted	O
with	O
Dodd	O
at	O
10	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Eades	O
.	O
Keen	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
the	O
time	O
before	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
;	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
6	O
Guineas	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
35.	O
Henry	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White-Chappel	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
Iron	O
Chains	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Calcot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Stable	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37.	O
George	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
,	O
3	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Caps	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Rose	B-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
at	I-place
Hoxton	I-place
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
(	O
my	O
Mistress	O
)	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
my	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
her	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Ladle	O
,	O
and	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Brandy	O
Bottle	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
rest	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Gown	O
and	O
my	O
Stays	O
in	O
the	O
Bundle	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
If	O
ye	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Things	O
,	O
pray	O
leave	O
mine	O
;	O
consider	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lame	O
Cripple	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
all	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
keeps	O
a	O
common	O
Baudy-House	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Creature	O
is	O
one	O
that	O
plies	O
there	O
;	O
pray	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
ask	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
common	O
Whore	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Wife	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
own	O
Game	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
'd	O
be	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
next	O
Morning	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
Contrivance	O
of	O
hers	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
so	O
she	O
may	O
drive	O
on	O
her	O
old	O
Trade	O
quietly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
38.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Prudence	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sweetapple	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
28	O
.	O
acquitted	O
.	O
39.	O
James	B-pers
Ireman	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bennet	I-pers
of	O
Hanwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
32	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Burgess	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
old	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
March	O
23	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
41.	O
Allen	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
Lombard-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Gallon-pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
42.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Rankey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Duke's-Place	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Damask	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
