TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Friday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
1733	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARBER	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1733	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILFORD	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Chapter-House	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXIII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARBER	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probyn	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goodyear	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Binks	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hamerton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pond	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tatland	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Power	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Fairchild	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pennock	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Mary	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Tea-pot	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
December	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
James	B-pers
Danselow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
riding	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Stables	O
,	O
December	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
3s	O
.	O
4d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hammersmith	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Main	I-pers
,	O
on	B-place
the	I-place
High-Seas	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Sheerness	I-place
,	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
by	O
beating	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Tiller	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Back	O
,	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
him	O
several	O
Mortal	O
Wounds	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wounds	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Hamlet	O
of	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
G.	O
Sugg	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
Fishermen	O
,	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
(	O
a	O
Boy	O
about	O
11	O
Years	O
old	O
)	O
was	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
.	O
On	O
(	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
October	O
)	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor's-Day	O
,	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
Fishing	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Groat	O
in	O
the	O
Shilling	O
of	O
what	O
we	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
large	O
Fish	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
the	O
small	O
Fish	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
from	O
Hammersmith	O
to	O
Fulham	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
3	O
Days	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
Money	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Sheerness	O
;	O
but	O
getting	O
no	O
Fish	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Feversham	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Woolstaple-Bay	O
,	O
where	O
having	O
caught	O
some	O
Fish	O
,	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Feversham	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
set	O
the	O
Boy	O
on	O
Shore	O
with	O
the	O
Fish	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
off	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Shore	O
being	O
very	O
slippery	O
the	O
Boy	O
let	O
the	O
Fish	O
fall	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
too	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Rope	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
when	O
presently	O
the	O
Boy	O
fell	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
went	O
a-shore	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
return	O
'd	O
a	O
second	O
time-to	O
the	O
Boat	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
fall	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
a-shore	O
once	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
came	O
on	O
Board	O
again	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
till	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
beat	O
the	O
Boy	O
for	O
asking	O
some	O
Body	O
at	O
Feversham	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Bread	O
.	O
Says	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
harm	O
in	O
asking	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
Bread	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
hungry	O
?	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
beat	O
you	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
when	O
we	O
come	O
into	O
Queenborough-Grounds	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
row	O
'd	O
through	O
Queenborough-Grounds	O
by	O
Milton-Creek	O
's	O
Mouth	O
towards	O
Sheerness	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
2	O
Inch	O
Rope	O
,	O
and	O
splitting	O
it	O
into	O
7	O
Strands	O
,	O
he	O
ty	O
'd	O
3	O
Knees	O
in	O
each	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
stripping	O
the	O
Boy	O
stark	O
naked	O
(	O
except	O
only	O
his	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Stockings	O
)	O
he	O
whipt	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
Cat	O
of	O
nine	O
Tails	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
full	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
by	O
the	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
2	O
Fishermen	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
kill	O
the	O
Boy	O
out-right	O
?	O
You	O
had	O
better	O
hurl	O
him	O
over-board	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Misery	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
off	O
beating	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
again	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
Marks	O
on	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Back	O
?	O
Sugg	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
black	O
and	O
blue	O
,	O
and	O
wheal	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Eye	O
was	O
cut	O
some	O
how	O
in	O
whipping	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saw	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Cat-o'-nine-Tails	O
over-board	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
I	O
have	O
beat	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
never	O
beat	O
you	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Sheerness	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
staid	O
2	O
Days	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
were	O
good	O
Friends	O
.	O
But	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
beat	O
the	O
Boy	O
again	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
eat	O
more	O
Victuals	O
than	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
.	O
Sirrah	O
!	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
eat	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Bread	O
without	O
asking	O
my	O
leave	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
strip	O
your	O
Skin	O
over	O
your	O
Shoulders	O
.	O
Two	O
Days	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
he	O
beat	O
the	O
Boy	O
with	O
a	O
Helm-stick	O
(	O
the	O
Titler	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
steer	O
the	O
Boat	O
with	O
)	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
eat	O
some	O
Victuals	O
without	O
asking	O
leave	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
beating	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
stript	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
black	O
and	O
blue	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Blood	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
start	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Skin	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Sheerness	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
all	O
good	O
Friends	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
beat	O
the	O
Boy	O
again	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
lousy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Lice	O
,	O
and	O
thrust	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
damn	O
his	O
Soul	O
he	O
'd	O
make	O
him	O
eat	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
himself	O
clean	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
3	O
Months	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
but	O
1	O
Shirt	O
to	O
his	O
Back	O
in	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
and	O
fought	O
together	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
quarrel	O
about	O
?	O
Sugg	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
work	O
any	O
more	O
with	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
abused	O
the	O
Boy	O
so	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
no	O
other	O
Motive	O
?	O
Sugg	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
by	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
about	O
the	O
Fish	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
and	O
sold	O
seven	O
hundred	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
share	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
spent	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
except	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
But	O
before	O
this	O
parting	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
a	O
Fisherman	O
's	O
Lave-Net	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Boat	O
;	O
and	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
parting	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
Lave-Net	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Boat	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
the	O
Boy	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
(	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
without	O
leave	O
)	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
see	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
beating	O
him	O
afresh	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
sad	O
condition	O
;	O
his	O
right	O
Eye	O
was	O
cut	O
down	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
left	O
Eye	O
that	O
was	O
cut	O
before	O
)	O
and	O
his	O
Cheek	O
was	O
cut	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
Blood	O
was	O
running	O
fresh	O
from	O
those	O
Wounds	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
run	O
from	O
his	O
Head	O
like	O
a	O
Spout	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Sugg	O
.	O
I	O
forget	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
or	O
two	O
Months	O
ago	O
.	O
And	O
four-Days	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
News	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Boy	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
from	O
the	O
Mast-Head	O
,	O
and	O
killed	O
himself	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
impossible	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Mast	O
is	O
so	O
low	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
may	O
stand	O
upon	O
his	O
Boat	O
's	O
Head	O
and	O
reach	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Finch	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
the	O
Boy	O
barbarously	O
with	O
a	O
Tiller	O
,	O
at	O
Sheerness	O
Dock	O
;	O
George	B-pers
Sugg	I-pers
(	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
)	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Boat	O
;	O
I	O
ridicu	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
so	O
doing	O
;	O
You	O
Villain	O
!	O
You	O
Rascal	O
you	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
your	O
Master	O
never	O
served	O
you	O
so	O
!	O
About	O
a	O
Week	O
or	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
Friday-night	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Boy	O
dead	O
in	O
his	O
Boat	O
to	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
run	O
her	O
a-ground	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Boy	O
in	O
her	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
?	O
Finch	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Boat	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Boat	O
in	O
over	O
Night	O
?	O
Finch	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
his	O
Father	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
crying	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
Matter	O
enough	O
,	O
his	O
Son	O
had	O
brought	O
his	O
Boy	O
home	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
his	O
Father	O
told	O
you	O
is	O
no	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Finch	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
himself	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
Cheer	O
Finch	O
?	O
Pretty	O
Cheer	O
indeed	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
fine	O
piece	O
of	O
Work	O
of	O
it	O
!	O
your	O
Boy	O
is	O
dead	O
it	O
seems	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
's	O
what	O
I	O
expected	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
have	O
beat	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Boy	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
?	O
Finch	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
such	O
as	O
you	O
think	O
might	O
occasion	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Finch	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Judgment	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
Witness	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sold	O
some	O
Fish	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
spent	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
but	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
concern	O
in	O
that	O
Fish	O
?	O
Finch	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
.	O
About	O
two	O
Weeks	O
before	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Death	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Sheerness	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
some	O
Fish	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
I	O
borrowed	O
a	O
Basket	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
(	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Absence	O
)	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
the	O
Boy	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
the	O
Basket	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
is	O
going	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
backwards	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
for	O
lending	O
me	O
the	O
Basket	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
when	O
the	O
Coroner	O
sat	O
,	O
his	O
Body	O
was	O
blackish	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
several	O
Wounds	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
those	O
Wounds	O
be	O
caused	O
by	O
a	O
Fall	O
from	O
the	O
Mast	O
?	O
Webster	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
could	O
never	O
be	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
those	O
Wounds	O
were	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Webster	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
judge	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Waterman	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
called	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
job	O
for	O
me	O
that	O
Tide	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Water-side	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
putting	O
the	O
Fish	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Boat	O
into	O
mine	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
that	O
Fish	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
bring	O
this	O
Fish	O
by	O
Billingsgate	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
want	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
back	O
thither	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
something	O
has	O
happened	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
laid	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
land	O
him	O
at	O
Card	O
Alley	O
(	O
by	O
the	O
Old	O
Swan	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Basket	O
and	O
sorted	O
the	O
Fish	O
,	O
and	O
bade	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
Market-Man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Blackbourn	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
Home	O
to	O
Hammersmith	O
that	O
Night	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
got	O
there	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
and	O
Sister	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Can	O
you	O
make	O
a	O
Coffin	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
brought	O
the	O
Measure	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
it	O
will	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
six	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
the	O
Coffin	O
Home	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Hand	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Body	O
from	O
the	O
Boat	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Justice	O
's	O
Warrant	O
for	O
moving	O
the	O
Body	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
(	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Blue	O
Anchor	O
at	O
the	O
Water-side	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Boat	O
lay	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Shore	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
another	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
Robin	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
push	O
'd	O
us	O
off	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Boat	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
it	O
lay	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
under	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
the	O
naked	O
Body	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
crouded	O
up	O
so	O
close	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
impossible	O
to	O
thrust	O
a	O
dead	O
Body	O
into	O
so	O
little	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
crept	O
in	O
there	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
beat	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
above	O
an	O
Hour	O
in	O
getting	O
the	O
Body	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
Hole	O
14	O
Inches	O
square	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
no	O
Clothes	O
on	O
,	O
only	O
it	O
was	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Red-rug	O
.	O
So	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Where	O
's	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Clothes	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Clothes	O
are	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
fell	O
from	O
the	O
Mast	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
himself	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
a-shore	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Body	O
a-thurt	O
[	O
athwart	O
]	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
's	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
before	O
with	O
the	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
launch	O
the	O
Boat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
follow	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Lane	O
's	O
end	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
us	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
help	O
'd	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Body	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
a-thurt	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Coffin	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Body	O
was	O
made	O
clean	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
on	O
a	O
Table	O
with	O
the	O
Back	O
upwards	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
Marks	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
?	O
Banks	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
red	O
Circle	O
round	O
one	O
Eye	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Witness	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
being	O
severely	O
whipt	O
sometime	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Marks	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
?	O
Banks	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
his	O
Back	O
was	O
clean	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Marks	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
him	O
and	O
helped	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Coffin	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
his	O
Head	O
?	O
Banks	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
those	O
Bruises	O
you	O
saw	O
could	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Banks	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
not	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Banks	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
sucked	O
his	O
Mother	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Character	O
has	O
he	O
?	O
Banks	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dafforn	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
(	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
the	O
Boy	O
died	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
unto	O
Sheerness	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Boy	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
very	O
hard	O
Frost	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
had	O
nothing	O
on	O
but	O
a	O
Serge	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Work	O
all	O
Night	O
and	O
all	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Cold	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
no	O
Victuals	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
wet	O
to	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seeing	O
a	O
dry	O
Jacket	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Sirrah	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
put	O
on	O
that	O
Jacket	O
?	O
I	O
did	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Boy	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Master	O
made	O
me	O
pull	O
it	O
off	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
my	O
Head	O
here	O
about	O
my	O
Temples	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
use	O
the	O
poor	O
Boy	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
ready	O
to	O
perish	O
with	O
Wet	O
and	O
Cold	O
,	O
he	O
'll	O
never	O
live	O
to	O
see	O
London	O
again	O
?	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
a	O
shore	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Gin	O
(	O
whether	O
he	O
intended	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
Boy	O
or	O
not	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
)	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Boy	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Temples	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Flesh	O
was	O
bruised	O
and	O
black	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
afterwards	O
understood	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
above	O
5	O
Hours	O
after	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
those	O
Wounds	O
were	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Dafforn	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
those	O
Wounds	O
and	O
want	O
of	O
looking	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
Hunger	O
and	O
Cold	O
together	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
Hunger	O
and	O
Cold	O
;	O
for	O
we	O
must	O
all	O
dye	O
if	O
we	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
eat	O
or	O
keep	O
us	O
warm	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
cut	O
some	O
Wood	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
his	O
Shirt	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
.	O
Benedict	B-pers
Duddle	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
Pursuant	O
to	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Orders	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
3	O
contus	O
'd	O
Wounds	O
,	O
2	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
very	O
considerable	O
:	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
cross	O
Incision	O
,	O
and	O
raised	O
the	O
temporal	O
Part	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
coagulated	O
Blood	O
in	O
the	O
Interstices	O
of	O
the	O
Fibres	O
of	O
the	O
Muscles	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
'd	O
the	O
Skull	O
round	O
in	O
the	O
ordinary	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
Contusion	O
or	O
Fracture	O
in	O
the	O
Skull	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Could	O
that	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Duddle	O
.	O
The	O
Dura	O
Mater	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Pia	B-pers
Mater	I-pers
much	O
inflamed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Vessels	O
much	O
extended	O
;	O
the	O
Vessels	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
were	O
very	O
turgid	O
;	O
the	O
whole	O
Substance	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
was	O
much	O
swell	O
'd	O
.	O
Now	O
the	O
violent	O
Concussion	O
proceeding	O
from	O
the	O
Blow	O
,	O
might	O
so	O
disturb	O
and	O
affect	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
occasion	O
these	O
Appearances	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
any	O
Instances	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
's	O
Death	O
being	O
caused	O
by	O
such	O
an	O
external	O
Violence	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Fracture	O
in	O
the	O
Skull	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Duddle	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Biggs	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
killed	O
at	O
Kensington	O
Gravel-Pis	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
was	O
a	O
twelve	O
Month	O
,	O
by	O
being	O
pushed	O
against	O
a	O
Cart-wheel	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
single	O
Wound	O
,	O
no	O
Contusion	O
or	O
Fracture	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
between	O
the	O
Pia	B-pers
Mater	I-pers
and	O
Dura	O
Mater	O
we	O
found	O
five	O
Ounces	O
of	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
Transactions	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Academy	O
of	O
Sciences	O
at	O
Paris	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
another	O
Instance	O
of	O
a	O
Criminal	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
broke	O
upon	O
the	O
Wheel	O
,	O
but	O
(	O
his	O
Hands	O
being	O
chained	O
behind	O
him	O
)	O
he	O
run	O
his	O
Head	O
against	O
a	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
immediately	O
:	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
who	O
opened	O
his	O
Head	O
found	O
no	O
Contusion	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
Thorax	O
or	O
Abdomen	O
that	O
could	O
occasion	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
Contusion	O
in	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
raised	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Muscles	O
discoloured	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
that	O
could	O
cause	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
Wound	O
but	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Delauny	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
Body	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Duddle	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Opinion	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
3	O
Contusions	O
between	O
the	O
temporal	O
and	O
coronal	O
Satur	O
.	O
We	O
opened	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
found	O
an	O
Inflammation	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
upper	O
and	O
lower	O
Brain	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
if	O
the	O
Brain	O
was	O
swell	O
'd	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
Marks	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
?	O
Delauny	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
Marks	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
clean	O
and	O
plain	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
served	O
his	O
Time	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
himself	O
well	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
his	O
Temper	O
,	O
was	O
he	O
good	O
natur	O
'd	O
?	O
Porter	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
possible	O
the	O
Boy	O
might	O
be	O
killed	O
if	O
he	O
fell	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
his	O
Mast	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
15	O
foot	O
high	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Here	O
was	O
one	O
Witness	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
reach	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Porter	O
.	O
He	O
tells	O
Lyes	O
then	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
usual	O
for	O
the	O
Boys	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
such	O
Masts	O
?	O
Porter	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
to	O
Reeve	O
the	O
Blocks	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
very	O
common	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
4	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
tempered	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
used	O
his	O
Wife	O
with	O
ill	O
Manners	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Woodmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
hurt	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
good	O
natur	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
general	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Fellows	O
abuse	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
again	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Savery	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Boat	O
by	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
where	O
's	O
your	O
Boy	O
?	O
why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
to	O
a	O
sad	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
Mast	O
at	O
Old-Haven	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
off	O
and	O
killed	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
a-shore	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
People	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
one	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
outwards	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
past	O
and	O
said	O
no	O
more	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
civil	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
only	O
.	O
*	O
4.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Hewsley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold-Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
10l	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
Cornelian	O
Seals	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
Sessions	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Arthur	O
Murphy	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
vide	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
1.	O
p.	O
5	O
.	O
Edward	O
Gouge	O
.	O
I	O
dined	O
in	O
Bloomsbury-Square	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
going	O
home	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
;	O
she	O
challenged	O
me	O
by	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
;	O
this	O
being	O
just	O
by	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
see	O
who	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
o'Clock	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
above	O
three	O
Minutes	O
before	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Linkmen	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Puddington	O
's	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
and	O
attacked	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
out	O
your	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
bid	O
you	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
?	O
Gouge	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
,	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
my	O
Judge	O
;	O
but	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
hardly	O
sensible	O
,	O
you	O
called	O
for	O
6	O
half	O
Pints	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
Puddington	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Gouge	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
I	O
own	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
necessary	O
to	O
ask	O
you	O
to	O
what	O
Degree	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
far	O
sensible	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
now	O
capable	O
of	O
giving	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
did	O
then	O
?	O
Gouge	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
my	O
sitting	O
by	O
Paddington	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
him	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
consider	O
'd	O
what	O
Company	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
felt	O
for	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
it	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Toft	I-pers
,	O
Headborough	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
o	O
'	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
stripp	O
'd	O
naked	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
a	O
Gold-Watch	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
.	O
Puddington	O
being	O
there	O
too	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
hearing	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
presently	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Place	O
he	O
spoke	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
search	O
and	O
welcome	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
I	O
refused	O
,	O
but	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Haselden	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Governor	O
of	O
the	O
Round-house	O
)	O
undertook	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
Examination	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
to	O
preserve	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
my	O
Husband	O
should	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
Puddington	O
a	O
proper	O
Man	O
to	O
trust	O
it	O
with	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Puddington	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
they	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
2	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
she	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
in	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Mercer	O
;	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Governor	O
of	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
whose	O
Son	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
conducted	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
stripp	O
'd	O
herself	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
Clothes	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
gone	O
far	O
,	O
I	O
recollected	O
that	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
stooping	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
poking	O
with	O
her	O
Right-hand	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
thus	O
-	O
and	O
with	O
her	O
Left-hand	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
lower	O
thus	O
-	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Bab	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
certainly	O
got	O
this	O
Watch	O
about	O
you	O
.	O
Where	O
have	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
?	O
Says	O
she	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
in	O
what	O
Place	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
married	O
Man	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
search	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
she	O
parted	O
her	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
remov	O
'd	O
the	O
Covering	O
,	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
Mr.	O
Cross	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
told	O
the	O
Governor	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
found	O
we	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
a	O
Resolution	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
some	O
Resistance	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cross	O
kept	O
her	O
Feet	O
in	O
a	O
proper	O
Situation	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Governor	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Premises	O
;	O
after	O
some	O
search	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Chain	O
at	O
last	O
;	O
but	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
much	O
ado	O
to	O
reach	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
sad	O
Condition	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
we	O
cleansed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
by	O
whom	O
it	O
was	O
seal	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
we	O
have	O
it	O
here	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
deny	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
me	O
?	O
Puddington	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
you	O
deny	O
'd	O
having	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
Cross	O
fought	O
about	O
the	O
Guinea	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
for	O
taking	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
This	O
Fellow	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Lawyer	O
Puddington	O
,	O
the	O
Law-splitter	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
swear	O
this	O
Candlestick	O
was	O
a	O
Ha'penny	O
Roll	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Farthing	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Frances	B-pers
Ravenscroft	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Linen	O
Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
17	O
Sets	O
of	O
Ivory	O
Fansticks	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Garier	I-pers
,	O
December	O
5	O
.	O
and	O
,	O
6.	O
Susan	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Principal	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Freeman	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
December	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Moge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
997	O
Pieces	O
of	O
foreign	O
silver	O
Coin	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Dollars	O
,	O
value	O
230	O
l.	O
and	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
foreign	O
silver	O
Coin	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
Ryals	O
,	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Cavalier	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Bugby-Hole	O
,	O
Decem	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Radford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
several	O
Bags	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
freight	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
one	O
Bag	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Peter	B-pers
Cavalier	I-pers
,	O
there	O
was	O
997	O
Dollars	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Ryals	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Chest	O
in	O
the	O
Gun	B-pers
Room	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
an	O
Italian	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
his	O
Passage	O
.	O
Upon	O
search	O
I	O
found	O
2	O
Dollars	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Bag	O
in	O
the	O
'Tween-decks	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Tuscana	O
Galley	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
800	O
and	O
odd	O
Dollars	O
,	O
110	O
more	O
we	O
found	O
by	O
his	O
Directions	O
in	O
a	O
Jarr	O
of	O
Tent	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
at	O
a	O
Silversmith	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
de	O
Moany	O
by	O
de	O
Goneroom	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
who	O
it	O
belong	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
till	O
soam	O
Body	O
come	O
to	O
ass	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Captain	O
when	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Tuscana	O
Galley	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
us	O
870	O
Dollars	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
for	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
should	O
enquire	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
By	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
Order	O
,	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Ship	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
Dollars	O
on	O
the	O
Sails	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
us	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Tuscana	O
Galley	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
869	O
or	O
870	O
Dollars	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
,	O
dare	O
was	O
all	O
.	O
We	O
computed	O
the	O
Complement	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
126	O
wanting	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
Sisteen	O
for	O
3	O
Guineas	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
all	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
By	O
my	O
ait	O
I	O
had	O
forgot	O
dare	O
is	O
110	O
in	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
de	O
Vine	O
,	O
in	O
de	O
Closet	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Tuscana	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
coud	O
have	O
gone	O
avay	O
vid	O
de	O
Moany	O
if	O
I	O
vood	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
2	O
Days	O
and	O
2	O
Nights	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
in	O
espettasion	O
dat	O
it	O
vood	O
be	O
ast	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
no	O
vant	O
to	O
concheal	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
ven	O
de	O
Captain	O
essamind	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
directly	O
vare	O
it	O
vas	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Charles	B-pers
Bosantine	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Mollineux	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10	O
,	O
11.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Walmsly	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Tea-spoons	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
Locket	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Locket	O
,	O
two	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
and	O
two	O
broad	O
Pieces	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Saunderson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
Decem	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
and	O
,	O
12.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Walmsly	O
and	O
W	O
-	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Margaret	O
Lucas	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
privately	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Edging	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
Decem	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Edward	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron-gate	O
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
Fence	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hadley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Dec.	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Mary	B-pers
Travillian	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lejardin	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
James	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
and	O
4	O
Bobbins	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Oakey	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Mary	B-pers
South	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
33	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
25s	O
.	O
2d	O
.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Batty	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Jan.	O
7	O
.	O
and	O
18.	O
Hester	B-pers
Hewson	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
South	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Drawers	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Hewson	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
appearing	O
that	O
Hewson	O
knew	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Edward	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Books	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
28	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
20.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handsaw	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Charles	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22	O
,	O
23.	O
Ann	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Rigsby	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Linen	O
Rags	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
Mary	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Dec.	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25	O
,	O
26.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Fenders	O
,	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Pots	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
John	B-pers
Moulder	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget-Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
John	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
30s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Morry	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29	O
,	O
30.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
4	O
Sheets	O
,	O
3	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
2	O
Plates	O
,	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Stocks	O
,	O
2	O
Towels	O
,	O
3	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Box	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Penitent-street	B-place
in	I-place
Ratcliffe	I-place
Highway	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
lived	O
almost	O
opposite	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
About	O
6	O
on	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
Doors	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Supper	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
single	O
Man	O
.	O
About	O
9	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
both	O
my	O
back	O
Door	O
and	O
fore	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
Comer	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
fitted	O
up	O
,	O
nor	O
made	O
so	O
secure	O
as	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
;	O
my	O
back	O
Door	O
was	O
fastened	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
Pin	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Wainscot	O
;	O
my	O
fore	O
Door	O
had	O
a	O
Lock	O
,	O
but	O
between	O
the	O
Lock	O
and	O
the	O
Staple	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hollow	O
place	O
through	O
which	O
the	O
Lock	O
might	O
be	O
push	O
'd	O
back	O
.	O
Behind	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
dead	O
Wall	O
8	O
Foot	O
high	O
.	O
The	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
Wainscot	O
where	O
the	O
Pin	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
Door	O
went	O
in	O
was	O
burst	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
Entry	O
was	O
made	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Goods	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Kemp	O
.	O
A	O
Clock	O
,	O
4	O
Sheets	O
,	O
3	O
Blankets	O
,	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
10	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
box	O
Iron	O
,	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
recover	O
them	O
?	O
Kemp	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
informed	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
in	O
my	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Gillam	I-pers
,	O
desiring	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
no	O
Body	O
see	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
but	O
his	O
Doughtear	O
.	O
Gillam	O
sent	O
this	O
Letter	O
to	O
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desiring	O
the	O
Bearer	O
to	O
read	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
over-heard	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lodged	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
Gillam's	O
's	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
this	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Gillam	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
wrote	O
it	O
?	O
Farmer	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
it	O
.	O
T.	O
Banks	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
wrote	O
the	O
Letter	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Let	O
it	O
be	O
read	O
.	O
Clerk	O
reads	O
.	O
For	O
Mrs.	O
Gillam	O
in	O
Swan-Alley	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
-	O
Mrs.	O
Gillam	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sadly	O
betrayed	O
by	O
the	O
Woman	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sincerely	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
good-will	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
you	O
to	O
put	O
every	O
thing	O
I	O
left	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
out	O
of	O
any	O
Body	O
's	O
sight	O
but	O
my	O
Daughter	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
will	O
come	O
with	O
the	O
Bearer	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
desire	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
I	O
left	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
can	O
ask	O
of	O
you	O
at	O
present	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
your	O
real	O
Friend	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
my	O
Power	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bankes	I-pers
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
they	O
can	O
hurt	O
me	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
but	O
my	O
Friend	O
.	O
T.	O
Banks	O
.	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Gillam	O
's	O
.	O
You	O
[	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
]	O
you	O
fastened	O
the	O
Doors	O
at	O
6	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
leave	O
the	O
Joiner	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Kemp	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
Joiner	O
was	O
putting	O
up	O
his	O
Tools	O
without	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
over-against	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
's	O
)	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
a-Clock	O
o	O
'	O
Friday	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
at	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
no	O
Credit	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
observe	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
.	O
By	O
and	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
(	O
her	O
Husband	O
)	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
taking	O
it	O
up	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
c	O
ould	O
well	O
carry	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
beyond	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
too	O
fast	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
your	O
Door	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
?	O
Ford	O
.	O
Just	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Yards	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
that	O
distance	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
your	O
Candle	O
?	O
Ford	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
easily	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
lived	O
but	O
hard	O
by	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
raised	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
Banks	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
good	O
Booty	O
.	O
T.	O
Banks	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
before	O
Justice	O
Philips	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bundle	O
burst	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
my	O
Wife	O
came	O
to	O
hold	O
a	O
Candle	O
.	O
Ford	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
then	O
as	O
I	O
say	O
now	O
.	O
T.	O
Banks	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stand	O
at	O
your	O
own	O
Door	O
?	O
Ford	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
exactly	O
.	O
T.	O
B	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
before	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Minutes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
taken	O
?	O
Kemp	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Night	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
Door	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Negus	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Night	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
charing	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
next	O
to	O
Jane	O
Gillam	O
's	O
in	O
Swan-Alley	O
;	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
dressing	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
strange	O
Disguise	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
tied	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
white	O
Shoes	O
about	O
him	O
like	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Apron	O
over	O
his	O
Shoulders	O
;	O
he	O
slopt	O
his	O
Hat	O
over	O
his	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
over	O
that	O
he	O
wrapt	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
Mouth	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
guess	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
all	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
Poverty	O
,	O
and	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
carry	O
a	O
Gown	O
to	O
his	O
Daughter	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
come	O
out	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
Gown	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
thro	O
'	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
bought	O
an	O
old	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
into	O
Penitent-street	O
,	O
he	O
pointed	O
to	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
my	O
Daughter	O
lives	O
,	O
carry	O
this	O
Gown	O
and	O
these	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
will	O
wait	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
my	O
Message	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
striking	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
;	O
Father	O
!	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
gone	O
to	O
Newgate	O
!	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
make	O
your	O
Escape	O
!	O
get	O
away	O
Backwards	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
House	O
is	O
beset	O
by	O
Kemp	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
coming	O
in	O
seiz	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Justice	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
his	O
Clerk	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
confin	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
then	O
,	O
because	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
living	O
by	O
charing	O
in	O
several	O
creditable	O
Families	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
known	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Prison	O
on	O
any	O
such	O
Account	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
Ruin	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
set	O
with	O
me	O
himself	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
.	O
About	O
12	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
some	O
Body	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
Who	O
's	O
there	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
answer	O
'd	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
.	O
Now	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
down	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Banks	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
as	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
for	O
being	O
a	O
naked	O
Woman	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
some	O
Mischief	O
if	O
I	O
said	O
otherwise	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
So	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
that	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Gillam	I-pers
.	O
About	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
o	O
'	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
Window	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a-bed	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
begg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
;	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
a-Clock	O
o	O
'	O
Saturday	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
it	O
seems	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
says	O
my	O
Landlady	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
Mr.	O
Banks	O
in	O
your	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
brought	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Trouble	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
slept	O
till	O
9	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
waked	O
him	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
'd	O
carry	O
this	O
Gown	O
to	O
my	O
Daughter	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
's	O
stark	O
naked	O
.	O
You	O
're	O
a	O
devilish	O
Dog	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
all	O
your	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Things	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
call	O
Martha	B-pers
Negus	I-pers
,	O
she	O
's	O
at	O
next	O
Door	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
called	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
foolish	O
in	O
going	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Officers	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Debt	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
meant	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
Woman	O
(	O
Martha	B-pers
Negus	I-pers
)	O
was	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
stay	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
lone	B-pers
Woman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
proper	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Heart	O
was	O
too	O
full	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
Nonsense	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
lay	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
called	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Black-Gown	O
(	O
Martha	B-pers
Negus	I-pers
)	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
waked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
clear	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
Mouth	O
of'em	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Martha	B-pers
Negus	I-pers
;	O
about	O
12	O
a-Clock	O
o'Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
;	O
says	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
call	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
much	O
Trouble	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
fear	O
of	O
an	O
Arrest	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
Brandy-Shop	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
but	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Yards	O
off	O
)	O
for	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
seen	O
if	O
you	O
stand	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
already	O
escaped	O
over	O
a	O
Wall	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
Kemp	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Brandy-Shop	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
Brandy-Shop	O
before	O
Negus	O
came	O
down	O
?	O
for	O
the	O
says	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Alex	B-pers
Yes	I-pers
he	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Negus	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
first	O
Hand	O
on	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
persidious	O
Fellow	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
into	O
all	O
that	O
Trouble	O
;	O
but	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
one	O
too	O
.	O
T.	O
Banks	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Lock	O
,	O
nor	O
Bolt	O
,	O
nor	O
Pin	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
stands	O
open	O
Day	O
and	O
Night	O
:	O
And	O
you	O
say	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
after	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Daws	O
there	O
?	O
Kemp	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
several	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Banks	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
Daws	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Spight	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Bundle	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
shall	O
prove	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Bundle	O
was	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Sheet	O
[	O
or	O
a	O
Blanket	O
]	O
and	O
thrown	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Street	O
was	O
very	O
dirty	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Blanket	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Gillam	O
's	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
dirty	O
.	O
Kemp	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
Blanket	O
's	O
and	O
found	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
again	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Daughter	O
.	O
)	O
About	O
5	O
a	O
Clock	O
o	O
'	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Daws	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Kemp	O
brought	O
these	O
Things	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
under	O
our	O
Window	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
me	O
look	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
they	O
turned	O
their	O
Backs	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
these	O
the	O
same	O
Things	O
in	O
Court	O
?	O
M.	O
B	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
opened	O
?	O
M.	O
B	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
Bundle	O
?	O
M.	O
B	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Daws	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecuter	O
who	O
laid	O
this	O
Bundle	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
?	O
M.	O
B	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
there	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
about	O
Kemp	O
's	O
House	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
before	O
this	O
Bundle	O
was	O
brought	O
?	O
M.	O
B	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Father	O
was	O
then	O
sitting	O
at	O
home	O
by	O
the	O
Fireside	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
This	O
will	O
not	O
account	O
for	O
his	O
carrying	O
those	O
Things	O
to	O
Gillam	O
's	O
.	O
T.	O
Banks	O
.	O
Daws	O
can	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
bringing	O
those	O
Goods	O
to	O
my	O
Window	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Daws	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
Goods	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
and	O
Kemp	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
Time	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
leave	O
any	O
Goods	O
whatever	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Window	O
?	O
Daws	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
T.	O
Banks	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
in	O
Kemp	O
's	O
House	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
?	O
Daws	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
upon	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
's	O
Outcry	O
,	O
that	O
Kemp	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
.	O
T.	O
Banks	O
.	O
Kemp	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
his	O
back	O
Door	O
was	O
not	O
forced	O
open	O
.	O
Kemp	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
Thing	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
open	O
.	O
T.	O
Banks	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Daughter	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	O
!	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Body	O
go	O
into	O
,	O
or	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Kemp	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
before	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
Alarm	O
?	O
M.	O
B.	O
I	O
saw	O
Kemp	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
leave	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
Workmen	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
before	O
Mrs.	O
Ford	O
called	O
out	O
?	O
M.	O
B	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Kemp	O
.	O
The	O
Workmen	O
was	O
without	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
M.	O
B	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Workman	O
come	O
only	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
M.	O
B	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
Kemp	O
did	O
not	O
lock	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Kemp	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
lock	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Death	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
appearing	O
that	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Banks	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
acted	O
under	O
his	O
Direction	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
31.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
without	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
striking	O
and	O
kicking	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Membrane	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
her	O
several	O
mortal	O
Bruises	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bell-Alley	B-place
in	I-place
Golden-Lane	I-place
.	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
was	O
seven-night	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
ten	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
waked	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
below	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
quarreling	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
Damn	O
his	O
Eyes	O
and	O
Liver	O
,	O
get	O
up	O
Bess	O
!	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
fuddled	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
was	O
fuddled	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
up	O
her	O
self	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
drunk	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
lifting	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
he	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
and	O
paid	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Feet	O
and	O
Hands	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
below	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
gush	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
it	O
was	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
struck	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
Goar	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
grievousest	O
Manner	O
that	O
ever	O
you	O
saw	O
any	O
Creature	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
Blood	O
descended	O
from	O
.	O
He	O
struck	O
her	O
no	O
more	O
after	O
the	O
Light	O
came	O
,	O
but	O
turned	O
her	O
Face	O
up	O
and	O
stamp	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Betty	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
I	O
have	O
killed	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
I	O
will	O
never	O
leave	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
freely	O
be	O
hanged	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
that	O
her	O
Shins	O
were	O
sadly	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
full	O
of	O
Scratches	O
too	O
;	O
she	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
her	O
Shift	O
was	O
bloody	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Shift	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rush	I-pers
.	O
Bird	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
waked	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
beating	O
his	O
Wife	O
sadly	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
both	O
their	O
Voices	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
get	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
you	O
Bitch	O
!	O
I	O
heard	O
several	O
blows	O
and	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
dragged	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
opened	O
our	O
Door	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
dragg	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
Rush	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
besides	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
so	O
?	O
Rush	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
to	O
that	O
Degree	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
might	O
not	O
her	O
Inability	O
proceed	O
from	O
her	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
?	O
Rush	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
or	O
no	O
:	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
our	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
stamp	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
by	O
the	O
Sound	O
he	O
stamp	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Candle	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
had	O
struck	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
lying	O
upon	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
goar	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
deplorable	O
Condition	O
.	O
He	O
turned	O
her	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Wife	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
I	O
have	O
killed	O
you	O
!	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
?	O
Rush	O
.	O
She	O
never	O
spoke	O
a	O
Word	O
after	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
higher	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Sister-in-Law	O
,	O
who	O
wash	O
'd	O
her	O
Wounds	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
died	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lodged	O
but	O
a	O
Month	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
that	O
Space	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
addicted	O
to	O
drinking	O
?	O
Rush	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
E.	O
Bird	O
again	O
.	O
They	O
and	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
addicted	O
to	O
Drinking	O
,	O
except	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
fuddled	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
my	O
Sister	O
.	O
The	O
ill	O
Usage	O
she	O
has	O
often	O
received	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
he	O
now	O
stands	O
indicted	O
for	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
No	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
Word	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
lived	O
afar	O
off	O
from	O
where	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
heard	O
from	O
others	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
is	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
nor	O
is	O
it	O
proper	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
run	O
into	O
Particulars	O
that	O
have	O
no	O
Relation	O
to	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Marriage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
lie	O
in	O
a	O
Ground	O
Room	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
often	O
fell	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Night	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
draw	O
her	O
along	O
under	O
my	O
Window	O
like	O
a	O
Beast	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
either	O
he	O
or	O
she	O
?	O
S.	O
M.	O
I	O
knew	O
their	O
Voices	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
strike	O
me	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
you	O
will	O
kill	O
me	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Ye	O
Bitch	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
my	O
Design	O
!	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
who	O
made	O
that	O
Answer	O
?	O
S.	O
M.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
partly	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
Witness	O
has	O
told	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Lies	O
about	O
it	O
already	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Decartney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
too	O
;	O
and	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
lay	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
Argument	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
She	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bitter	O
Groan	O
,	O
Oh	O
!	O
Oh	O
!	O
Oh	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Ye	O
Bitch	O
,	O
get	O
up	O
!	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
only	O
up	O
,	O
or	O
up	O
Stairs	O
?	O
B.	O
D.	O
Not	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
up	O
,	O
from	O
where	O
she	O
fell	O
.	O
And	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
without	O
you	O
help	O
me	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
ye	B-pers
Bitch	I-pers
,	O
I	O
'll	O
help	O
ye	O
up	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
Dear	O
Sam	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
strike	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
ye	O
do	O
you	O
'll	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O
Ye	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
my	O
Design	O
to	O
kill	O
you	O
!	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
they	O
spoke	O
those	O
Words	O
?	O
B.	O
D.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
by	O
their	O
Voices	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
'em	O
twenty	O
five	O
Years	O
.	O
Prison	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
more	O
years	O
than	O
you	O
are	O
old	O
.	O
B.	O
D.	O
May	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Drunkard	O
,	O
like	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
served	O
his	O
Wife	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
dy	O
'd	O
then	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
charged	O
with	O
?	O
S.	O
L.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
was	O
a-se'nnight	O
I	O
met	O
his	O
Landlady	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
sad	O
Accident	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
for	O
Sam	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
had	O
killed	O
Bess	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
see	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
plovable	O
Condition	O
;	O
all	O
her	O
Head	O
was	O
cut	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
put	O
my	O
Finger	O
in	O
the	O
Wounds	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
of	O
her	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
cold	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
bled	O
three	O
quarts	O
of	O
Blood	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
she	O
's	O
a	O
dying	O
Woman	O
;	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
Rogue	O
up	O
?	O
Then	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
stoop	O
'd	O
to	O
kiss	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
killed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
Bitches	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
wo	O
n't	O
stick	O
to	O
hang	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
get	O
off	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
Poker	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
swearing	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
Sacrifice	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Bitch	O
that	O
offered	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
.	O
Con	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
?	O
S.	O
L.	O
He	O
's	O
a	O
Bunter	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
Wife	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
26	O
or	O
27	O
Years	O
old	O
when	O
she	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
likely	O
sober	O
Body	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Godman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Overseers	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
and	O
the	O
Coroner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
before	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Convulsions	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
expiring	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
vain	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
save	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
died	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
view	O
'd	O
her	O
afterwards	O
,	O
her	O
Head	O
and	O
Body	O
were	O
full	O
of	O
Contusions	O
all	O
over	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
Condition	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Cut	O
in	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Head	O
was	O
'swell	O
'd	O
in	O
Comparison	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
a	O
Peck	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Muscles	O
that	O
cover	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Sutors	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
manner	O
separated	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
Pint	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Pint	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
several	O
Handfuls	O
.	O
This	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
caus	O
'd	O
by	O
external	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
such	O
an	O
Effect	O
upon	O
the	O
Sutors	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
or	O
examine	O
any	O
farther	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
was	O
always	O
drunk	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
same	O
Night	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
she	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
Home	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
did	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
both	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
much	O
addicted	O
to	O
pilfering	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
would	O
often	O
thieve	O
wet	O
Shirts	O
and	O
Smocks	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Character	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
this	O
of	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Witness	O
that	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
Character	O
of	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
pillfering	O
:	O
One	O
Day	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
wet	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
dry	O
'd	O
it	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
throw	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Indeed	O
she	O
was	O
fuddled	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
often	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
mightily	O
given	O
to	O
drinking	O
.	O
Another	O
.	O
You	O
lie	O
,	O
Hussey	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
honest	O
working	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
slave	O
like	O
a	O
Pack-Horse	O
when	O
you	O
would	O
come	O
Home	O
with	O
an	O
empty	O
Basket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
32.	O
John	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
Mears	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cromwit	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Emerton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Deal	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Ladle	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
9	O
Guineas	O
,	O
11	O
s.	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Napkin	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
2	O
Fans	O
,	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
,	O
a	O
Case-knife	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pairs	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
December	O
16	O
.	O
And	O
33.	O
Michael	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
and	O
2	O
Knives	O
,	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick	O
Cellar	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
,	I-place
facing	I-place
Somerset-house	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
harboured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Emerton	O
about	O
3	O
Weeks	O
in	O
my	O
Cellar	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
shabby	O
Fellow	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
now	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
good	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
from	O
me	O
paid	O
for	O
'em	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
odd	O
Chars	O
,	O
run	O
of	O
Errands	O
,	O
and	O
water	O
Horses	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
sit	O
up	O
by	O
my	O
Fire	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
lay	O
up	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
between	O
:	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
two	O
little	O
Girls	O
(	O
Ann	B-pers
Delamore	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hemming	I-pers
)	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
long	O
before	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Girls	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Emerton	I-pers
had	O
taken	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
run	O
up	O
Swan-yard	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
?	O
Holder	O
.	O
Nine	O
Guineas	O
,	O
11	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
Halfpence	O
;	O
a	O
Silver	O
Punch-Ladle	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
3	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
3	O
Knives	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
that	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
the	O
Box	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
up	O
?	O
M.	O
H.	O
It	O
stood	O
on	O
a	O
Trunk	O
in	O
my	O
Bed-room	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
with	O
the	O
Publick	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
The	O
Door	O
of	O
my	O
Room	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
your	O
Goods	O
again	O
?	O
M.	O
H.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
in	O
Wells	O
's	O
Yard	O
in	O
Tottenham-Court	O
Road	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Lodging	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
2	O
of	O
the	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
were	O
quite	O
lost	O
.	O
This	O
honest	O
Man	O
here	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
thither	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
Messenger	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Gore	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
Gore	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
could	O
raise	O
.	O
The	O
Messenger	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
Directions	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
Gore	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Knives	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
Gore	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
.	O
We	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
all	O
he	O
knew	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
Emerton	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
we	O
discharg	O
'd	O
Gore	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
Justice	O
bound	O
him	O
over	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Emerton	O
.	O
But	O
after	O
this	O
Gore	O
sent	O
my	O
Punch-Ladle	O
to	O
pawn	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
before	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
)	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
are	O
poer	O
old	O
Folks	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Pains	O
to	O
scrape	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Rogue	O
Emerton	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Dinner	O
that	O
Day	O
)	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
of	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
us	O
but	O
3	O
pence	O
ha'peny	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Alex	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
one	O
Michael	O
Tool	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
for	O
offering	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Punch	O
Ladle	O
.	O
Tool	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Gore	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
Gore	O
;	O
who	O
after	O
some	O
shuffling	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
Tool	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
Gore	O
.	O
Emerton	O
gave	O
the	O
Ladle	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
touch	O
'd	O
it	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
Senses	O
.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Hitchcock	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sweeping	O
Swan-Yard	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Cellar	O
)	O
when	O
Emerton	O
came	O
running	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Hurry	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
)	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
Answer	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
running	O
;	O
when	O
presently	O
the	O
Girl	O
(	O
Ann	B-pers
Delamore	I-pers
)	O
came	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
John	O
!	O
John	O
!	O
do	O
n't	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
Grandmother	O
's	O
Box	O
!	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Delamore	I-pers
;	O
stand	O
up	O
,	O
Child	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
A.	O
D.	O
Almost	O
twelve	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Suppose	O
now	O
you	O
should	O
take	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
true	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
will	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
A.	O
D.	O
After	O
I	O
die	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
be	O
happy	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Let	O
her	O
be	O
sworn	O
.	O
Now	O
besure	O
you	O
say	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Truth	O
.	O
A.	O
D.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
My	O
Grandmother	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
left	O
John	B-pers
Emerton	I-pers
and	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Girl	O
(	O
Mary	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
)	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
wanted	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
I	O
draw	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
Molly	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
's	O
go	O
down	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
John	O
's	O
a	O
doing	O
.	O
So	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Grandmother	O
's	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
by	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
John	O
!	O
John	O
!	O
do	O
n't	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
Grandmother	O
's	O
Box	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
coming	O
again	O
presently	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
that	O
Box	O
use	O
to	O
stand	O
?	O
A.	O
D.	O
In	O
my	O
Grandmother	O
's	O
Bed-Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
?	O
A.	O
D.	O
Not	O
justly	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
in	O
it	O
often	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
Grandmother	O
kept	O
her	O
Ladle	O
there	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
use	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
I	O
left	O
no	O
Soul	O
below	O
but	O
John	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
.	O
Emerton	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Gully-hole	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Molly	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
,	O
your	O
Mother	O
wants	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
my	O
Mother	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
down	O
4	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
turned	O
me	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Mother	O
was	O
at	O
young	O
Mrs.	O
Holder	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Mother	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
in	O
going	O
back	O
I	O
saw	O
Nanny	O
Delamore	O
by	O
the	O
Gully-hole	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
Grandmother	O
.	O
that	O
John	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
Lord	O
Nanny	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
wonder	O
what	O
this	O
John	O
is	O
doing	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
;	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
turning	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
by	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
walk	O
'd	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Queen's-Head	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
John	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
coming	O
again	O
,	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
Swan-Alley	O
like	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
C.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
Box	O
use	O
to	O
stand	O
?	O
M.	O
H.	O
In	O
the	O
inner	O
Room	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
Chimly	O
Corner	O
;	O
He	O
had	O
it	O
partly	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Lock	O
.	O
Nathaniel	O
Lake	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Holder	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
Emerton	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
before	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
him	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
run	O
from	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Old	O
Playhouse	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
pray	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Gore	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
(	O
in	O
Colston's-Court	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
)	O
and	O
desire	O
Gore	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Holder	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
Gore	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
and	O
two	O
Knives	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
;	O
when	O
Gore	O
saw	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
the	O
Box	O
is	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
Emerton	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
Gore	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
Ladle	O
were	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Gore	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
greater	O
values	O
than	O
the	O
Ladle	O
and	O
Spoons	O
,	O
why	O
should	O
you	O
ask	O
after	O
them	O
only	O
?	O
Lake	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Holder	O
did	O
ask	O
for	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
Mr.	O
Lake	O
in	O
taking	O
Emerton	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
writ	O
down	O
Gore	O
's	O
Name	O
with	O
Chalk	O
upon	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
Gore	O
to	O
bring	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Gloves	O
and	O
Knives	O
at	O
Gore	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
:	O
I	O
remember	O
in	O
particular	O
this	O
broken	O
Ring	O
and	O
this	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Holder	O
owns	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Emerton	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Noon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stone	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
notice	O
given	O
me	O
,	O
stop	O
such	O
a	O
silver	O
Ladle	O
as	O
this	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Friday	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
Michael	B-pers
Tool	I-pers
,	O
of	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
the	O
Handle	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
strange	O
work	O
with	O
this	O
Ladle	O
?	O
Ay	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
a	O
sad	O
Accident	O
happened	O
when	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
China	O
Punch	O
bowl	O
was	O
broke	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
jump	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
'Saule	O
me	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
pepper	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Gore	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
(	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Theatre	O
)	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Gore	O
a	O
playing	O
at	O
Cards	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
play	O
'd	O
the	O
wrong	O
Card	O
then	O
.	O
Says	O
Tool	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Ladle	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
Gore	O
after	O
some	O
Shuffling	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
save	O
it	O
to	O
Tool	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Tool	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
Headborough	O
.	O
Gore	O
let	O
us	O
search	O
his	O
Room	O
readily	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
,	O
at	O
Emerton	O
's	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Wells-Court	O
by	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Pound	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Shirt	O
hanging	O
in	O
Gore	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
When	O
Emerton	O
sent	O
you	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
meant	O
I	O
should	O
pawn	O
this	O
Shirt	O
.	O
Gore	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
Shoes	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Holder	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
that	O
are	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
there	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
yours	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
claims	O
them	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
them	O
:	O
Officer	O
,	O
give	O
those	O
Shoes	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
's	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Gore	O
.	O
I	O
thank	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
I	O
claim	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Emerton	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
Mrs.	O
Holder	O
's	O
Cellar	O
3	O
Weeks	O
Night	O
and	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
happening	O
to	O
meet	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
of	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
come	O
out	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Holder	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
want	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
much	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
without	O
any	O
more	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
no	O
Body	O
will	O
ask	O
you	O
any	O
Questions	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Girls	O
called	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
again	O
presently	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
return	O
according	O
to	O
your	O
Promise	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
acquaint	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Emerton	O
.	O
My	O
Friend	O
kept	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
and	O
besides	O
I	O
ow	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
s.	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
Remittances	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
afterwards	O
received	O
indeed	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Friend	O
hearing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
15	O
s.	O
upon	O
the	O
Ladle	O
and	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
other	O
odd	O
Trifles	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
might	O
make	O
Use	O
of	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
returning	O
me	O
the	O
15s	O
.	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
promised	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wanting	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
Gore	O
's	O
Wife	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
6	O
s.	O
Court	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
this	O
Friend	O
of	O
yours	O
?	O
Emerton	O
.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
;	O
but	O
I	O
hear	O
he	O
is	O
absconded	O
since	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Michael	B-pers
Tool	I-pers
:	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
call	O
and	O
pay	O
Mrs.	O
Holder	O
;	O
but	O
happening	O
to	O
be	O
drinking	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Lake	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
else	O
is	O
as	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
have	O
sworn	O
.	O
Gore	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
received	O
any	O
Goods	O
from	O
Emerton	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hear	O
that	O
my	O
Wife	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
Michael	B-pers
Tool	I-pers
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Ladle	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Nolton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Milford-lane	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Gore	O
above	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
followed	O
the	O
Sea	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
Painter	O
by	O
Trade	O
;	O
he	O
painted	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
lodged	O
there	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
last	O
Summer	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
paid	O
above	O
50	O
s.	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
Receipt	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
civil	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Rigg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
3	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
every	O
Night	O
at	O
the	O
Theatre-Alehouse	O
in	O
Clare	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
swear	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
nor	O
give	O
an	O
abrupt	O
Answer	O
to	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
spend	O
your	O
time	O
there	O
every	O
Night	O
?	O
Rigg	O
.	O
In	O
drinking	O
and	O
playing	O
at	O
Cards	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
Emerton	O
belong	O
to	O
your	O
Club	O
too	O
?	O
Rigg	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
there	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Gore	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Emerton	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
34	O
,	O
35	O
,	O
36.	O
John	B-pers
Ackers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Welton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Penknife	O
and	O
35s	O
.	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Key	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shute	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
December	O
12	O
.	O
[	O
At	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
near	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
a	O
Letter	O
for	O
my	O
Master	O
Col.	O
Shute	B-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
Foreign	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
dead	O
Wall	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Albemarle-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
seiz	O
'd	O
by	O
some	O
Street	O
Robbers	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
many	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
;	O
they	O
sat	O
me	O
upon	O
a	O
Rail	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
dead	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
blinded	O
me	O
with	O
their	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
punching	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
with	O
something	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
1	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
clasp	O
Penknife	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Clock	O
Case-key	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
giving	O
me	O
a	O
thump	O
upon	O
my	O
Back	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Mascall	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
Booth	O
and	O
I	O
stop't	O
a	O
Coach	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
two	O
Purses	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
Silver	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
we	O
attacked	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Albemarle-street	O
,	O
Welton	O
stopt	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
Ackers	O
jobb	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
3	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Booth	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
clapt	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
blinded	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
R.	O
Harvey	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
like	O
Iron	O
at	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Mascall	O
.	O
Weston	O
took	O
19s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
Sam	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
(	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
5	O
of	O
us	O
)	O
took	O
a	O
clasp	O
Knife	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
Money	O
than	O
19	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
often	O
cheat	O
one	O
another	O
in	O
those	O
Cases	O
,	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
5	O
l.	O
for	O
ought	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Ackers	O
afterwards	O
took	O
the	O
Knife	O
from	O
Goodman	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
over	O
a	O
House	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
through	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
bought	O
8	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
Meat	O
at	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Sign	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
Court	O
that	O
goes	O
to	O
Blackmore-street	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
a	O
Tin	O
Shop	O
.	O
There	O
we	O
eat	O
the	O
Meat	O
and	O
spent	O
17	O
Pence	O
half	O
penny	O
in	O
Beer	O
and	O
Bread	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Meat	O
was	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
was	O
it	O
drest	O
?	O
Mascall	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
ready	O
drest	O
,	O
but	O
cold	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
roasted	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Breast	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
2	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
Marrow-bone	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Booth	O
.	O
Does	O
a	O
Marrow-bone	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
Breast	O
of	O
Mutton	O
?	O
Mascall	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
both	O
pieces	O
were	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Bowl-yard	O
,	O
where	O
Welton	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
his	O
Goat	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
we	O
redeemed	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
we	O
constantly	O
use	O
,	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Lawrence-Lane	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
grand	O
bandy	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
harbour	O
Thieves	O
and	O
Whores	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
'em	O
in	O
at	O
all	O
Hours	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
There	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
about	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
asked	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
they	O
denied	O
me	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
Ackers	O
and	O
Booth	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
bought	O
some	O
Victuals	O
with	O
it	O
for	O
my	O
Family	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lay	O
there	O
together	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
Mascall	O
.	O
They	O
commonly	O
lie	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
'em	O
there	O
at	O
9	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
Shilling	O
more	O
for	O
my	O
Share	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
got	O
but	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
differ	O
?	O
Mascall	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Goodman	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
Start	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
voluntairly	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hilder	O
and	O
made	O
my	O
Information	O
.	O
Goodman	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Robbery	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
Information	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
upon	O
this	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Mascall	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
that	O
Morning	O
as	O
usual	O
about	O
nine	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
staid	O
till	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
