TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
1733	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARBER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1733	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILFORD	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Chapter-House	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXIII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
former	O
Numbers	O
in	O
the	O
present	O
Mayoralty	O
,	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARBER	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lee	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Gwin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newcomb	I-pers
,	O
Elias	B-pers
Fosset	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burdet	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Goodchild	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stamford	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ayloff	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Huddle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bignell	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Shipton	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
John	B-pers
Dominicus	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Gold-Rings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
Cornelins	O
Herbert	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
on	O
London-Bridge	B-place
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
weighty	O
Gold-Rings	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
two	O
that	O
were	O
very	O
heavy	O
.	O
He	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
well	O
pleas	O
'd	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Pen	O
and	O
Ink	O
to	O
set	O
down	O
the	O
Weight	O
and	O
Value	O
.	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
suspect	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
think	O
right	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
two	O
Rings	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Gout	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
He	O
was	O
soon	O
seiz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
Rings	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
Rings	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
charged	O
me	O
5	O
s.	O
more	O
than	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
cheated	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
two	O
Rings	O
to	O
shew	O
to	O
a	O
Friend	O
before	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Herbert	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth-Coat	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bainton	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
3.	O
John	B-pers
Wily	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
June	O
18	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Ridinghood	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
May	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
5.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hayman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Harry	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
Toby	B-pers
Chauncey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Croker	I-pers
,	O
June	O
13	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
6	O
,	O
7.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
17	O
yards	O
of	O
Printed	O
Linen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
,	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Slight	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Chiswel	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
White	B-place
Cross	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
wanted	O
some	O
Printed	O
Linen	O
;	O
my	O
Mistress	O
took	O
down	O
3	O
Peices	O
.	O
They	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
third	O
Piece	O
particularly	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
shew	O
'd	O
'em	O
several	O
more	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
took	O
down	O
all	O
the	O
Printed	O
Linens	O
on	O
the	O
Shelf	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
wanted	O
14	O
Yards	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
pitch	O
'd	O
upon	O
one	O
Piece	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
but	O
6	O
Yards	O
;	O
they	O
agreed	O
upon	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
Brian	O
gave	O
my	O
Mistress	O
2	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
having	O
some	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
change	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
Brian	O
drawing	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
Peticoats	O
with	O
a	O
Hitch	O
and	O
a	O
Hitch	O
thus	O
-	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
imagine	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
Peticoat	O
was	O
got	O
loose	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
tying	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
because	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
my	O
Mistress	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
her	O
Goods	O
and	O
mist	O
the	O
third	O
Piece	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
printed	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
Sprig	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
down	O
Chiswel	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Black	O
Raven	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
The	O
Linen	O
,	O
it	O
seems	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
thither	O
Mr.	O
Brian	O
,	O
the	O
Landlord	O
of	O
the	O
Raven	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Maid	O
found	O
it	O
dropt	O
behind	O
a	O
Door	O
in	O
an	O
Entry	O
,	O
thro	O
'	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Piece	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Shop-mark	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
Mrs.	O
Brian	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
bought	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
Linen	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Roper	O
mist	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
small	O
sprig	O
Linen	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Run	O
Husband	O
,	O
Run	O
Father	O
.	O
They	O
ran	O
and	O
I	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brian	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Brian	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
searched	O
?	O
Graves	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
50	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
P.	O
Brian	O
.	O
The	O
Men	O
searched	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Modesty	O
would	O
permit	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Women	O
carried	O
us	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
Passage	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
and	O
searched	O
us	O
to	O
our	O
Shifts	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Eaves	I-pers
.	O
I	O
only	O
felt	O
on	O
the	O
out-side	O
of	O
their	O
Cloathes	O
thus	O
-	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
searched	O
them	O
any	O
farther	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Linen	O
might	O
be	O
folded	O
up	O
so	O
as	O
not	O
easily	O
to	O
be	O
felt	O
by	O
such	O
a	O
slight	O
Search	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brian	O
's	O
Maid	O
is	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
is	O
bought	O
off	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
offer	O
'd	O
12	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Son	O
20	O
Guineas	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Friends	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
was	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Orders	O
?	O
Eaves	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brian	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Three-threads	O
.	O
Presently	O
Mr.	O
Eaves	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Printed	O
Linen	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
searched	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
by	O
feeling	O
about	O
the	O
out-side	O
of	O
their	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
but	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
dark	O
Passage	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
privately	O
by	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
them	O
there	O
neither	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
my	O
Maid	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
past	O
thro	O
'	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
she	O
trod	O
on	O
something	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
it	O
up	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
Printed	O
Linen	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Roper	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Maid	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Piece	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Were	O
not	O
several	O
People	O
in	O
that	O
Passage	O
besides	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Brian	O
.	O
Nobody	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
besides	O
my	O
own	O
Family	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
numbers	O
of	O
People	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brian	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
about	O
my	O
Bar	O
there	O
was	O
so	O
many	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
hardly	O
stand	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
your	O
Maid	O
take	O
the	O
Linen	O
up	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Brian	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
directly	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
her	O
saying	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Evidence	O
,	O
except	O
she	O
was	O
here	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Brian	O
.	O
She	O
's	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Mother	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
here	O
's	O
nobody	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
this	O
Linen	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Piece	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
the	O
Burrough	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Atkinson	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
she	O
goes	O
a	O
Nursing	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
any	O
Crime	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
to	O
hear	O
this	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
5	O
Years	O
too	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
my	O
Nurse	O
and	O
behaved	O
exceeding	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Brian	O
,	O
lodged	O
2	O
Years	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
made	O
Mantua	O
's	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Slight	I-pers
,	O
again	O
.	O
Brian	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
in	O
Wild-street	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
8.	O
Mary	B-pers
Burness	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Curtis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Gold-Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Bathmetal	O
Mourning-Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
C.	O
Alexander	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
gotten	O
Oarders	O
to	O
gang	O
wi	O
'	O
my	O
Colonel	O
tull	O
Bristo	O
'	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
tuck	O
my	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
tull	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Moather	O
was	O
seek	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanno	O
'	O
gang	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
Toon	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
find	O
my	O
sell	O
a	O
Loading	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
discharged	O
my	O
aul	O
Landlady	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
mat	O
the	O
Preesoner	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Wastminster	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
seeing	O
me	O
Stranger-like	O
in	O
Boots	O
and	O
Spurs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
leetle	O
in	O
Leequor	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
taud	O
her	O
I	O
danno	O
'	O
want	O
Drink	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
Loadging	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
quo	O
'	O
she	O
,	O
gin	O
ye	O
wull	O
gang	O
wi	O
'	O
me	O
tull	O
Mrs.	O
Humphries	O
in	O
Bell-Alley	B-place
,	O
ye	O
shall	O
ha	O
'	O
a	O
Loadging	O
and	O
a	O
Bed-fellow	O
too	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
tuck	O
haud	O
o	O
'	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
lad	O
me	O
awa	O
'	O
to	O
Moather	O
Humphries	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hoor	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
Leequor	O
and	O
my	O
Loadging	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Preesoner	O
went	O
up	O
tull	O
Beed	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Humphries	O
lighted	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
undrest	O
me	O
and	O
got	O
intull	O
the	O
Beed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
tuck	O
oot	O
my	O
Watch	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
Cloak	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
part	O
II	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
intull	O
my	O
Fobe	O
and	O
laid	O
my	O
Breeks	O
under	O
my	O
Heed	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Preesoner	O
wonno	O
'	O
strip	O
,	O
but	O
laid	O
her	O
sell	O
doon	O
by	O
me	O
wi	O
'	O
her	O
Clothes	O
on	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
then	O
?	O
C.A	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Buruess	O
,	O
because	O
you	O
beat	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
you	O
thenk	O
tull	O
frighten	O
me	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
wonno	O
'	O
do	O
,	O
troath	O
wull	O
it	O
not	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
so	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Humphries	O
to	O
caw	O
me	O
up	O
by	O
sax	O
a	O
Cloak	O
in	O
the	O
Moarning	O
;	O
and	O
than	O
,	O
being	O
pretty	O
weel	O
in	O
for't	O
,	O
I	O
sell	O
faist	O
asleep	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
next	O
Moarning	O
Mrs.	O
Humphries	O
came	O
tull	O
,	O
my	O
Beed-side	O
and	O
wak	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Loard	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
quo	O
'	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
this	O
Betch	O
has	O
roab	O
'd	O
ye	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
brock	O
open	O
my	O
Door	O
and	O
run	O
awa	O
'	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
had	O
you	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
C.	O
A.	O
Troath	O
had	O
I	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
I	O
laost	O
my	O
Siller	O
Watch	O
with	O
2	O
Seals	O
,	O
a	O
Gowd	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brace	O
Mourning	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
hauf	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
aw	O
'	O
tacket	O
oot	O
o	O
'	O
my	O
Breeks	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
what	O
of	O
all	O
that	O
?	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
Humphries	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Lodgers	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Of	O
Whores	O
you	O
mean	O
.	O
She	O
keeps	O
a	O
Bawdy-House	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
Truth	O
o	O
n't	O
.	O
Humph	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
indeed	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lighted	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Fob	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
call	O
him	O
up	O
at	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
together	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Hark	O
you	O
,	O
Landlady	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
remember	O
that	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
Husband	O
were	O
whipt	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
Bawdy-House	O
?	O
Humph	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
-	O
Next	O
Morning	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Door	O
broke	O
open	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Fright	O
,	O
and	O
waked	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
2	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Loadging	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'd	O
find	O
her	O
if	O
possible	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Hussy	O
,	O
you	O
lie	O
;	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
vile	O
Toad	O
,	O
a	O
vile	O
old	O
Baud	O
;	O
you	O
lie	O
,	O
you	O
lie	O
,	O
you	O
lie	O
.	O
Humph	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
Wednesday	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
help	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
far	O
gone	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
both	O
be	O
discharged	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
that	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
Jack	O
!	O
Jack	O
!	O
He	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Trisle	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
go	O
off	O
again	O
:	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
2	O
Rings	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
about	O
Noon	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
She	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
tumbled	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
hired	O
to	O
swear	O
this	O
.	O
Kelly	O
.	O
The	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
Brags	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Pocket	O
of	O
6	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
O	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
another	O
Witness	O
a	O
getting	O
up	O
!	O
let	O
's	O
hear	O
what	O
she	O
can	O
say	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
De	O
Presonare	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
'ave	O
de	O
loshing	O
in	O
mine	O
'Ouse	O
,	O
and	O
dis	O
Man	O
here	O
,	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
Dat	O
he	O
vas	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
up	O
de	O
Voman	O
and	O
de	O
Voman	O
pick	O
his	O
Poket	O
of	O
his	O
Vash	O
and	O
oder	O
Tings	O
,	O
and	O
vare	O
be	O
dis	O
Voman	O
,	O
he	O
vant	O
dis	O
Voman	O
.	O
I	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
her	O
have	O
de	O
Vash	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
18d	O
.	O
ven	O
she	O
vas	O
drunk	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Now	O
you	O
have	O
spoke	O
the	O
right	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
blame	O
you	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Punt	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
House	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Brass	O
Mourning	O
Ring	O
clenched	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lately	O
had	O
her	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
times	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
Facts	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
no	O
reason	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
too	O
.	O
So	O
many	O
against	O
one	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
hard	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
well	O
known	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
bold	O
Woman	O
.	O
He	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
lye	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
honest	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mother	O
Humphries	O
's	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
much	O
against	O
my	O
Will	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
no	O
Denial	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
a	O
Loadging	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Anniseed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
reckoning	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
3s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Ring	O
upon	O
my	O
Finger	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
forget	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
no	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
the	O
matter	O
I	O
may	O
not	O
speak	O
for	O
myself	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Whores	O
and	O
Bands	O
that	O
will	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
your	O
Defence	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
hear	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
be	O
suffer	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
such	O
abusive	O
Language	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
stir	O
till	O
I	O
have	O
told	O
the	O
whole	O
Story	O
of	O
these	O
Bands	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Take	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
Execustioner	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
hear	O
,	O
Child	O
?	O
Come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
beat	O
your	O
March	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
9.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Shifts	O
,	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
and	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
June	O
21	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Altimira	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
3	O
Shifts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
.	O
May	O
31	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
11.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bains	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Cater	I-pers
,	O
May	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
12.	O
Mary	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
18s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
John	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Firkins	O
of	O
Tallow	O
,	O
value	O
40s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Mary	B-pers
Powers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Charles	B-pers
Milson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
2	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
13d	O
.	O
May	O
9	O
.	O
C.	O
Milson	O
.	O
Between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
2	O
Men	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin's-Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
very	O
much	O
abused	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
13d	O
.	O
My	O
Watch	O
was	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Sale	O
next	O
Day	O
in	O
Picadilly	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
stopt	O
and	O
advertis	O
'd	O
.	O
Alex	O
Geron	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
offered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
2	O
Women	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
being	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
those	O
2	O
Women	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
16.	O
Susan	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
4	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
3	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
value	O
25s	O
.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
enamell	O
'd	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tomlins	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
de	I-pers
Monstieur	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cornelian	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Friend	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
in	O
Spring-Garden	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Creamer	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Five	B-place
Bells	I-place
Tavern	I-place
,	O
behind	O
the	O
New	B-place
Church	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
hardly	O
quite	O
dark	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
both	O
disorder	O
'd	O
with	O
drinking	O
,	O
but	O
especially	O
my	O
Friend	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Creamer	O
refused	O
us	O
Admittance	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chair	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
my	O
Friend	O
was	O
getting	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Creamer	O
bid	O
the	O
Chairman	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Chairman	O
took	O
my	O
Friend	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
This	O
provok	O
'd	O
me	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
Chairman	O
,	O
when	O
presently	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fighting	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
Watch	O
drawn	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Mob	O
soon	O
gather	O
'd	O
about	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
getting	O
up	O
they	O
clear	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Ring	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
have	O
room	O
to	O
fight	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
my	O
saying	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
Fletcher	O
,	O
Chairman	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Partner	O
were	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Five	O
Bells	O
to	O
fetch	O
Esquire	O
Northmore	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
several	O
of	O
us	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
over-ran	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Partner	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Chairman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
both	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
grapple	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
drawn	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
under	O
a	O
Gate	O
till	O
the	O
Pursuers	O
past	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
turning	O
back	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
wiping	O
his	O
Hands	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
3	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
saw	O
your	O
Hand	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Coming	O
along	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
a-fighting	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
fought	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
8	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Creamer	O
lost	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
lost	O
their	O
Hats	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
Harry	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
here	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
Day	O
that	O
he	O
Knew	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
.	O
Warner	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Fishmongers	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
Character	O
formerly	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
late	O
he	O
has	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
common	O
Pick-pockets	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
make	O
a	O
pass	O
at	O
several	O
Gentlemens	O
Pockets	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Crotchet	O
,	O
Fishmonger	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
He	O
lived	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
with	O
me	O
(	O
3	O
Years	O
ago	O
)	O
and	O
before	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
5	O
Years	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Weston	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Fishmonger	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Bell-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
Journeyman	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
no	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
then	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
little	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
of	O
late	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
18.	O
Rose	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Guineas	O
and	O
33s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
June	O
7	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
36s	O
.	O
and	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Edging	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
White	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
red	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Oak	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
May	O
15	O
.	O
John	O
Doe	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
robb	O
'd	O
no	O
of	O
26	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Money	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
the	O
Keys	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
a-bed	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
J.	O
D.	O
My	O
Eye-sight	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
good	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Bed	O
side	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
slipt	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
besides	O
,	O
nobody	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
nobody	O
else	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
ran	O
away	O
next	O
Day	O
*	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Money	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
afterwards	O
;	O
for	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
upon	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
Lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
50	O
Guineas	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
24	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
33	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
*	O
Probably	O
he	O
meant	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
:	O
The	O
Fact	O
(	O
as	O
appears	O
by	O
her	O
Confession	O
)	O
being	O
done	O
about	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
Chappel-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
12	O
Guineas	O
,	O
2	O
half	O
Guinea	O
3s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Groat	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
Master	O
of	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
again	O
there	O
.	O
Her	O
Confession	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
.	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Clerk	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
therein	O
owns	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
one	O
a	O
Clock	O
on	O
Friday	O
Night	O
[	O
Morning	O
]	O
she	O
stole	O
24	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
John	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
She	O
had	O
bought	O
herself	O
some	O
new	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
that	O
she	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
.	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
Master	O
Doe	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
some	O
Cambrick	O
and	O
Edging	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Edging	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Muslin	O
Hood	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
my	O
Sister	O
's	O
(	O
Mary	B-pers
Oaks	I-pers
)	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
likewife	O
taken	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
mine	O
)	O
and	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hulm	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Chandler	B-pers
Woman	I-pers
in	O
my	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Oaks	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
3	O
Months	O
in	O
my	O
Sister	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
discharged	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
made	O
the	O
Confession	O
my	O
Sister	O
has	O
sworn	O
to	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hulm	I-pers
.	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
plain-work	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
she	O
had	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
one	O
Suit	O
for	O
making	O
another	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Box	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Green	O
Grocer	O
's	O
Cellar	O
in	O
St.	O
Alban	O
's	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Box	O
was	O
setch	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Edging	O
,	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Muslin	O
Hood	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
And	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
19.	O
William	B-pers
Sidwell	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Edward	I-pers
Woodnot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Angel-Court	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
Edward	B-pers
Woodnot	I-pers
,	O
May	O
11	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Woodnot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Angel-Court	O
,	O
by	O
Story	O
's	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
to	O
a	O
neighbouring	O
Distiller	O
's	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
Steps	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Key	O
into	O
the	O
Lock	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
I	O
felt	O
somebody	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
fearing	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
Rogue	O
who	O
intended	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
suddenly	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
an	O
Offer	O
to	O
strike	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
would	O
have	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
aware	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
partly	O
shunn	O
'd	O
the	O
Force	O
of	O
the	O
Blow	O
.	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Cloak	O
and	O
tore	O
the	O
String	O
(	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
String	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
torn	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
10	O
hard	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
choak	O
'd	O
)	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
still	O
pull	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
crying	O
out	O
had	O
alarm	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulling	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
before	O
Williams	O
could	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
presently	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
the	O
Cloak	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
E.W	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Moon-light	O
,	O
and	O
besides	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Westminster	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
-	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
;	O
not	O
the	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
who	O
came	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
a	O
Chairman	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
fir	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hilliard	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Which	O
side	O
of	O
your	O
Cloak	O
did	O
I	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
?	O
Did	O
I	O
Discharge	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
was	O
elevated	O
.	O
E.W	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hilliard	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
in	O
Angel-Court	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
Chairmen	O
who	O
had	O
stopt	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Woodnot	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
[	O
and	O
others	O
]	O
surrounded	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
why	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
secure	O
him	O
?	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
wait	O
upon	O
their	O
Matter	O
(	O
Mistress	O
)	O
but	O
they	O
hop	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
attended	O
by	O
several	O
others	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
struggled	O
hard	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
Success	O
,	O
the	O
People	O
pressing	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
me	O
now	O
in	O
your	O
power	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
let	O
me	O
be	O
stifled	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
liberty	O
to	O
breathe	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
By	O
all	O
means	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Crowd	O
making	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
still	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
to	O
his	O
Pocket	O
or	O
Bosom	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
People	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Have	O
a	O
Care	O
!	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Pistol	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Pistol	O
presented	O
at	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
surprise	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
whether	O
't	O
was	O
he	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
who	O
held	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Pistol	O
was	O
immediately	O
fir	O
'd	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
no	O
Mischief	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
assisting	O
we	O
tyed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
See	O
here	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
Lame	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
!	O
how	O
can	O
a	O
lame	O
Man	O
fire	O
a	O
Pistol	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
My	O
House	O
is	O
next	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
,	O
Murder	O
!	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
disengaging	O
himself	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
he	O
too	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
a	O
Chairman	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
lock	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
I	O
'd	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Court	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Hilliard	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
bringing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
innocent	O
lame	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
did	O
an	O
ill	O
Thing	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
struggle	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hop	O
'd	O
we	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
Breath	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
setting	O
his	O
Back	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
downward	O
to	O
his	O
Pocket	O
or	O
Bosom	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
and	O
fire	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Hilliard	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wrenched	O
the	O
Pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
bound	O
him	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
loose	O
Gun-powder	O
in	O
every	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
one	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Cartridges	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
pimple	O
Stones	O
(	O
Pebbles	O
)	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
were	O
to	O
serve	O
for	O
Bullets	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
by	O
main	O
Strength	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
walk	O
one	O
step	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
for	O
better	O
Security	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
from	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
damn	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
stick	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Guts	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Where	O
are	O
those	O
Pebble-Stones	O
?	O
J.	O
W	O
..	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
thrown	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
the	O
Cartridges	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
loose	O
Powder	O
.	O
Morris	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Chairman	O
.	O
Our	O
Chair	O
stands	O
at	O
Angel-Court	O
End	O
,	O
by	O
Story	O
's	O
Steps	O
.	O
We	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
running	O
and	O
crying	O
stop	O
Thief	O
too	O
;	O
my	O
Partner	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
deliver	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hilliard	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
Lady	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
the	O
String	O
is	O
broke	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
Cloak	O
off	O
?	O
M.W	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
I.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
Cloak	O
off	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Woodnot	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Chairman	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
crying	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
running	O
down	O
like	O
mad	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
thus	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
my	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
partner	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Cloak	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
is	O
lame	O
in	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
run	O
and	O
cry	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
?	O
J.	O
W.	O
ha	O
!	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Cloak	O
of	O
o	O
'	O
your	O
Back	O
?	O
J.W	O
.	O
My	O
Back	O
?	O
That	O
's	O
another	O
wise	O
Question	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
me	O
was	O
the	O
Cloak	O
f	O
?	O
J.W	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Yard	O
.	O
R	O
Blunt	O
,	O
Constable	O
Upon	O
searching	O
we	O
seen	O
Powder	O
in	O
every	O
ready	O
made	O
little	O
Pebble	O
stones	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
threw	O
you	O
Mr.	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
you	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
of	O
Then	O
he	O
threw	O
himself	O
into	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Body	O
in	O
such	O
odd	O
would	O
pise	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
these	O
20	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
transported	O
about	O
14	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
cutting	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Wig	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Sadwell	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
from	O
Francis	B-pers
Negoes	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
1719	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
in	O
Pall-Mall	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cut	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
Capitally	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
Repriev	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
for	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
his	O
Tryal	O
in	O
the	O
SESSIONS-PAPER	O
for	O
October	O
1719	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Pistol	O
and	O
Powder	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
Cook	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
New-England	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
another	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
Captain	O
invited	O
the	O
other	O
Captain	O
on	O
board	O
our	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Captain	O
brought	O
his	O
Cook	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Cook	O
was	O
more	O
expert	O
than	O
I	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
Stories	O
and	O
singing	O
a	O
Song	O
,	O
and	O
besides	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
dance	O
,	O
and	O
tumble	O
,	O
and	O
play	O
twenty	O
Tricks	O
to	O
make	O
Diversion	O
;	O
and	O
your	O
Captains	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
loe	O
to	O
have	O
their	O
Frolicks	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
at	O
Sea	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
this	O
Captain	O
set	O
great	O
Store	O
by	O
this	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Cook	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
liking	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
he	O
,	O
Let	O
's	O
take	O
some	O
Cartridges	O
of	O
Powder	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
Wildfire	O
to	O
run	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Glory	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
are	O
come	O
safe	O
to	O
old	O
England	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
Powder	O
,	O
sweet	O
Jesus	O
Almighty	O
knows	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Pistol	O
,	O
this	O
Cook	O
was	O
an	O
,	O
Flannovernia	O
and	O
a	O
loyal	O
Soul	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
drunk	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
King	O
George	O
's	O
Health	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
every	O
Glass	O
we	O
fir	O
'd	O
off	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
honour	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Family	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Lord	O
above	O
knows	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
whole	O
truth	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
Pistol	O
on	O
no	O
other	O
Account	O
than	O
to	O
shew	O
my	O
Loyalty	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Day	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
too	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
Ship	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
At	O
Limehouse	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
Angel-Court	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
God	O
knows	O
that	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
elevated	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
give	O
a	O
particular	O
Account	O
;	O
only	O
I	O
remember	O
we	O
came	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Cook	O
row	O
'd	O
us	O
a-shore	O
with	O
the	O
wrong	O
Ends	O
of	O
the	O
Oars	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
relations	O
that	O
liv	O
'd	O
about	O
Angel-Court	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
might	O
bear	O
him	O
Company	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
and	O
Powder	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Ball	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
seems	O
you	O
had	O
small	O
Pebbles	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Pebbles	O
?	O
Why	O
I	O
remember	O
we	O
were	O
heaving	O
Ballast	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cook	O
and	O
I	O
threw	O
many	O
a	O
Shovelful	O
of	O
Ballast	O
at	O
one	O
another	O
for	O
Sport	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
suppose	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
got	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Captains	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
happens	O
that	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
are	O
here	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
innocent	O
lame	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
further	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
20.	O
Henry	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
June	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
halt	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Aaron	B-pers
Newbolt	I-pers
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
A	O
Newbolt+	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Society	O
of	O
London	O
Scholars	O
(	O
Bell-Ringers	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Lion	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Michael's-Alley	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
till	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
and	O
a	O
Weaver	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
we	O
parted	O
at	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
down	O
Hounditch	O
.	O
My	O
Business	O
requiring	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
up	O
at	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seeing	O
a	O
Light	O
at	O
the	O
George	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
to	O
fit	O
up	O
there	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
for	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
sung	O
a	O
Song	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
and	O
Woman	O
were	O
sitting	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
my	O
reckoning	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
Charish	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
2	O
Tankards	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
paid	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
my	O
sha	O
e	O
came	O
to	O
;	O
they	O
saw	O
which	O
Pocket	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Money	O
into	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
my	O
Watch	O
too	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
lost	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
stood	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
wrist	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Money	O
chink	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
shifted	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
who	O
stood	O
close	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hands	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
went	O
off	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
6s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
some	O
Copper	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
Poulterer	O
,	O
who	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
walk	O
'd	O
100	O
Miles	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
in	O
27	O
Hours	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
George	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
?	O
A.	O
N.	O
With	O
neither	O
,	O
!	O
went	O
in	O
alone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
me	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
that	O
you	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
?	O
That	O
's	O
your	O
own	O
Opposal	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
not	O
worth	O
my	O
Argument	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
Husband	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
virtuous	O
Man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
say	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
Oath	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
no	O
Woman	O
but	O
alone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
sing	O
'd	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Song	O
to	O
please	O
Ladies	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
us	O
and	O
sing	O
'd	O
another	O
Song	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
paid	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and.	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
Jack-Aks	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
no	O
Body	O
could	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
stumbled	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
22.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
27	O
Yards	O
of	O
superfine	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
May	O
23	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Cloth	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Three-Kings	B-place
on	I-place
Ludgate-Hill	I-place
)	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
heard	O
that	O
5	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
was	O
at	O
Samuel	B-pers
Laurenson	I-pers
's	O
(	O
a	O
Scourer	O
)	O
Laurenson	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Michael	B-pers
Elston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elston	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Tom	B-pers
Kempson	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kempson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
at	O
Dson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
Ludgate	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
agreed	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Tommy	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Coast	O
was	O
clear	O
;	O
upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
Watch-word	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Cloth	O
on	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wincox	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
leave	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Sheeppens	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
watch	O
'd	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Elston	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bid	O
us	O
leave	O
it	O
till	O
Morning	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
in	O
several	O
Pieces	O
.	O
Her	O
Husband	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
15	O
or	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Yard	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
2	O
Guineas	O
cown	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
divided	O
equally	O
betwixt	O
us	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
several	O
time	O
,	O
afterwards	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
s.	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
15	O
or	O
16s	O
for	O
the	O
Remainder	O
of	O
my	O
Share	O
.	O
Sam	B-pers
Lawrenson	I-pers
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Elston	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
5	O
Yards	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
this	O
Cloth	O
to	O
be	O
press	O
'd	O
and	O
shrunk	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Suit	O
for	O
a	O
Customer	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
Taylor	O
by	O
Trade	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
then	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Elston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
Laurenson	O
swears	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
Cloth	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Elston	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Whitehead	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Suit	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
We	O
preferr	O
'd	O
a	O
Bill	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
against	O
Mrs.	O
Whitehead	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Elston	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
Kempson	O
?	O
Look	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
Elston	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Man	O
once	O
,	O
or	O
so	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
?	O
Elston	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
Shop	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
for	O
?	O
Elston	O
.	O
To	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
were	O
a	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
sell	O
Drams	O
too	O
?	O
Elston	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
does	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
On	O
your	O
Oath	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
bring	O
the	O
Cloth	O
to	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Elston	O
No	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Whitehead	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Prison	O
on	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Elston	O
's	O
Wife	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Mrs.	O
Whitehead	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
above	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
some	O
Cloth	O
to	O
make	O
Husband	O
a	O
Suit	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
another	O
Remnant	O
to	O
be	O
laid	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fetched	O
it	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
no	O
Money	O
for	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
only	O
my	O
Husband	O
lent	O
her	O
2	O
is	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Piece	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
Mrs.	O
Whitehead	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
street	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Kempson	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
insisted	O
up	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
Kempson	O
,	O
damn	O
Blood	O
Bed	O
,	O
you	O
through	O
the	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
go	O
And	O
so	O
-	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
5	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
which	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
impeach	O
the	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Whitehead	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wilcox	O
's	O
for	O
a	O
Farthing	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
Small	O
Beer	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Tom	B-pers
Kempson	I-pers
had	O
been	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
Roll	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Going	O
out	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Bundle	O
in	O
-street	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
you	O
'll	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Elston	O
's	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Bag	O
.	O
It	O
keeps	O
Company	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Whitehead	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
has	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
me	O
purpose	O
to	O
he	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Cox	O
came	O
alone	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
an	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
lived	O
a	O
Year	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Whitehead	O
.	O
Kempson	O
An	O
honest	O
Character	O
?	O
Its	O
false	O
.	O
He	O
hang	O
'd	O
jan.	O
Drinkwater	O
and	O
Bernard	O
Fink	O
about	O
2	O
3	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
They	O
were	O
convicted	O
Partridge	O
's	O
Evidence	O
of	O
robbing	O
Amy	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Drinkwater	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Bernard	O
Fink	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Sessions-Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
VI	O
.	O
for	O
July	O
1731	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
23.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
a	O
Pan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Millen	I-pers
May	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
Ann	B-pers
Kersey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Purse	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Sherburn	I-pers
,	O
May	O
21	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25	O
,	O
26	O
Robert	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Cecil	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Samuel	B-pers
Manfield	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
a	O
Watch	O
Key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
June	O
7	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Manfield	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Spaw	O
by	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
crossing	O
the	O
Fields	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Road	O
to	O
St.	B-place
John's-street	I-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
Barley-Mow	O
.	O
I	O
here	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
3	O
Men	O
;	O
one	O
collar	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
something	O
that	O
cut	O
me	O
into	O
'	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
.	O
They	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
one	O
Pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Cane	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
my	O
a	O
king	O
for	O
my	O
Cane	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
sooner	O
than	O
they	O
wou	O
'd	O
have	O
done	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
the	O
Drovers	O
,	O
who	O
come	O
that	O
Road	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Nights	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
afterwards	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
in	O
a	O
News-Paper	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kempson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Races	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
on	O
Sn-Hill	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Pints	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
.	O
Then	O
says	O
Tanner	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
Money	O
to	O
fetch	O
me	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
.	O
God	O
damn	O
your	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
go	O
out	O
all	O
together	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
Haymaker	O
's	O
Coat	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Barley-Mow	O
and	O
sit	O
upon	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
waited	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
(	O
about	O
the	O
Size	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
came	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Tanner	O
stood	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
;	O
and	O
Cecil	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Knife	O
,	O
struck	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
Tanner	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
said	O
we	O
had	O
used	O
him	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
his	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
return	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Haycocks	O
near	O
Hoxton	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
till	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
Tanner	O
looking	O
on	O
the	O
Hat	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
this	O
Cut	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
Cecil	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
God	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
Tanner	O
again	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
barbarous	O
?	O
We	O
not	O
thinking	O
it	O
proper	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
Cut	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Shilling	O
a-piece	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Hat	O
to	O
myself	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
Tanner	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
grey	O
Coat	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
(	O
he	O
has	O
it	O
on	O
now	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
agreed	O
to	O
meet	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
in	O
Old-street	O
Square	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Skittles	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Tanner	O
had	O
won	O
all	O
Cecil	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
[	O
Tanner	O
]	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
again	O
.	O
But	O
not	O
meeting	O
us	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Promise	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
before-hand	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
surrender	O
'd	O
myself	O
directly	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cathery	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
advertised	O
the	O
Robbery	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
.	O
I	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
Whitehead	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
Witness	O
that	O
saw	O
us	O
together	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Overy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
Kempson	O
took	O
a	O
Walk	O
on	O
Thursday	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Hampstead	O
Horse-races	O
.	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Heath	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Turn	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Men	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Glimpse	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
for	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
S	O
Law	O
Mrs.	O
Whitehead	O
,	O
who	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
's	O
in	O
Brick-lane	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
Kempson	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
Kempson	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
wants	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
so	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
Because	O
(	O
I	O
said	O
)	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Races	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
Kempson	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
walk	O
.	O
But	O
at	O
last	O
Kempson	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Sister	O
's	O
Husband	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Races	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
about	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
they	O
began	O
some	O
Discourse	O
about	O
a	O
Robbery	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Skickle	O
and	O
I	O
walking	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Secret	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
very	O
odd	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
should	O
give	O
such	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
himself	O
to	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
But	O
you	O
made	O
no	O
Discovery	O
of	O
this	O
Secret	O
.	O
Overy	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
But	O
Kempson	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Whitehead	O
assisted	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cathery	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
Kempson	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
by	O
the	O
Barley-Mow	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Came	O
a	O
Watch-Key	O
,	O
and	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
Tanner	O
in	O
Cow-lane	O
,	O
and	O
Cecil	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
that	O
Whitehead	O
kept	O
to	O
harbour	O
Thieves	O
.	O
Whitehead	O
had	O
other	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Brick-lane	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Use	O
.	O
This	O
Hat	O
and	O
Watch	O
Key	O
were	O
given	O
by	O
Whitehead	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Hat	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Watch-Key	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
broke	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
the	O
Street-Robbers	O
with	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Cecil	O
.	O
Kempson	O
met	O
me	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
Whitehead	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
called	O
a	O
considerable	O
Number	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
(	O
who	O
made	O
a	O
good	O
Appearance	O
)	O
in	O
their	O
Behalf	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
the	O
Characters	O
of	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
,	O
young	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
27.	O
Dubartus	B-pers
Stiff	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
by	O
maticiously	O
giving	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
5	O
Inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
for	O
killing	O
John	O
Scot	O
in	O
the	O
Fury	O
of	O
his	O
Mind	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
Weapon	O
drawn	O
,	O
nor	O
having	O
first	O
struck	O
the	O
said	O
Dubartus	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stockdon	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Whitsun	O
Monday	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Piccadilly	B-place
,	O
by	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Sunderland	O
's	O
Wall	O
;	O
three	O
Men	O
of	O
our	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dupny	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
walking	O
just	O
before	O
us	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
past	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
leaning	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
Make	O
haste	O
home	O
,	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
or	O
your	O
Master	O
will	O
be	O
angry	O
,	O
and	O
wo	O
n't	O
give	O
you	O
another	O
Holiday	O
to	O
Morrow	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
answered	O
,	O
Suppose	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
then	O
?	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
and	O
not	O
mind	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
As	O
I	O
affront	O
nobody	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
take	O
an	O
Affront	O
from	O
anybody	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
revenge	O
my	O
own	O
Cause	O
.	O
This	O
occasioned	O
more	O
Words	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
still	O
urged	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
no	O
Hurt	O
.	O
By	O
this	O
Time	O
our	O
three	O
Friends	O
were	O
gone	O
a	O
pretty	O
Way	O
forward	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
prevent	O
Mischief	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Austin	O
cry	O
'd	O
Hoy	O
!	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cry	O
'd	O
Hoy	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Honesty	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
alone	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
Company	O
.	O
Our	O
Company	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
affronted	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
resented	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
some	O
angry	O
Words	O
past	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
Porter	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
were	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Porter	O
fell	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
Porter	O
staid	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Deceased	O
called	O
to	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Jemmy	O
,	O
Jemmy	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
stabb	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Man	O
has	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
name	O
what	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
nearest	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
our	O
Acquaintance	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
;	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
Stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pursued	O
him	O
down	O
Duke-street	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
Shop	O
just	O
by	O
;	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
young	O
Man	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Croud	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
lived	O
but	O
21	O
Hours	O
afterwards	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Cook	O
(	O
and	O
some	O
Relation	O
)	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
at	O
the	O
Gloucester-Head	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Pall-Mall	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
?	O
S.	O
S.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Or	O
strike	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
?	O
S.	O
S.	O
Yes	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Blow	O
given	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
struck	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
it	O
began	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
On	O
which	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
did	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
begin	O
?	O
S.	O
The	O
same	O
side	O
as	O
my	O
Lord	O
Sunderland	O
's	O
is	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
?	O
S.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
quite	O
dark	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
well	O
enough	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dupny	I-pers
.	O
We	O
were	O
100	O
Yards	O
before	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
when	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Hoy	O
!	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
a	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
Company	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
back	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
(	O
whose	O
Name	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
)	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
both	O
be	O
a	O
one	O
Man	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
will	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
too	O
,	O
you	O
Dog	O
.	O
And	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
Porter	O
on	O
the	O
Nose	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
bleed	O
;	O
they	O
closed	O
;	O
Porter	O
flung	O
him	O
and	O
fell	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Brown	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
were	O
at	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
Brown	O
went	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
.	O
When	O
Porter	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
Porter	O
looked	O
about	O
for	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
before	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Jemmy	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
stab	O
'd	O
!	O
I	O
'm	O
stuck	O
!	O
I	O
'm	O
dead	O
Man	O
!	O
We	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
within	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
fronting	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Man	O
has	O
Stab	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stockton	I-pers
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Stop	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
Brown	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
Stab	O
'd	O
?	O
S.D	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
for	O
before	O
he	O
said	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Brown	O
a	O
hundred	O
Yards	O
off	O
-	O
We	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
a	O
Chairman	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Rogue	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Lad	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
served	O
you	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
your	O
Lodging	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Answer	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
the	O
Knife	O
-	O
Lock	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
J.	O
Porter	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
at	O
Sunderland-Gate	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
as	O
far	O
before	O
him	O
as	O
the	O
Plumber	O
's	O
against	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Church	O
when	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Hoy	O
!	O
A	O
Boy	O
told	O
us	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
stept	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
Sure	O
you	O
two	O
wo	O
n't	O
beat	O
one	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
too	O
,	O
ye	B-pers
Dog	I-pers
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
my	O
Nose	O
a	O
bleeding	O
.	O
We	O
fought	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
myself	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
which	O
Way	O
he	O
went	O
-	O
The	O
Deceased	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Jemmy	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Stab	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
facing	O
the	O
Deceased	O
as	O
far	O
from	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
Rogue	O
has	O
kill	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
came	O
so	O
near	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Push	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
brush	O
'd	O
my	O
Coat	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
his	O
Knife	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
could	O
ha	O
ve	O
closed	O
him	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
kept	O
on	O
pursuing	O
and	O
crying	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
having	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Depositions	O
of	O
Dupuy	O
and	O
Porter	O
,	O
proceeded	O
thus	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
push	O
twice	O
at	O
Porter	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
once	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
in	O
Duke-Street	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
?	O
E.	O
A	O
Yes	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
Moon-light	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Knife	O
?	O
E.	O
A	O
A	O
Penknife	O
with	O
a	O
pretty	O
broad	O
Handle	O
[	O
blade	O
]	O
broader	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
usually	O
seen	O
a	O
Penknife	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
the	O
Deceased	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
Stab	O
'd	O
?	O
E.	O
A	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
Yards	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
's	O
Hat	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Deceased	O
point	O
to	O
any	O
Body	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
Man	O
?	O
E.	O
A	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
meant	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
begun	O
to	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
Brown	O
was	O
then	O
standing	O
near	O
the	O
Centry-box	O
by	O
the	O
dead	O
Wall	O
on	O
t'other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Coker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Duke-Street	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
towards	O
German-Street	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
not	O
till	O
the	O
Company	O
comes	O
up	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
about	O
20	O
Yards	O
off	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
some	O
Body	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
Stuck	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
where	O
's	O
the	O
Knife	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
thrown	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
And	O
another	O
said	O
,	O
Why	O
was	O
you	O
such	O
a	O
Villain	O
to	O
Sab	O
him	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
off	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
go	O
which	O
Way	O
I	O
would	O
they	O
were	O
after	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Malice	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
Eyes	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
killed	O
him	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
suffer	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
There	O
must	O
be	O
Blood	O
for	O
Blood	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Steven	O
's	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
had	O
two	O
Wounds	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
Stab	O
about	O
two	O
Inches	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
cut	O
up	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Inches	O
in	O
drawing	O
the	O
Knife	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Grissel	O
between	O
the	O
Ribs	O
was	O
divided	O
in	O
two	O
Places	O
,	O
the	O
Caul	O
hung	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Guts	O
,	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
my	O
Fist	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
I	O
reduced	O
them	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Hick-up	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
concluded	O
that	O
his	O
Stomach	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
certainly	O
die	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
struck	O
first	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
,	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
was	O
very	O
sudden	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
strike	O
first	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
opening	O
him	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lower	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
Liver	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Knife	O
had	O
past	O
into	O
the	O
Cavity	O
of	O
the	O
Stomach	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Master	O
is	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
against	O
my	O
Lord	O
Sunderland	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
running	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Way	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
foremost	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
I	O
suppose	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
Coat	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
foremost	O
turn	O
short	O
and	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
the	O
Side	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Knife	O
:	O
The	O
Deceased	O
presently	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Jemmy	O
,	O
Jemmy	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Stuck	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stockton	I-pers
came	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Deceased	O
into	O
our	O
Shop	O
;	O
a	O
Puddle	O
of	O
Blood	O
ran	O
from	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
led	O
him	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
home	O
this	O
broad	O
Clasp-penknife	O
;	O
but	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
or	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
nor	O
would	O
the	O
Deceased	O
own	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
bloody	O
.	O
Mr.Powell	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
and	O
Nephew	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
abou	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
himf	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
my	O
Uncle	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
should	O
die	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
Yes	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Aggressor	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
before	O
that	O
Night	O
he	O
Stab	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
engaged	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
I	O
neither	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
he	O
me	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
received	O
these	O
two	O
Wounds	O
.	O
-	O
Here	O
is	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
his	O
Shirt	O
.	O
These	O
long	O
Cuts	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
were	O
made	O
when	O
he	O
received	O
those	O
Wounds	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
Holiday	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
So	O
,	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
make	O
haste	O
home	O
,	O
or	O
your	O
Master	O
wo	O
n't	O
let	O
you	O
have	O
another	O
Holiday	O
.	O
Sirrah	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Master	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
hip	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Company	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
this	O
thing	O
it	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Blows	O
and	O
Bruise	O
I	O
received	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
disordered	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
sensible	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Fox	O
swears	O
that	O
one	O
like	O
you	O
ran	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
pursued	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
short	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
He	O
perhaps	O
may	O
tell	O
whereabout	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Blow	O
(	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
do	O
so	O
)	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Fox	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
this	O
hither	O
Side	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Kennel	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dobney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
13	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Joyner	O
and	O
Carpenter	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
civil	O
,	O
honest	O
,	O
good-natured	O
,	O
careful	O
young	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
overagainst	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
happened	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
Sea	O
.	O
)	O
Brown	O
returned	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
very	O
much	O
beaten	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
Clothes	O
torn	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
sent	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
)	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
hear	O
what	O
Porter	O
would	O
say	O
;	O
and	O
Porter	O
said	O
thus	O
:	O
When	O
the	O
Deceased	O
hip	O
'd	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
These	O
Fellows	O
are	O
a	O
going	O
to	O
lick	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
sure	O
,	O
not	O
two	O
to	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
which	O
struck	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
kick	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
must	O
he	O
broke	O
;	O
for	O
you	O
might	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
Sound	O
of	O
the	O
Fall	O
20	O
Yards	O
off	O
.	O
Now	O
I	O
query	O
,	O
whether	O
a	O
Person	O
after	O
such	O
a	O
Fall	O
could	O
have	O
the	O
proper	O
Use	O
of	O
his	O
Senses	O
.	O
Susan	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
whitish	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
without	O
Hat	O
or	O
Wig	O
,	O
run	O
down	O
Duke-Street	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
Four	O
to	O
one	O
!	O
and	O
three	O
Men	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
His	O
running	O
down	O
Duke-Street	O
was	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
wounded	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
industrious	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
nor	O
heard	O
him	O
swear	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
any	O
Riot	O
or	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
Seven	O
or	O
eight	O
more	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pint-mug	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
June	O
27	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29.	O
William	B-pers
Chickley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
dead	O
Fowls	O
and	O
a	O
Chicken	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mackrel	I-pers
,	O
June	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30	O
,	O
31.	O
Edward	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gamball	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
May	O
3	O
.	O
R.	O
Haydon	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
lost	O
more	O
large	O
leaden	O
Pipes	O
and	O
brass	O
Cocks	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Ditch-side	O
,	O
than	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
l.	O
will	O
make	O
good	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Harry	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
stole	O
these	O
Pipes	O
and	O
Cocks	O
about	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Whitsunday	O
Morning	O
.	O
Fish	O
put	O
us	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
tell	O
us	O
of	O
a	O
rare	O
Chance	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
one	O
Parcel	O
till	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Will	O
.	O
Green	O
,	O
in	O
Stanhope-Street	O
,	O
Clare-Market	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
for	O
19	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
He	O
called	O
us	O
good	O
Boys	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
take	O
Care	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
about	O
Eleven	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
as	O
much	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Dunghill	O
by	O
the	O
Ditch-side	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
a	O
Boy	O
who	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Brown-low-Street	O
with	O
some	O
Lead	O
we	O
had	O
stole	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Green	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
here	O
about	O
7	O
Months	O
ago	O
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
It	O
was	O
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
and	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
See	O
his	O
Trial	O
in	O
the	O
SESSIONS-PAPER	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
1.	O
page	O
13	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
stained	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Barwell	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
13	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
Grays-Inn-Walks	B-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Outcry	O
of	O
several	O
that	O
had	O
their	O
Pockets	O
pick	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
I	O
there	O
missed	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
step	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Door-keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Walks	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
any	O
suspicious	O
Persons	O
loitering	O
about	O
there	O
:	O
A	O
Boy	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
pick	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
Passage	O
by	O
the	O
Bookseller	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
down	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
what	O
d	O
'ye	O
mean	O
?	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
many	O
Protestations	O
of	O
his	O
Innocence	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
Pick-pocket	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
only	O
retain	O
'd	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Day	O
to	O
attend	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
what	O
they	O
stole	O
.	O
Rich	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
Father	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kneel	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Christ	O
to	O
witness	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
pick	O
'd	O
a	O
Pocket	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
my	O
Father	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
thoroughly	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
it	O
's	O
your	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
expect	O
no	O
Mercy	O
.	O
Holt	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
;	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
allow	O
'd	O
him	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
for	O
receiving	O
Handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
a	O
silver	O
Dish	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Crispin	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
33.	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Paul	O
Crispin	O
.	O
What	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
tha	O
ith	O
thith	O
,	O
I	O
lotht	O
a	O
thilver	O
Dith	O
belonging	O
to	O
Brigadier	O
Churchill	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Grate	O
in	O
Compton-Thtreet	B-place
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Greek-Thtreet	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
when	O
,	O
becauth	O
it	O
ish	O
impothible	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
mitht	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
wath	O
called	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Thilver-Thmith	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dith	O
wath	O
left	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Cover	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
Baker	O
wath	O
taken	O
Prithoner	O
,	O
he	O
akth	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wath	O
not	O
rob	O
'd	O
of	O
thuch	O
a	O
Dith	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thaid	O
,	O
Yeth	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
Aleck	O
Watson	O
and	O
Jemmy	O
Maddox	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
silver	O
Dish	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Window	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
We	O
raised	O
up	O
the	O
Grate	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
Stick	O
under	O
it	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
from	O
pinching	O
our	O
Fingers	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
drew	O
the	O
Dish	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Walker	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
in	O
Cross-Lane	O
,	O
near	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
kept	O
it	O
for	O
us	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
Watson	O
,	O
and	O
Mattox	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Dish	O
to	O
James	O
[	O
William	O
]	O
Howard	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
Mattox	O
went	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Ship	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
me	O
out	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
six	O
Guineas	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rodes	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Goat	O
and	O
Leak	O
in	O
White-horse-Alley	O
.	O
Howard	O
Where	O
did	O
we	O
go	O
first	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
To	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
Backside	O
of	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
ran	O
up	O
a	O
Score	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
-	O
[	O
Sessions	O
house	O
]	O
Gate	O
,	O
leaning	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
bought	O
half	O
a	O
Goos	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Rodes	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
stay	O
'd	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
Cherry-Beer	O
and	O
Brandy	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
and	O
Mattox	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
six	O
Guineas	O
more	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
Coach	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Walker	O
's	O
in	O
Cross-Lane	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
trusted	O
us	O
with	O
Liquor	O
till	O
the	O
Dish	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bought	O
two	O
Fowls	O
and	O
Bacon	O
for	O
us	O
:	O
There	O
we	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
we	O
three	O
had	O
two	O
Guineas	O
a-piece	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
about	O
6	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
odd	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
it	O
we	O
spent	O
in	O
eating	O
the	O
Goose	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
thing	O
or	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
and	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
left	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
Mrs.	O
Walker	O
.	O
Watson	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
together	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
bought	O
some	O
new	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
about	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
,	O
and	O
Tom	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
sent	O
a	O
Letter	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
be	O
before-hand	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
surrender	O
'd	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
my	O
Information	O
against	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
At	O
Buck	O
's	O
Brandy	O
shop	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Walker	O
's	O
in	O
Cross-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
six	O
at	O
Night	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
thieing	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
the	O
Dish	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
help	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Grate	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
Who	O
carried	O
the	O
Dish	O
to	O
Walker	O
's	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
first	O
to	O
Mattox	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
Arm	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Howard	O
with	O
the	O
Dish	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Walker	O
lent	O
him	O
her	O
Apron	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
thought	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
hisfs	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
a	O
Bag	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
.	O
Howard	B-pers
Was	I-pers
you	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
?	O
Baker	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
C	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Gen	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Horn	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
and	O
Mattox	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Dish	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Watson	O
,	O
and	O
Walker	O
,	O
stay	O
'd	O
there	O
till	O
you	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
brought	O
us	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Stay	O
'd	O
where	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
Clerkenwell-Green	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
you	O
swore	O
just	O
now	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
stood	O
leaning	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
at	O
the	O
Old-Bailey-Gate	O
,	O
Gate	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
that	O
you	O
went	O
thence	O
to	O
Rode	O
's	O
and	O
eat	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Goose	O
:	O
that	O
you	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
waited	O
till	O
they	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
Baker	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
stay	O
'd	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
because	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
Money	O
to	O
discharge	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
till	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Rodes	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
Rodes	O
's	O
they	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
swore	O
you	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
stood	O
watching	O
till	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
gave	O
this	O
Reason	O
for	O
your	O
watching	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
afraid	O
they	O
would	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
And	O
now	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
but	O
stay	O
'd	O
at	O
Clerkenwell-Green	O
till	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
give	O
a	O
Reason	O
for	O
that	O
too	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
Mattox	O
,	O
Watson	O
and	O
Baker	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
together	O
towards	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Mattox	O
had	O
a	O
deep	O
silver	O
Dish	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Baker	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Dish	O
.	O
Walker	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
run	O
up	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
s.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
they	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
but	O
to	O
tag	O
after	O
their	O
Tails	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
and	O
not	O
well	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
a	O
Coach	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
drove	O
to	O
the	O
Horn	O
at	O
Clerkenwell-Green	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
discharge	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
paid	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Mattox	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
his	O
Name	O
is	O
Howard	O
)	O
who	O
drank	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
and	O
Mattox	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
Mattox	O
chang	O
'd	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
four	O
Pints	O
of	O
Ale	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
had	O
.	O
They	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
Eating	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Goose	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Dish	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
C.	O
Walker	O
.	O
Some	O
Hours	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Night	O
?	O
