TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	O
BILLERS	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1734	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILFORD	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Chapter-House	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXIV	O
.	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BILLERS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Soan	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Skip	I-pers
,	O
Josias	B-pers
Ragdell	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Falkner	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ferris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Alford	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Gwillim	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burret	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Eager	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Dukes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Atley	I-pers
,	O
Luke	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Letherington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
14	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linen	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
August	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
2.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Nicoragna	O
Wood	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Lang	I-pers
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
3.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Lamp-Oil	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Catlin	I-pers
,	O
August	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
4.	O
Mary	B-pers
Eager	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Essex	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Left-thigh	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Groin	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
4	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
August	O
30	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Mealing	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
was	O
seven-night	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
about	O
8	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
eating	O
a	O
Pear	O
;	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Liquor	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
a	O
Pear	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
stood	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
Andrews	O
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
his	O
Seat	O
at	O
work	O
-	O
he	O
makes	O
Leather-Clogs	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
a	O
Kiss	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
he	O
flew	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
I	O
'm	O
stabb	O
'd	O
!	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Loin	O
of	O
Mutton	O
in	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
Thigh	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Knife	O
drop	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
side	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
's	O
Seat	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
bloody	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Quarrel	O
betwixt	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
one	O
Word	O
of	O
Anger	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
offer	O
any	O
Rudeness	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
only	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
kiss	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
kiss	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
kiss	O
'd	O
her	O
before	O
when	O
she	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Stand	O
aside	O
if	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
quiet	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
been	O
playing	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
behind	O
my	O
Right-hand	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
cry	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
stabb	O
'd	O
!	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Blood	O
run	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
has	O
thrown	O
it	O
on	O
your	O
Seat	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
bloody	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
us	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
my	O
work	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
upon	O
my	O
Seat	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
hear	O
any	O
Words	O
pass	O
betwixt	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gassen	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
were	O
sitting	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bob	O
'd	O
the	O
Rump	O
of	O
a	O
Loin	O
of	O
Mutton	O
against	O
her	O
Apron	O
and	O
her	O
Breast	O
.	O
They	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
three	O
Minutes	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Lord	O
she	O
has	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
!	O
He	O
had	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
her	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
any	O
Rudeness	O
,	O
nor	O
were	O
there	O
any	O
Words	O
between	O
them	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
kiss	O
'd	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Anger	O
,	O
nor	O
struggling	O
upon	O
that	O
Account	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
liked	O
it	O
well	O
enough	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
his	O
Uncle	O
Mealing	O
,	O
O	O
Uncle	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Knife	O
bloody	O
on	O
Andrews	O
's	O
Seat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kersey	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
The	O
Wound	O
enter	O
'd	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
below	O
the	O
Groin	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
crural	O
Artery	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
Mortal	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lost	O
so	O
much	O
Blood	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Was	O
it	O
not	O
barbarous	O
to	O
stab	O
the	O
Man	O
thus	O
?	O
And	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
Tho	O
'	O
I	O
did	O
stab	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
in	O
jest	O
.	O
I	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
You	O
will	O
not	O
much	O
care	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
your	O
Jest	O
.	O
Who	O
heard	O
me	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
Says	O
she	O
.	O
Why	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
you	O
impudent	O
Jade	O
,	O
says	O
I.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
Women	O
like	O
her	O
self	O
used	O
to	O
resort	O
to	O
Hornsey-Lane	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
eating	O
a	O
Pear	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
They	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Gin	O
and	O
Anniseed	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Knife	O
to	O
pate	O
a	O
Pear	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
bob	O
'd	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Rump	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
under	O
my	O
Coats	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
push	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
how	O
he	O
run	O
against	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
'till	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
Meally	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
then	O
no	O
Pear	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
.	O
Three	O
or	O
Four	O
Women	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
Fruit	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
industrious	O
quiet	O
peaceable	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
inclin	O
'd	O
to	O
passion	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
in	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
Justice	O
-	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
most	O
infamous	O
Character	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Companions	O
are	O
the	O
common	O
Pest	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
several	O
Informations	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
make	O
it	O
their	O
common	O
practice	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
Highgate-lane	O
,	O
and	O
expose	O
their	O
Bodies	O
to	O
all	O
comers	O
for	O
a	O
Penny	O
or	O
Two-pence	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
They	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
George	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Croft	I-pers
,	O
by	O
forcing	O
a	O
Horse	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
rode	O
to	O
run	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
Horse	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
Feet	O
kick	O
'd	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
gave	O
her	O
several	O
mortal	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
she	O
languish	O
'd	O
till	O
the	O
8th	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Corder	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
riding	O
over	O
Fulham-bridge	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
up	O
Bear-street	B-place
,	I-place
which	I-place
is	I-place
the	I-place
High-street	I-place
in	I-place
Fulham	I-place
.	O
He	O
rid	O
a	O
full	O
Gallop	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
his	O
Horse	O
could	O
well	O
go	O
.	O
In	O
turning	O
the	O
Corner	O
going	O
into	O
Bear-street	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
rid	O
over	O
a	O
Maid	O
who	O
was	O
leading	O
two	O
Children	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Children	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
the	O
Horse	O
kick	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
or	O
no	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
falling	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
whipt	O
his	O
Horse	O
forward	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Arm	O
Door	O
which	O
faces	O
Bear-street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
Horse	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Corder	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
whip	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
After	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Corner	O
by	O
the	O
Church-bridge	O
,	O
he	O
whipt	O
his	O
Horse	O
into	O
Bear-street	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
presently	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
came	O
a	O
great	O
pace	O
before	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Corner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
South	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
Town	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Timber	O
on	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
Riding	O
full	O
speed	O
from	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Bear	O
Street	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
Yards	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
She	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
jumpt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Track	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
wheel	O
towards	O
the	O
Posts	O
in	O
the	O
Path-way	O
,	O
ran	O
against	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Hind-Leg	O
catch	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
20	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Corner	O
turning	O
out	O
of	O
Bear-Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
200	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Church-bridge	O
-	O
My	O
Face	O
was	O
not	O
towards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Osgood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
Door	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
rid	O
up	O
Bear-Street	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
against	O
Dr.	O
Dwight	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
20	O
Yards	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Horse	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
cuts	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
Horse	O
went	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
before	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
hold	O
the	O
Horse	O
?	O
Osgood	O
.	O
With	O
his	O
left	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
softly	O
with	O
right	O
Hand	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
apprehend	O
that	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Horse	O
or	O
force	O
him	O
forward	O
?	O
Osgood	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
endeavour	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
to	O
push	O
him	O
forward	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
South	I-pers
.	O
Was	O
not	O
I	O
thrown	O
off	O
the	O
Horse	O
when	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
beat	O
down	O
?	O
South	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
Horse	O
's	O
foot	O
hitch	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
and	O
you	O
fell	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
you	O
in	O
helping	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
under	O
my	O
Gateway	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rid	O
up	O
the	O
Town	O
:	O
He	O
whipt	O
his	O
Horse	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Osgood	O
,	O
That	O
Fellow	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
knocked	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
doing	O
Mischief	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
ride	O
against	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
150	O
Yards	O
off	O
.	O
John	O
Lovejoy	O
.	O
My	O
Shop	O
's	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
between	O
the	O
Kings-Arms	O
and	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
whipt	O
his	O
Horse	O
as	O
he	O
rode	O
by	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Butcher	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
Blood	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
!	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
ride	O
so	O
hard	O
for	O
?	O
You	O
'll	O
do	O
some	O
Mischief	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
the	O
Butcher	O
.	O
You	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
ride	O
so	O
fast	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
for	O
?	O
You	O
'll	O
ride	O
over	O
Somebody	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
some	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Horse	O
run	O
rather	O
faster	O
than	O
before	O
.	O
Indeed	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
whip	O
or	O
spur	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
bore	O
upon	O
his	O
Stirrups	O
and	O
lean	O
'd	O
forward	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
that	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
pull	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Beacham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Yard	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Timber	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
about	O
10	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Accident	O
.	O
My	O
Face	O
was	O
towards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
rid	O
by	O
our	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
after	O
he	O
past	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Partner	O
,	O
Robin	B-pers
South	I-pers
,	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
come	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
Man	O
has	O
rid	O
over	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
beat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
left	O
Foot	O
hung	O
in	O
the	O
Stirrup	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Body	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
but	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
raised	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
fell	O
again	O
in	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
sake	O
Brother	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
Hand	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
Gate	O
I	O
heard	O
Somebody	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
Get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
spoke	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Horse	O
stand	O
still	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
disentangled	O
?	O
Beacham	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
run	O
down	O
Sow	O
gilders-Lane	O
.	O
-	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Accident	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
It	O
's	O
a	O
sad	O
Misfortune	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
's	O
strange	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
stop	O
your	O
Horse	O
.	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
-	O
But	O
if	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
50	O
or	O
60	O
l.	O
I	O
sha	O
n't	O
value	O
that	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hassam	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
detain	O
'd	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
.	O
He	O
struck	O
his	O
whip	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
Damn	O
it	O
,	O
here	O
I	O
am	O
detain	O
'd	O
for	O
killing	O
one	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
in	O
London	O
-	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
God	O
Damn	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
contain	O
'd	O
here	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
What	O
signifies	O
killing	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
or	O
two	O
?	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
killed	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
past	O
by	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Accident	O
.	O
In	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
Speechless	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
all	O
appearance	O
Dead	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
contused	O
Wound	O
in	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
the	O
Temporal	O
Muscle	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Skull	O
was	O
laid	O
bare	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
likewise	O
another	O
contused	O
Wound	O
on	O
her	O
Nose	O
.	O
She	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Petersham	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
at	O
Putney-gate	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
Grinder	O
set	O
down	O
his	O
Barrow	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Horse	O
started	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
thrown	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Rails	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
forward	O
with	O
such	O
force	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Fulham	O
Turnpike	O
keeper	O
perceiving	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
open	O
the	O
Gate	O
for	O
fear	O
I	O
should	O
fall	O
upon	O
the	O
Spikes	O
.	O
My	O
Horse	O
got	O
the	O
Bitt	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
manage	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stop	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
And	O
if	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Cut	O
or	O
two	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
running	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Toriana	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
paid	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
at	O
Putney	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
a	O
Knife-grinder	O
coming	O
from	O
Fulham	O
,	O
set	O
down	O
his	O
Barrow	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Horse	O
took	O
such	O
a	O
Fright	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
leap	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Rails	O
.	O
The	O
Turnpike	O
Man	O
at	O
Fulham	O
threw	O
open	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
through	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
go	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Throp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
Horse	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Track	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
stood	O
up	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
times	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
held	O
his	O
Horse	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Horse	O
ran	O
against	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
in	O
Sow-gelders-lane	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Sow-gelders-lane	O
?	O
I	O
apprehend	O
(	O
by	O
what	O
the	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
)	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Bear-street	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
Sow-gelders-lane	O
turns	O
out	O
of	O
Bear-street	O
-	O
The	O
Corner	O
goes	O
by	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
around	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
down	O
this	O
Lane	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
-	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
much	O
farther	O
than	O
to	O
yonders	O
Spikes	O
-	O
So	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
turning	O
.	O
Robin	B-pers
South	I-pers
,	O
again	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Sowgelders-lane	O
about	O
25	O
Yards	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Bear-street	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Piggot	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Bear-street	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
turning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Hollo	O
!	O
Get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
stop	O
my	O
Horse	O
.	O
Cornelius	O
Matthews	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Sow-gelders-lane	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
out	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Corner	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
lean	O
'd	O
back	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
to	O
the	O
Reins	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
's	O
time	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Rider	O
too	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
the	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
'd	O
Hallo	O
!	O
Have	O
a	O
care	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
stop	O
my	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
led	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Child	O
got	O
loose	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wailwright	O
.	O
The	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
exprest	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
concern	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
Visit	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
disguis	O
'd	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
sober	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
hurt	O
a	O
Worm	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Master	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
Man	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
apt	O
to	O
start	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Nobody	O
could	O
stop	O
;	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
more	O
he	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
back	O
the	O
worse	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
used	O
to	O
ride	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Horn	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
run-away	O
Horse	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
;	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
civil	O
,	O
and	O
obliging	O
Servant	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
to	O
Morrow	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
before	O
any	O
other	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ingram	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
my	O
Nieces	O
upwards	O
of	O
13	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
himself	O
very	O
sedately	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
inclin	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Mischievous	O
,	O
ill-natur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
him	O
capable	O
of	O
so	O
rash	O
an	O
Action	O
,	O
as	O
wilfully	O
riding	O
full	O
speed	O
through	O
a	O
Town	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
appear	O
'd	O
very	O
much	O
dejected	O
since	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
Ann	O
Cross	O
received	O
her	O
Death	O
Accidentally	O
.	O
6.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
,	O
Carnally	O
knowing	O
,	O
and	O
wickedly	O
abusing	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
at	O
Lion's-Inn	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
indecent	O
liberties	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
:	O
And	O
her	O
Parents	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
whipt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
never	O
to	O
go	O
near	O
him	O
again	O
:	O
But	O
that	O
not	O
long	O
afterwards	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
so	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
under	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Coland	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serafton	O
,	O
two	O
Surgeons	O
,	O
Deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
small	O
Inflamation	O
in	O
her	O
Parts	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
is	O
was	O
the	O
Venereal	O
Disorder	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
Laceration	O
,	O
and	O
without	O
that	O
there	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
Penetration	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
7	O
Judith	B-pers
Cupid	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Euper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk-gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
5	O
Silver-spoons	O
,	O
Linen	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
;	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cobb	I-pers
,	O
August	O
29	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Cobb	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Stoke-Newington	B-place
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
taken	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
greater	O
part	O
were	O
by	O
her	O
Directions	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Earthen-mugs	O
tipt	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Winckles	I-pers
,	O
August	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9	O
,	O
10.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edesbury	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Edsfworth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-Cup	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
July	O
23	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
Ship-Tavern	B-place
at	I-place
Temple-Bar	I-place
and	O
was	O
burnt	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
that	O
happen	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
-	O
And	O
afterwards	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass-candlestick	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Cup	O
was	O
mine	O
by	O
the	O
Mark	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jemmit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Gloucester-Court	O
in	O
White-Cross-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
had	O
something	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
leave	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
Nobody	O
but	O
her	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
a	O
Cask	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
Man	O
came	O
again	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
the	O
Bundle	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
Nobody	O
but	O
herself	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
then	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
it	O
except	O
I	O
come	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
something	O
of	O
Value	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Something	O
of	O
Value	O
?	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
Then	O
it	O
can	O
never	O
belong	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
thinks	O
herself	O
rich	O
when	O
she	O
's	O
worth	O
a	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Cinders	O
-	O
You	O
must	O
know	O
she	O
's	O
a	O
Cinder-Wench	O
-	O
It	O
's	O
no	O
matter	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Salver	O
Taster	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
opens	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Rabbit-skins	O
,	O
a	O
Brass-candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Silver-cup	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
Taster	O
?	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
sizeable	O
one	O
!	O
By	O
and	O
by	O
in	O
comes	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charges	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
upon	O
enquiring	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
Edesbury	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Woman	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
my	O
Shop	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Covent-Garden	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
man	O
(	O
Edesbury	O
)	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Cup	O
and	O
Candlestick	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
leave	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edesbury	I-pers
.	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
lying	O
Toad	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
in	O
your	O
Life	O
before	O
-	O
My	O
Lord	O
she	O
's	O
wicked	O
vile	O
Woman	O
,	O
never	O
set	O
Eyes	O
on	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Days	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
seems	O
you	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
together	O
.	O
Edesbury	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
true	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
least	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
her	O
till	O
that	O
Morning	O
when	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Woolpack	O
in	O
Petticoat-Inn	O
till	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
Craft	O
-	O
The	O
gentle	O
Craft	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Prize-shoe	O
to	O
be	O
shewn	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Shop-mates	O
home	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
coming	O
back	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
with	O
these	O
Things	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
You	O
Bitch	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
in	O
your	O
Lap	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
where	O
Tom	O
Gilpin	O
was	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
Tom	B-pers
Gilpin	I-pers
?	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
she	O
then	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Tom	O
Gilpin	O
?	O
Edesbury	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
well	O
observed	O
indeed	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
over-run	O
my	O
self	O
a	O
little	O
there	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
a	O
bad	O
memory	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
forgot	O
the	O
main	O
Article	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Shop-mate	O
and	O
Tom	O
Gilpin	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
met	O
this	O
Creature	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
Tom	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
she	O
dropt	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Shop-mate	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
Tom	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Shop	O
mate	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Bitch	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
where	O
Tom	O
Gilpin	O
was	O
;	O
You	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
must	O
reason	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
last	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
into	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
down	O
Chancery-lane	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
came	O
to	O
Fetter	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
Harp-Alley	O
to	O
Fleet-ditch	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
Fleet-lane	O
to	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
and	O
cross	O
Newgate-street	O
to	O
Giltspur-street	O
,	O
and	O
through	O
Pye-Corner	O
into	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
Long-lane	O
,	O
and	O
cross	O
Aldersgate-street	O
to	O
Barbican	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
down	O
Red-Cross-street	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
White-Cross-street	O
to	O
Jemmit	O
's	O
Brandy-shop	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Things	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
call	O
there	O
and	O
demand	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
aright	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
seems	O
you	O
knew	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
of	O
value	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Jemmit	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
Edesbury	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
Christ	O
's	O
sake	O
be	O
favourable	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
these	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
Edesbury	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believ	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
there	O
-	O
And	O
has	O
for	O
her	O
part	O
she	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Jemmit	O
a	O
slap	O
of	O
the	O
Chops	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Newgate	O
.	O
William	O
Drogheda	O
and	O
Job	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Edesbury	O
had	O
Lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
High	O
Way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Leghorn	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Top	O
Knot	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
August	O
2	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Leg-horn	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Muslin-hood	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Susan	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
With	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Leghorn	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Callimanco	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
mixt	O
Metal-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
and	O
Place	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Prayer	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
him	O
were	O
examined	O
a-part	O
.	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
,	O
but	O
nearer	O
10	O
than	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
With	I-pers
were	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
between	O
West-End	B-place
and	O
Kilburn	B-place
:	O
I	O
being	O
foremost	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
of	O
their	O
Hats	O
,	O
and	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Gown	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
shoot	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
stir	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shoes	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
thought	O
my	O
Buckles	O
were	O
Silver	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
look	O
'd	O
white	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
mixed	O
Metal	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
his	O
Face	O
plainly	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
as	O
light	O
as	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
-	O
He	O
worked	O
labouring	O
Work	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
next	O
Day	O
a	O
Mowing	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Whitaker	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
as	O
Hampstead-Fair	O
was	O
on	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
had	O
all	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Fair	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Kilburn	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Saturday	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
work	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
returning	O
from	O
Hampstead-Fair	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
betwixt	O
West-End	O
and	O
Kilburn	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
Frock	O
and	O
metal	O
Buttons	O
past	O
by	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Good	O
Night	O
,	O
Gentlewomen	O
;	O
Good	O
Night	O
,	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
we	O
said	O
to	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
Paddington	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
started	O
out	O
upon	O
West	O
,	O
from	O
behind	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
your	O
Blood	O
!	O
your	O
Money	O
!	O
He	O
took	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
West	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
With	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
Hood	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
West	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
pull	O
out	O
his	O
Buckles	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
,	O
but	O
nearer	O
10	O
than	O
9	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
pretty	O
good	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
Wig	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
new	O
shaved	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
white	O
Frock	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susan	B-pers
With	I-pers
,	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Kilburn	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
had	O
more	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
parted	O
from	O
us	O
at	O
a	O
Cross-path	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
came	O
by	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Good	O
Night	O
,	O
Ladies	O
;	O
Good	O
Night	O
,	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
us	O
said	O
to	O
West	O
,	O
Who	O
is	O
that	O
,	O
John	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
call	O
to	O
mind	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
within	O
two	O
Fields	O
of	O
our	O
own	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
bolted	O
out	O
from	O
a	O
Bush	O
;	O
Lord	O
bless	O
me	O
!	O
says	O
my	O
Mother	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
Leghorn	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
and	O
Topknot	O
,	O
a	O
muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
nearer	O
10	O
than	O
9	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
with	O
metal	O
Buttons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
Wig	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
a	O
Mowing	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
on	O
a	O
white	O
Frock	O
and	O
metal	O
Buttons	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
look	O
'd	O
cleaner	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
With	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
nearer	O
10	O
than	O
9	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
betwixt	O
Kilburn	O
and	O
West-End	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
fustian	O
Frock	O
with	O
metal	O
Buttons	O
overtook	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Good	O
Night	O
,	O
Neighbours	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
West	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
John	O
?	O
Yes	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
He	O
robb	O
'd	O
John	O
first	O
,	O
clapping	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Women	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Callimanco-Gown	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
John	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
pull	O
out	O
his	O
Buckles	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
got	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
us	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
our	O
Clothes	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
.	O
William	O
Sands	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Paddington	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Walk	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
Landlord	O
of	O
the	O
Green-man	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
Sir	O
!	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
Warrant	O
nor	O
Constable	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Phoo	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
any	O
one	O
may	O
take	O
a	O
Felon	O
without	O
a	O
Warrant	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
these	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
sad	O
thing	O
to	O
swear	O
away	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Life	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
'd	O
have	O
you	O
be	O
very	O
cautious	O
-	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
And	O
they	O
all	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
positive	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Deverel	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Headborough	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Parish	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
Noon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Men	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
Pillory	O
,	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
by	O
Carnaby-Market	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
in	O
Carnaby-street	O
,	O
till	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Bell-Lane	O
,	O
in	O
Mary-bone	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
of	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
House	O
is	O
two	O
Miles	O
from	O
Kilburn	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
a	O
labouring	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Character	O
has	O
been	O
pretty	O
good	O
latterly	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
he	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
one	O
Smith	O
,	O
a	O
Horse-Courser	O
,	O
who	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
Occasion	O
?	O
Deverel	O
.	O
To	O
bilk	O
every	O
Body	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sands	O
again	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
that	O
Smith	O
accused	O
of	O
Horse	O
stealing	O
?	O
Deverel	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
such	O
things	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
News	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sands	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Green-Man	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Deverel	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
?	O
Deverel	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
so	O
?	O
Deverel	O
.	O
The	O
Women	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
different	O
Stories	O
;	O
some	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
about	O
9	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
before	O
9	O
;	O
besides	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
there	O
two	O
Minutes	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
Dough	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Baker	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
yet	O
you	O
staid	O
long	O
enough	O
to	O
hear	O
them	O
tell	O
different	O
Stories	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Deverel	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
near	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Men	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
We	O
talk	O
'd	O
about	O
mowing	O
some	O
Grass	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Whitaker	O
.	O
John	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
rent	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
9.	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
till	O
a	O
Quarter	O
past	O
9	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
cut	O
some	O
Grass	O
for	O
Whitaker	O
.	O
-	O
Goslin	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
two	O
Doors	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
to	O
and	O
again	O
all	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
talking	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
about	O
Mowing	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Whitaker	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
me	O
were	O
before	O
Justice	O
Binfield	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
positive	O
;	O
for	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
committed	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Commitment	O
was	O
only	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
as	O
will	O
appear	O
by	O
the	O
Copy	O
of	O
that	O
Commitment	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
12.	O
Jane	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Table	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Ansley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13	O
,	O
14.	O
William	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Black-head	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Paps-Nose	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
3	O
Hats	O
,	O
4	O
Caps	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Cotton-Gown	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
6	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Linen-Frocks	O
,	O
6	O
Aprons	O
,	O
12	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ketteridge	I-pers
;	O
and	O
two	O
Gowns	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Trip	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
called	O
the	O
Happy	O
Return	O
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Ketteridge	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Ship	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Hat	O
at	O
Ben	O
.	O
Green	O
's	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Hats	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
-	O
Green	O
produced	O
Lucas	O
,	O
from	O
whom	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Hat	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
Lucas	O
's	O
Information	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Ben	O
.	O
Green	O
.	O
Lucas	O
brought	O
this	O
Hat	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
dress	O
-	O
The	O
Captain	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
all	O
his	O
Hats	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Ship	O
.	O
He	O
bought	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
an	O
Hour	O
afterwards	O
came	O
for	O
another	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
Hat	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
you	O
now	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
's	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
be	O
dress	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Hat	O
that	O
Lucas	O
left	O
.	O
Why	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Hats	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Captain	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
can	O
help	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
Lucas	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
he	O
frequented	O
in	O
Wells-street	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
Reynold	O
's	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
in	O
Weil	O
street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
we	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Iron-Gate	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
stole	O
a	O
Boat	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sculls	O
,	O
and	O
row	O
'd	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
.	O
About	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
The	B-place
Happy	I-place
Return	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
King	I-place
James's-Stairs	I-place
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
no	O
Light	O
on	O
Board	O
,	O
we	O
wrenched	O
open	O
the	O
Cabbin-window	O
.	O
Then	O
Newell	O
struck	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
lighting	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Martin	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
speak	O
to	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
Shoes	O
and	O
crept	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
2	O
Coats	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
3	O
Hats	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
some	O
Linen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
sold	O
the	O
Watch	O
for	O
36s	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
12s	O
.	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
Share	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
12s	O
.	O
a-piece	O
.	O
Martin	O
allow	O
'd	O
4s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
he	O
reckoned	O
18	O
d.	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
Share	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
18	O
d.	O
a-piece	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
Hat	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
gone	O
off	O
,	O
for	O
50s	O
.	O
We	O
spent	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
15s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
a-piece	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Hat	O
next	O
Day	O
to	O
Green	O
's	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
more	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
Headborough	O
,	O
in	O
White-chapel	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Lucas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
-	O
Newell	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Lade	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
Newell	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
self	O
a	O
voluntary	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Lucas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Faucet	I-pers
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
this	O
Ship	O
;	O
but	O
Lucas	O
's	O
Friends	O
had	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Keeper	O
.	O
Newell	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
this	O
time	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
Against	O
Abraham	O
Gibson	O
,	O
in	O
Sept.	O
1733	O
.	O
Session-Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
VII	O
.	O
pag	O
.	O
184	O
.	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
Hat	O
among	O
others	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Martin	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Newell	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15	O
,	O
16.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Morgan	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
Cooper	O
for	O
receiving	O
,	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
5	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Alice	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hage	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-clothes	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Clavey	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
13	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
18.	O
Ann	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
19.	O
Jane	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Sheet	O
.	O
Allen	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Thomson	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tracey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
and	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pickfat	I-pers
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dove	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pickfat	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Virginia	B-pers
Planks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
six	O
Beach	O
Banisters	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Hatley	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
10	O
.	O
And	O
23.	O
William	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Planks	O
.	O
Dun	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
Moore	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
Grace	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
Linen	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trevit	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
Mary	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Enes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Mantle	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
July	O
23	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26	O
,	O
27.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Dimmock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Glinn	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
Linen	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
6	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Linen	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Mathew	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
.	O
Dimmock	O
acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
Glinn	O
guilty	O
of	O
both	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
John	B-pers
Spencely	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nehemiah	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
acquitted	O
.	O
29.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tenoe	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Smock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tyrrel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
July	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
First	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39s	O
.	O
and	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Second	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Robert	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Lambert	B-pers
Ludlow	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Aug.	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31.	O
Ann	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
Richard	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
after	O
May	O
1	O
,	O
1734	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Upper-Park	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
on	O
MargARET	B-pers
TREVOR	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
maliciously	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
,	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
Chattels	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
Miss	O
MARGARET	O
TREVOR	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
:	O
little	O
after	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
Sister	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Queen	B-place
's	I-place
Gravel	I-place
walk	I-place
,	I-place
a	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
something	O
to	O
me	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
Deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
!	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
Purpose	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
Words	O
exactly	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
frighted	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Grass	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
was	O
immediately	O
taken	O
by	O
some	O
Person	O
who	O
jump	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
Miss	O
M.	O
TREVOR	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
frighted	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
Purse	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
opened	O
.	O
Miss	O
GERTRUDE	B-pers
TREVOR	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
coming	O
towards	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
voluntary	O
Confession	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Confession	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
,	O
That	O
being	O
lately	O
come	O
from	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Namure	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
want	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Queen's-walk	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Upper-Park	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
two	O
young	O
Gentlewomen	O
walking	O
by	O
themselves	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Mask	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
rob	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
their	O
Money	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
dropt	O
a	O
Purse	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
squaling	O
out	O
aloud	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
away	O
his	O
Pistol	O
and	O
Mask	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
33.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Langloge	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Porta	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Millanese	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tadie	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
,	O
August	O
20	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
being	O
Foreigners	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
Interpret	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tadie	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
Lodgings	O
at	O
Mr.	O
James	O
Bowden	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Costa	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Vassalli	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
inform	O
him	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Vassalli	O
lived	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
direct	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
enquire	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Welford	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
Directions	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
write	O
a	O
Letter	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
furnish	O
'd	O
with	O
Pens	O
,	O
and	O
Ink	O
,	O
and	O
Paper	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
Cecil-Court	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Martin's-Lane	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
chose	O
to	O
write	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
he	O
might	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
at	O
my	O
Desk	O
and	O
began	O
his	O
Letter	O
.	O
My	O
Desk	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
writing	O
there	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
17	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
Crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Shillings	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Water	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Glass	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
still	O
writing	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
finish	O
'd	O
his	O
Letter	O
,	O
he	O
directed	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Vassalli	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
shut	O
my	O
Desk	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
to	O
Dinner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Angelis	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
staid	O
till	O
evening	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Costa	O
waiting	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
3	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
my	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Costa	O
perceiving	O
some	O
alteration	O
in	O
my	O
countenance	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
15	O
Guineas	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
But	O
I	O
know	O
and	O
can	O
swear	O
who	O
has	O
it	O
-	O
For	O
while	O
my	O
Desk	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Nobody	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
-	O
I	O
added	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
turned	O
pale	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
ask	O
Mr.	O
Bowden	O
's	O
Advice	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
best	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Costa	O
quickly	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
And	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
St.	O
Martin's-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
And	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
the	O
Pavement	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
motion	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Money	O
fall	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
stopt	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
made	O
great	O
resistance	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
mob	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sharper	O
coming	O
by	O
and	O
claiming	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
I	O
assaulted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
for	O
Water	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
my	O
Letter	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Desk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tadie	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
run	O
from	O
your	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
the	O
Money	O
away	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
Loss	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Costa	O
Let	O
us	O
go	O
,	O
or	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
imputed	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
assaulted	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
by	O
3	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
run	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
throw	O
the	O
Money	O
away	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
save	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
it	O
dropt	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Costa	O
.	O
I	O
waited	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Tadie	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bowden	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
Noon	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Tadie	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
3	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Tadie	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
He	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Desk	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Drawers	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
himself	O
a	O
knock	O
of	O
the	O
Pate	O
,	O
-	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
lost	O
any	O
Money	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
by	O
God	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
by	O
God	O
who	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
the	O
end	O
o	O
n't	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
name	O
any	O
body	O
then	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Tadie	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
Nobody	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
while	O
the	O
Desk	O
was	O
open	O
?	O
Tadie	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
de	O
Costa	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
name	O
the	O
Person	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Costa	O
.	O
While	O
Mr.	O
Tadie	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Burden	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turn	O
'd	O
his	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
fumbled	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
to	O
shift	O
his	O
Money	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropt	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
;	O
I	O
stoop	O
'd	O
to	O
reach	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
himself	O
-	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Tadie	O
knock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tadie	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
but	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Martino	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Herbert	O
,	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Jeweller	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
Money	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
steps	O
:	O
What	O
's	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
has	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
says	O
one	O
,	O
What	O
Gentleman	O
?	O
Says	O
I	O
.	O
This	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
says	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
pointed	O
to	O
a	O
stranger	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
drest	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
Suit	O
and	O
Ruffles	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
some	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
that	O
stranger	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
did	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Mistress	O
came	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
not	O
touch	O
anymore	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
kick	O
'd	O
it	O
towards	O
the	O
stranger	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
himself	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
hearing	O
a	O
fresh	O
Noise	O
,	O
I	O
stept	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tadie	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
that	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
Why	O
here	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
Stranger	O
that	O
has	O
taken	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
those	O
about	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
the	O
Cane	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Roboullet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
Murder	O
Tadie	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Relations	O
,	O
either	O
here	O
or	O
in	O
Italy	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
he	O
would	O
burn	O
his	O
House	O
-	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
hither	O
to	O
change	O
his	O
Religion	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
murder	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
thrown	O
upon	O
the	O
Pavement	O
,	O
but	O
believ	O
'd	O
they	O
might	O
throw	O
it	O
after	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
-	O
The	O
Justice	O
and	O
he	O
discoursed	O
in	O
Latin	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
rightly	O
understand	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
do	O
n't	O
pronounce	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
the	O
English	O
do	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
change	O
his	O
Religion	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Tadie	O
dissuaded	O
him	O
from	O
so	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
better	O
to	O
prevail	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
lent	O
me	O
16	O
Guineas	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Angelis	O
knows	O
I	O
had	O
Money	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Angelo	B-pers
de	I-pers
Angelis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Prisoner	O
dined	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
that	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Martino	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
born	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
over	O
with	O
both	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
now	O
a	O
Trunk	O
and	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Vasselli	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
that	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tadie	O
's	O
.	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
sign	O
'd	O
with	O
Fran	O
.	O
Vasselli	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
Dated	O
at	O
Lumley-Castle	O
in	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
August	O
27	O
.	O
1734	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
35.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Macguire	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shipwith	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
John	O
Shipwith	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
Mr.	O
James	O
at	O
Whetstone	B-place
,	O
that	O
my	O
Horse	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Grounds	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Horse	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
Grounds	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
July	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
mist	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
again	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hare	O
of	O
Barnet	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
stopt	O
there	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Shipwith	O
's	O
Horse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
London-bridge	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
from	O
Whetstone	O
to	O
Barnet	O
was	O
the	O
wrong	O
way	O
to	O
London-bridge	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nickson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Horse	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
the	O
Gate	O
with	O
a	O
Halter	O
.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Buckle	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
ride	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
soon	O
overtake	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nickols	I-pers
.	O
Hearing	O
Somebody	O
cry	O
out	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
's	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
him	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
in	O
Barnet	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
to	O
London-bridge	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
the	O
Road	O
to	O
St.	O
Albans-Well	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
lent	O
me	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
ride	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
but	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Miles	O
farther	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
riding	O
along	O
by	O
Barnet	O
Market	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	O
had	O
no	O
Saddle	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
a	O
Brible	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
stolen	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
gallop	O
:	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
him	O
!	O
And	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
36	O
John	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cooper	O
's	O
Addice	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
December	O
1	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
Brewhouse	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
the	O
Goods	O
before	O
last	O
Christmas	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Ring	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
prosecute	O
sooner	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
very	O
strange	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
Partners	O
in	O
a	O
Malt	O
house	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Adz	O
there	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
there	O
still	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
,	O
Last	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
an	O
unhappy	O
Quarrel	O
;	O
your	O
Brother	O
charges	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
His	O
Brother	O
!	O
Slaughter	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
are	O
Brothers-in-law	O
-	O
And	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Breeches	O
are	O
not	O
worth	O
Threepence	O
.	O
But	O
then	O
there	O
's	O
the	O
Ring	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
Aye	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
-	O
There	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
Family	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Osgood	I-pers
.	O
We	O
met	O
at	O
Slaughter	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
agree	O
the	O
Matter	O
up	O
.	O
Says	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
Slaughter	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
encourage	O
an	O
informing	O
Rogue	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
in	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
intend	O
to	O
turn	O
Informer	O
too	O
?	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
laid	O
an	O
Information	O
before	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
-	O
Says	O
I	O
to	O
Smith	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
have	O
you	O
make	O
the	O
Matter	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
Knot	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
Smith	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
a	O
Rogue	O
he	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
too	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
hang	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
sworn	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
when	O
he	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
now	O
it	O
can	O
be	O
only	O
Transportation	O
.	O
I	O
saved	O
his	O
Life	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
hang	O
himself	O
;	O
for	O
his	O
Sister	O
found	O
him	O
swinging	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
up	O
such	O
a	O
damn	O
'd	O
Squaul	O
of	O
Fire	O
and	O
Murder	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
run	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
surprize	O
.	O
He	O
began	O
to	O
keck	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
Sot	O
as	O
was	O
,	O
cut	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
damn	O
'd	O
Clum-foot	O
came	O
thump	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
his	O
Sister	O
about	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
-	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
last	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
pay	O
half	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
due	O
on	O
the	O
Information	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecution	O
appearing	O
malicious	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
37.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
36	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
Sept.	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38.	O
Edward	B-pers
Chilton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Nassau	B-pers
Paulet	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
commonly	O
called	O
Lord	O
Nassau	O
Pawlett	O
Aug.	O
25	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
39.	O
Martha	B-pers
Wasely	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Diamond	O
and	O
Ruby	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Buttons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Foulk	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
June	O
5.	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
fifth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
:	O
And	O
40.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pene	I-pers
,	O
for	O
Receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
41.	O
Robert	B-pers
Colson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
4	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Head	O
,	O
a	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Tortoise	O
shell	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Cypher	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
Diamond	O
Sparks	O
,	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Timothy	B-pers
Towle	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Path	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Violin	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
5	O
Music	O
Books	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
And	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Whitsun	O
Eve	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
were	O
going	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
to	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
we	O
had	O
gone	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
before	O
I	O
bethought	O
my	O
self	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
forgot	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
my	O
Husband	O
left	O
the	O
Bundle	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
stept	O
back	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
waiting	O
and	O
looking	O
for	O
his	O
return	O
;	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
supposing	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
my	O
Husband	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
went	O
forward	O
slowly	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
overtaken	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
in	O
light	O
Colour	O
'd	O
Stockings	O
.	O
They	O
past	O
by	O
me	O
without	O
speaking	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
they	O
were	O
Thieves	O
,	O
because	O
of	O
their	O
white	O
Stockings	O
-	O
For	O
it	O
seems	O
white	O
Stockings	O
is	O
a	O
mighty	O
Fashion	O
among	O
Thieves	O
-	O
One	O
of	O
these	O
Men	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
walked	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
into	O
a	O
small	O
puddle	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
thank	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Field	O
;	O
where	O
the	O
path	O
divides	O
in	O
two	O
;	O
one	O
goes	O
to	O
a	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
Gap	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
:	O
But	O
presently	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
towards	O
me	O
-	O
And	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
Money	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
young	O
Woman	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
none	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
down	O
my	O
Bosom	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
thing	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
-	O
No	O
-	O
Do	O
n't	O
frighten	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
Damn	O
your	O
blood	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
stand	O
still	O
and	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
hurt	O
you	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
why	O
I	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
me	O
no	O
Harm	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
quiet	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
my	O
Ring	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
again	O
what	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
thrust	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
and	O
broke	O
my	O
Pocket	O
off	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Cypher-ring	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wedding-Ring	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
return	O
me	O
my	O
Wedding-ring	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
send	O
them	O
twice	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
Place	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
appoint	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
complain	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
they	O
jump	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Ditch	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
dark	O
Clothes	O
,	O
white	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blue	O
Linsey	O
Woolsey	O
Apron	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
met	O
my	O
Husband	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
,	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
the	O
Beadle	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
List	O
of	O
what	O
the	O
Woman	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
-	O
These	O
2	O
Aprons	O
and	O
Pinners	O
were	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Waker	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
robbing	O
Timothy	B-pers
Towle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
others	O
have	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Blue-House-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
on	O
the	O
13	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
or	O
there	O
abouts	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
Door	O
in	O
Vine-Street	O
,	O
drinking	O
with	O
one	O
Bung	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
Bung	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
screw	O
Pistol	O
charged	O
with	O
2	O
Balls	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pan	O
full	O
of	O
Powder	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
Wife	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Woman	O
before	O
-	O
She	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Towle	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Fenicks	I-pers
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Hamersmith	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
2	O
Men	O
near	O
Holland	O
walk	O
by	O
Kensington	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Moon	O
light	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
both	O
by	O
his	O
Person	O
and	O
Voice	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
to	O
me	O
asked	O
what	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
but	O
little	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
curst	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
presenting	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Deliver	O
directly	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
your	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
strip	O
off	O
my	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
.	O
My	O
Violin	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
lining	O
of	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
Pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
to	O
John	O
Gay	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
Acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
John	O
Gay	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
brought	O
this	O
Fiddle	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
because	O
Towle	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Fiddle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
name	O
was	O
scratch	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Towle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fenicks	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
attackt	O
us	O
with	O
Pistols	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
clapt	O
to	O
our	O
Ears	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
volley	O
of	O
Oaths	O
demanded	O
our	O
Money	O
.	O
For	O
my	O
part	O
:	O
was	O
pretty	O
easy	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
lose	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Shilling	O
from	O
Towle	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
turn	O
again	O
and	O
ease	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Fiddle	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
shabby	O
Coat	O
and	O
a	O
Crape	O
Hatband	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
Fiddle	O
at	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Colson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Fiddle	O
from	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
Pawn	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Robert	O
Colson	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
And	O
Acquitted	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
42.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Handkerchies	O
,	O
6	O
Napkins	O
,	O
5	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
2	O
Penknives	O
,	O
a	O
Gold-ring	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Isabel	B-pers
Alman	I-pers
;	O
and	O
8	O
Stocks	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Basson	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43	O
Nary	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Leghorn	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
22	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ovet	I-pers
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
William	O
Ovet	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
my	O
Drawers	O
on	O
Friday	O
Noon	O
,	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
22	O
Guineas	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
and	O
Faulcon-Inn	O
in	O
Aldersgate-Street	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
a	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drinking	O
Tea	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
dropt	O
a	O
Box	O
with	O
14	O
Guineas	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tredway	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
and	O
Faulcon	O
;	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
2	O
others	O
of	O
her	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
with	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
time	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Box	O
dropt	O
under	O
the	O
Table	O
where	O
she	O
sat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dog	O
got	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
plaid	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
Guineas	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Box	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
44.	O
Judith	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Speer	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
8	O
.	O
George	O
Speer	O
.	O
This	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dakers	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-Street	O
about	O
11	O
o	O
'	O
Clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
White-Swan	B-place
in	I-place
Sheer-Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
ask	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Farthing	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
we	O
came	O
thither	O
,	O
says	O
Tom	B-pers
Dakers	I-pers
to	O
me	O
,	O
What	O
signifies	O
our	O
coming	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
but	O
Six-pence	O
?	O
O	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
Money	O
enough	O
!	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
4	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
in	O
my	O
Fob	O
,	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
presence	O
?	O
Speer	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Chair	O
-	O
May	O
be	O
she	O
might	O
see	O
me	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
sat	O
in	O
one	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
in	O
another	O
close	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
my	O
Breeches	O
and	O
-	O
In	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Minutes	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
-	O
Soon	O
after	O
a	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
all	O
my	O
Gold	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-box	O
in	O
my	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
losing	O
that	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
mind	O
my	O
Money	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Fob	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
wiser	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
-	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
again	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
me	O
in	O
her	O
Life	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
signified	O
nothing	O
my	O
going	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
but	O
Six-pence	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
go	O
:	O
And	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
Money	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
4	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
-	O
They	O
sat	O
down	O
together	O
;	O
she	O
undid	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
busy	O
with	O
him	O
-	O
In	O
about	O
9	O
Minutes	O
another	O
Gentlewoman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
complain	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Woman	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Drinkwater	O
the	O
Drawer	O
knows	O
me	O
well	O
enough	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
People	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
charged	O
we	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
going	O
down	O
Fleet-Street	O
to	O
meet	O
my	O
Brother	O
at	O
the	O
Six	O
Bells	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Horn	O
and	O
Horse-Shoe	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Mantua	O
maker	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
many	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
she	O
live	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
She	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Holborn	O
when	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
's	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
ago	O
-	O
She	O
never	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
but	O
about	O
Business	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Hambro'-Coffee-house	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
anything	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
failing	O
-	O
She	O
did	O
Live	O
in	O
Holborn	O
formerly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
afterwards	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
at	O
Deptford	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Buchanan	I-pers
.	O
She	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
when	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
-	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
she	O
was	O
reckon	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Humphry	O
Watson	O
,	O
the	O
Fishmonger	O
's	O
Son	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
45.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Poplin-gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Northup	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
14	O
.	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
46.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roof	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Roof	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
Aug.	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
47.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Malbourn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
Mobs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
48.	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
2	O
Hats	O
,	O
3	O
Wigs	O
,	O
2	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
5	O
Dishes	O
,	O
11	O
Plates	O
,	O
3	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Brass-candlesticks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
;	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Properties	O
of	O
divers	O
Persons	O
,	O
May	O
5	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
time	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Taylor	O
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
Information	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
readily	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
enter	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
Bake-house	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
and	O
let	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
Accomplice	O
stood	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
named	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
particulars	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
out	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
List	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
you	O
have	O
Lost	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
shewing	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
added	O
-	O
And	O
these	O
are	O
your	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
(	O
shewing	O
his	O
Feet	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
these	O
are	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
Shoes	O
.	O
And	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
another	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
That	O
's	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Wigs	O
upon	O
that	O
Man	O
's	O
Head	O
-	O
And	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
have	O
gone	O
up	O
again	O
alive	O
-	O
We	O
put	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
Sacks	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
past	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
Theobald	O
's	O
Row	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
Stop	O
us	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
-	O
Wright	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Will	O
.	O
Wig	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
several	O
Particulars	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
having	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
some	O
trifling	O
Things	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
picking	O
Pockets	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
clear	O
my	O
self	O
by	O
turning	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
,	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
every	O
individual	O
Particular	O
relating	O
to	O
this	O
Fact	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
mentioned	O
so	O
many	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
concerned	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
3	O
Prisoners	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
Will	O
.	O
Jackson	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
Gulliford	O
and	O
Garterin	O
Jack	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
p.	O
161	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
49	O
Thomas	B-pers
Armson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
l.	O
2	O
s	O
the	O
8	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
,	O
Sept.	O
6	O
.	O
William	O
Ward	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
William	O
Newman	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
a	O
Week	O
;	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
my	O
Chest	O
on	O
Friday	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
buying	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Clothes	O
at	O
Watford	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
but	O
7	O
Hours	O
since	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
7	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
36	O
s.	O
was	O
quite	O
lost	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Haymaking	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
my	O
Cows	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Cows	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
Horse	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Watford	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
An	O
Irishman	O
(	O
a	O
Haymaker	O
)	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
50.	O
George	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
15	O
,	O
1732	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
my	O
Hat	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
an	O
old	O
Hat	O
,	O
not	O
worth	O
a	O
Ha'penny	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Exchange	O
is	O
no	O
Robbery	O
-	O
He	O
's	O
a	O
Rat-catcher	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tatterson	I-pers
.	O
He	O
laid	O
down	O
his	O
old	O
Hat	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
new	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Exchange	O
is	O
no	O
Robbery	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Joke	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rigsworth	I-pers
.	O
He	O
laid	O
down	O
his	O
old	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
,	O
Exchange	O
is	O
no	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
new	O
one	O
and	O
morris	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
hard	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
Hat	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
Two-penny	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
in	O
the	O
Stone	O
cutter	O
's	O
Yard	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Gin-shop	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
came	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Hat	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
prosecute	O
sooner	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
3	O
Hours	O
after	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
my	O
Hat	O
was	O
?	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
Damn	O
it	O
