TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BILLERS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1734	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILFORD	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Chapter-House	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXIV	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
foregoing	O
Numbers	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sessions-Papers	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BILLERS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	B-pers
Probyn	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Comyns	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	B-pers
Urlin	I-pers
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Daker	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Sweeting	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Doubleton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pittle	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tawney	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Milward	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Strutton	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Snee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sawhill	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Littlewood	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Oswin	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Grain	I-pers
.	O
1	O
,	O
2.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Wig-box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Barber's-Shop	O
on	O
London-Bridge	B-place
.	O
The	O
Wig	O
was	O
Edw	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
's	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
him	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
sometime	O
ago	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
.	O
About	O
12	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
having	O
just	O
let	O
a	O
Customer	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sweep	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Back	O
being	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
Body	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Wig-box	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Shelf	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
myself	O
had	O
writ	O
Mr	O
.	O
Bright	O
's	O
Name	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Casely	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Cock-my-Chin	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
stealing	O
Oil	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Old-Swan	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
two	O
Kettles	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Hempdresser	O
,	O
in	O
Bridewell-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
going	O
over	O
London-Bridge	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Dun	O
's	O
Shop	O
open	O
.	O
Stay	O
,	O
says	O
Jack	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
something	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
Wig	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
Jack	O
.	O
His	O
Mother	O
seeing	O
this	O
,	O
bid	O
me	O
follow	O
her	O
to	O
Plumb-pudding-Square	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
to	O
Plumb-pudding-Square	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Wig	O
.	O
She	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
Lodging	O
on	O
the	O
Pipes	O
,	O
that	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Water-house	O
at	O
the	O
Bridge	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
found	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
for	O
a	O
Black-guard	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
promis	O
'd	O
never	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
I	O
heard	O
,	O
that	O
Jack	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry-Compter	O
,	O
I	O
borrow	O
'd	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Hempman	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Jack	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
2	O
d.	O
-	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lingard	O
's	O
Gin-shop	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Wig	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
17	O
s.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Lingard	O
kick	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
met	O
Jack	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
Black-Shoe-Boy	O
,	O
eating	O
a	O
Marrow-bone	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
bit	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
hungry	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
2	O
Guineas	O
bid	O
for	O
taking	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
them	O
that	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
been	O
hard	O
at	O
Work	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
And	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
cleaning	O
Shoes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
my	O
Son	O
was	O
?	O
He	O
damn	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Son	O
had	O
stole	O
his	O
Blacking-pot	O
-	O
A	O
Porter	O
afterwards	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Son	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Evidence	O
at	O
the	O
Old-Swan	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Kettle	O
of	O
Stuff	O
to	O
the	O
Hempman	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Wig-box	O
at	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
Door	O
-	O
Yesterday	O
a	O
Woman	O
brought	O
me	O
2	O
d.	O
for	O
some	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
against	O
my	O
Mother	O
only	O
because	O
she	O
abus	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
Sunday	O
-	O
Cock-my-Chin	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
you	O
that	O
draw	O
'd	O
me	O
away	O
when	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Bradley	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Pudding-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Shilling	O
a	O
Week	O
for	O
cleaning	O
Shoes	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
all	O
the	O
Butchers	O
in	O
East-cheap	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
can	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
found	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gullender	I-pers
,	O
April	O
24	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
4.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Greenfield	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
by	O
beating	O
and	O
kicking	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
privy	O
Members	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
several	O
mortal	O
Bruises	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
'till	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Two	O
Men	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
about	O
a	O
Bett	O
of	O
2	O
d.	O
laid	O
in	O
a	O
Nine-pin-Ground	O
,	O
in	O
Hampstead	B-place
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
took	O
the	O
part	O
of	O
him	O
who	O
lost	O
the	O
Bett	O
,	O
a	O
fourth	O
Man	O
began	O
to	O
quarrel	O
with	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
fight	O
any	O
Man	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
strip	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
venture	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
fight	O
for	O
Love	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
boxt	O
fairly	O
;	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
the	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Nine-pin-Ground	O
among	O
Black-guards	O
;	O
but	O
would	O
fight	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
for	O
having	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
clapp	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Lad	O
.	O
They	O
shook	O
Hand	O
three	O
times	O
very	O
lovingly	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
boxing	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Temples	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
stagger	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
falling	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kick	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
and	O
the	O
Groin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
for	O
dead	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
himself	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dyed	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
quarrel	O
with	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
challeng	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
fought	O
for	O
Love	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
knock	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
reel	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
kick	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
no	O
Design	O
to	O
kick	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
or	O
the	O
Groin	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
quiet	O
peaceable	O
Man	O
,	O
whether	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taverner	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Samuel	I-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Silk-purse	O
,	O
2	O
Gold-rings	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
Jan.	O
2	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Russel	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
going	O
from	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
to	O
Newington	B-place
,	O
Green	O
,	O
my	O
Chariot	O
was	O
stopt	O
near	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
whitish	O
Horse	O
but	O
very	O
dirty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Chariot	O
Door	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
deliver	O
!	O
-	O
be	O
quick	O
-	O
Your	O
Purse	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
your	O
Rings	O
!	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
frighten	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
Purse	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
Glove	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
2	O
Rings	O
,	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Mourning-ring	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
return	O
me	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
damn	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
off	O
.	O
My	O
Coachman	O
drove	O
to	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
take	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
pursue	O
the	O
Highwayman	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
But	O
some	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
as	O
like	O
him	O
as	O
possible	O
and	O
such	O
Clothes	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Russel	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Sea	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
he	O
be	O
discharged	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Bristol	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Russel	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
speaks	O
of	O
,	O
was	O
Robert	B-pers
Morpeth	I-pers
who	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
*	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
at	O
Bristol	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Morpeth	O
's	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
Son	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
Son	O
was	O
discharged	O
and	O
gone	O
to	O
Sea	O
.	O
*	O
In	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
against	O
William	B-pers
Byrom	I-pers
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver-Cup	O
,	O
but	O
Byrom	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Session	O
Paper	O
.	O
Numb	O
.	O
2.	O
p.	O
53	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
because	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
rich	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
convicted	O
Nobody	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Booth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
at	O
Holloway	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Friends	O
let	O
him	O
slip	O
away	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
to	O
Morpeth	O
,	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
Family-Ring	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Russel	O
,	O
and	O
Morpeth	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Collin	O
's	O
(	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
)	O
and	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
is	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
-	O
How	O
came	O
Morpeth	O
to	O
be	O
discharged	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Booth	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
he	O
was	O
referr	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
Justice	O
Harvey	O
to	O
be	O
discharged	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
farther	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
We	O
waited	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Sessions	O
and	O
a	O
Month	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Prosecution	O
then	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
according	O
discharged	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Coachman	O
.	O
)	O
A	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
that	O
goes	O
to	O
Newington-Green	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
they	O
past	O
the	O
Chariot	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
short	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
stop	O
!	O
But	O
not	O
stoping	O
immediately	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Damn	O
your	O
Body	O
and	O
Soul	O
,	O
stop	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
this	O
Minute	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Chariot-door	O
to	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Lady	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Damn	O
'd	O
their	O
Bloods	O
for	O
a	O
Couple	O
of	O
Bitches	O
,	O
bid	O
them	O
deliver	O
their	O
Watches	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
demanded	O
their	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
Ring	O
off	O
my	O
Mistresses	O
's	O
Finger	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Rogue	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
Off-side	O
of	O
the	O
Chariot	O
.	O
They	O
rid	O
away	O
together	O
towards	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
drove	O
to	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
rais	O
'd	O
an	O
Hue	O
and	O
Cry	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
to	O
Holloway	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
parted	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
towards	O
Highgate	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
follow	O
'd	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
quitted	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
a	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
.	O
I	O
dismounted	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
-	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
leap	O
'd	O
the	O
Hedge	O
with	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
offer	O
'd	O
a	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
came	O
behind	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
backwards	O
.	O
My	O
Horse	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
with	O
another	O
Horse	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
a	O
Kicking	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
seiz	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
those	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
let	O
him	O
slip	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
seems	O
they	O
were	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
among	O
several	O
in	O
Newgate	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
brown	O
Clothes	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Horse	O
was	O
a	O
White	O
Grey	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
dirty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ogle	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
and	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
more	O
were	O
binding	O
Hay	O
at	O
Holloway	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
Hue	O
and	O
Cry	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ride	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
between	O
Mother	O
Red-Cap	O
's	O
and	O
the	O
Castle	O
,	O
and	O
Ward	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
quitted	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
ran	O
through	O
a	O
great	O
Slough	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Hedge	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
.	O
We	O
ran	O
to	O
assist	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
being	O
unwilling	O
to	O
ride	O
through	O
the	O
Slough	O
,	O
put	O
me	O
upon	O
his	O
Horse	O
and	O
I	O
leap	O
'd	O
the	O
Hedge	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
drew	O
a	O
Pistol	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
fire	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
behind	O
him	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pistol	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
Ward	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
Man	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Ward	O
's	O
Horse	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
another	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
I	O
met	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
pursue	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
Ogle	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
Field	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Pistol	O
loaded	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
considering	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
hazarded	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Danger	O
was	O
over	O
when	O
you	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Pistol	O
?	O
Ogle	O
.	O
But	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
knew	O
him	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
Ogle	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
often	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Clothes	O
had	O
I.	O
Ogle	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
Particular	O
do	O
ye	O
know	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
?	O
Ogle	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
lay	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
Scars	O
in	O
his	O
Throat	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
See	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
find	O
such	O
Marks	O
now	O
.	O
Ogle	O
.	O
(	O
Going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Yes	O
-	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hodgkin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
others	O
in	O
Bristol	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
by	O
Newington	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
dogg	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Castle	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sick	O
a	O
Bed	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Swan-Alley	O
,	O
but	O
failing	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Pear-Tree-street	O
,	O
in	O
Brick-lane	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
up	O
close	O
,	O
for	O
Fear	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
5	O
Months	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bristol	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Dublin	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
did	O
he	O
never	O
go	O
out	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
privately	O
-	O
And	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Week	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Pinnock	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
every	O
Day	O
with	O
Victuals	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
6.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas-bag	O
,	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
8	O
Moidores	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Moidore	O
,	O
7	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fleet	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
4	O
Moidores	O
,	O
3	O
other	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Thornbury	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fleet	I-pers
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Fleet	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
2	O
Months	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
my	O
Bureau	O
(	O
which	O
stands	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Thornbury	O
's	O
Dressing-room	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Floor	O
)	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
the	O
Back-doors	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
Madam	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Fleet	O
.	O
A	O
Table-cloth	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
Money	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Bureau	O
.	O
For	O
Mr.	O
Thornbury	O
who	O
is	O
my	O
Relation	O
,	O
receives	O
my	O
Rents	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
settled	O
with	O
him	O
since	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thornbury	O
.	O
About	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
usual	O
undrest	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
Dressing-room	O
where	O
the	O
Bureau	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
my	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
to	O
clean	O
them	O
next	O
Morning	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
his	O
Livery	O
and	O
my	O
Buckles	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
said	O
Let	O
him	O
go	O
-	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
sorry	O
Fellow	O
.	O
But	O
going	O
into	O
my	O
Dressing	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Bureau	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
mist	O
27	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Fleet	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
23	O
l.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bateman	I-pers
the	O
Coachman	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
some	O
Bank-Notes	O
were	O
gone	O
too	O
.	O
But	O
opening	O
a	O
Book	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
safe	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cheshire-Cheese	O
in	O
Arundel-street	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
hired	O
a	O
Horse	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
behind	O
St-Clement's-Church	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
changed	O
his	O
Livery	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
1000	O
Advertisements	O
printed	O
,	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
all	O
over	O
England	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Huntington	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
Post	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
41l	O
.	O
and	O
my	O
Buckles	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
Huntington	O
Goal	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Buckles	O
seal	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
this	O
Bag	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
my	O
Partner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
let	O
a	O
Horse	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Evening	O
Madam	O
Fleet	O
's	O
Servant	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
hired	O
a	O
Horse	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
Yes	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
3	O
Days	O
after	O
this	O
the	O
York	O
Coachman	O
brought	O
back	O
my	O
Horse	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Stevenage	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
took	O
Post	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
to	O
Huntington	O
before	O
the	O
Coach	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
accordingly	O
took	O
Post	O
Horses	O
at	O
Mid	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
Huntington	O
by	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
York	O
Coach	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Landlord	O
follow	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
6	O
Miles	O
overtook	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
Mistress	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Mistresses	O
's	O
Money	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Cloak-bag	O
.	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Cloak-bag	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
12	O
Moidores	O
,	O
11	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Forkington	O
,	O
at	O
Huntington	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
wrote	O
this	O
Letter	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
)	O
to	O
his	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Great-James-street	O
in	O
Bedford-Row	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Letter	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
He	O
therein	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
confest	O
all	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
begs	O
Pardon	O
of	O
his	O
Mistress	O
,	O
acknowledges	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
her	O
Pardon	O
once	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
fellow	O
Servants	O
twitting	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
put	O
him	O
upon	O
Robbing	O
her	O
and	O
running	O
away	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
likewise	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
owns	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Escritore	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Fleet	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
12	O
Moidores	O
,	O
3	O
Portugal	O
2	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
3	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
8	O
l.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
own	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
my	O
Mrs.	O
would	O
take	O
me	O
into	O
her	O
Service	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
in	O
Confusion	O
and	O
Light-headed	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
a	O
late	O
Feaver	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
or	O
sign	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
remember	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
Pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
general	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
hurt	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
7	O
Charles	B-pers
Barney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Drury	I-pers
Acquitted	O
.	O
8	O
,	O
9	O
,	O
10.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bellers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smallwood	I-pers
,	O
3	O
Boys	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Shoes	O
,	O
2	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Hankerchief	O
,	O
5	O
silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Head	O
of	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
a	O
Handle	O
of	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
May	O
21	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
a	O
Boy	O
(	O
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
the	O
3	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
forc	O
'd	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
his	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
offering	O
the	O
silver	O
Buttons	O
to	O
Sale	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
appearing	O
to	O
their	O
Characters	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
11.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coles	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
May	O
13	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Errand-boy	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Spoons	O
being	O
mist	O
he	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
at	O
Wybourn	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
5	O
Roses	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
William	B-pers
Kay	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
Man	O
)	O
who	O
receive	O
the	O
Spoons	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12	O
,	O
13.	O
William	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
2	O
little	O
Boys	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bell-metal	O
Mortar	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Westal	I-pers
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kinch	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edw	B-pers
Sawtill	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
changing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
change	O
her	O
Guinea	O
too	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
Sugar	O
and	O
Plumbs	O
I	O
saw	O
she	O
had	O
Silver	O
and	O
Halfpence	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
more	O
Silver	O
than	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
occasion	O
for	O
more	O
Silver	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
Silver	O
and	O
Gold	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
thrust	O
her	O
Hand	O
among	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
here	O
's	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
What	O
she	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
And	O
catching	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
Business	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
would	O
change	O
no	O
Money	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
Guinea	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Guinea	O
of	O
hers	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
you	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Paper	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Guinea	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
cast	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
some	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
a	O
Fluster	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
exactly	O
tell	O
how	O
much	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
hard	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
lose	O
my	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
very	O
quietly	O
.	O
A	O
Friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
gone	O
away	O
so	O
easy	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
now	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
cool	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
more	O
carefully	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
wanted	O
20	O
s.	O
or	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
reckon	O
'd	O
the	O
two	O
Guineas	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
Zacheus	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Guinea	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
at	O
Ware	O
,	O
in	O
Col.	O
Paget	O
's	O
Regiment	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
16.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Waker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
Guineas	O
,	O
4	O
Moidores	O
,	O
4	O
other	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Jo	O
.	O
Hague	O
;	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Touchet	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Holden	B-pers
Bouker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
promissory	O
Notes	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
24	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
for	O
60	O
l.	O
one	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
for	O
25	O
l.	O
one	O
for	O
24	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
for	O
30	O
l.	O
one	O
for	O
19	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
9	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
in	O
January	O
and	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Lancashire	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
thousand	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Cash	O
and	O
Notes	O
,	O
*	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
one	O
Cox	O
,	O
a	O
Portugueze	O
Priest	O
,	O
had	O
brought	O
back	O
some	O
Money	O
and	O
Notes	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
above	O
800	O
l.	O
I	O
got	O
Advertisements	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
-	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
at	O
Bath	O
,	O
wrote	O
me	O
word	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
accidentally	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
advis	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
down	O
some	O
Body	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
so	O
many	O
Friends	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
gay	O
Appearance	O
and	O
extravagant	O
Expences	O
,	O
that	O
otherwise	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
difficult	O
to	O
hold	O
him	O
.	O
*	O
Then	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
sum	O
is	O
not	O
charged	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
Council	O
.	O
Were	O
not	O
all	O
your	O
Notes	O
brought	O
back	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
all	O
again	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
for	O
60	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
and	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
much	O
worth	O
,	O
but	O
besides	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
67	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
apply	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
to	O
make	O
you	O
Satisfaction	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
.	O
She	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Matter	O
easy	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
deceived	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
recommended	O
her	O
son	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
former	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
4	O
Years	O
in	O
Town	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
come	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
weeks	O
from	O
Portugal	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Touchet	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
March	O
3	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
before	O
Sermon	O
time	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
dress	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
Church	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
missing	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Cash-drawers	O
under	O
the	O
Sink	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
home	O
our	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
unlock	O
'd	O
the	O
Desk	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Drawers	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
and	O
plunder	O
'd	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Bath	O
,	O
brought	O
me	O
my	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Shirts	O
.	O
Holden	B-pers
Bouker	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
dine	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
called	O
home	O
by	O
Sam	B-pers
Touchet	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Cash-drawers	O
under	O
the	O
Shew-board	O
.	O
The	O
Desk	O
is	O
double	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
three	O
Drawers	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Flaps	O
lock	O
'd	O
fast	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
opening	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
neither	O
Bill	O
nor	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Maid	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
at	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
Prayers	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
come	O
home	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
12	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Portugueze	O
Chappel	O
,	O
but	O
considering	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
his	O
time	O
to	O
return	O
,	O
I	O
waited	O
'till	O
1	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
Touchet	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
recommended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
Water-side	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
some	O
such	O
Person	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
Gravesend-Boat	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
got	O
a	O
Post-horse	O
,	O
and	O
arriv	O
'd	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
before	O
the	O
Boat	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
among	O
the	O
Passengers	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
concluding	O
he	O
was	O
still	O
in	O
Town	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
one	O
to	O
lie	O
at	O
the	O
Water-side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
myself	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
Post-house	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
neither	O
Place	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
,	O
being	O
Monday	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Notes	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
know	O
the	O
Notes	O
were	O
stoln	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
at	O
Noon	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
our	O
People	O
at	O
home	O
look	O
'd	O
much	O
pleasanter	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Portugueze	O
Ambassador	O
's	O
Priest	O
had	O
brought	O
cash	O
and	O
Notes	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
854	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
safe	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
one	O
who	O
had	O
recommended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
hir	O
'd	O
a	O
Horse	O
for	O
Windsor	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
left	O
him	O
the	O
Horse	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
no	O
concern	O
about	O
losing	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
7	O
l.	O
for	O
Security	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Windsor	O
,	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Orange	O
.	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
500	O
Advertisements	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
spread	O
in	O
England	O
and	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Next	O
Wednesday	O
a	O
Letter	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Ford	O
,	O
at	O
Bath	O
,	O
advising	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
seeing	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
he	O
had	O
stopt	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Bath	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
from	O
Ilchester	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
them	O
both	O
here	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
Bath	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Writing	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Letter	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
directed	O
,	O
To	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Star	O
,	O
in	O
Castle-Court	O
,	O
near	O
Lawrence-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
dated	O
March	O
23	O
,	O
1733	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
therein	O
declares	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Remorse	O
pursues	O
him	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
enjoy	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
Pleasure	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
promised	O
himself	O
-	O
Confesses	O
the	O
Robbery	O
-	O
Begs	O
Forgiveness	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
great	O
Confusion	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Bills	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
Anthony	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
.	O
My	O
People	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Priest	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Notes	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Campion	O
.	O
H.	O
Boucker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Receit	O
of	O
these	O
Letters	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bath	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
premeditated	O
the	O
Robbery	O
for	O
several	O
Weeks	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Desk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Notes	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
80	O
l.	O
in	O
Cash	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Portugueze	O
Chappel	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
met	O
Campion	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
they	O
walk	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
Kensington	O
towards	O
Chiswick	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
Campion	O
the	O
Notes	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
l.	O
in	O
Cash	O
,	O
and	O
Campion	O
advis	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
write	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Falkner	I-pers
;	O
then	O
they	O
parted	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
Brentford	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
hir	O
'd	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
thro	O
'	O
Windsor	O
to	O
Reading	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Lace	O
for	O
his	O
Hat	O
.	O
Thence	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Oxford	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
Bath	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
and	O
Justices	O
at	O
Bath	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Confession	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
]	O
He	O
herein	O
confesses	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Notes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Desk	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Notes	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
l.	O
to	O
Campion	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
.	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
Horse	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
to	O
Oxford	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
tence	O
to	O
Bath	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
21	O
l.	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
having	O
bought	O
new	O
Clothes	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
Boots	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
besides	O
having	O
his	O
Pocket	O
pick	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Whore	O
at	O
Oxford	O
.	O
Boker	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
Confession	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Ilchester	O
Goal	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
no	O
Reward	O
,	O
that	O
your	O
Master	O
has	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
for	O
making	O
this	O
Matter	O
up	O
?	O
Bouker	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Bond	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
Note	O
or	O
Bond	O
given	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Havers	I-pers
?	O
Bouker	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Was	O
Havers	O
never	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
your	O
Master	O
?	O
Bouker	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ford	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
in	O
Bath	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
a	O
Person	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
He	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
stiffly	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
sighing	O
,	O
It	O
signifies	O
nothing	O
to	O
equivocate	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Portugueze	O
Chappel	O
,	O
and	O
beckon	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Hyde-Park	O
Corner	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
of	O
Money	O
and	O
Notes	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
Notes	O
,	O
and	O
scatter	O
them	O
at	O
t'other	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
some	O
Body	O
that	O
found	O
'em	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
should	O
escape	O
the	O
better	O
-	O
We	O
walked	O
towards	O
Chiswick	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
25	O
l.	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Notes	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
,	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
's	O
Friend	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
give	O
30	O
l.	O
the	O
Affair	O
should	O
be	O
accommodated	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
went	O
to	O
give	O
Security	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
placed	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
Hands	O
,	O
something	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
-	O
I	O
lodg	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Havers	O
's	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
put	O
5	O
l.	O
more	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
's	O
Orders	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
'd	O
stand	O
by	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
did	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
told	O
her	O
so	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
comply	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
Benefit	O
Ticket	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
is	O
about	O
19	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Campion	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
drew	O
him	O
aside	O
,	O
for	O
Campion	O
kept	O
a	O
School	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
marry	O
'd	O
against	O
his	O
Friends	O
Consent	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
Distress	O
-	O
Campion	O
and	O
Cox	O
,	O
the	O
Priest	O
,	O
were	O
examin	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Lambert	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
Campion	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
very	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
was	O
present	O
then	O
;	O
and	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Commitment	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
.	O
No	O
?	O
-	O
Here	O
's	O
the	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Commitment	O
!	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
.	O
Then	O
that	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
second	O
Appearance	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Commitment	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
.	O
Campion	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
that	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
for	O
when	O
the	O
Justice	O
took	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
And	O
will	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
your	O
Absence	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
.	O
Campion	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
'till	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Louisa	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father-in-Law	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Bond	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Must	O
I	O
make	O
it	O
for	O
thirty	O
Pound	O
?	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
agree	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
make	O
it	O
easy	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
easy	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
.	O
And	O
Ross	O
said	O
,	O
Down	O
with	O
your	O
ready	O
Rhino	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Ross	O
was	O
very	O
eager	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
no	O
Instructions	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
always	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
talk	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
does	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
stand	O
to	O
.	O
And	O
Ross	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
'll	O
place	O
30	O
l.	O
there	O
shall	O
be	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
17.	O
John	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Pattey	I-pers
,	O
May	O
1	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pattey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
washing	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Shirt	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	B-place
Alehouse	I-place
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
a	O
Lather	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Tub	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Anderson	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Shirt	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
Door	O
,	O
in	O
Maid-Lane	O
,	O
in	O
Wood-Street	O
.	O
His	O
Breeches	O
stood	O
wide	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Bulk	O
strutted	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
my	O
Fist	O
.	O
I	O
clapp	O
'd	O
fast	O
hold	O
on	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
you	O
Rogue	O
!	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
yours	O
?	O
Pattey	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Condition	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
all	O
wet	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
lather	O
'd	O
it	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
let	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
step	O
over	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
satisfy	O
me	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Passage	O
,	O
on	O
t'other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Shirt	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Boy	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hester	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Pattey	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	B-pers
Alehouse	I-pers
Door	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
stuck	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Inches	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
She	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Villain	O
,	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
wet	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
given	O
it	O
a	O
Lather	O
.	O
He	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
make	O
her	O
easy	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
standing	O
together	O
(	O
no	O
Body	O
being	O
there	O
but	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
a	O
Boy	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Shirt	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Men	O
there	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Minutes	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
without	O
him	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
Hours	O
after	O
,	O
this	O
Woman	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
Shirt	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
there	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
convince	O
her	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
a	O
Boy	O
found	O
a	O
Shirt	O
.	O
Several	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
18.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
and	O
a	O
Curtain	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
19.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ballance	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch-Case	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
,	O
May	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
William	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	I-pers
was	I-pers
indicted	I-pers
for	I-pers
the	I-pers
Murder	I-pers
of	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
,	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
several	O
mortal	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
,	O
on	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
Face	O
,	O
Eyes	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
Stomach	O
,	O
April	O
29	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
Wounds	O
,	O
and	O
Bruises	O
,	O
she	O
languish	O
'd	O
'till	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dyed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Adger	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
(	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
)	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
some	O
Straw	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Ray	O
?	O
Says	O
I	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
Answer	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill.	O
Aye	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
She	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
Black	O
Eye	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
accidentally	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
are	O
always	O
giving	O
her	O
black	O
Eyes	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Fault	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
for	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
two	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
Sam	O
Badham	O
and	O
another+	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
other	O
Man	O
struck	O
my	O
Wife	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
I	O
coming	O
home	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
said	O
will	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
murder	O
'd	O
?	O
And	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Part	O
,	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
black	O
Eye	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Mother	O
(	O
Mrs.	O
Ray	O
)	O
had	O
fetch	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Eagle-street	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
in	O
a	O
loose	O
Gown	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
terrible	O
black	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
kneel	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Bed-side	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
plain	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
speak	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
kill	O
'd	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
murder	O
'd	O
!	O
This	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
could	O
understand	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
faultring	O
in	O
her	O
Speech	O
by	O
the	O
Hurt	O
she	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
I	O
held	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
kiss	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
kiss	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
slid	O
her	O
Head	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
-	O
Three	O
Weeks	O
before	O
this	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Do	O
?	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
bad	O
enough	O
-	O
See	O
how	O
this	O
Rogue	O
kills	O
me	O
and	O
cuts	O
me	O
to	O
Pieces	O
-	O
See	O
how	O
he	O
has	O
cut	O
my	O
Gown	O
-	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
Condition	O
my	O
Arms	O
are	O
in	O
.	O
And	O
indeed	O
her	O
Arms	O
were	O
black	O
and	O
blue	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
spent	O
6	O
Pence	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
Friends	O
again	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
Token	O
that	O
I	O
scor	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
not	O
paid	O
it	O
yet	O
-	O
*	O
Stephen	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
.	O
These	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
murdering	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
discharg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Goal-Delivery	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
April	O
29.	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Banks	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
faces	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beating	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Soul	O
but	O
they	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
clenched	O
thus	O
-	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
violent	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
She	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Murder	O
!	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
another	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
which	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Mob	O
gathering	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
Door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
wanted	O
?	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
By	O
and	O
by	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Cary	O
's	O
)	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
-	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Farrier	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Eagle-street	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
seen	O
him	O
beat	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
her	O
Arms	O
as	O
black	O
as	O
this	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
frequently	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Murdering	O
Thieving	O
Dog	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
by	O
Inches	O
.	O
In	O
particular	O
,	O
six	O
Weeks	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
burn	O
Cork	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Cork-Shop	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
drest	O
vastly	O
clean	O
,	O
and	O
leaning	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
drest	O
so	O
soon	O
.	O
She	O
wink	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Labour	O
.	O
I	O
laught	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Labour	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
return	O
'd	O
so	O
soon	O
.	O
She	O
wink	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Hansel	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
laid	O
out	O
a	O
Penny	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
burn	O
my	O
Cork	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
by	O
the	O
dead	O
Wall	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
ye	O
think	O
?	O
My	O
Rogue	O
has	O
laid	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
where	O
we	O
lye	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
directly	O
.	O
He	O
beats	O
and	O
pinches	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
dye	O
by	O
Inches	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fosbrook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
's	O
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
April	O
29	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
a	O
usual	O
Thing	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
mind	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Dog	O
!	O
You	O
Villain	O
!	O
You	O
private	O
murdering	O
Rogue	O
!	O
I	O
'll	O
skreen	O
you	O
no	O
longer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
World	O
shall	O
know	O
what	O
a	O
Rogue	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
who	O
added	O
,	O
That	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
6	O
Weeks	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
cry	O
Murder	O
!	O
and	O
a	O
Soldier	O
coming	O
by	O
push	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Damn	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
you	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
An	B-pers
Beldam	I-pers
.	O
One	O
Morning	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
d	O
'ye	O
do	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Ray	O
?	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
do	O
well	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
such	O
a	O
Rogue	O
of	O
a	O
Husband	O
.	O
Her	O
Arm	O
was	O
as	O
black	O
as	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
her	O
Thigh	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
her	O
Clothes	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
-	O
such	O
an	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
a	O
Thigh	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
in	O
my	O
Days	O
!	O
Lauk	O
a	O
dazy	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
married	O
?	O
A	O
Rogue	O
!	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
a	O
private	O
Rogue	O
!	O
I	O
dye	O
by	O
Inches	O
-	O
But	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Field	O
;	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
take	O
no	O
Notice	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smallman	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
About	O
3	O
Weeks	O
before	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
calling	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
11	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
charged	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
Husband	O
before	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
murder	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
at	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
pacify	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
Old	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
knock	O
my	O
Head	O
off	O
-	O
Five	O
Nights	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
beating	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Door	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
ask	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
must	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
to	O
murder	O
her	O
?	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
disturb	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
?	O
Damn	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
too	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
-	O
His	O
Brother	O
threatens	O
to	O
murder	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
Mr.	O
Broomfield	O
,	O
in	O
opening	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
livid	O
Spek	O
on	O
the	O
Eye-lid	O
;	O
under	O
the	O
Eye	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
incision	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
an	O
aqueous	O
Humour	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
usual	O
issued	O
from	O
the	O
Eye	O
.	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
no	O
Contusion	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
briuse	O
on	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
4	O
Inches	O
broad	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
black	O
as	O
my	O
Hat	O
.	O
We	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Thorax	O
;	O
the	O
Breast-bone	O
,	O
and	O
Pectoral	O
Muscles	O
on	O
each	O
Side	O
were	O
much	O
bruised	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
amiss	O
in	O
the	O
Heart	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Abdomen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Adhesion	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
to	O
the	O
Pleura	O
.	O
The	O
Liver	O
was	O
much	O
swell	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Largeness	O
of	O
it	O
had	O
thrust	O
up	O
the	O
Disphragma	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Lungs	O
had	O
not	O
room	O
to	O
play	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
those	O
Bruises	O
were	O
Mortal	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Fitzhenry	O
.	O
Such	O
violent	O
bruises	O
often	O
produce	O
Feavers	O
,	O
which	O
prove	O
Fatal	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bromfield	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Surgeon	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
beat	O
.	O
She	O
lay	O
under	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Very	O
ill	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
her	O
Husband	O
said	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
black-Eye	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
God	O
forbid	O
!	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
for	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Aye	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
true	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
my	O
Husband	O
had	O
been	O
here	O
then	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
prevented	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
quarrel	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
a	O
Word	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
three	O
times	O
there	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
a	O
Word	O
past	O
between	O
'em	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
violent	O
Convulsion	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
one	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fitzhenry	O
,	O
Apothecary	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
at	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
honestly	O
pay	O
me	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
-	O
She	O
had	O
strong	O
Convulsions	O
,	O
attended	O
with	O
a	O
Fever	O
;	O
her	O
Eye	O
was	O
very	O
black	O
;	O
she	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
propos	O
'd	O
Blisters	O
between	O
her	O
Shoulders	O
and	O
on	O
her	O
Ams	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Woman	O
(	O
who	O
seemed	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
)	O
objected	O
to	O
the	O
Blisters	O
on	O
her	O
Arms	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
why	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
one	O
Blister	O
put	O
on	O
between	O
her	O
Shoulders	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
spoke	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
she	O
grew	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Convulsions	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
Bruises	O
apt	O
to	O
produce	O
Convulsions	O
,	O
or	O
Fevers	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Fitzhenry	O
.	O
The	O
least	O
Inflammation	O
of	O
the	O
Blood	O
may	O
sometimes	O
have	O
such	O
Effects	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
she	O
walk	O
'd	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
Help	O
;	O
but	O
growing	O
worse	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
never	O
spoke	O
,	O
except	O
Oh	O
!	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
otherwise	O
;	O
I	O
forgot	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
Knees	O
,	O
reading	O
the	O
Visitation	O
of	O
the	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
did	O
not	O
speake	O
one	O
Word	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
into	O
Convulsions	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
held	O
her	O
till	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
being	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
my	O
Son	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Dear	O
Mother	O
have	O
Compassion	O
on	O
poor	O
Molly	O
,	O
for	O
now	O
she	O
's	O
ill	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Convenience	O
fit	O
for	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
pointed	O
to	O
her	O
Arm	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
blood	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bled	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
Subscribed	O
three	O
Blisters	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
her	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
were	O
you	O
unwilling	O
to	O
have	O
Blisters	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
Arms	O
?	O
-	O
Were	O
you	O
afraid	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
should	O
see	O
her	O
Arms	O
?	O
Susan	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
only	O
for	O
Fear	O
of	O
terrifying	O
of	O
her	O
too	O
much	O
:	O
For	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
Blisters	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
terrible	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
God	O
has	O
ordain	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
dye	O
,	O
all	O
that	O
the	O
Physicians	O
can	O
say	O
or	O
Subscribe	O
signifies	O
nothing	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
God	O
has	O
not	O
ordain	O
'd	O
that	O
we	O
should	O
shorten	O
our	O
Lives	O
by	O
a	O
wilfull	O
Neglect	O
-	O
Had	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
no	O
Bruises	O
?	O
Susan	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
Bruise	O
on	O
her	O
Stomach	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
a	O
Fellow	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
-	O
Jenny	B-pers
Stuart	I-pers
saw	O
him	O
strike	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
have	O
bribed	O
Jenny	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Nothing	O
of	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
proved	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Cradock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
Convulsions	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Years	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
waisted	O
to	O
a	O
'Notomize	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
always	O
used	O
her	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
mislested	O
her	O
,	O
whatever	O
she	O
could	O
eat	O
or	O
drink	O
he	O
would	O
always	O
get	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Blow	O
;	O
but	O
Poverty	O
was	O
upon	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Elms	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
every	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
blows	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sickly	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
Men	O
are	O
now	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
blow	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
coming	O
into	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
beating	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
20.	O
Roger	B-pers
Bow	I-pers
,	O
Waterman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
8	O
Inches	O
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crumpton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
in	O
Hungerford	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Loddington	O
the	O
Butcher	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
next	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Water-side	O
in	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
Slip-shod	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pin	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
Sleeve	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
.	O
Damn	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
reaching	O
over	O
the	O
Butcher	O
's	O
Shop-board	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Carving-knife	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
my	O
Blood	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
cut	O
my	O
own	O
Throat	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
directly	O
stab	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
dropt	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
stept	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	B-pers
,	I-pers
O	I-pers
Lord	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
Stab	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
Blood	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Cawl	O
hang	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Wound	O
was	O
about	O
an	O
Inch	O
broad	O
.	O
I	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wilky	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
somebody	O
said	O
he	O
stab	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
Hand	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
stab	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
right	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
-	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
but	O
5	O
Weeks	O
in	O
Town	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
Senses	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crumpton	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
ail	O
'd	O
him	O
-	O
Indeed	O
he	O
afterwards	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Devil	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
all	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
some	O
Mischief	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Roughhead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
Carver	O
off	O
the	O
Shop-board	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
at	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
throw	O
down	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Yards	O
off	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
he	O
run	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Roughhead	I-pers
He	O
ran	O
but	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Doors	O
.	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
himself	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
across	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
a	O
Fishmonger	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
the	O
Fish	O
about	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Roughhead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
drunken	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
drunk	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
disorder	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Roughhead	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
certainly	O
disorder	O
'd	O
with	O
Drinking	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
any	O
other	O
Disorder	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wilky	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
drest	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
lower	O
Belly	O
.	O
A	O
Piece	O
of	O
his	O
Cawl	O
hung	O
out	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cut	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
probe	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
went	O
quite	O
through	O
;	O
I	O
drest	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
Knife	O
had	O
divided	O
the	O
Epigastrick	O
Artery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
great	O
Gut	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Mob	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
below	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
a	O
swearing	O
at	O
a	O
prodigious	O
rate	O
;	O
he	O
curst	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
lamented	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
above	O
before	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
Damn	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Liquor	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
dye	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
pleasure	O
in	O
Life	O
.	O
He	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
kill	O
'd	O
quite	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
light-headed	O
several	O
Weeks	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
8	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Cornwal	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Baltuck	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Day	O
the	O
Lieutenant	O
put	O
him	O
under	O
Confinement	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
troublesome	O
and	O
out	O
of-the-way	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Costelow	I-pers
.	O
6	O
Years	O
ago	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Cornwal	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Spithead	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Morning	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
shore	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
We	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
running	O
with	O
his	O
Breeches	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
swearing	O
,	O
Damn	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Putney	O
.	O
But	O
a	O
Man	O
whipt	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Horse-whip	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
drunk	O
then	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Costelow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
enquir	O
'd	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Parson	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
him	O
be	O
blooded	O
.	O
He	O
continued	O
on	O
board	O
3	O
Months	O
after	O
,	O
but	O
plaid	O
no	O
more	O
such	O
Tricks	O
-	O
The	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Steelyard	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
Hat	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
get	O
an	O
Enterprize	O
of	O
uncustom	O
'd	O
Goods	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
hir	O
'd	O
a	O
File	O
of	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
-	O
Then	O
he	O
spit	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
went	O
a	O
shore	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
sociable	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
running	O
without	O
Coat	O
or	O
Cap	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
his	O
Breeches	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
his	O
Shirt	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ran	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Cockswain	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
For	O
being	O
mad	O
?	O
Or	O
for	O
being	O
drunk	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
shamm	O
'd	O
Madness	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
.	O
About	O
9	O
a	O
Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
Prentice	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
to	O
Tower-hill	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
to	O
morrow	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
needs	O
have	O
me	O
go	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Bishop's-gate-street	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
somewhere	O
there-abouts	O
.	O
He	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
several	O
Houses	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
right	O
.	O
Thence	O
he	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
Fenchurch-street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
still	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Loss	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
to	O
humour	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
one	O
Place	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Patience	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
Custom-house	O
Duty	O
,	O
lodg	O
'd	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Nights	O
a	O
Week	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Cock	O
at	O
Iron-Gate	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Clay	O
.	O
He	O
seem	O
'd	O
much	O
disturb	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
drank	O
2	O
Pints	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
and	O
sleep	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
Devil	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Fire	O
!	O
Murder	O
!	O
and	O
swore	O
and	O
tore	O
at	O
a	O
strange	O
Rate	O
.	O
By	O
degrees	O
he	O
grew	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
'till	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Maid	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
9	O
the	O
same	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
,	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
Oars	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
in	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
drink	O
,	O
but	O
threw	O
it	O
all	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
three	O
Great-coats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Fowls	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
To	O
humour	O
him	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
mincing	O
some	O
Meat	O
.	O
He	O
catch	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
held	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
I	O
'll	O
cut	O
your	O
Throat	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
Maid	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Meat	O
and	O
Pans	O
in	O
the	O
Ashes	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
the	O
Knife	O
against	O
my	O
Belly	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
blunt	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Coats	O
thick	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Uproar	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
?	O
He	O
damn	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
threw	O
Bricks	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
unbraced	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
where	O
his	O
Knife	O
was	O
,	O
spirted	O
some	O
Beer	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ran	O
out	O
.	O
E.	O
Smith	O
,	O
Wade	O
's	O
Maid	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
all	O
Night	O
upon	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
threw	O
some	O
Flowers	O
,	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
threw	O
.	O
Mud	O
in	O
Peoples	O
Faces	O
.	O
He	O
met	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
anp	O
then	O
threw	O
Dirt	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
The	O
Soldier	O
drawing	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
kill	O
a	O
Madman	O
?	O
He	O
threw	O
a	O
Girl	O
's	O
Walnuts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Greens	O
about	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
Soap	O
,	O
to	O
wash	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
rubb	O
'd	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Face	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
smear	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
over	O
with	O
Soot	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
blacked	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
's	O
Face	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
all	O
the	O
Windows	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
and	O
break	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
iron	O
Bars	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
his	O
Shoes	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
Yard	O
-	O
The	O
last	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
was	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Sam	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
his	O
Partner	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
pretty	O
quiet	O
'till	O
about	O
8	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
swear	O
Treason	O
against	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
for	O
damn	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
she	O
lov	O
'd	O
the	O
Pretender	O
.	O
He	O
drank	O
nothing	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Holbrook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
with	O
Daniel	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Noon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Men	O
work	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
all	O
their	O
Tools	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
them	O
a	O
Holliday	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
us	O
to	O
treat	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
gave	O
him	O
3	O
d.	O
Now	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
buy	O
as	O
much	O
Bread	O
,	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
Gin	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
all	O
can	O
eat	O
and	O
drink	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
3	O
penny	O
Loaves	O
,	O
threw	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
calling	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Office	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seiz	O
'd	O
a	O
Cart-load	O
of	O
Co-chineal	O
in	O
Stock's-Market	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Basket-woman	O
had	O
rescu	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
his	O
Commission	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
ten	O
Men	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
to	O
recover	O
the	O
Seizure	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
more	O
Assistance	O
-	O
Some	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
talk	O
like	O
a	O
Madman	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
?	O
Will	O
you	O
lend	O
me	O
Assistance	O
?	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
God	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
serve	O
the	O
Crown	O
no	O
longer	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
without	O
staggering	O
.	O
Juryman	O
.	O
Keeper	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
observ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
under	O
any	O
Disorder	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
?	O
Keeper	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
21.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
by	O
strangling	O
it	O
with	O
both	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Turnly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Windsor	O
,	O
a	O
Pastry-Cook	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
John's-Lane	I-place
:	O
I	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
there	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Lady-Day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
look	O
'd	O
big	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Easter	O
,	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
lank	O
.	O
We	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
deliver	O
'd	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
appear	O
'd	O
publickly	O
every	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
In	O
short	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
all	O
alike	O
,	O
or	O
things	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
kept	O
so	O
private	O
.	O
We	O
watch	O
'd	O
and	O
harke	O
'd	O
all	O
as	O
ever	O
we	O
could	O
.	O
One	O
while	O
we	O
fancy	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
might	O
be	O
at	O
Nurse	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
often	O
whipping	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
,	O
we	O
concluded	O
it	O
was	O
baked	O
in	O
the	O
Oven	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
Mrs.	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
going	O
in	O
o	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
Wig-box	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
smelt	O
something	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
so	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
consulted	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
have	O
kept	O
this	O
Thing	O
in	O
hugger-mugger	O
,	O
we	O
wont	O
let	O
'em	O
know	O
the	O
Child	O
is	O
found	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
so	O
Mr.	O
Goldsmith	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Child	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
mouldy	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
deny	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
Juryman	O
.	O
You	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
deligent	O
in	O
watching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
ever	O
tax	O
her	O
with	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
Turnly	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
a	O
Word	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
Creature	O
.	O
Margaret	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Windsor	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Water	O
come	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
much	O
better	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
first	O
found	O
,	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Dinah	B-pers
Beaven	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Child	O
was	O
crouded	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
and	O
patrify	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
full	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
discern	O
no	O
Mark	O
of	O
Violence	O
.	O
Indeed	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
happen	O
to	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
's	O
Child	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
has	O
fell	O
from	O
her	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hawkey	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
her	O
Coat	O
,	O
for	O
garnish	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
these	O
Babby	O
Things	O
,	O
sew	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Coat	O
-	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
Stay	O
,	O
a	O
Forehead-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Biggin	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
22	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ewer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Turkey-quilt	O
embroider	O
'd	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
3	O
Sattin	O
Pillow-bears	O
embroider	O
'd	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
July	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
5th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
In	O
June	O
and	O
July	O
,	O
1731	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Family	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
his	O
House	O
(	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
)	O
was	O
enter	O
'd	O
,	O
his	O
Boxes	O
,	O
Chests	O
,	O
and	O
Cabinet	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Drawers	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
rich	O
Furniture	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Above	O
a	O
Bushel	O
of	O
Soot	O
,	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Dining	O
room	O
Hearth	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
believe	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
Body	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
Chimney	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
sifted	O
fine	O
,	O
no	O
bits	O
of	O
Mortar	O
were	O
among	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Footsteps	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
besides	O
,	O
the	O
Chimney	O
was	O
hooded	O
at	O
top	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Street-door	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
advertis	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
August	O
,	O
1731	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pawn	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pretty	O
,	O
in	O
Vere-Street	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
lent	O
him	O
to	O
raise	O
Money	O
to	O
christen	O
his	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	I-pers
Mary	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isabella	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
August	O
1731	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
(	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
)	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
silk	O
Quilt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
see	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ewer	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
my	O
Word	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
lend	O
you	O
this	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
but	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Gorton	I-pers
,	O
April	O
14	O
.	O
S.	O
Gorton	O
.	O
Coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
South	O
Door	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James's-Church	I-place
,	O
on	O
Easter-Day	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
Right-hand	O
on	O
my	O
Gold-Watch	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
crouded	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
an	O
Arm	O
under	O
my	O
Elbow	O
.	O
In	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
Hand	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
Cloak	O
,	O
close	O
at	O
my	O
Right-side	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
why	O
she	O
crouded	O
me	O
so	O
?	O
She	O
look	O
'd	O
full	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
perceived	O
her	O
Hand	O
on	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
but	O
presently	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
Hand	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dial-plate	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
being	O
outwards	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
mistrust	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Push	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Toad	O
!	O
What	O
Business	O
has	O
your	O
Hand	O
on	O
my	O
Watch	O
?	O
My	O
Hand	O
?	O
Says	O
she	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
down	O
the	O
Steps	O
.	O
In	O
pushing	O
her	O
my	O
Watch	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
on	O
the	O
Backside	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
she	O
has	O
stole	O
my	O
Watch-Case	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
steal	O
your	O
Watch-Case	O
?	O
Says	O
she	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
the	O
Sacrament	O
this	O
Morning	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
The	O
Beadle	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
slightly	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Case	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
sat	O
all	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
West	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
were	O
got	O
a	O
good	O
Way	O
out	O
of	O
Church	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
the	O
same	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
pass	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Ray	O
.	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
to	O
knock	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
in	O
German-Street	O
,	O
a	O
Crowd	O
got	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutrix	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
her	O
Watch-Case	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
black	O
Cloak	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Chair-woman	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
is	O
a	O
Cobler	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
two	O
as	O
honest	O
People	O
as	O
live	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Whitfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
14	O
Years	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Couple	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
Estate	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
own	O
Industry	O
,	O
they	O
live	O
so	O
comfortably	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
are	O
not	O
two	O
such	O
happy	O
People	O
within	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
5	O
Years	O
at	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
's	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Family	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Sir	O
George	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
he	O
intends	O
to	O
trust	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
House	O
this	O
Summer	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Langhorn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Woman	O
as	O
ever	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
.	O
Her	O
Husband	O
is	O
my	O
Tenant	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
very	O
honest	O
People	O
.	O
By	O
their	O
Economy	O
they	O
make	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Appearance	O
,	O
for	O
Persons	O
of	O
their	O
Station	O
-	O
We	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
here	O
to	O
speak	O
in	O
their	O
Behalf	O
.	O
Acquitt	O
.	O
24.	O
Edward	B-pers
Landy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Frederick	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
a	O
false	O
Letter	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Balchen	I-pers
.	O
But	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Flaw	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Honybrook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
cutting	O
and	O
ripping	O
56	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Compart	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
May	O
,	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26	O
,	O
27.	O
Martha	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
April	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
Charles	B-pers
Thomson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold-Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
French	O
Six-Pence	O
,	O
May	O
2	O
.	O
and	O
29	O
,	O
30.	O
Charles	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Thomson	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31	O
,	O
32.	O
Charles	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Waterfield	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
36	O
Pewter-plates	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Pewter-dishes	O
,	O
May	O
27	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
33	O
,	O
34.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
of	O
13	O
d.	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
April	O
28	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
examin	O
'd	O
a-part	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Hampstead	B-place
Half-way-House	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Fig-Lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
met	O
us	O
-	O
York	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
Cummins	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Husband	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
something	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
now	O
let	O
's	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
?	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
they	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Half-way-House	O
.	O
We	O
stood	O
pausing	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
'em	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
go	O
forward	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Fields	O
to	O
Pancras	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
Red-Lion-Street	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Moreland	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Half-way-House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
Men	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
2	O
Women	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Lord	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
those	O
are	O
the	O
Men	O
.	O
You	O
frighten	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
speak	O
so	O
loud	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
they	O
should	O
hear	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
may	O
be	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
his	O
Name	O
is	O
Cummins	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
frequents	O
the	O
Mag-Pye	O
and	O
Horse-Shoe	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
3	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
my	O
Landlord	O
Falkner	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Morland	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
farther	O
Information	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
us	O
Directions	O
in	O
Writing	O
to	O
find	O
Cummins	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
same	O
Evening	O
to	O
the	O
Mag-Pye	O
and	O
Horse-Shoe	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
York	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Falkner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
