TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Seventh	O
,	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	O
BILLERS	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1734	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
WILFORD	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Chapter-House	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXIV	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
the	O
foregoing	O
Numbers	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sessions-Papers	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BILLERS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Trimmer	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Trimmer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
Wharton	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Sell	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mullings	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Emmiot	I-pers
,	O
Gray	B-pers
Sambatch	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foden	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
.	O
I	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Jan.	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3	O
,	O
4.	O
Henry	B-pers
Whitesides	I-pers
,	O
*	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
19	O
pair	O
of	O
Men	O
's	O
Wash-leather	O
Gloves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joan	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
Whitesides	O
was	O
in	O
April	O
,	O
1732	O
,	O
convicted	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
.	O
Sessions-Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
,	O
IV	O
.	O
pag	O
.	O
114	O
.	O
And	O
last	O
Sessions	O
he	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Burglary	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Wall	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
Shop	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Mark-lane	B-place
in	I-place
Tower-street	I-place
.	O
In	O
the	O
Evening	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
Sash-door	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
bolt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
backward	O
to	O
light	O
Candles	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
5	O
Minutes	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Pigeon-holes	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Men	O
's	O
Gloves	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
suspicious	O
Persons	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
as	O
Whitesides	O
loitering	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
standing	O
by	O
a	O
Ballad-singer	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
we	O
might	O
chance	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
some	O
Gin-shop	O
.	O
So	O
Pitt	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
backside	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
House	O
,	O
from	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
going	O
into	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Whitesides	O
trying	O
on	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
Gloves	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Fore-door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Marshall	O
shutting	O
up	O
the	O
Stall	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
Apple-stall	O
;	O
)	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
made	O
some	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
seizing	O
Marshall	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
Whitesides	O
took	O
the	O
Alarm	O
and	O
hid	O
the	O
Gloves	O
;	O
for	O
at	O
our	O
first	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Back-room	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Paper	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
lying	O
loose	O
on	O
the	O
Dresser	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
upon	O
farther	O
search	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
rest	O
under	O
a	O
Cherry-Sieve	O
.	O
Whitesides	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
Marshall	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pitts	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
was	O
singing	O
Ballads	O
,	O
and	O
Whitesides	O
came	O
and	O
saunter	O
'd	O
about	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
hardly	O
three	O
Minutes	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
Robert	O
Alcock	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Gloves	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
a	O
loose	O
Chap	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
we	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Chance	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
a	O
selling	O
the	O
Gloves	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Gin-ships	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
and	O
2	O
more	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
a	O
Back-window	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Whitesides	O
standing	O
by	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
trying	O
a	O
Pair	O
on	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
Marshall	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
backwards	O
,	O
Whitesides	O
ran	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Marshall	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Dresser	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
we	O
found	O
under	O
a	O
Cherry-sieve	O
,	O
which	O
a	O
Girl	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
.	O
Marshall	O
bid	O
Whitesides	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
Man	O
they	O
bought	O
the	O
Gloves	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
Whitesides	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
trust	O
him	O
.	O
Whitesides	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
here	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
resolving	O
to	O
get	O
clear	O
of	O
ill	O
Company	O
I	O
enter	O
'd	O
my	O
self	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
Ship	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
Leave	O
of	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Marshall	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
stepp	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
try	O
them	O
on	O
.	O
Marshall	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
very	O
true	O
,	O
for	O
Whitesides	O
is	O
an	O
innocent	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Gloves	O
in	O
a	O
Dust-hole	O
by	O
the	O
Postern	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
one	O
Mrs	O
Pattison	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
at	O
the	O
Corner-house	O
going	O
to	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
the	O
Girl	O
(	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
)	O
to	O
shut	O
up	O
Shop	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
Whitesides	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
See	O
here	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
!	O
and	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
What	O
will	O
you	O
have	O
for	O
a	O
Pair	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Groat	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
went	O
backwards	O
to	O
try	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
these	O
People	O
came	O
and	O
broke	O
in	O
upon	O
us	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold-ring	O
,	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Quality-binding	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Balladine	O
Silk	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
six	O
Towels	O
,	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Sheriff	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
John	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bromfield	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
Clerk	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
guilty	O
or	O
not	O
guilty	O
?	O
-	O
Why	O
ca	O
n't	O
you	O
Plead	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Let	O
some	O
Body	O
near	O
him	O
tell	O
him	O
his	O
Charge	O
.	O
Whitesides	O
(	O
bauling	O
in	O
his	O
Ear	O
)	O
So	O
ho	O
!	O
you	O
are	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Stockings	O
!	O
are	O
you	O
guilty	O
or	O
not	O
guilty	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
Show	O
him	O
the	O
Charge	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
[	O
Then	O
a	O
Paper	O
was	O
shewn	O
him	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
read	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
could	O
you	O
make	O
him	O
hear	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
deaf	O
then	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
no	O
Body	O
belonging	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
that	O
knows	O
whether	O
he	O
can	O
hear	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Whitesides	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
hear	O
sometimes	O
when	O
they	O
baul	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
must	O
make	O
him	O
hear	O
now	O
.	O
Whitesides	O
,	O
bauling	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
hear	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Indeed	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
deaf	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
remains	O
obslinate	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
press	O
'd	O
.	O
Whitesides	O
,	O
bauling	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
says	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
press	O
'd	O
to	O
Death	O
if	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
hear	O
!	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ha	O
!	O
Court	O
.	O
Read	O
the	O
Law	O
-	O
Batlet	O
the	O
Executioner	O
first	O
tye	O
his	O
Thumbs	O
.	O
[	O
Then	O
the	O
Executioner	O
ty	O
'd	O
his	O
Thumbs	O
together	O
with	O
Whipcord	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
an	O
Officer	O
drew	O
the	O
Knot	O
very	O
hard	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
deaf	O
as	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Executioner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
or	O
not	O
guilty	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
sweet	O
,	O
sugar	O
,	O
precious	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
deaf	O
indeed	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
these	O
ten	O
Years	O
.	O
Executioner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
or	O
not	O
guilty	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
Hold	O
him	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
-	O
Now	O
loosen	O
the	O
Cord	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
must	O
expect	O
if	O
he	O
continues	O
obstinate	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
trifled	O
with	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
away	O
but	O
in	O
five	O
Minutes	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
pleaded	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bromfield	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Woolpack	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Bridge	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Master's-Shop	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
some	O
Stockings	O
;	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
pair	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
heard	O
some	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
say	O
,	O
Friend	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
dropt	O
your	O
Stockings	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Stockings	O
drop	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Great-coat	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Companion	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
Stockings	O
drop	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Hutchins	O
coming	O
outseiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Stockings	O
under	O
his	O
Great-coat	O
before	O
he	O
let	O
them	O
fall	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
that	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fluster	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
33	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cotton-check	O
,	O
Value	O
33	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Aaron	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Isabella	B-pers
Grub	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Aprons	O
and	O
3	O
Shifts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abigail	B-pers
Grub	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
a	O
Trevit	O
,	O
Fender	O
,	O
Box-Iron	O
,	O
2	O
Plates	O
,	O
2	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Varney	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
John	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Catherine	I-place
Creed-Church	I-place
,	O
was	O
(	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
with	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Nutmegs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
About	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Wood	O
(	O
who	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Captain	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
for	O
2	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Nutmegs	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Shaw	O
had	O
then	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
other	O
Customers	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
they	O
very	O
civilly	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
till	O
those	O
who	O
came	O
first	O
were	O
served	O
and	O
gone	O
.	O
Then	O
She	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Drawer	O
of	O
Nutmegs	O
,	O
they	O
tumbled	O
them	O
over	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
largest	O
they	O
could	O
pick	O
out	O
.	O
Captain	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
very	O
fine	O
ones	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
as	O
good	O
take	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
will	O
serve	O
us	O
all	O
the	O
Voyage	O
.	O
She	O
put	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
Scale	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turned	O
them	O
over	O
there	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Captain	O
again	O
got	O
his	O
Hand	O
among	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
Drawer	O
.	O
She	O
saw	O
the	O
Captain	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
twice	O
to	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
she	O
watched	O
him	O
more	O
narrowly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
Time	O
,	O
perceiving	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
Nutmegs	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
pray	O
,	O
says	O
She	O
,	O
buy	O
;	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
Steal	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
ye	O
mean	O
?	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
mistake	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
the	O
Nutmegs	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Osborn	O
her	O
Neighbour	O
came	O
over	O
:	O
She	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
they	O
had	O
served	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Captain	O
giving	O
a	O
Spring	O
got	O
loose	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
surprized	O
the	O
Captain	O
should	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
what	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
being	O
so	O
busy	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
Scale	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Osborn	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
swore	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Osborn	O
stopt	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
struggling	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barclay	O
coming	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Osborn	O
's	O
Assistance	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
making	O
a	O
Motion	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
27	O
Nutmegs	O
,	O
17	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
or	O
the	O
Nutmegs	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
where	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
his	O
Companion	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Captain	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Fishmonger	O
at	O
t'other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
.	O
His	O
Defence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
meeting	O
the	O
Captain	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
,	O
but	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
drunk	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
Spices	O
for	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
Voyage	O
;	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
Nutmegs	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Licensed	O
Pedlar	O
,	O
kept	O
Fairs	O
,	O
and	O
dealt	O
in	O
Hard-ware	O
,	O
Plate	O
,	O
China	O
,	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
Linnen	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
often	O
traded	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
believ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
12.	O
Magdalen	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Byon	I-pers
,	O
by	O
dragging	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
forcing	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
weak	O
,	O
and	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
groaning	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
almost	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
stand	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
with	O
Cold	O
,	O
and	O
Want	O
of	O
due	O
Care	O
,	O
requisite	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
weak	O
and	O
sick	O
Condition	O
,	O
she	O
Instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
Feb.	O
7	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Byon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
keeps	O
a	O
Lodging-house	O
overagainst	O
St.	B-place
Giles's-Round-house	I-place
,	O
and	O
letts	O
Lodgings	O
for	O
Two-pence	O
a	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Fan	O
Painter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
a	O
Groat	O
for	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
groaning	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
would	O
turn	O
us	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
my	O
Wife	O
had	O
only	O
got	O
a	O
Cold	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
us	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
lie	O
there	O
;	O
my	O
Wife	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
stay	O
till	O
Morning	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
all	O
she	O
could	O
say	O
signified	O
nothing	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
pacify	O
'd	O
till	O
we	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
with	O
much	O
ado	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
help	O
'd	O
my	O
Wife	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Stockings	O
and	O
some	O
otherof	O
her	O
Clothes	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Husband	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
coming	O
yet	O
?	O
I	O
'll	O
fetch	O
you	O
with	O
a	O
Devil	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hurried	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
us	O
Time	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Things	O
;	O
So	O
the	O
Maid	O
and	O
I	O
help	O
'd	O
my	O
Wife	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
Bench	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
drest	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
to	O
Church-lane	O
,	O
she	O
drop	O
'd	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
lain	O
Two-Nights	O
before	O
at	O
the	O
Church	O
Warden	O
of	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
receive	O
us	O
without	O
a	O
pass	O
from	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
dismal	O
Groans	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
your	O
Wife	O
was	O
only	O
drunk	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
rotten	O
with	O
the	O
Pox	O
,	O
she	O
shall	O
not	O
lye	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
take	O
your	O
Groat	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
your	O
Time	O
to	O
dress	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
drest	O
her	O
and	O
led	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
helped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
is	O
rotten	O
with	O
the	O
Pox	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
.	O
Coroner	O
.	O
The	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Blotches	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
13.	O
Henry	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Alice	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
Jan	O
29	O
.	O
Alice	O
Gregory	O
.	O
Between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
William	O
's	O
were	O
walking	O
from	O
Hampstead	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
thick	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
between	O
Pancras	B-place
Church	I-place
and	O
the	O
Turnpike	B-place
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
her	O
Money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
but	O
three	O
Farthings	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
turned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
all	O
;	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
over	O
a	O
Field	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
Eye	O
upon	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
dropt	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
Some	O
Men	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
we	O
told	O
them	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pursu	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
.	O
My	O
Cousin	O
Gregory	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Hampstead	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
foremost	O
was	O
crossing	O
a	O
Bridge	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stept	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
he	O
damn	O
'd	O
my	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
but	O
three	O
Farthings	O
.	O
He	O
pray	O
'd	O
the	O
Lord	O
to	O
damn	O
the	O
three	O
Farthings	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Cousin	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
upon	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
damn	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
her	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
care	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
had	O
Company	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
called	O
John	O
!	O
and	O
Dick	O
!	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pray	O
'd	O
God	O
to	O
Damn	O
John	O
and	O
Dick	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
Cousin	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Woman	O
.	O
And	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
robbing	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
his	O
Stick	O
in	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
I	O
stoop	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Knock	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
2	O
Men	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
the	O
Stick	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
Path	O
.	O
You	O
Dog	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
you	O
still	O
.	O
The	O
Men	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dowle	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Row	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
bear	O
Witness	O
!	O
These	O
Men	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
!	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
a	O
Note	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gregory	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
both	O
mine	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Row	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dowle	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
being	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
were	O
just	O
got	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
We	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Lane	O
where	O
we	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
us	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
was	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
Field	O
:	O
We	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Ditch	O
I	O
might	O
catch	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
getting	O
sight	O
of	O
another	O
Person	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
mistook	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
rid	O
after	O
him	O
towards	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Lewin	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
over	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
directed	O
Dowle	O
and	O
Row	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
go	O
from	O
these	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
observing	O
he	O
mended	O
his	O
Pace	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Field	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Deeploe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Copenhagen-house	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
rid	O
after	O
me	O
instead	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
had	O
much	O
ado	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
Deeploe	O
.	O
Who	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
and	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Deeploe	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Brasier	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
in	O
Bull	O
and	O
Mouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Deeploe	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
my	O
School-fellow	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
great	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
14.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Goyley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
two	O
Stories	O
high	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
whereby	O
both	O
her	O
Thighs	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
Instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
Dec.	O
24	O
.	O
Unity	B-pers
Ledger	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
keeps	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
a	O
Garret	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
were	O
lying	O
upon	O
a	O
Bed	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Drunk	O
?	O
Ledger	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
them	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
bid	O
them	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
kick	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
away	O
some	O
Company	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
let	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
come	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mothers	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
on	O
Christmas-Eve	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
He	O
said	O
Lord	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
ill	O
-	O
pray	O
call	O
John	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
Brown	O
and	O
John	O
Barns	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
I	O
am	O
sadly	O
frighten	O
'd	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
I	O
am	O
ruin	O
'd	O
!	O
Bess	O
Morris	O
(	O
her	O
right	O
Name	O
is	O
Palmer	O
)	O
has	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
herself	O
.	O
We	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Yard-door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
lay	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Face	O
bruised	O
and	O
stone	O
Dead	O
and	O
Stiff	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
we	O
carried	O
her	O
into	O
Parkers-lane	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
Jack	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
ruin	O
'd	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
I	O
wish	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
this	O
Bess	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
has	O
not	O
dropt	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
her	O
dead	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
with	O
her	O
Legs	O
across	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
having	O
a	O
Drop	O
of	O
Gin	O
in	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
Six-pence	O
to	O
help	O
to	O
lift	O
her	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
Yard	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
they	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
throw	O
me	O
behind	O
the	O
Fire	O
for	O
speaking	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Posey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
Window	O
looks	O
into	O
his	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
there	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
nothing	O
:	O
But	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
Window	O
,	O
call	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
groaning	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
her	O
how	O
She	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Muscles	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Cramp	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
lie	O
still	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
Light	O
and	O
not	O
disturb	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
I	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
contused	O
Wound	O
in	O
her	O
Forehead	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Fracture	O
there	O
.	O
Both	O
her	O
Thighs	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
the	O
left	O
was	O
Fractur	O
'd	O
near	O
the	O
Middle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
right	O
near	O
her	O
Knee	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
much	O
contused	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Wound	O
on	O
her	O
Ancle	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
Another	O
Surgeon	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Fractures	O
;	O
but	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
,	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
a	O
penn'orth	O
of	O
Muscles	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Cramp	O
in	O
her	O
Knee	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
'till	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
very	O
strange	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
miserable	O
Condition	O
,	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
her	O
Thighs	O
broke	O
,	O
should	O
talk	O
of	O
buying	O
Muscles	O
,	O
and	O
complain	O
of	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Cramp	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
intolerable	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
poor	O
Wretches	O
should	O
be	O
suffer	O
'd	O
to	O
drink	O
till	O
they	O
have	O
lost	O
their	O
Senses	O
.	O
The	O
Houses	O
that	O
allow	O
of	O
such	O
scandalous	O
Practices	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
suppress	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
one	O
who	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
it	O
above	O
five	O
Weeks	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
and	O
Barns	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
move	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
5	O
l.	O
to	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
5	O
l.	O
to	O
bury	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Fine	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
laid	O
upon	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
15.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Arrington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
ring	O
,	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Snapes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
John	B-pers
Cowell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stables	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
16	O
.	O
Acquit	O
.	O
17	O
,	O
18.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Webber	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Webstet	I-pers
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Webber	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
two	O
Napkins	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hardwick	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Jan.	O
14	O
.	O
and	O
Gilbert	O
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
Webber	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Sattin	O
,	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
much	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
24	O
quartern	O
Loaves	O
,	O
a	O
Bushell	O
of	O
Flower	O
,	O
3	O
pound	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Parker	B-pers
Allet	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
20	O
.	O
and	O
Gilbert	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Webster	O
and	O
Gilbert	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Parker	O
Allet	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Sept.	O
3	O
.	O
Webber	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Indictments	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
Gilbert	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Tenant	I-pers
,	O
June	O
23	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20	O
,	O
21.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
Porrige-pot	O
,	O
Sauce	O
pan	O
,	O
and	O
Sheet	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Cockton	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
4	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
22.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
Malachy	B-pers
Sowry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
,	O
already	O
convicted	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Needle	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
a	O
silver	O
Badge	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
and	O
12	O
silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
,	O
Nov	O
9	O
.	O
1730	O
She	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
said	O
Badge	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
23.	O
William	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Leash	O
thread	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Combie	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dufour	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24	O
,	O
25.	O
William	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headclothes	O
,	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Smocks	O
,	O
3	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Aug.	O
26	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
and	O
she	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26	O
Peter	B-pers
Longsworth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
Feb.	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
Edward	B-pers
Tudor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heneage	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
4	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
Jan.	O
17	O
.	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
.	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
Jan.	O
7	O
.	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
half	O
Anchor	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
a	O
Gallon-pot	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
2	O
Quart-pot	O
,	O
Jan.	O
6	O
.	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
First	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heneage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
shut	O
my	O
Cellar	O
door	O
fast	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
4	O
Firkins	O
of	O
Butter	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Roop	I-pers
.	O
Near	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
open	O
Mr.	O
Hencage	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
in	O
Church-Lane	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
handed	O
up	O
2	O
Firkins	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
return	O
'd	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
2	O
more	O
.	O
He	O
kept	O
them	O
all	O
Day	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
carry	O
them	O
out	O
at	O
Night	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Person	O
he	O
dealt	O
with	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
if	O
a	O
Stranger	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
afterwards	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
fetch	O
'd	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
20	O
s.	O
for	O
my	O
Share	O
.	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
usually	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
a	O
Nights	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Thief	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
-	O
Tindall	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
Grace's-Alley	B-place
in	O
Whitechapple	O
Parish	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Osborn	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
put	O
the	O
Candle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
push	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
fast	O
with	O
my	O
Knee	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
private	O
Watch	O
belonging	O
to	O
Well-close-Square	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
hoisted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Watch	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
Liberty	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
Dogs	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
John	O
Jones	O
.	O
Tindall	O
called	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Thief	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Parish	O
Watch	O
:	O
They	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
Well-street	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hitchins	I-pers
.	O
Tindall	O
calling	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
;	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
Chap	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
hurt	O
his	O
Back	O
-	O
We	O
deliver	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Parish	O
Watch	O
,	O
who	O
let	O
him	O
escape	O
;	O
but	O
Jones	O
and	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
overtook	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
down	O
.	O
Third	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Cellar	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
Brewers	O
came	O
to	O
put	O
down	O
some	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Hinges	O
of	O
my	O
Cellar	O
door	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Brandy	O
,	O
a	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
two	O
Quart	O
Pot	O
.	O
When	O
Roop	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Roop	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
wrenched	O
open	O
the	O
Cellar-door	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Crow	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
half	O
Anchor	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
a	O
Gallon-pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Gallon-pot	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
Lock	O
to	O
the	O
Cellar-door	O
?	O
Roop	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
forc	O
'd	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Lock	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
a	O
Bolt	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
see	O
,	O
now	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Fellow	O
will	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
swears	O
a	O
Bolt	O
was	O
a	O
Lock	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
hard	O
if	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Life	O
must	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
upon	O
his	O
Oath	O
.	O
Roop	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Bolt	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
such	O
mighty	O
Difference	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
three	O
indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
28.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold-watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
24l	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mouldon	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
17	O
*	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
the	O
Tryal	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Distance	I-pers
for	O
the	O
same	O
Fact	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions-Paper	O
,	O
pag	O
.	O
56	O
.	O
29.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
6	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Nutmegs	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Shuckburg	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bullen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gallon-pot	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Penelope	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Gold-ring	O
,	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Westfield	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
Hugh	O
Hughs	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
both	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Westfield	O
,	O
a	O
Sugar-baker	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
7	O
Weeks	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
,	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
by	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Wig	O
box	O
empty	O
;	O
my	O
Trunk	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
2	O
Shirts	O
and	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gold-ring	O
,	O
10	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Shirts	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
left	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bignell	I-pers
When	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
Night	O
at	O
Hazard	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
so	O
much	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shirt	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
32.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
a	O
Dutch	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Sattin-gown	O
,	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
John	B-pers
Bulnay	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Pocket-book	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
Ist	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
John	B-pers
Bridgeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bodington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
8lb	O
.	O
of	O
Steel	O
,	O
Jan.	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
William	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Guineas	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
about	O
May	O
or	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
Time	O
exactly	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
antient	O
(	O
near	O
100	O
Years	O
old	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
40	O
Guineas	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Coat-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
Coat	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
came	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Candle	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
no	O
Body	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
I	O
arose	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ask	I-pers
.	I-pers
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Months	O
after	O
,	O
at	O
Poole	O
in	O
Montgomeryshire	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
thither	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Relations	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Nichols	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
and	O
here	O
the	O
Confession	O
is	O
in	O
writing	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Burough	O
of	O
Poole	O
,	O
}	O
.	O
The	O
Examination	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
William	B-pers
Prichard	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
William	O
ap	O
Richard	O
,	O
taken	O
the	O
27th	O
Day	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1733	O
,	O
before	O
William	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
Borough	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
'	O
THE	O
said	O
Examinant	O
,	O
saith	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
'	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
'	O
this	O
Examinant	O
,	O
was	O
hir	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
'	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
of	O
Blackwall	B-place
,	O
'	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stepney	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
'	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
Year	O
,	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
Wages	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
continu	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Service	O
till	O
the	O
'	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
about	O
which	O
time	O
,	O
'	O
by	O
the	O
Threatenings	O
and	O
Instigations	O
of	O
'	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
a	O
fellow	O
Servant	O
of	O
this	O
Examinant	O
's	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
(	O
formerly	O
'	O
a	O
Servant	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
'	O
who	O
frequently	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Carpenter	O
's	O
'	O
House	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
unknown	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
familiar	O
and	O
vitious	O
Conversation	O
,	O
'	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
Brown	O
,	O
during	O
'	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
Examinant	O
continu	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
'	O
said	O
Service	O
)	O
this	O
Examinant	O
was	O
prevail	O
'd	O
'	O
upon	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
said	O
Master	O
's	O
Bed-chamber	O
,	O
'	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
said	O
Master	O
's	O
Pockets	O
and	O
'	O
take	O
such	O
Money	O
as	O
he	O
should	O
find	O
there	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
bring	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
Brown	O
and	O
James	O
'	O
Davies	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Examinant	O
should	O
'	O
have	O
part	O
of	O
such	O
Money	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
Examinant	O
'	O
did	O
accordingly	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bed-chamber	O
'	O
of	O
his	O
said	O
Master	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
'	O
time	O
(	O
his	O
said	O
Master	O
being	O
then	O
asleep	O
)	O
and	O
'	O
upon	O
search	O
,	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
said	O
Master	O
's	O
'	O
Coat-pockets	O
,	O
this	O
Examinant	O
found	O
there	O
'	O
in	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
Bag	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
'	O
Gold	O
contain	O
'd	O
therein	O
,	O
which	O
this	O
Examinant	O
'	O
took	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
deliver	O
'd	O
'	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
Brown	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Presence	O
of	O
'	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
Davies	O
;	O
whereupon	O
the	O
said	O
'	O
Davies	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
said	O
Brown	O
to	O
deliver	O
'	O
this	O
Examinant	O
15	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
this	O
'	O
Examinant	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
make	O
'	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
Way	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
'	O
Brown	O
,	O
thereupon	O
,	O
deliver	O
'd	O
this	O
Examinant	O
'	O
the	O
said	O
15	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
'	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
pursuant	O
to	O
the	O
Directions	O
'	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Davies	O
:	O
And	O
this	O
Examinant	O
'	O
saith	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
Brown	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
'	O
knew	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Carpenter	O
had	O
'	O
a	O
large	O
.	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
'	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Davies	O
,	O
'	O
prevail	O
'd	O
upon	O
this	O
Examinant	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
And	O
'	O
this	O
Examinant	O
saith	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
'	O
the	O
said	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
'	O
Brown	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Davies	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
this	O
Examinant	O
,	O
'	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
his	O
said	O
Master	O
's	O
.	O
'	O
Watch	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
,	O
this	O
'	O
Examinant	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
'	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
the	O
'	O
said	O
Davies	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
for	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Mark	O
of	O
William	O
+	O
Davies	O
,	O
alias	O
William	O
Prichard	O
,	O
alias	O
William	O
ap	O
Richard	O
.	O
Taken	O
at	O
Poole	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Montgomery	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
and	O
Year	O
first	O
within	O
written	O
,	O
before	O
me	O
William	O
Nicholls	O
,	O
Capital	O
Bailiff	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
and	O
Burrough	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
insisted	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
36.	O
Judith	B-pers
Defour	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Defour	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Cullinder	I-pers
,	O
by	O
choaking	O
and	O
strangling	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
29	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wolveridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
leading	O
to	O
Bethnal-green	B-place
.	O
About	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
Outcry	O
that	O
a	O
Child	O
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Child	O
dead	O
;	O
it	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
black	O
Circle	O
about	O
the	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mark	O
like	O
the	O
Print	O
of	O
a	O
Thumb	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
right	O
Ear	O
.	O
Some	O
Gentlemen	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
three	O
Women	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Child	O
lay	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
three	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
barbarous	O
as	O
to	O
murder	O
her	O
own	O
Infant	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
only	O
stripp	O
'd	O
it	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
naked	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Agony	O
of	O
Grief	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Then	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Vagabond	O
Creature	O
,	O
one	O
Sukey	O
,	O
that	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
equally	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
stripp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ty	O
'd	O
a	O
Linen	O
Handkerchief	O
hard	O
about	O
its	O
Neck	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
from	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
laid	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
And	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Stay	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
Stockings	O
for	O
a	O
Groat	O
.	O
We	O
parted	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
join	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
the	O
like	O
Confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Chamberlain	O
,	O
insisting	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Creature	O
Sukey	O
was	O
equally	O
guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
(	O
at	O
a	O
Throwster	O
's	O
)	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
Seven	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
'till	O
Morning	O
-	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
something	O
that	O
deserved	O
New	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
all	O
Night	O
-	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Church-wardens	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
we	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
Child	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Work	O
house	O
(	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
Work-house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
Leave	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
for	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
)	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Mother	O
had	O
.	O
She	O
worked	O
'till	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
had	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
.	O
Thn	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
Penny	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Roll	O
and	O
Cheese	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Penny	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
fetching	O
a	O
Roll	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Roll	O
and	O
a	O
h	O
'	O
p'orth	O
of	O
Gin	O
-	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
something	O
that	O
deserved	O
Newgate	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
hoped	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
wrong	O
'	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
her	O
best	O
way	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
plain	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
Mistress	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
more	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
Child	O
all	O
Night	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
.	O
What	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
dismal	O
cold	O
Night	O
!	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
cruel	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
Sukey	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
bid	O
Elizabeth	O
Scot	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Bread	O
and	O
Butter	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
hungry	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Cold	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
stript	O
and	O
lying	O
dead	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Linnen-rag	O
tied	O
hard	O
about	O
its	O
poor	O
Neck	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Prig	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
Sunday	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
,	O
without	O
an	O
Order	O
from	O
the	O
Church-Wardens	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
as	O
from	O
the	O
Church-Warden	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
the	O
Child	O
out	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Church-Warden	O
had	O
given	O
no	O
such	O
Note	O
-	O
The	O
Child	O
had	O
been	O
New-clothed	O
but	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
.	O
Job	B-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
Fore-part	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Neck	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
Circle	O
,	O
like	O
that	O
in	O
executed	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Violence	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Confession	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
}	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
.	O
The	O
Examination	O
and	O
Confession	O
of	O
Judith	O
Defour	O
,	O
taken	O
this	O
30th	O
Day	O
of	O
January	O
1733	O
,	O
before	O
me	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
County	O
.	O
'	O
THIS	O
Examinant	O
confesseth	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
'	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
three	O
Months	O
since	O
,	O
she	O
'	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
female	O
bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
be-	O
'	O
got	O
on	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Cullender	I-pers
,	O
'	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	O
Market	O
,	O
by	O
'	O
Trade	O
a	O
Weaver	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
'	O
Child	O
was	O
haptized	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mary	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
said	O
Child	O
,	O
Mary	O
hath	O
been	O
'	O
for	O
some	O
Weeks	O
past	O
in	O
the	O
Work	O
house	O
,	O
'	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Hamlet	O
of	O
Bethnal-green	O
,	O
in	O
'	O
the	O
said	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
'	O
went	O
on	O
Sunday	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
'	O
Morning	O
to	O
the	O
Work-house	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
'	O
said	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
been	O
'	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
new	O
clothed	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
'	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
it	O
with	O
'	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
in	O
the	O
'	O
Evening	O
,	O
when	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
'	O
one	O
Susannah	O
-	O
her	O
Surname	O
to	O
her	O
'	O
unknown	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
a	O
Sister	O
now	O
'	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
Work-house	O
,	O
who	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
'	O
Susannah	O
,	O
not	O
her	O
Sister	O
)	O
pursaded	O
her	O
,	O
'	O
this	O
Examinant	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Clothes	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
and	O
leave	O
it	O
'	O
there	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
went	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
together	O
'	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
Joan	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
where	O
'	O
they	O
stripp	O
'd	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
ty	O
'd	O
a	O
linen	O
'	O
Rag	O
very	O
hard	O
about	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Neck	O
,	O
'	O
to	O
prevent	O
its	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
strangled	O
'	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
'	O
leaving	O
the	O
Child	O
behind	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
'	O
near	O
dead	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Witts	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
'	O
in	O
Swan-Yard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Leonard	O
'	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Clothes	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
'	O
say	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Stays	O
,	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
Stockings	O
'	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Witts	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
for	O
them	O
'	O
Sixteen-pence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
parted	O
the	O
Money	O
'	O
equally	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Mark	O
of	O
Judith	O
+	O
Defour	O
.	O
Taken	O
before	O
me	O
the	O
Day	O
and	O
Year	O
above	O
written	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
wicked	O
Creature	O
Sukey	O
seduced	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Defour	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
.	O
She	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
right	O
Mind	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
always	O
roving	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Favoary	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
37.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Holbrook	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Post-boy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth-coat	O
,	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Waist-coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
Nov.15	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
About	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
met	O
one	O
Michael	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
which	O
way	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Stepney	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
of	O
my	O
Company	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
together	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
Question	O
,	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
Reply	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
They	O
led	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
damn	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
strip	O
;	O
But	O
I	O
not	O
pulling	O
off	O
my	O
Clothes	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
expected	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
me	O
twice	O
across	O
this	O
Hand	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
-	O
here	O
are	O
the	O
Marks	O
plain	O
enough	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
-	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
Cap	O
,	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waist-coat	O
,	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
you	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
Hands	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
mine	O
,	O
you	O
'd	O
murder	O
me	O
-	O
No	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
a	O
hair	O
of	O
your	O
Head	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
would	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
Abbot	O
had	O
not	O
prevented	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
Abbot	O
to	O
bind	O
me	O
Hand	O
and	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
But	O
my	O
Shoes	O
being	O
off	O
I	O
got	O
loose	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
when	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
My	O
son	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
all	O
Blood	O
with	O
two	O
large	O
Wounds	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Emm	B-pers
Hooker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
Coat	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Coat	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
bragging	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
at	O
a	O
Gin-shop	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
Abbot	O
up	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
.	O
We	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
to	O
Shadwell	O
;	O
we	O
said	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Stepney	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Fields	O
-	O
In	O
the	O
Fields	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
him	O
strip	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
pulling	O
off	O
his	O
Waist-coat	O
)	O
cut	O
him	O
across	O
the	O
Hand	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
afterwards	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
threw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
bind	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
38.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Josiah	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bennit	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
Shifts	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bye	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
Caleb	B-pers
Charlesworth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
3	O
Quart	O
,	O
3	O
Pint	O
,	O
a	O
Half-pint	O
,	O
a	O
Quartern	O
,	O
and	O
Half-quartern	O
,	O
Pewter-pots	O
,	O
a	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Mantle	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
Nov.	O
16	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
David	O
Morgan	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Window	O
shutters	O
fast	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
broke	O
open	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
Day	O
light	O
.	O
The	O
Roof	O
of	O
the	O
Shutters	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
pull	O
'd	O
pown	O
-	O
I	O
lost	O
3	O
Ale-house	O
Quart-pots	O
,	O
3	O
Pints	O
,	O
a	O
Half-pint	O
,	O
a	O
Quartern	O
and	O
Half-quartern	O
.	O
A	O
Table-cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Mantle	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
-	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
Quartern-pot	O
-	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
House	O
broke	O
this	O
Year	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
broke	O
open	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
stole	O
his	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
-	O
We	O
cut	O
the	O
Slider	O
of	O
the	O
Window-shutters	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Abbot	O
's	O
Information	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
whisper	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
I	O
afterwards	O
understood	O
to	O
bid	O
Mrs.	O
Silver	O
put	O
the	O
Quartern-pot	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
shou	O
'd	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
this	O
Man	O
to	O
Silver	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Silver	I-pers
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Chandler's-shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Abbot	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Abbot	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Pot	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
something	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
both	O
refus	O
'd	O
-	O
Word	O
was	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
heave	O
the	O
Pot	O
away	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
got	O
in	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
one	O
Morning	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Silver	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
young	O
Fellow	O
there	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
heard	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Abbot	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Acquaintance	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
41.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cummims	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
6	O
.	O
Robert	O
Wright	O
.	O
Me	O
Loard	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
faxt	O
of	O
Feebruary	O
,	O
aboot	O
ten	O
at	O
Neet	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
and	O
twa	O
mare	O
young	O
Men	O
were	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
a	O
talking	O
wi'twa	O
young	O
Women	O
,	O
the	O
Preesoner	O
cam	O
and	O
taip	O
'd	O
me	O
o	O
'	O
the	O
shoolder	O
,	O
and	O
aix	O
'd	O
me	O
an	O
I	O
wanno'gi	O
'	O
her	O
a	O
drink	O
,	O
I	O
preesently	O
ken	O
'd	O
wha	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
served	O
her	O
with	O
Breed	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Maister	O
leeves	O
intull	O
St.	O
Ann's-	O
Pairish	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
St.	O
Geil	O
's	O
,	O
or	O
St.	O
Mairtin's-Parish	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
kenna	O
weel	O
whuch	O
o	O
'	O
the	O
twa	O
)	O
when	O
I	O
mat	O
wi	O
'	O
the	O
Preesoner	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
twa	O
Men	O
ged	O
wi'her	O
tull	O
a	O
House	O
;	O
now	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
quo	O
'	O
she	O
,	O
an	O
ye	O
wull	O
gi'me	O
a	O
Draim	O
I	O
wall	O
be	O
much	O
obleeged	O
tull	O
ye	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
caw	O
'd	O
for	O
hauf	O
a	O
pint	O
o'Leequor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Landlady	O
caw	O
'd	O
Betty	O
to	O
come	O
tull	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Preesoner	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Betty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
twa	O
Men	O
ged	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
But	O
yen	O
o	O
'	O
the	O
Men	O
dinna	O
bide	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
hauf	O
an	O
Oor	O
his	O
Companion	O
and	O
Batty	O
get	O
away	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
no	O
Saul	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
she	O
Preesoner	O
and	O
my	O
sell	O
.	O
Then	O
Sir	O
she	O
sate	O
her	O
sell	O
o	O
'	O
my	O
Knee	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
what	O
wull	O
ye	O
gi	O
us	O
to	O
Neet	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
dinna	O
maiter	O
an	O
I	O
gi	O
her	O
anything	O
,	O
an	O
I	O
cud	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
toll	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
that	O
preesent	O
Time	O
d'na	O
care	O
to	O
be	O
consairn	O
'd	O
wi	O
'	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
laid	O
herself	O
on	O
the	O
Beed	O
and	O
said	O
my	O
Breeches	O
hurted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
doon	O
,	O
and	O
pulloot	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Batty	O
cam	O
up	O
tull	O
her	O
.	O
Hanah	O
quo	O
'	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
mean	O
ye	O
by	O
sairving	O
me	O
so	O
?	O
Ye	O
ha	O
'	O
tacken	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
it	O
coast	O
me	O
five	O
Punds	O
.	O
Haudyer	O
Peace	O
quo	O
'	O
she	O
and	O
be	O
easy	O
,	O
be	O
easy	O
,	O
canno	O
'	O
ye	O
be	O
easy	O
-	O
No	O
I	O
canno	O
'	O
be	O
easy	O
till	O
I	O
ha	O
'	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
for	O
it	O
coast	O
me	O
five	O
Punds	O
.	O
Come	O
,	O
quo	O
'	O
she	O
,	O
lat	O
us	O
ha	O
'	O
t'other	O
Quartern	O
and	O
be	O
easy	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
wan	O
na	O
be	O
easy	O
Why	O
ye	O
Dug	O
,	O
quo	O
'	O
she	O
,	O
do	O
ye	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
,	O
ha	O
'	O
got	O
yer	O
Watch	O
.	O
Troath	O
ha	O
'	O
ye	O
,	O
quo	O
'	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
felt	O
ye	O
,	O
when	O
ye	O
tuck	O
it	O
awa	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wonna	O
'	O
pairt	O
wi	O
'	O
it	O
so	O
for	O
it	O
coast	O
me	O
five	O
Punds	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
sairch	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
hanno	O
'	O
got	O
it	O
aboot	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
sairch	O
the	O
Beed	O
,	O
and	O
upo	O
'	O
that	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
tumbled	O
doon	O
Stairs	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
ran	O
a'ter	O
her	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
cross	O
the	O
wa	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
roab	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
that	O
coast	O
me	O
five	O
Punds	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
tuck	O
me	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
the	O
Hoarse-shoe	O
and	O
Rummer	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Landloard	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pack	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
seed	O
he	O
and	O
she	O
Laughing	O
togaither	O
,	O
whuch	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
leetle	O
jeelous	O
that	O
he	O
wau	O
'd	O
no	O
'	O
tack	O
careo	O
'	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
that	O
coast	O
me	O
five	O
Punds	O
.	O
Then	O
in	O
came	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
d	O
'ye	O
do	O
wi'my	O
Wife	O
,	O
ye	O
Dug	O
?	O
Troath	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
quo	O
,	O
an	O
she	O
be	O
yer	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
Stole	O
my	O
Watch	O
that	O
coast	O
me	O
five	O
Punds	O
.	O
Wi	O
'	O
that	O
the	O
Preesoner	O
dinged	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
awa	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wud	O
a	O
'	O
run	O
a'ter	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
wunna	O
lat	O
me	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
twa	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
a'ter	O
I	O
enqueer	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
cunno	O
'	O
find	O
her	O
till	O
Satturday	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
mat	O
wi	O
'	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
aix	O
'd	O
her	O
for	O
my	O
Watch	O
that	O
coast	O
me	O
five	O
Punds	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
pretanded	O
to	O
be	O
Agnorant	O
of	O
the	O
maiter	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Wairant	O
and	O
tuck	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Manged	O
wi	O
'	O
me	O
from	O
yen	O
Pawnbroker	O
tull	O
another	O
till	O
we	O
foond	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
Name	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
hauf	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
feed	O
it	O
I	O
kend	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
-	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
Instant	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pledg	O
'd	O
this	O
Watch	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
neither	O
humour	O
him	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
nor	O
return	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
!	O
against	O
me	O
-	O
Pray	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
without	O
his	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
withoot	O
my	O
Consant	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
this	O
Watch	O
privily	O
and	O
without	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
his	O
knowledge	O
,	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
42.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Plates	O
,	O
5	O
Knives	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Forks	O
,	O
theGoods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Mullington	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Stay	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Quartern-loaf	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Morning	I-pers
.	O
And	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
Stay	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
Rebecca	O
Morning	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Child	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern-loaf	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Henley	O
's	O
Child	O
being	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
Word	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
that	O
both	O
the	O
Children	O
had	O
been	O
Stript	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pye	I-pers
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
Brother	O
's	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
a	O
Woman	O
was	O
stripping	O
a	O
Child	O
under	O
a	O
shed	O
in	O
Finsbury	B-place
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Light	O
and	O
overtook	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Children	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Grub-street	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
these	O
Children	O
.	O
She	O
answer	O
'd	O
what	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
nothing	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
We	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
Apron	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Children	O
's	O
Clothes	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Going	O
by	O
the	O
Farrier	O
's	O
shed	O
in	O
Finsbury	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
say	O
,	O
damn	O
you	O
you	O
little	O
Bitch	O
,	O
stand	O
still	O
.	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
Where	O
Mr.	O
Pye	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Candle	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Children	O
's	O
Clothes	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
44.	O
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Pound	O
of	O
Leather	O
,	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Rasp	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Nippers	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burbridge	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45.	O
Susan	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet-Riding-hood	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
46.	O
John	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Tea-tongs	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
silver	O
Tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Allfree	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
47.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
48.	O
John	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
Plaisterer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
200	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
fixt	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hackshaw	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Hoxton	B-place
Square	I-place
,	O
Feb.	O
16	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Morning	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hackshaw	O
's	O
empty	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
but	O
3	O
Doors	O
from	O
mine	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
Bar	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar-door	O
loose	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
some	O
Rogues	O
have	O
been	O
stealing	O
the	O
Leaden-sink	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
That	O
would	O
be	O
worse	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
than	O
when	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
Pipes	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
examine	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Lead	O
of	O
the	O
Sink	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
away	O
.	O
O	O
,	O
thinks	O
I	O
,	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
do	O
less	O
than	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Welcome	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
Robin	B-pers
Ballance	I-pers
to	O
bring	O
his	O
Gun	O
and	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
12	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
stirring	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
ticking	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
light	O
was	O
struck	O
.	O
I	O
goes	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
-	O
Her	O
Name	O
is	O
Nanny	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
now	O
my	O
Chaps	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
call	O
the	O
Watch	O
-	O
I	O
warrant	O
you	O
the	O
Rogues	O
have	O
got	O
Pistols	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
have	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
send	O
the	O
Dog	O
in	O
first	O
and	O
he	O
wo	O
n't	O
value	O
their	O
Pistols	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
a	O
Pistol	O
from	O
a	O
Broom-stick	O
.	O
Then	O
Bob	O
shall	O
go	O
with	O
his	O
Gun	O
,	O
and	O
Fire	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
hide	O
myself	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Danger	O
is	O
over	O
.	O
But	O
all	O
this	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
make	O
her	O
easy	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
obey	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
orders	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
for	O
an	O
Estate	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
But	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
full	O
of	O
their	O
good	O
breeding	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
stood	O
disputing	O
who	O
should	O
enter	O
first	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
vext	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
their	O
Noise	O
would	O
alarm	O
the	O
Rogues	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
it	O
proved	O
,	O
for	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Window	O
slap	O
to	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
thinks	O
I	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
made	O
their	O
Escape	O
Backwards	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
watch	O
'd	O
all	O
Night	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
push	O
'd	O
in	O
foremost	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Body	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
looking	O
into	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
there	O
stood	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
squeez	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
bolt	O
upright	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
's	O
Lathing-hammer	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
Knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
as	O
he	O
fell	O
.	O
His	O
Head	O
run	O
with	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
so	O
,	O
than	O
he	O
should	O
serve	O
me	O
worse	O
with	O
his	O
Hammer	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Hammer	O
from	O
him	O
-	O
Here	O
it	O
is	O
-	O
And	O
this	O
Knife	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
a	O
Fill	O
of	O
a	O
Farthing	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
49.	O
Mary	B-pers
Goat	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Tatty	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
hair	O
Pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
Lace	O
for	O
Shoes	O
,	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Edging	O
,	O
a	O
Girdle	O
,	O
a	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50.	O
John	B-pers
Melton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elias	B-pers
Micklethwait	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
Feb.	O
25	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
51.	O
James	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
30	O
Yards	O
of	O
strip	O
'd	O
Cotton	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
52.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lisle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
53.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Cloak	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
54.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Candles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Battle	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
55.	O
John	B-pers
Bracket	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Braithwaite	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bernard	I-pers
,	O
by	O
striking	O
and	O
beating	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
of	O
no	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Right-side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Bruise	O
she	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Alcroft	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
keeps	O
a	O
Chandler's-shop	O
in	O
Creed-lane	B-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
Six-pence	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
upon	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
push	O
'd	O
one	O
another	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
Back	O
and	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
broke	O
the	O
Stick	O
upon	O
his	O
Knee	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Fire	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
an	O
Oaken	O
walking	O
Stick	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hollo'ing	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
her	O
cry	O
Murder	O
?	O
Alcroft	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
pick	O
out	O
one	O
Word	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
Blows	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
her	O
?	O
Alcroft	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
count	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
struck	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
she	O
fall	O
down	O
?	O
Alcroft	O
.	O
She	O
remain	O
'd	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
that	O
Posture	O
-	O
She	O
liv	O
'd	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
aged	O
between	O
13	O
and	O
14	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
walking	O
Stick	O
across	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
held	O
a	O
Cloth	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Mouth	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Stick	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
dragg	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulders	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
Head	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
ever	O
he	O
could	O
against	O
the	O
Post	O
of	O
the	O
Partition	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
times	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
Blows	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Stick	O
?	O
Ann	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
strike	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
the	O
Stick	O
?	O
Ann	O
Johnson	O
.	O
No	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
burn	O
the	O
Stick	O
?	O
Ann	O
Johnson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Alcroft	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Body	O
put	O
a	O
Cloth	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Mouth	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Alcroft	O
there	O
?	O
Ann	O
Johnson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Ann	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Body	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Murder	O
,	O
worse	O
than	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
meddled	O
with	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
presently	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Water	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
she	O
lean	O
'd	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
8	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
dy	O
'd	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
9.	O
Percival	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
externally	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
Bruises	O
,	O
one	O
above	O
the	O
Right-ear	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
over	O
the	O
Right-eye	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Fracture	O
in	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
which	O
began	O
over	O
the	O
Right-ear	O
,	O
ron	O
to	O
the	O
Orbit	O
of	O
the	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
Jaw-bone	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Places	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
small	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Skull	O
were	O
beat	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Skull	O
being	O
remov	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
8	O
Ounces	O
of	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
,	O
part	O
between	O
the	O
first	O
Skin	O
and	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
another	O
part	O
between	O
the	O
first	O
Skin	O
and	O
the	O
Second	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
lateral	O
Ventricles	O
of	O
the	O
Brain	O
.	O
The	O
Skull	O
being	O
broke	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
receive	O
her	O
Pension	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
half	O
drunk	O
about	O
11	O
,	O
when	O
William	B-pers
Whitehouse	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Arnot	I-pers
were	O
talking	O
about	O
buying	O
a	O
Goose	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
join	O
her	O
Six-pence	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
buy	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
none	O
to	O
my	O
Mind	O
,	O
return	O
'd	O
without	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
'd	O
beat	O
my	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Men	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
one	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
Three	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
with	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
pretty	O
quiet	O
till	O
the	O
Goose	O
was	O
ready	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
join	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
cursed	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
it	O
might	O
choak	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
Stick	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
broke	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
We	O
heard	O
her	O
fall	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
afterward	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Box	I-pers
.	O
She	O
would	O
have	O
join	O
'd	O
for	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goose	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
violent	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
and	O
curs	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
it	O
might	O
choak	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'd	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Bit	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
cut	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
for	O
me	O
?	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
.	O
Laid	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
Whitehouse	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
pity	O
she	O
should	O
lye	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
Arnot	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
way	O
to	O
lye	O
and	O
Water	O
herself	O
.	O
Whitehouse	O
going	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
Arnot	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Push	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
fell	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
broke	O
it	O
across	O
his	O
Knee	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
That	O
's	O
my	O
Stick	O
Then	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
another	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
's	O
Keffel	O
-	O
We	O
call	O
'd	O
it	O
her	O
Keffel	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Welsh-woman	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
got	O
her	O
Stick	O
and	O
burnt	O
that	O
too	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
it	O
was	O
burning	O
,	O
Alcroft	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Candle	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
Let	O
's	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
at	O
quiet	O
here	O
.	O
No	O
do	O
n't	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
turn	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
fasten	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
She	O
kick	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
fall	O
down	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
has	O
not	O
kill	O
'd	O
herself	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
lead	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
drag	O
her	O
out	O
?	O
Box	O
.	O
He	O
led	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	O
Johnson	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
upon	O
her	O
Knees	O
and	O
he	O
dragg	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
Box	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Ann	O
Johnson	O
there	O
?	O
Box	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
A.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
?	O
Ann	O
Johnson	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
.	O
Box	O
.	O
There	O
's	O
a	O
Curtain	O
to	O
the	O
Kitchen-door	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
over	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Water	O
thrown	O
at	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
?	O
Box	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Blows	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Box	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Nor	O
see	O
him	O
beat	O
her	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Partition	O
?	O
Box	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Ann	O
Johnson	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
beat	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
drag	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
her	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Partition	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
Water	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Alcroft	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
her	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Blows	O
with	O
Box	O
's	O
Stick	O
.	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Stick	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Fire	O
when	O
Alcroft	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Alcroft	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
for	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
break	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
strike	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Alcroft	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Box	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
Woman	O
beat	O
herself	O
?	O
Box	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
's	O
my	O
Opinion	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Stairs	O
,	O
for	O
(	O
the	O
Stairs	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
)	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
tumble	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
?	O
Box	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
having	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
as	O
Francis	B-pers
Box	I-pers
,	O
added	O
,	O
Hearing	O
something	O
fall	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
had	O
hurt	O
herself	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
drunk	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Arnot	I-pers
threw	O
some	O
Water	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
For	O
my	O
part	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
Head	O
hung	O
thus	O
-	O
John	B-pers
Mapelow	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lay	O
on	O
her	O
Right-side	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Face	O
towards	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
pretty	O
close	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
not	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
She	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
Murder	O
when	O
no	O
Body	O
touch	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
did	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
She	O
cry	O
'd	O
Murder	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
frequently	O
did	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
you	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
do	O
some	O
of	O
you	O
:	O
Mischief	O
-	O
I	O
came	O
at	O
Night	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
neither	O
up	O
nor	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
tapping	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
You	O
Dogs	O
,	O
you	O
Sons	O
of	O
Bitches	O
;	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Box	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
noisy	O
Bitch	O
,	O
you	O
sha	O
n't	O
come	O
in	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
still	O
crying	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
crying	O
Murder	O
ever	O
since	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
Gethings	O
helping	O
her	O
up	O
a	O
Stair	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
rowling	O
about	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
,	O
Curse	O
you	O
,	O
curse	O
you	O
all	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Drop	O
of	O
Blood	O
on	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
was	O
bloody	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Box	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
appear	O
and	O
give	O
Evidence	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
and	O
the	O
Coroner	O
?	O
Box	O
.	O
No	O
Body	O
gave	O
me	O
Orders	O
to	O
appear	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
appear	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Trotman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
drunk	O
at	O
2	O
a	O
Clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
several	O
times	O
from	O
8	O
till	O
9	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
still	O
crying	O
Murder	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
no	O
Body	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
At	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
8	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
2	O
Stairs	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
Right	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Post	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
mortal	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
Ann	O
Johnson	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
what	O
past	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
Key-hole	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Ann	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
besides	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Key-hole	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Window	O
is	O
always	O
shut	O
at	O
7	O
a	O
Clock	O
.	O
Indeed	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
Murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Curiosity	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Juryman	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strike	O
her	O
with	O
Violence	O
.	O
Alcroft	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
so	O
violent	O
as	O
to	O
murder	O
her	O
-	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
an	O
old	O
troublesome	O
Bitch	O
.	O
Ann	O
Johnson	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Cap	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
ever	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Wainscot	O
,	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
so	O
hard	O
with	O
the	O
Stick	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
very	O
often	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
noisy	O
and	O
troublesome	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
civil	O
quiet	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaugher	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
56	O
,	O
57.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Clerk	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bedenham	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Merchant	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Blackhorse-Alley	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Dimity-pocket	O
,	O
two	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
6s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Jewess	O
.	O
)	O
Going	O
thro	O
'	O
Fleet-street	O
with	O
Betty	O
Hays	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Black-horse-Alley	B-place
,	O
and	O
Lydia	O
said	O
to	O
Hester	O
,	O
Here	O
comes	O
Jew	O
Kate	O
,	O
and	O
t'other	O
Bitch	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Pocket	O
with	O
two	O
Keys	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
Alley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
