TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1734-5	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	O
BELLAMY	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1734-5	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXV	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BELLAMY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Ld	O
.	O
Ch	O
.	O
Baron	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fortescue	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lee	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Town	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Denning	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Pinkney	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crutchly	I-pers
,	O
Calvert	B-pers
Ben	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lashiere	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hawksworth	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Fortune	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
Yards	O
of	O
Edging	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
,	O
January	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Alice	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Brass	O
Cocks	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
Alice	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	O
guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lockwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Dowell	B-pers
Chessey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
46	O
Yards	O
of	O
White	O
China	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
January	O
11	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Chessey	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Eastcheap	I-place
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
last	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Shop	O
Door	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
White	O
China	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
seeing	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
presently	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Piece	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
got	O
above	O
ten	O
Yards	O
from	O
our	O
Door	O
-	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
this	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Is	O
it	O
yours	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
Business	O
have	O
you	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Pray	O
Sir	O
be	O
easy	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
pray	O
be	O
easy	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Door	O
lock	O
'd	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
shut	O
to	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perrin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Chessey	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Piece	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
-	O
Smith	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
that	O
Piece	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
it	O
yours	O
;	O
and	O
Smith	O
answered	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
If	O
it	O
is	O
yours	O
,	O
pray	O
be	O
merciful	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Perrin	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Nor	O
I	O
neither	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
walked	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Piece	O
very	O
soberly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Mary	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
December	O
23	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
5.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Firkins	O
of	O
Soap	O
,	O
a	O
Tea	O
Table	O
,	O
five	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Caraway	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
6.	O
Edward	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
January	O
5	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gibbons	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Forster	O
's	O
Lecture	O
in	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Jury	I-place
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
;	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Pew	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
my	O
Purse	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
virtue	O
of	O
your	O
Oath	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
before	O
you	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Crowd	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Gibbons	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Mascal	B-pers
Brockelsby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Lecture	O
about	O
five	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
seated	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
going	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
whisking	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
over	O
the	O
Pews	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
under	O
his	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
round	O
his	O
right	O
Wrist	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gibbons	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Pew	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
crowded	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
turned	O
her	O
Coat	O
aside	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
towards	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Pulpit	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gibbons	O
missing	O
her	O
Purse	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
then	O
got	O
somewhere	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Clerk	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
Minutes	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
holding	O
by	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Vestry	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Half-pence	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
refused	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
knew	O
better	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
fresh	O
Wounds	O
in	O
his	O
Head	O
under	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
Wounds	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Wrist	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
those	O
Wounds	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
We	O
enquired	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
He	O
refused	O
to	O
satisfy	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
damn	O
'd	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
very	O
opprobious	O
Language	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Fellows	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
Black	O
Hood	O
.	O
By	O
their	O
Behaviour	O
I	O
took	O
'em	O
to	O
be	O
Confederates	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
several	O
Stops	O
to	O
hinder	O
the	O
People	O
from	O
passing	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
frequently	O
wink	O
'd	O
upon	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
into	O
the	O
Gallery	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
crowded	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Lady	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Pew	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
stoop	O
'd	O
thus	O
,	O
towards	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brotherton	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
whisking	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
in	O
the	O
Isle	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Gibbons	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
Purse	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
Vestry	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Friends	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
send	O
for	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
no	O
Friend	O
.	O
Somebody	O
asking	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
came	O
thither	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
his	O
Diversion	O
.	O
He	O
treated	O
us	O
all	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
scurrilous	O
Language	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
once	O
at	O
my	O
Shop	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
whom	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Shop-lifter	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Vestry	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Friends	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
proper	O
Place	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
my	O
Head	O
off	O
my	O
Shoulders	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
good	O
reason	O
to	O
give	O
'em	O
ill	O
Language	O
when	O
they	O
falsly	O
accused	O
me	O
with	O
being	O
a	O
Thief	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Journey-Man	O
Glover	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
knew	O
him	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Rose-street	O
,	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Cawel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
Gloves	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Tobacconist	O
in	O
Black-Fryars	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Months	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
.	O
He	O
's	O
my	O
Brother	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
Glove-making	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
am	O
I	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
7.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bullen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pint	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Nov.	O
26	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
8.	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Saddle	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rowland	B-pers
Davenant	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Tyer	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Jane	B-pers
Anslow	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Palmer	B-pers
Grice	I-pers
,	O
December	O
19	O
.	O
Palmer	B-pers
Grice	I-pers
.	O
About	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
met	O
Jenny	B-pers
Anslow	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
It	O
's	O
very	O
cold	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Dram	O
?	O
Aye	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy	O
shop	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
We	O
ca	O
n't	O
have	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
my	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Old-Bedlam	B-place
we	O
may	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
her	O
Landlady	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
Landlady	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Jenny	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
making	O
very	O
free	O
with	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
got	O
my	O
Watch	O
away	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
aware	O
:	O
But	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
mist	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Low	I-pers
came	O
in	O
and	O
rescued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Watch-man	O
coming	O
his	O
Rounds	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Houses	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
'em	O
all	O
three	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
found	O
my	O
Watch	O
under	O
Jenny	O
Anslow	O
's	O
Arm-Pit	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
confirmed	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Anslow	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Man	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
needs	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
whereof	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
oblige	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
give	O
him	O
Change	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
leave	O
me	O
his	O
Watch	O
in	O
pawn	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
obliged	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
without	O
any	O
Money	O
;	O
whereof	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
afford	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
nothing	O
;	O
especially	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
so	O
much	O
Pains	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
wore	O
out	O
a	O
Bunch	O
of	O
Rods	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Anslow	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
John	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Quart	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Master	B-pers
,	I-pers
Fellows	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Scholars	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
College	I-pers
of	I-pers
St.	I-pers
John	I-pers
the	I-pers
Evangelist	I-pers
,	I-pers
in	I-pers
the	I-pers
University	I-pers
of	I-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
,	O
December	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ambrook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
male	O
Bastard	O
Infant	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
born	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
2	O
Stories	O
high	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ambrook	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Tiles	O
covering	O
a	O
Shed	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
the	O
said	O
Bastard	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
he	O
instantly	O
dyed	O
,	O
December	O
28	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
Standing	O
at	O
my	O
Garden-Door	O
in	O
Crown-Alley	B-place
in	I-place
upper	I-place
Moorfelds	I-place
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Noise	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
clapping	O
to	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Garden	O
and	O
saw	O
something	O
lye	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
Shed	O
which	O
joins	O
to	O
William	O
Ambrook	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
guess	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
poked	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
New-born	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Life	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Body	O
move	O
.	O
Several	O
People	O
came	O
round	O
it	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
staid	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Minutes	O
,	O
or	O
perhaps	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
understood	O
,	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Male	O
Child	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Window	O
over	O
the	O
Shed	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ambrook	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Sister	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
about	O
Noon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
extreamly	O
ill	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
a	O
Stool	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Stuff	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
stool	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
undrest	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
two	O
Hours	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
standing	O
upright	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
two	O
Arms	O
thus	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
almost	O
distracted	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
a	O
Stool	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
;	O
for	O
about	O
four	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
a	O
Child	O
was	O
flung	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Child	O
till	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
Nor	O
did	O
I	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
till	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
disorderly	O
Condition	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Signs	O
of	O
a	O
Delivery	O
by	O
the	O
Bed-side	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Notion	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
being	O
thrown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
concluded	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
hers	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
has	O
a	O
Window	O
that	O
looks	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
Shed	O
where	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Extremity	O
of	O
Pain	O
she	O
thought	O
the	O
Room	O
was	O
on	O
Fire	O
when	O
she	O
threw	O
it	O
out	O
-	O
Before	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Alley	O
which	O
is	O
White-Cross	O
Alley	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Pomeroy	O
a	O
Watch	O
Maker	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Debrather	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
English	O
Man	O
born	O
and	O
bred	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Land	O
,	O
and	O
dont	O
very	O
well	O
understand	O
English	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
speak	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
into	O
my	O
Garden	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
the	O
Cruelness	O
in	O
this	O
Alley	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
upon	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
surrounded	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Mother	O
?	O
Whereup	O
,	O
I	O
fetch	O
my	O
short	O
staff	O
,	O
and	O
charge	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
to	O
aid	O
and	O
assist	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Ann	O
Ambrook	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
need	O
not	O
go	O
any	O
further	O
,	O
for	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
my	O
Sorrow	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
where	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
above	O
.	O
Whereup	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
quicker	O
than	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
see	O
such	O
a	O
Sight	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
run	O
down	O
so	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
-	O
and	O
running	O
down	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Four	O
or	O
five	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
?	O
Debrather	O
.	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
call	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Steps	O
-	O
and	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
Ann	O
Ambrook	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Newman	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Church-Warden	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
Midwife	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Joel	B-pers
Fremoult	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
The	O
Church-Wardens	O
of	O
Shoreditch	O
Parish	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
Child	O
on	O
Monday	O
Evening	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Contusion	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Scalp	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
extravastated	O
and	O
congeal	O
'd	O
Blood	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Fracture	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Scull	O
of	O
so	O
tender	O
a	O
Child	O
is	O
not	O
properly	O
Bone	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
Grisle	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Prohiberance	O
in	O
the	O
Scull	O
it	O
self	O
where	O
the	O
Bruise	O
was	O
:	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
its	O
death	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Pomeroy	O
's	O
House	O
last	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
who	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Trunk	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
Child-bed	O
Linnen	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
Linnen	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
and	O
Pomeroy	O
's	O
Maid	O
produced	O
a	O
Key	O
with	O
which	O
the	O
Trunk	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Susan	O
Anderson	O
,	O
again	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Key	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
forced	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
File	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Statute	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Indicted	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
12.	O
Mary	B-pers
Perrin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
four	O
Rose	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
1	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
3	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
A	O
Bank	O
Note	O
for	O
40	O
l.	O
payable	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
6	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
12	O
Moidores	O
and	O
20	O
Guineas	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Windsor	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
December	O
12	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Windsor	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Chambermaid	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
without	O
giving	O
me	O
any	O
notice	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Day	O
I	O
mist	O
the	O
goods	O
-	O
And	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Hundreds	O
of	O
Essex	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Chevalier	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
by	O
Madam	O
Windsor	O
's	O
Order	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
known	O
at	O
her	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
12	O
Month	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
Rochford	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
farther	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Thought	O
of	O
so	O
doing	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
it	O
by	O
another	O
Person	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Barly	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Kirton	I-pers
,	O
July	O
12	O
.	O
And	O
14.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
(	O
with	O
Frances	B-pers
Eustace	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stol'n	O
.	O
All	O
acquitted	O
.	O
15.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Barly	O
and	O
a	O
Sack	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Kirton	I-pers
,	O
December	O
4	O
.	O
And	O
.	O
16.	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stol'n	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Barly	O
Meal	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Kirton	I-pers
,	O
December	O
12	O
.	O
And	O
18.	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
(	O
with	O
Frances	B-pers
Eustace	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stol'n	O
.	O
Lee	O
and	O
Stiles	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
Matthews	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
42	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambletee	O
,	O
value	O
55	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Clinton	I-pers
,	O
November	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Ann	B-pers
Vansteenhelan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
November	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
John	B-pers
Spencely	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Aaron	B-pers
Orm	I-pers
,	O
December	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
,	O
December	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
Jane	B-pers
Viner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Waring	I-pers
,	O
December	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10.	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
Edward	B-pers
Stabby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Paper	O
Shew-board	O
with	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
January	O
11	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Pearks	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bonus	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Shew-board	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
from	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop-window	O
in	O
Bedford	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
a-cross	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
pretended	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
under	O
the	O
Shop-window	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dirty	O
Weather	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shewboard	O
was	O
clean	O
,	O
the	O
Loops	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
were	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
were	O
torn	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
Pretence	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
25.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
*	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shew	O
Glass	O
lined	O
with	O
Velvet	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
A	O
Mother	O
of	O
Pearl	O
Snuff-box	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Rim	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
two	O
Tortoise-Shell	O
Snuff-boxes	O
with	O
Silver	O
Rims	O
,	O
value	O
32	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-box	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
16	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Shoe-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
13	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
7	O
Silver	O
Girdle-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
13	O
Silver	O
Stock-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
13	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Sleeve-buttons	O
,	O
with	O
Stones	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
40	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Shoe-buckles	O
gilt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
Metal	O
Girdle-buckles	O
gilt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
11	O
Pair	O
of	O
Metal	O
Knee-buckles	O
gilt	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
Brass	O
Cane-heads	O
gilt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bill	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
January	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
Alias	O
Faulkner	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bill	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
make	O
'em	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Court	I-place
next	I-place
to	I-place
Castle	I-place
Street	I-place
against	I-place
Cranbourn	I-place
Alley	I-place
.	O
The	O
Shew-Glass	O
stood	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
Window	O
,	O
half	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
out	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
an	O
Outcry	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
Wife	O
told	O
me	O
we	O
were	O
undone	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Shew-Glass	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Kenring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
next	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
my	O
Arms	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
Gentlewomen	O
were	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
towards	O
the	O
Shop	O
Window	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Glass	O
Lamp	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
clap	O
his	O
Arm	O
over	O
the	O
Shew	O
Glass	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
so	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
mighty	O
full	O
of	O
your	O
Play	O
methinks	O
,	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Shew	O
Glass	O
:	O
Why	O
that	O
's	O
a	O
fair	O
Robbery	O
.	O
For	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
in	O
jest	O
by	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
the	O
Man	O
did	O
not	O
turn	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
begun	O
to	O
fear	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
earnest	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
followed	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
my	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Glass	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
no	O
farther	O
from	O
me	O
than	O
from	O
hence	O
to	O
that	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
afterwards	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
till	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Pine	O
Apple	O
Door	O
in	O
Castle-Street	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Byrom	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
turning	O
the	O
narrow	O
Passage	O
from	O
Castle-Street	O
into	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
past	O
by	O
me	O
with	O
something	O
very	O
Combustible	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
And	O
presently	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
crying	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
drop	O
something	O
that	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
under	O
the	O
Lamp	O
.	O
That	O
Man	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
from	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
up	O
Castle-Street	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
dark	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
stooping	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
follow	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
Pine-Apple	O
Eating-House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Thief	O
was	O
run	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
mistaken	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
hold	O
him	O
fast	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Thief	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
I	O
obliged	O
him	O
to	O
turn	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Shew	O
Glass	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
were	O
picking	O
the	O
Toys	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kennel	O
.	O
I	O
led	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Constable	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
26.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
(	O
with	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
150	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
.	O
being	O
fixt	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goodrick	I-pers
.	O
Esq	O
;	O
January	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
22	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callimanco	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Grimolt	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
January	O
10	O
.	O
Cole	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
James	O
guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	B-pers
,	O
December	O
20	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Confectionary	O
.	O
And	O
upon	O
offering	O
to	O
pawn	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
in	O
Charles-Street	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Square	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
stopt	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Hodges	O
applying	O
to	O
the	O
Board	O
of	O
Green-Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examined	O
,	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Spoons	O
with	O
the	O
Desert	O
from	O
the	O
Princess	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
to	O
the	O
Confectionary	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
scraped	O
out	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
John	B-pers
Pawley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Drawer	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Studds	O
,	O
six	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
forty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hargrove	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30.	O
Rowland	B-pers
Kendenell	I-pers
,	O
Hester	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Culpan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Huffard	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Uffart	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
December	O
27	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Culpan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
Linnen	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty	O
sixth	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Feathers	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
sold	O
as	O
many	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
House	O
as	O
came	O
to	O
4	O
l.	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
(	I-place
or	I-place
Horn	I-place
)	I-place
and	I-place
Horse-Shoe	I-place
-	O
One	O
John	B-pers
Uffard	I-pers
keeps	O
the	O
House	O
-	O
And	O
there	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
eighteen	O
Penny	O
Bowls	O
of	O
Punch	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
paid	O
three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
Rowland	B-pers
Kendenell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Drawer	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
thirty	O
five	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Landlady	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
followed	O
him	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Demand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
my	O
Life	O
was	O
in	O
danger	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
rob	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
worth	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
Cox	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
away	O
peaceably	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
still	O
insisted	O
upon	O
their	O
first	O
Demand	O
of	O
thirty	O
five	O
Shillings	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
Cox	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
But	O
Kendenell	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
coming	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
Guinea	O
.	O
And	O
with	O
that	O
they	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Kendenell	O
wrenched	O
open	O
my	O
Hand	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
murder	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
Mason	O
had	O
not	O
desired	O
'em	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
to	O
beat	O
me	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Yards	O
of	O
Kenting	O
Linnen	O
under	O
my	O
Coat	O
.	O
Kendenell	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
has	O
he	O
got	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
Budget	O
?	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Voice	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
say	O
,	O
Beat	O
the	O
Dog	O
!	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Tom	O
Smith	O
who	O
lived	O
next	O
Door	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Tom	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
called	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
ventur	O
'd	O
in	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
for	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
sworn	O
his	O
Life	O
away	O
-	O
And	O
Justice	O
Mitford	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
them	O
,	O
advised	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
know	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
vile	O
Creatures	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Cox	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
bring	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
you	O
into	O
our	O
House	O
?	O
Culpan	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Cox	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
-	O
He	O
staid	O
till	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hickembotham	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
came	O
several	O
times	O
as	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
Culpan	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
satisfaction	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
them	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
not	O
sure	O
that	O
Lewis	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Feathers	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
Sheeting	O
,	O
Damask	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Work	O
'd	O
Petticoat	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
4	O
l.	O
He	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Horn	O
and	O
Horse-shoe	O
next	O
Door	O
.	O
He	O
returned	O
about	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
prodigiously	O
.	O
His	O
Shirt	O
was	O
bloody	O
and	O
torn	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
strong	O
as	O
Towelling	O
.	O
His	O
Nose	O
bled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wiped	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
Apron	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
hardly	O
have	O
ventured	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Mason	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
Betty	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Horn	O
and	O
Horse-shoe	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
Hill	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
-	O
She	O
is	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
sometimes	O
goes	O
into	O
Gentlemen	O
's	O
Company	O
-	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
-	O
About	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
mind	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Oath	O
never	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
House	O
again	O
-	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
some	O
Trouble	O
-	O
for	O
Cox	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Uffard	I-pers
,	O
had	O
sent	O
my	O
next	O
Door	O
Neighbour	O
(	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
)	O
to	O
Goal	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
Affair	O
of	O
their	O
own	O
coming	O
on	O
,	O
they	O
thought	O
it	O
best	O
to	O
drop	O
that	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Bill	O
Ignoramus	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Cox	O
's	O
Brother	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Ca	O
n't	O
we	O
mitigate	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
're	O
a	O
roguish	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wont	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Defence	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty	O
sixth	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
And	O
her	O
Brother	O
,	O
Mr	O
,	O
Uffard	O
.	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
Day	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
an	O
ordinary	O
mean-drest	O
Creature	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
together	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Kendenell	O
,	O
the	O
Drawer	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
above	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
drank	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Bowls	O
of	O
Arrack	O
Punch	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
!	O
did	O
you	O
two	O
drink	O
all	O
that	O
?	O
Frances	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Frances	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
Till	O
a	O
Quarter	O
past	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
-	O
But	O
now	O
I	O
think	O
o	O
n't	O
,	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
came	O
up	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
her	O
drink	O
with	O
us	O
-	O
We	O
had	O
something	O
for	O
Supper	O
:	O
and	O
after	O
Supper	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
but	O
stay	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
how	O
much	O
he	O
spent	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
:	O
The	O
Drawer	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
thirty	O
one	O
Shillings	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
Bill	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
time	O
enough	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
going	O
yet	O
-	O
The	O
Supper	O
was	O
cold	O
Victuals	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
on	O
Christmass-Day	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
two	O
Shillings	O
for	O
eating	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
for	O
Punch	O
and	O
Wine	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
:	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
several	O
other	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
Culpan	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
up	O
any	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
If	O
her	O
Character	O
was	O
inquired	O
into	O
-	O
Frances	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Character	O
?	O
Mind	O
the	O
Ignorance	O
of	O
the	O
Fellow	O
!	O
-	O
Sure	O
I	O
think	O
my	O
Character	O
will	O
stand	O
upon	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
footing	O
as	O
yours	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
A	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Pall-mall	O
employed	O
me	O
to	O
cut	O
some	O
Diamonds	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
my	O
Work	O
home	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
in	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
she	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Mason	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Harris	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
At	O
three	O
Quarters	O
past	O
eight	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
.	O
They	O
drank	O
Wine	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
Pint	O
.	O
In	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
the	O
Woman	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Harris	O
went	O
up	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Bowls	O
of	O
Arrack	O
Punch	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
Work	O
to	O
Pall-mall	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
paid	O
me	O
5	O
l.	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
Cox	O
's	O
at	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
Bottle	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Harris	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
staid	O
above	O
with	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
And	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
down	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Women	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
called	O
for	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
Bowls	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
because	O
her	O
Brother	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
rung	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
the	O
Drawer	O
went	O
up	O
.	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
told	O
him	O
2	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
He	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
used	O
him	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Bell	O
ringing	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
he	O
complained	O
as	O
before	O
of	O
being	O
beat	O
and	O
abused	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
consented	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
-and	O
Mrs.	O
Mason	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
all	O
went	O
up	O
together	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Drawer	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
his	O
Shirt	O
-	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
told	O
him	O
2	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
He	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Gill	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
drank	O
and	O
paid	O
her	O
fix	O
Pence	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Complaint	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
Good	O
Morrow	O
to	O
ye	O
Landlady	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
away	O
-	O
And	O
as	O
for	O
Linnen	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
.	O
At	O
nine	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
dirty	O
ordinary	O
Creature	O
.	O
They	O
drank	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
They	O
staid	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Creature	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Drawer	O
desired	O
this	O
Lady	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Harris	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
several	O
Bowls	O
of	O
Arrack	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
before	O
they	O
parted	O
.	O
My	O
Bed	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
to	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
what	O
was	O
doing	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
go	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Women	O
come	O
up	O
.	O
Between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Bill	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
but	O
assaulted	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
hearing	O
this	O
,	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
were	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
tore	O
his	O
Shirt	O
.	O
They	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Mason	O
,	O
and	O
Moses	O
Levi	O
:	O
And	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
made	O
no	O
more	O
scruple	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
's	O
Hands	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
went	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
drank	O
a	O
Gill	O
of	O
Brandy	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Good	O
Morrow	O
Landlady	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
quarrelling	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Drawer	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Levi	O
,	O
swore	O
otherwise	O
.	O
-	O
Here	O
Levi	O
-	O
You	O
said	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
Cox	O
and	O
Mason	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fought	O
together	O
.	O
Levi	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Skirmish	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
struck	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
parted	O
'em	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
say	O
you	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
Eleanor	O
Sutton	O
?	O
Eleanor	O
Sutton	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Drawer	O
quarrelled	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
present	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Noise	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
the	O
Drawer	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
Levi	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
paid	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Humour	O
-	O
The	O
Quarrel	O
was	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Smith	O
,	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
impossible	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
most	O
,	O
a	O
Quarter	O
past	O
three	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
crying	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
31.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wheel	I-pers
,	O
January	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Callico	O
Work	O
'd	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
lined	O
with	O
Blue	O
Sattin	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
four	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
rich	O
Laced-handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
six	O
Suits	O
of	O
Laced	O
Pinners	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
double	O
Laced	O
Hankerchief	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Mother	O
of	O
Pearl	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
,	O
six	O
Silk	O
Aprons	O
,	O
twelve	O
Cambrick	O
Hankerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Clogs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chilton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
May	O
12	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Chilton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Hen	B-place
and	I-place
Chickens	I-place
in	I-place
Cloth-Fair	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
and	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
Month	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Son	O
about	O
seventeen	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
lame	O
of	O
the	O
Palsly	O
,	O
and	O
quite	O
helpless	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
twelfth	O
of	O
last	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
only	O
my	O
Son	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
We	O
returned	O
at	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
the	O
Maid	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
four	O
o'Clock	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
House	O
where	O
we	O
staid	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
coming	O
by	O
nine	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
borrowed	O
a	O
Ladder	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Busling	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
heard	O
her	O
come	O
down	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
found	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
us	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
we	O
were	O
much	O
surprised	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Richardson	O
,	O
a	O
Milliner	O
in	O
Paternoster-Row	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
and	O
enquired	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
a	O
Friend	O
at	O
Gloucester	O
informing	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
married	O
to	O
one	O
Gardner	O
a	O
Chimney-Sweeper	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
were	O
then	O
gone	O
about	O
the	O
Country	O
sweeping	O
Chimneys	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
Patterns	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hemmings	O
,	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
Gloucester	O
Goal	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
Having	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Lythe	O
,	O
the	O
Arch	O
Deacon	O
of	O
Gloucester	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
her	O
Lodging	O
at	O
Little-worth	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Cloak	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
matches	O
with	O
the	O
Pattern	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
her	O
there	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
my	O
Master	O
-	O
She	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
at	O
Gloucester	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Callico	O
Gown	O
to	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Gown	O
accordingly	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Maid	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
to	O
Pieces	O
to	O
clean	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
very	O
black	O
by	O
wearing	O
it	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
sweet	O
Chimneys	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
lined	O
with	O
blue	O
Sattin	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hemmings	O
.	O
The	O
Cloak	O
was	O
first	O
found	O
at	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
James	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Dragon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Quilted	O
Coat	O
were	O
her	O
Mistress	O
Chilton	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Gown	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
at	O
Shresbury	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
beafore	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
33.	O
Peter	B-pers
Votiere	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hyat	I-pers
,	O
January	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
David	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Siver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lanty	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Coburn	I-pers
,	O
December	O
26	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
35.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gowen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Plate	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
four	O
Clouts	O
,	O
a	O
Box-Iron	O
and	O
Heater	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
April	O
24	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
36.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hewit	I-pers
,	O
January	O
2	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
37.	O
Mary	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Grigs	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38.	O
William	B-pers
Willicomb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
December	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stew	O
Pan	O
,	O
a	O
Sauce	O
Pan	O
,	O
a	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Dish	O
,	O
four	O
Plates	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
40.	O
John	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
December	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41.	O
Susan	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Sauce	O
Pans	O
,	O
a	O
Porringer	O
,	O
a	O
Towel	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Greenwall	I-pers
,	O
January	O
1	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
42.	O
Mary	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
21	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Check	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
December	O
16	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
43.	O
William	B-pers
Beer	I-pers
,	O
*	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
last	O
Sessions	O
against	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Pim	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Corbet	O
Anthorp	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Part	O
II	O
.	O
Page	O
3	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
three	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
.	O
January	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
44.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Churchill	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Holms	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
.	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Wast-coat	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
Street	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
Churchill	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
Iron	O
and	O
Heater	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Nut	I-pers
January	O
7	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
46.	O
Martha	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Racket	I-pers
's	O
,	O
December	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
47.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Lock	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Phillip	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
December	O
6	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
48.	O
Henry	B-pers
Stary	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
January	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
49.	O
John	B-pers
Putney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
150	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
Stable	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Beverage	I-pers
,	O
December	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50.	O
Jane	B-pers
Heybourn	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Habron	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Mullington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
December	O
14	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Mullington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
three	B-place
Cups	I-place
in	I-place
Bedford	I-place
Street	I-place
near	I-place
Bedford	I-place
Row	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
found	O
my	O
Cup-board	O
wrench	O
'd	O
open	O
and	O
mist	O
my	O
Plate	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
such	O
Plate	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
stopt	O
it	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Round	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
last	O
and	O
she	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
hid	O
her	O
self	O
in	O
my	O
Club-Room	O
'till	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
all	O
abed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
wrench	O
'd	O
open	O
my	O
Cup-board	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Mug	O
and	O
Spoons	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
off	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
unbolted	O
the	O
Back-door	O
which	O
she	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Reynold	O
a	O
Pawn	O
broker	O
in	O
Hart-Street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
An	O
Old	O
Woman	O
who	O
lives	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
,	O
brought	O
this	O
Tankard	O
and	O
two	O
Spoons	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
pledged	O
as	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
stept	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
accidentally	O
called	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
this	O
Account	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
came	O
over	O
not	O
long	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
outright	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
advised	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
upon	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
stopt	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
Aunt	O
Hastings	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Captain	O
's	O
Widow	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Trinity	O
Alms-houses	O
at	O
Mile-End	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
that	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
hid	O
her	O
self	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
'till	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
abed	O
and	O
then	O
forced	O
open	O
the	O
Cup-board	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
self	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Back-doors	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tickeridge	O
.	O
Between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
that	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
Tankard	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
stolen	O
and	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
apprehend	O
her	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Mistress	O
you	O
ha	O
n't	O
paid	O
your	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
ye	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
an	O
impudent	O
Fellow	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hilder	O
she	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
conceal	O
'd	O
her	O
self	O
in	O
Mullinton	O
's	O
Club	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
off	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
wrench	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Cupboard-door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
thence	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
opened	O
the	O
Back-door	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
by	O
two	O
Names	O
,	O
Williams	O
and	O
Hephourn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
Scotch	O
Guards	O
in	O
the	O
Barracks	O
at	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
often	O
beat	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
do	O
such	O
things	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
A	O
little	O
before	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Hart-Street	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Liquor	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
three	O
Pence	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
drink	O
a	O
Spoonfull	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
Coffee	O
.	O
She	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
being	O
greatly	O
fatigued	O
with	O
sitting	O
up	O
three	O
Nights	O
with	O
her	O
Aunt	O
at	O
Mile-End	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
from	O
thence	O
in	O
the	O
Rain	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
wet	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
Aunt	O
had	O
done	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
than	O
she	O
expected	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
some	O
Plate	O
.	O
She	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
and	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
present	O
Money	O
upon	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
Servant	O
carried	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
two	O
Spoons	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Reynold	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
Friends	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
Yes	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
at	O
a	O
Box-makers	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Gray's-Inn-Passage	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Three	O
Cups	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
which	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
a	O
Woman	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Plate	O
which	O
I	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Landlord	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
the	O
Mug	O
and	O
three	O
Spoons	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
fourth	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Plate	O
with	O
his	O
Second	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
know	O
the	O
Marks	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
your	O
's	O
Mr.	O
Mullington	O
.	O
I	O
hid	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
your	O
Club-room	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
abed	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Tankard	O
off	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cup-board	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
silly	O
in	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
51.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Margaret	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Place	O
called	O
Dumb	B-place
's	I-place
Alley	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
Highway	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
George	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
.	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
five	O
Shifts	O
,	O
six	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
eight	O
Caps	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Fan	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Knot	O
.	O
two	O
Combs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Head	O
,	O
November	O
30	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
thirtieth	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
Service	O
in	O
the	O
Meuse	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
with	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
first	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
She	O
followed	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
quit	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
turning	O
out	O
of	O
Holborn	O
into	O
Dumb	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Bundle	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
occasion	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
forward	O
.	O
She	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
my	O
Knees	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Bundle	O
The	O
last	O
time	O
that	O
she	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
I	O
broke	O
my	O
Face	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
-	O
Dumb	O
's	O
Alley	O
is	O
pretty	O
long	O
and	O
very	O
narrow	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Houses	O
that	O
had	O
Doors	O
opening	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Men	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
how	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
they	O
run	O
into	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
a	O
wrong	O
Woman	O
.	O
But	O
afterwards	O
they	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Carman	O
,	O
by	O
whose	O
means	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
bed	O
in	O
a	O
two	O
Penny	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Fletcher	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Church-Street	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
then	O
got	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
her	O
Neck	O
though	O
she	O
afterwards	O
made	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
But	O
these	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Sattin	O
Gown	O
,	O
three	O
Shifts	O
,	O
two	O
Aprons	O
.	O
Cambrick	O
Head	O
Cloths	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Caps	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Landlady	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
's	O
Possession	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Butler	O
had	O
redeem	O
'd	O
them	O
and	O
bought	O
them	O
outright	O
.	O
The	O
risoner	O
made	O
a	O
Confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Mitford	O
in	O
Wild	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
sign	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Ball	O
in	O
King-Street	O
by	O
the	O
Seven-Dials	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-brokers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
out	O
these	O
Goods	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sample	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
were	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
Masters	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
four	O
Doors	O
beyond	O
Dumb	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Alley	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
end	O
next	O
Holborn	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
past	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
towards	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
under	O
an	O
Arch	O
that	O
leads	O
into	O
High-Street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
.	O
Lord	O
Master	O
!	O
says	O
she	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
afterwards	O
to	O
a	O
Pawn-brokers	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Bishop	O
's	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Carman	O
,	O
who	O
by	O
the	O
Description	O
we	O
gave	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
directed	O
us	O
for	O
farther	O
Information	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
Sister	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
That	O
Night	O
as	O
my	O
Sister	O
left	O
her	O
Service	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
with	O
her	O
Face	O
cut	O
and	O
very	O
bloody	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
End	O
of	O
Dumb	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Soul	O
in	O
the	O
Alley	O
but	O
my	O
self	O
when	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
52.	O
William	B-pers
Whitmore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Dillow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
five	O
Plates	O
,	O
two	O
Sauce	O
Pans	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
three	O
Hats	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Aprons	O
,	O
November	O
28	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
53.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Bag	O
,	O
seven	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
thirty	O
six	O
Shillings	O
each	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
sixteen	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Pollamounter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Glascock	I-pers
,	O
December	O
26	O
.	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Nicholas	O
Pollamounter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty	O
sixth	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
Coach	O
in	O
Westminister	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cornish	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
Sheer-Lane	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
.	O
And	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
two	O
Girls	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
Humour	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Angel	B-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
Tavern	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Corner	I-place
of	I-place
Sheer-Lane	I-place
,	I-place
by	I-place
Temple-Bar	I-place
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Glascock	I-pers
keeps	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lives	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
two	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Cakes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cornish	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
our	O
Company	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
eleven	O
Portugal	O
Six	O
and	O
Thirty	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
and	O
sixteen	O
Guineas	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
.	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
this	O
Bag	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
which	O
was	O
6	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
The	O
two	O
Girls	O
were	O
dismist	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
rung	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Girl	O
whose	O
Name	O
was	O
Margaret	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
came	O
in	O
.	O
She	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
time	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Bag	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Cornish	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
my	O
Loss	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
make	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
Reward	O
for	O
my	O
Trouble	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
you	O
to	O
your	O
Money	O
again	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
and	O
Cornish	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
she	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
Cornish	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
insisted	O
upon	O
a	O
Discharge	O
,	O
and	O
Cornish	O
writ	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
returned	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Cornish	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
counted	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
received	O
four	O
Six	O
and	O
Thirty	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
for	O
returning	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
rest	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
Right-hand	O
Breeches-Pocket	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
safe	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
besides	O
having	O
the	O
four	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
,	O
insisted	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Arrack	O
Punch	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
another	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
not	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
above	O
where	O
I	O
first	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Girls	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
below	O
Stairs	O
.	O
At	O
drinking	O
the	O
second	O
Bowl	O
,	O
the	O
Landlady	O
,	O
Mary	O
Glascock	O
,	O
called	O
Cornish	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Peg	O
Bouther	O
together	O
.	O
Peg	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
Minutes	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Minutes	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
begun	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Noise	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Girl	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
mistrust	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
served	O
me	O
so	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
sober	O
-	O
nor	O
quite	O
drunk	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
knew	O
Peg	O
full	O
well	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
But	O
Cornish	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
drank	O
nothing	O
but	O
Water	O
with	O
a	O
Toast	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
Company	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Girl	O
returned	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
Pollamounter	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
you	O
and	O
she	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
cautious	O
of	O
asking	O
Questions	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
will	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
-	O
But	O
were	O
not	O
you	O
robb	O
'd	O
three	O
times	O
-	O
were	O
you	O
not	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Crown	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
two	O
Girls	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Pollamounter	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Crown	O
freely	O
.	O
P.	O
Council	O
.	O
What	O
Employment	O
are	O
you	O
of	O
?	O
Pollamounter	O
.	O
None	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
Estate	O
in	O
Cornwall	O
-	O
and	O
this	O
Money	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
upon	O
a	O
Mortgage	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Pollamounter	O
and	O
I	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
two	O
little	O
Girls	O
who	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
treated	O
them	O
with	O
Wine	O
and	O
Cakes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
our	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
so	O
much	O
Impudence	O
as	O
in	O
them	O
Girls	O
-	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Girls	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Pollomounter	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
Bag	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
6	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
The	O
Bell	O
was	O
rung	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
in	O
came	O
Peg	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
sat	O
by	O
Pollamounter	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
he	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
soon	O
returned	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Be	O
easy	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
;	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
in	O
Sheer-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
drank	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
he	O
and	O
Peg	O
and	O
Pollamounter	O
.	O
They	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
returning	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Discharge	O
was	O
insisted	O
on	O
.	O
Peg	O
took	O
the	O
Bag	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
sixteen	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
Six	O
Six	O
and	O
Thirty	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
more	O
of	O
these	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
cast	O
up	O
the	O
whole	O
to	O
be	O
30	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
I	O
counted	O
it	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Pollamounter	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
done	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Arrack	O
Punch	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
drank	O
nothing	O
but	O
Water	O
with	O
a	O
Toast	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Glascock	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
great	O
Business	O
to	O
talk	O
about	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
good	O
natur	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Pollamounter	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
easy	O
without	O
prosecuting	O
the	O
Girl	O
-	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
Room	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
Pollamounter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
Peg	O
was	O
gone	O
Pollamounter	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
mist	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
grew	O
very	O
uneasy	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
set	O
me	O
and	O
him	O
at	O
odds	O
,	O
by	O
insinuating	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
calling	O
in	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
Watch	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
that	O
House	O
:	O
And	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Girl	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
next	O
Day	O
at	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
Ale-house	O
.	O
She	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
Pollamounter	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
all	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
keeping	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
came	O
into	O
your	O
Room	O
,	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Glascock	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
up	O
first	O
there	O
was	O
Pollamounter	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
little	O
Girls	O
-	O
You	O
came	O
up	O
upon	O
a	O
Squabble	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
Crown	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Glascock	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
upon	O
this	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
stead	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Pollamounter	O
pull	O
Peg	O
Boucher	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
No	O
-	O
She	O
came	O
in	O
of	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Pollamounter	O
Charge	O
you	O
with	O
having	O
his	O
Money	O
?	O
Cornish	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
did	O
your	O
endeavour	O
to	O
insinuate	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
going	O
to	O
quarrel	O
,	O
you	O
push	O
'd	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
sha	O
n't	O
sight	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Were	O
not	O
you	O
and	O
he	O
going	O
to	O
fight	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
No	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
City	O
Watch	O
and	O
should	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
K.	O
Council	O
.	O
Do	O
ye	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
Reward	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
Pollamounter	O
complain	O
'd	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
Six	O
and	O
Thirty	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
wanting	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
take	O
what	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-Shop	O
in	O
Sheer	O
Lane	O
when	O
Will	O
.	O
Jones	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
Mary	O
Glascock	O
's	O
Porter	O
)	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Mistress	O
wanted	O
me	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
Jack	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
Jack	O
Smith	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Peggy	O
'	O
l	O
There	O
's	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
above	O
,	O
Pollamounter	O
and	O
Cornish	O
,	O
and	O
Pollamounter	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
Now	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
get	O
it	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
6	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
every	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Glascock	O
and	O
Ann	O
the	O
Daughter	O
,	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
Crown	O
a-piece	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
ring	O
the	O
Bell	O
for	O
a	O
signal	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
shall	O
come	O
up	O
and	O
introduce	O
your	O
self	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
Money	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
into	O
this	O
Room	O
below	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lives	O
with	O
Mary	O
Glascock	O
-	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
Wife	O
-	O
but	O
-	O
something	O
else	O
-	O
So	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
rung	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pointed	O
to	O
Pollamounter	O
's	O
right	O
Pocket	O
where	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Pollamounter	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
readily	O
agreed	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
an	O
Excuse	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
agreed	O
upon	O
.	O
Mary	O
Glascock	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
the	O
Daughter	O
presently	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
Ann	O
the	O
Daughter	O
took	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
Mary	O
Glascock	O
.	O
said	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
should	O
tell	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
he	O
told	O
nine	O
Six	O
and	O
Thirty	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
Sixteen	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Moidore	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
Mary	O
Glascock	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
the	O
Daughter	O
told	O
it	O
they	O
could	O
make	O
but	O
seven	O
Six	O
and	O
Thirty	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Glascock	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
the	O
Daughter	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
brought	O
us	O
a	O
Gimblet	O
with	O
which	O
Ann	O
the	O
Daughter	O
fastned	O
the	O
Door	O
within	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
blew	O
the	O
Candle	O
out	O
that	O
Pollamounter	O
might	O
not	O
find	O
us	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
Pollamounter	O
had	O
mist	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
suppress	O
the	O
House	O
if	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
not	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
may	O
get	O
something	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
returning	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
share	O
that	O
among	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
share	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
But	O
be	O
sure	O
you	O
get	O
a	O
Discharge	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
you	O
may	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
's	O
Act	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
Pollamounter	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
the	O
Girl	O
!	O
She	O
only	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
Jest	O
.	O
Cornish	O
came	O
in	O
presently	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
Discharge	O
was	O
writ	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
nothing	O
for	O
returning	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
all	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Stay	O
,	O
Peggy	O
and	O
drink	O
him	O
down	O
dead	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
may	O
get	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wont	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
has	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
divide	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
proportion	O
as	O
we	O
first	O
agreed	O
upon	O
-	O
Pollamounter	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
Chicken	O
for	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Arrack	O
Punch	O
made	O
stronger	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
And	O
this	O
made	O
Pollamounter	O
quite	O
drunk	O
.	O
Then	O
Mary	O
Glascock	O
called	O
Cornish	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Pollamounter	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
will	O
do	O
.	O
And	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
out	O
of	O
Pollamounter	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
.	O
He	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
out	O
four	O
Guineas	O
;	O
but	O
Cornish	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
sooner	O
than	O
was	O
expected	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
We	O
have	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
divide	O
it	O
now	O
:	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
and	O
burn	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
make	O
the	O
Division	O
to-morrow	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
Door	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Dividend	O
,	O
Pollamounter	O
and	O
Cornish	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
-	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Drink-water	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
:	O
But	O
if	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
charged	O
it	O
upon	O
Cornish	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
House	O
would	O
swear	O
it	O
-	O
While	O
we	O
had	O
this	O
Discourse	O
,	O
Pollamounter	O
and	O
Cornish	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Constable	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
body	O
but	O
one	O
Man	O
that	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
-	O
So	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
Drinkwater	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Smith	O
-	O
From	O
the	O
Cock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
,	O
hard	O
by	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
's	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
thither	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
will	O
say	O
that	O
Cornish	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
my	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
House	O
shall	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
shall	O
all	O
get	O
clear	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
not	O
said	O
one	O
thing	O
that	O
's	O
true	O
-	O
How	O
should	O
I	O
tell	O
her	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
Pollamounter	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
Boucher	O
.	O
Well	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
drinking	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
hear	O
Cornish	O
call	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Name	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Drawer	O
.	O
Pollamounter	O
and	O
Cornish	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
little	O
Girls	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
In	O
five	O
Minutes	O
the	O
Bell	O
rung	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
Pollamounter	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
shew	O
him	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
Room	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Girls	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
fetch	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Girl	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Crown	O
of	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Girl	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
was	O
sreer	O
than	O
Gift	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
'em	O
.	O
He	O
rung	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
send	O
my	O
Mistress	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
in	O
a	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mistress	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
step	O
up	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
that	O
they	O
first	O
went	O
into	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Joke	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
-	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
little	O
Girls	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Peg	O
Boucher	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Door	O
of	O
Pollamounter	O
's	O
Room	O
stood	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
there	O
with	O
Peg	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
Pollamounter	O
pulled	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
her	O
upon	O
his	O
Knee	O
.	O
K.	O
Council	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
that	O
Girl	O
Boucher	O
come	O
in	O
by	O
her	O
self	O
and	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
Room	O
?	O
Redman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
both	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
when	O
Pollamounter	O
pulled	O
her	O
in	O
.	O
K.	O
Council	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
?	O
Redman	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
K.	O
Council	O
.	O
Sure	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
very	O
angry	O
?	O
Redman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
K.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
so	O
easily	O
quit	O
he	O
:	O
then	O
?	O
-	O
It	O
looks	O
a	O
little	O
strange	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Redman	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
no	O
more	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
very	O
quietly	O
-	O
The	O
Bell	O
rung	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
Peg	O
was	O
still	O
upon	O
Pollamounter	O
's	O
Knee	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
Peg	O
and	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
before	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Girl	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
together	O
.	O
She	O
staid	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
-	O
He	O
followed	O
in	O
five	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Girl	O
or	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
forty	O
Pounds	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Cornish	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
little	O
Girl	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
your	O
Loss	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
will	O
try	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
So	O
Pollamounter	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
The	O
little	O
Girl	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Cornish	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Peg	O
,	O
but	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
Peg	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
by	O
her	O
self	O
and	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Provost	O
,	O
the	O
Bar-keeper	O
;	O
where	O
Pollamounter	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
below	O
Stairs	O
.	O
The	O
Bar-keeper	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shewed	O
Peg	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
your	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Joke	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
willingly	O
return	O
it	O
if	O
you	O
'	O
l	O
forgive	O
me	O
.	O
But	O
before	O
she	O
delivered	O
it	O
,	O
Cornish	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
Cornish	O
in	O
Pollamounter	O
's	O
Presence	O
.	O
They	O
counted	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
thirty	O
Pound	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
said	O
some	O
Jacobus	O
's	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
Peg	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
declar	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
a	O
Farthing	O
more	O
-	O
When	O
Peg	O
first	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
above	O
Stairs	O
-	O
Nor	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Pollamounter	O
and	O
Cornish	O
when	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
counted	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
staid	O
drinking	O
with	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Friends	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
any	O
more	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
Company	O
.	O
Pollamounter	O
having	O
got	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
broild	O
Fowl	O
and	O
Mushroom	O
Sauce	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Arnack	O
Punch	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Supper	O
was	O
ready	O
Cornish	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
invited	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Glascock	O
to	O
eat	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
both	O
refused	O
.	O
Cornish	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
supt	O
,	O
Pollamounter	O
and	O
Peg	O
beginning	O
to	O
talk	O
about	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
Cornish	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
Pollamounter	O
had	O
another	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
Cornish	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
see	O
that	O
his	O
Friend	O
Pollamounter	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
my	O
self	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
to	O
snuff	O
the	O
Candles	O
,	O
and	O
Peg	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
.	O
Pollamounter	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
no	O
complaint	O
then	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Cornish	O
,	O
You	O
Rogue	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
Money	O
!	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
shivered	O
his	O
Stick	O
to	O
pieces	O
by	O
striking	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
my	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
against	O
all	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
K.	O
Council	O
.	O
What	O
Room	O
did	O
Pollamounter	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Girls	O
go	O
into	O
at	O
first	O
?	O
Redman	O
.	O
The	O
Nine	O
at	O
the	O
Stair	O
's	O
Head	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
Peg	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Eight	O
on	O
the	O
Left-hand	O
at	O
the	O
Stair	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Nine	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
Pollamounter	O
pulled	O
her	O
in	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Minutes	O
he	O
left	O
Cornish	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
little	O
Girls	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
Peg	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
?	O
K.	O
Council	O
Do	O
you	O
make	O
a	O
Practice	O
of	O
carrying	O
Gentlemen	O
and	O
such	O
Ladies	O
into	O
private	O
Rooms	O
?	O
Redman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
my	O
Business	O
to	O
oblige	O
my	O
Mistresses	O
Customers	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
wait	O
upon	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
if	O
need	O
required	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Pollamounter	O
and	O
Cornish	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
they	O
forced	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
other	O
little	O
Girl	O
into	O
the	O
Tavern	O
.	O
K.	O
Council	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
E.	O
Smith	O
Sixteen	O
-	O
We	O
sat	O
drinking	O
together	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Pollamounter	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Crown	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
impudent	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
E.	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Crown	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
