TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1735.	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	O
BELLAMY	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1735	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXV	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BELLAMY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fortescue	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Reeve	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lingwood	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Thorley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Plowman	I-pers
,	O
Haly	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mazarine	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Plucknet	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
Pennington	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Edmond	B-pers
Vick	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Gethings	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Calloway	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Snee	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Littlewood	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bridge	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
1.	O
John	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Pound	O
of	O
Indico	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
2.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
alias	O
Lane	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
June	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
John	B-pers
Dwyer	I-pers
,	O
+	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Book	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
The	O
Whole	O
Duty	O
of	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Line	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
+	O
In	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
Dwyer	O
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
two	O
Felonies	O
.	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Page	O
23	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Susan	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cotmore	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
Mary	O
Cotmore	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
Peas	O
in	O
Stock	O
's	O
Market	O
.	O
She	O
sat	O
next	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
dull	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
(	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
upon	O
my	O
Basket	O
of	O
Peas	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
waked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Does	O
Sue	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
you	O
go	O
Partners	O
?	O
No	O
-	O
Then	O
she	O
has	O
pick	O
'd	O
your	O
Pocket	O
-	O
I	O
presently	O
felt	O
and	O
mist	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
While	O
Mary	B-pers
Cotmore	I-pers
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
jog	O
her	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
Silver	O
out	O
of	O
Cotmore	O
's	O
Pocket	O
Apron	O
;	O
she	O
dropt	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
rub	O
'd	O
her	O
Eyes	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
waked	O
-	O
I	O
told	O
Mary	O
Cotmore	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
why	O
she	O
play	O
'd	O
the	O
rogue	O
with	O
her	O
Money	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
my	O
Soul	O
and	O
Eyes	O
,	O
says	O
Sue	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
lost	O
fourteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
five	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
5.	O
James	B-pers
Newby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Pin	O
for	O
a	O
Press	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Phillis	I-pers
;	O
and	O
three	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
Iron	O
at	O
the	O
late	O
Fire	O
in	O
Cecil	B-place
Court	I-place
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
.	O
Thimble	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Esquire	O
Webb	O
's	O
at	O
Hammersmith	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
June	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
attacked	O
me	O
between	O
the	O
Hedge	O
and	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
within	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Gate	O
.	O
He	O
clap	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Pistol	O
-	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
your	O
Money	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
ye	O
dead	O
this	O
minute	O
.	O
Honest	O
Friend	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
may	O
see	O
by	O
my	O
Dress	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'	O
l	O
give	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
old	O
pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
two	O
Brass	O
Thimbles	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Shillings	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
for	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
when	O
he	O
tore	O
my	O
Pocket	O
off	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
saved	O
the	O
half	O
Crown	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
my	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
John	B-pers
Row	I-pers
let	O
me	O
in	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
(	O
William	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
)	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
John	O
Row	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
-	O
This	O
Brass	O
Thimble	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
fits	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
like	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
John	O
Row	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
towards	O
the	O
Church	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Six	O
Bells	O
Alehouse	O
near	O
Hammersmith	O
Church	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
ask	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Fulham	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
came	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
eighteen	O
Pence	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Brass	O
Thimble	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
make	O
any	O
Objection	O
[	O
Resistance	O
]	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
me	O
?	O
Row	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
W.	O
Bright	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Justice	O
Beare	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
a	O
Hay-making	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
must	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
7.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Francis	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Boice	I-pers
,	O
March	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Malcolm	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Price	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
June	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Buckland	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ironmonger	I-pers
,	O
May	O
4	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Ticking	O
Pockets	O
,	O
two	O
Keys	O
,	O
two	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
First	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ironmonger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Horse	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
A	O
Neighbour	O
lost	O
a	O
Bridle	O
and	O
Saddle	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
absconded	O
I	O
advertized	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
Oxfordshire	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
swopt	O
this	O
Horse	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
Grey	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
forty	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
Hearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
entered	O
himself	O
for	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
he	O
confest	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
was	O
read	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
Second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
asleep	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Wife	O
's	O
Pocket	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
-	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
afterwards	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
he	O
confest	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
11.	O
John	B-pers
Hobby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Shagreen	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
with	O
Silver	O
Clasps	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pen	O
and	O
Pencil	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
June	O
16	O
He	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box	O
Iron	O
and	O
a	O
Heater	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Caruthers	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sneesby	I-pers
+	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Snaseby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
an	O
unfinish	O
'd	O
Half-beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
+	O
In	O
October	O
1732	O
.	O
Sneesby	O
was	O
tryed	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
.	O
His	O
Trial	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
for	O
that	O
Year	O
,	O
Number	O
8	O
.	O
Page	O
232	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
May	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
John	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Sweetingham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Oswald	B-pers
Manwaring	I-pers
,	O
May	O
19	O
.	O
H	B-pers
Sweetingham	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
stoop	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
welcome	O
to	O
drink	O
it	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Black-Spread	B-place
Eagle	I-place
in	I-place
Paternoster	I-place
Row	I-place
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
two	O
went	O
to	O
Cutting	O
of	O
Cards	O
for	O
six	O
Pence	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
six	O
Pence	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
lost	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
four	O
Guineas	O
for	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
offering	O
me	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
play	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
Cut	O
.	O
I	O
Cut	O
once	O
and	O
lost	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
Cut	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Man	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
was	O
at	O
stake	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
So	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Cut	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
catch	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
All	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
and	O
stamp	O
'd	O
and	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
tear	O
my	O
Hair	O
off	O
for	O
Vexation	O
.	O
Mr	O
Jordan	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
my	O
Journeyman	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
near	O
two	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
home	O
that	O
afternoon	O
almost	O
frighted	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Wits	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
Story	O
then	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
by	O
Trade	O
-	O
When	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
Rochester	O
-	O
and	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
once	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Lodging	O
there	O
,	O
from	O
Easter	O
to	O
Whitsuntide	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
by	O
very	O
good	O
Witnesses	O
-	O
but	O
they	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
here	O
to	O
Day	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Beadle	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
Gambler	O
+	O
for	O
several	O
Years	O
past	O
.	O
+	O
A	O
Gambler	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Modern	O
Cant	O
Names	O
for	O
a	O
Money	O
Dropper	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cane	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Head	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burgoyn	I-pers
,	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Culley	I-pers
,	O
June	O
7	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
18.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Noland	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Callico	O
Quilted	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Mary	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bed	O
and	O
three	O
Pictures	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
at	O
the	O
Fire	O
in	O
Cecil	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Possession	O
.	O
In	O
hot	O
Defence	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
in	O
that	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Fire	O
happened	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
hurry	O
and	O
fright	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
these	O
Goods	O
instead	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
20.	O
Ann	B-pers
Blackerby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Wastecoat	O
trim	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
Lace	O
.	O
value	O
40	O
s	O
a	O
Stock	O
and	O
Stock	O
Buckle	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Forrester	I-pers
Gent	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Witchead	I-pers
June	O
2	O
.	O
David	O
Forrester	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Night	O
of	O
June	O
1	O
was	O
a	O
lattle	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
fra	O
'	O
Charing-Crose	O
I	O
mat	O
this	O
Woman	O
and	O
anither	O
near	O
the	O
Saven	O
Dials	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
me	O
intull	O
a	O
Hoose	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Tavern	O
Brandy	B-pers
Shop	I-pers
,	O
and	O
got	O
mare	O
Liquor	O
tull	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gard	O
me	O
mare	O
fuddled	O
than	O
before	O
.	O
They	O
wanted	O
Money	O
o	O
'	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
tald	O
'em	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
my	O
Sward	O
,	O
what	O
wad	O
ye	O
ha	O
'	O
mare	O
?	O
Tack	O
ye	O
that	O
for	O
a	O
Pledge	O
,	O
but	O
dunna	O
ye	O
tack	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
send	O
for	O
some	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Moarning	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
ged	O
to	O
bed	O
wi'the	O
Prasoner	O
and	O
the	O
ither	O
Woman	O
.	O
Next	O
Moarning	O
,	O
Su	O
Murphey	O
,	O
who	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Hoose	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
tald	O
me	O
that	O
this	O
twa	O
Woman	O
were	O
rin	O
away	O
wi	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
Sa	O
I	O
gade	O
to	O
Justice	O
Mitford	O
who	O
committed	O
Murphey	O
tull	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
granted	O
me	O
a	O
Warant	O
for	O
apprehending	O
the	O
Prasoner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
twa	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
tull	O
the	O
Round-Hoose	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
I	O
gade	O
tull	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Stockings	O
upon	O
her	O
Legs	O
.	O
I	O
wad	O
a	O
'	O
taken	O
'em	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
she	O
wad	O
sware	O
a	O
Robery	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
sa	O
she	O
tack	O
'em	O
off	O
her	O
sell	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Was	O
I	O
in	O
your	O
Company	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
you	O
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Minion	I-pers
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
alias	O
Day	O
?	O
D.	O
Forrester	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
with	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
say	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
Carnal	O
Copulation	O
with	O
me	O
-	O
You	O
told	O
Su	O
Minion	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
alias	O
Day	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
loth	O
to	O
disturb	O
your	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
you	O
should	O
lye	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
you	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Sword	O
for	O
-	O
Edward	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
Chairman	O
.	O
Between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
that	O
Morning	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Brandy	B-pers
Shop	I-pers
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Sue	B-pers
Day	I-pers
said	O
they	O
'd	O
take	O
a	O
Dram	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
With	O
all	O
my	O
Heart	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
goes	O
and	O
knocks	O
my	O
Wife	O
up	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
having	O
no	O
Liquor	O
.	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Quart	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
and	O
slept	O
'till	O
she	O
waked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
having	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
a	O
Laced	O
Waistcoat	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
afraid	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
two	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
one	O
another	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
abused	O
my	O
Wife	O
-	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Your	O
Wife	O
?	O
Ye	O
Rascal	O
!	O
What	O
is	O
Mrs	O
Wileman	O
your	O
Wife	O
?	O
She	O
hanged	O
a	O
Man	O
two	O
Sessions	O
ago	O
-	O
Every	O
body	O
knows	O
Moll	O
Wileman	O
.	O
E	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
And	O
what	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
more	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilted	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
Blue	O
Belt	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
and	O
buckled	O
it	O
on	O
next	O
to	O
her	O
Smock	O
-	O
So	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Night	O
Cellar	O
at	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
being	O
pawn	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Name	O
I	O
might	O
come	O
into	O
a	O
scrape	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
she	O
abused	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
and	O
met	O
Tom	B-pers
Day	I-pers
-	O
Sue	B-pers
Minion	I-pers
goes	O
for	O
Tom	O
's	O
Wife	O
-	O
and	O
Tom	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
would	O
be	O
easy	O
and	O
give	O
no	O
body	O
any	O
trouble	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
his	O
Things	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asks	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Sword	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
took	O
Coach	O
to	O
Cabbage	O
Lane	O
-	O
I	O
dogged	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
housed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Waist-coat	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
-	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
Sword	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
alias	O
Wileman	O
.	O
After	O
my	O
Husband	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Sue	B-pers
Day	I-pers
drank	O
twelve	O
or	O
eighteen	O
Penn'orth	O
of	O
Surfeit	O
Water	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
this	O
Laced	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
Hemmings	O
's	O
Row	O
for	O
thirteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
lye	O
Mrs.	O
Wileman	O
!	O
You	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Sue	O
Day	O
who	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
Creatures	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
they	O
two	O
were	O
a	O
bitching	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
says	O
Sue	O
Day	O
,	O
This	O
Bitch	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
both	O
been	O
a-bed	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
away	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
Stockings	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
And	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
away	O
his	O
Coat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
too	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
awaked	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
gone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
the	O
finest	O
Man	O
upon	O
Earth	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
gave	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
Sue	O
Day	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
-	O
Next	O
Morning	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
his	O
Sword	O
-	O
The	O
Stockings	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
them	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Wileman	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
got	O
drunk	O
and	O
quarrelled	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
York	O
Buildings	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
Tom	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
because	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
this	O
has	O
followed	O
.	O
Sue	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
below	O
,	O
will	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Sword	O
to	O
Day	O
.	O
Susan	O
Murphey	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
send	O
a	O
Porter	O
for	O
some	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
oblige	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Pledge	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
often	O
been	O
tricked	O
that	O
way	O
but	O
was	O
grown	O
wiser	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
his	O
Sword	O
to	O
Sue	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
lay	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
carry	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
So	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
as	O
a	O
Present	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
a	O
Pledge	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Landlady	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
vile	O
notorious	O
Woman	O
Susan	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
-	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
Verdict	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Curse	O
and	O
God	O
's	O
Curse	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
ye	O
!	O
and	O
the	O
Prayers	O
of	O
my	O
Children	O
fall	O
upon	O
ye	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
June	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mac	I-pers
Cray	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mac	I-pers
Creagh	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
Dr.	O
of	O
Laws	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l	O
two	O
Iron	O
Keys	O
,	O
six	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Foreign	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
48	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
June	O
11	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
eleventh	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
at	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Minutes	O
past	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
Hackney	O
Coach	O
with	O
Mr.	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Road	I-place
,	O
between	O
Blackland	O
and	O
Bloody-bridge	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Red-Lyon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
gallopping	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
rid	O
by	O
the	O
Coach	O
unmasked	O
,	O
and	O
bidding	O
the	O
Coachman	O
stop	O
,	O
turned	O
back	O
with	O
a	O
Black	O
Crape	O
pulled	O
over	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
holding	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
Oaths	O
and	O
Execrations	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
Purse	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
some	O
Foreign	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tooth	O
pick	O
Case	O
which	O
was	O
painted	O
In	O
the	O
hurry	O
I	O
likewise	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
Keys	O
-	O
I	O
shall	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
-	O
opens	O
a	O
Paper	O
Parcel	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
my	O
Bureau	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
this	O
little	O
Nick	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Specks	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
used	O
it	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
times	O
in	O
a	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Lock	O
has	O
four	O
Bolts	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
bent	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Bureau	O
open	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
prevents	O
the	O
Key	O
from	O
turning	O
so	O
freely	O
as	O
it	O
otherwise	O
would	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
easily	O
have	O
been	O
set	O
to	O
rights	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Case	O
as	O
this	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
proper	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
Alterations	O
-	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
any	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
but	O
whoever	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Fellow	O
what	O
dost	O
want	O
?	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
your	O
B	O
-	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Your	O
Money	O
-	O
If	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
two	O
Keys	O
of	O
an	O
Escritore	O
into	O
his	O
Hat	O
-	O
These	O
two	O
Keys	O
I	O
believe	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
then	O
left	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
reflected	O
on	O
for	O
being	O
so	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
declares	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
no	O
knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
particular	O
-	O
I	O
sat	O
backwards	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
forwards	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
galloping	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
as	O
the	O
Coach	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Face	O
though	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
his	O
Reverence	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
fetter	O
'd	O
with	O
others	O
who	O
were	O
not	O
fetter	O
'd	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
tallest	O
Man	O
but	O
his	O
Face	O
was	O
cover	O
'd	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
cover	O
'd	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
more	O
certain	O
-	O
Cover	O
your	O
Face	O
-	O
pull	O
your	O
Hat	O
down	O
to	O
your	O
Nose	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
only	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
Links	O
which	O
were	O
held	O
in	O
an	O
odd	O
manner	O
:	O
But	O
yet	O
I	O
never	O
exprest	O
any	O
doubt	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
the	O
Person	O
;	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
fix	O
upon	O
him	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
fetter	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
that	O
all	O
that	O
stood	O
with	O
him	O
were	O
fetter	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Edmonds	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Doctor	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Doctor	O
cast	O
his	O
Eye	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
the	O
first	O
or	O
second	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
Doctor	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Dr.	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
-	O
The	O
second	O
time	O
I	O
went	O
I	O
mentioned	O
the	O
Tooth	O
pick	O
Case	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
observed	O
an	O
alteration	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Countenance	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tears	O
came	O
in	O
his	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Juryman	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
return	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
past	O
the	O
Coach	O
?	O
Dr.	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
The	O
time	O
was	O
so	O
short	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
name	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Juryman	O
.	O
Instantly	O
?	O
Dr.	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Minute	O
.	O
Juryman	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
so	O
light	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
plainly	O
see	O
his	O
Face	O
?	O
Dr.	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
longest	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
-	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Stockwell	O
's	O
at	O
Little	O
Chelsea	O
at	O
forty	O
eight	O
Minutes	O
past	O
eight	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Atley	O
I	O
keep	O
The	O
Man	O
in-the-Moon	O
Tavern	O
in	O
White	O
Chappel	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
on	O
twelfth	O
of	O
June	O
-	O
and	O
just	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
shifted	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
ride	O
out	O
-	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
he	O
pulled	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
those	O
very	O
Keys	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
which	O
were	O
just	O
now	O
produced	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
Doctor	O
challenged	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Lock	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Snelson	I-pers
,	O
Headborough	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hammerton	O
*	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
He	O
struck	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
.	O
I	O
beat	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
snapt	O
another	O
Pistol	O
but	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
these	O
two	O
Pistols	O
,	O
these	O
two	O
Daggers	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Great	O
Knife	O
.	O
*	O
Mr.	O
Hammerton	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
thirteen	O
Shillings	O
near	O
Barnes	O
Common	O
in	O
Surry	O
.	O
In	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Boy	O
riding	O
one	O
Horse	O
and	O
leading	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Nag	O
's	O
Head	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Man-in-the-moon	O
in	O
White	O
Chappel	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hammerton	O
waited	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
take	O
Horse	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
Mac	O
Cray	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
Laced	O
Suit	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
The	O
Man-in-the-moon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hammerton	O
knowing	O
him	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
deny	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
those	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
enough	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
some	O
Members	O
of	O
Parliament	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Sudbury	O
in	O
Suffolk	O
to	O
serve	O
Subpoena	O
's	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
some	O
contested	O
Elections	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
being	O
a	O
Party-business	O
,	O
procured	O
me	O
such	O
Enemies	O
that	O
my	O
Life	O
has	O
been	O
ever	O
since	O
in	O
danger	O
-	O
They	O
got	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
Suffolk	O
to	O
swear	O
a	O
Rape	O
against	O
me	O
+	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Robbery	O
now	O
sworn	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
prove	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
the	O
Keys	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
possession	O
.	O
+	O
He	O
stands	O
indicted	O
at	O
St.	O
Edmond	O
's	O
Bury	O
for	O
ravishing	O
Martha	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
three	O
other	O
Indictments	O
.	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Council	O
.	O
We	O
fear	O
some	O
bad	O
Practices	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
pray	O
that	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
may	O
be	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Let	O
it	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
++	O
,	O
Attorney	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
eleventh	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Stag	O
and	O
Hounds	O
(	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
)	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Ruffhead	O
,	O
a	O
Client	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
.	O
++	O
Campbell	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Jack	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
tryed	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Pollamounter	I-pers
.	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Number	O
2	O
.	O
Page	O
40	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
hear	O
your	O
Client	O
's	O
Business	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
no	O
private	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
Three	O
Years	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Sudbury	O
at	O
the	O
Election	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
Council	O
How	O
come	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
when	O
you	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
remarkable	O
Day	O
-	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Accession	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
What	O
Dress	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
Campbell	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Clothes	O
as	O
were	O
now	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
much	O
finer	O
Dress	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
did	O
he	O
follow	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Obrien	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
a	O
proper	O
Dresss	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Station	O
?	O
would	O
his	O
Business	O
as	O
an	O
Attorney	O
's	O
Clerk	O
maintain	O
him	O
in	O
Apparel	O
trim	O
'd	O
with	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Clerk	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
nor	O
for	O
a	O
Year	O
before	O
-	O
but	O
he	O
practiced	O
for	O
himself	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
Law	O
Suits	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
sometimes	O
discounted	O
Notes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
telling	O
what	O
happened	O
in	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
asked	O
you	O
what	O
Business	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
.	O
Your	O
Answer	O
naturally	O
refers	O
to	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
a	O
Year	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
.	O
But	O
proceed	O
.	O
Campbell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Stag	O
and	O
Hounds	O
.	O
sat	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Quartern	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
Gin	O
.	O
Ruffhead	O
and	O
Brown	O
(	O
another	O
of	O
my	O
Clients	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
happened	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
no	O
doubt	O
will	O
inform	O
the	O
Court	O
-	O
We	O
settled	O
the	O
Accompts	O
,	O
drank	O
three	O
Three-Shilling	O
Bowls	O
of	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
and	O
neither	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
nor	O
any	O
other	O
of	O
us	O
stir	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
What	O
Dress	O
were	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
Campbell	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
as	O
now	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
lighter	O
Bob	O
Wig	O
(	O
an	O
old	O
Brown	O
Coat	O
with	O
Silver	O
Thread	O
Buttons	O
.	O
)	O
Ruffhead	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Butcher	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
meet	O
Mr.	O
Campbell	O
on	O
the	O
eleventh	O
of	O
June	O
at	O
the	O
Stag	O
and	O
Hounds	O
about	O
settling	O
some	O
S.	O
S.	O
Stock	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
Father	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
-	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
him	O
whither	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Silver-button	O
'd	O
Coat	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Campbell	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Campbell	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Dress	O
as	O
now	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
three	O
Three-Shilling	O
owls	O
of	O
Punch	O
.	O
Julian	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
know	O
de	O
Presonaar	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
as	O
twice	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
What	O
Country	O
man	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Brown	O
,	O
Italian	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
talka	O
de	O
Fransh	O
-	O
I	O
ave	O
occasion	O
to	O
vant	O
Maitre	O
Campbell	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
is	O
Ouse	O
de	O
Day	O
as	O
the	O
King	O
come	O
to	O
de	O
Crown	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
ye	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
Day	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Because	O
of	O
de	O
great	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
mush	O
ring	O
of	O
de	O
Bells	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
are	O
ye	O
sure	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
no	O
can	O
tell	O
vat	O
Day	O
-	O
But	O
ven	O
I	O
come	O
dare	O
I	O
meet	O
Mr.	O
Ruffhead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
vant	O
Mr.	O
Campbell	O
too	O
.	O
So	O
ve	O
go	O
togader	O
to	O
de	O
Stag	O
and	O
de	O
Hound	O
,	O
and	O
dare	O
I	O
find	O
him	O
and	O
de	O
Presonaar	O
-	O
De	O
Presonaar	O
vas	O
in	O
de	O
Vite	O
Grey	O
Coat	O
vid	O
de	O
Button	O
Silver	O
and	O
de	O
Scarlet	O
Vaistcoat	O
vid	O
de	O
Lace	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
talked	O
English	O
as	O
you	O
do	O
now	O
-	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
sometime	O
ago	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Yes	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
when	O
I	O
committed	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Street	O
Robbery	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
pretended	O
then	O
he	O
could	O
speak	O
no	O
English	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
interpreted	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
Proof	O
against	O
him	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
luck	O
to	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
In	O
September	O
1731	O
Julian	O
Brown	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Rebecca	B-pers
White	I-pers
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
near	O
Hungerford	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
he	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
of	O
English	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
and	O
another	O
Witness	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
very	O
plainly	O
D	O
-	O
your	O
Blood	O
ye	O
Bitch	O
,	O
deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
-	O
She	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
was	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
Church	O
Porch	O
(	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
himself	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
Pocket	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
1731	O
.	O
Number	O
7	O
.	O
Page	O
11	O
.	O
Court	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Ten	O
Years	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Considering	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
learn	O
a	O
Word	O
of	O
English	O
in	O
the	O
six	O
first	O
Years	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
Improvement	O
in	O
the	O
four	O
following	O
-	O
What	O
Employment	O
are	O
you	O
of	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
ave	O
serve	O
tree	O
Years	O
vid	O
de	O
Franch	O
Ambassador	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
I	O
be	O
de	O
Perugue	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
leeve	O
at	O
de	O
Shandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Plumb	O
tree	O
court	O
in	O
Dyer	O
's	O
Street	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
my	O
Lord	O
Sherburn	O
's	O
Service	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
When	O
de	O
Shustice	O
Devcil	O
send	O
a	O
me	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
vill	O
no	O
take	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
have	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
since	O
his	O
Commitment	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
But	O
von	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
dat	O
was	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Days	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
de	O
Preeson	O
.	O
For	O
den	O
Mr.	O
Campbell	O
come	O
and	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
You	O
know	O
de	O
Man	O
that	O
vas	O
vid	O
us	O
in	O
'Obourn	O
,	O
I	O
say	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Vell	O
he	O
say	O
,	O
dis	O
Man	O
is	O
apprehend	O
for	O
de	O
Robbery	O
,	O
vill	O
you	O
go	O
vid	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
told	O
I	O
,	O
vid	O
all	O
mine	O
'	O
Art	O
-	O
So	O
we	O
bote	O
go	O
dare	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
see	O
de	O
Shentleman	O
in	O
'is	O
Night	O
Gown	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
told	O
ye	O
this	O
but	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
your	O
meeting	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
natural	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
recollect	O
what	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
that	O
meeting	O
was	O
on	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Vy	O
mine	O
Head	O
vas	O
full	O
of	O
de	O
Law-Suits	O
-	O
I	O
ave	O
noting	O
to	O
do	O
vid	O
de	O
Day	O
of	O
de	O
Veek	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taken	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Hammerton	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
twelfth	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
seventeenth	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Butcher	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
meet	O
me	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
the	O
twelfth	O
of	O
June	O
near	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Keys	O
?	O
Council	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
ye	O
mean	O
by	O
putting	O
Words	O
into	O
his	O
Mouth	O
?	O
Chamberlain	O
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
the	O
twelfth	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Shirly	O
(	O
a	O
Barber	O
in	O
Stretton	O
Grounds	O
)	O
happened	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Horse	O
Guards	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
by	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stoop	O
down	O
and	O
take	O
up	O
three	O
small	O
Keys	O
in	O
a	O
Bunch	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
drop	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
?	O
Chamberlain	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
dirty	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
?	O
Chamberlain	O
.	O
A	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Obrien	O
-	O
and	O
since	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
might	O
practice	O
for	O
himself	O
-	O
Besides	O
he	O
had	O
good	O
Friends	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
sent	O
him	O
Money	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
pretty	O
well	O
acquainted	O
then	O
?	O
Chamberlain	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
About	O
any	O
Business	O
?	O
Chamberlain	O
.	O
We	O
only	O
met	O
to	O
drink	O
-	O
My	O
first	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
was	O
by	O
an	O
accidental	O
Meeting	O
at	O
The	O
Sun	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
.	O
Juryman	O
.	O
We	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
if	O
the	O
Lock	O
were	O
rectify	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
the	O
better	O
judge	O
if	O
the	O
Key	O
belongs	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
a	O
Lock	O
Smith	O
in	O
Court	O
Streightened	O
the	O
Bolt	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
and	O
tryed	O
the	O
Key	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
see	O
the	O
Key	O
does	O
not	O
now	O
do	O
exactly	O
.	O
Lock-Smith	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
Key	O
might	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Lock	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
usual	O
when	O
a	O
Key	O
has	O
been	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
made	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
alteration	O
in	O
the	O
Lock	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
new	O
Key	O
made	O
But	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Key	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
though	O
I	O
have	O
opened	O
the	O
Lock	O
with	O
it	O
twenty	O
times	O
a	O
Day	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
had	O
often	O
some	O
difficulty	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
turned	O
it	O
round	O
four	O
,	O
five	O
,	O
or	O
six	O
times	O
to	O
double-lock	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
another	O
Lock	O
fit	O
that	O
Key	O
?	O
Lock	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
common	O
-	O
But	O
as	O
this	O
Lock	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
with	O
Violence	O
,	O
that	O
may	O
have	O
made	O
some	O
alteration	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
besides	O
,	O
bending	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bolts	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
very	O
Strange	O
that	O
his	O
Reverence	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
positive	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
one	O
side	O
Glance	O
of	O
my	O
Face	O
late	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Minutes	O
past	O
Nine	O
,	O
the	O
longest	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
light	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
-	O
But	O
I	O
remembered	O
his	O
Voice	O
too	O
-	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
willing	O
to	O
speak	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
first	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
positive	O
to	O
his	O
Voice	O
as	O
a	O
Man	O
could	O
possibly	O
be	O
-	O
Besides	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Hand	O
!	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
Reverence	O
wo	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Hand	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
positive	O
Evidence	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
one	O
is	O
directly	O
contradictory	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
can	O
not	O
possibly	O
both	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
there	O
can	O
be	O
no	O
Medium	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
must	O
be	O
perjur	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
withdrew	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
short	O
stay	O
returned	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
for	O
their	O
farther	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
the	O
People	O
at	O
the	O
Stag	O
and	O
Hounds	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
A	O
Messenger	O
was	O
immediately	O
dispatch	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Forster	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Stag	O
and	O
Hounds	O
near	O
The	O
Three	O
Cups	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
ye	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Forster	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
ye	O
remember	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
lately	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Forster	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Anniversary	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Accession	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
was	O
a	O
remarkable	O
Day	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
remember	O
to	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
Forster	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
what	O
Day	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Campbell	O
?	O
Forster	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
there	O
that	O
Evening	O
from	O
seven	O
to	O
eleven	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
.	O
Its	O
possible	O
he	O
might	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
among	O
my	O
Customers	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Forster	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Campbell	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Has	O
Campbell	O
been	O
there	O
since	O
?	O
Forster	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
then	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
time	O
,	O
apply	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
eleventh	O
of	O
June	O
?	O
Forster	O
No	O
.	O
Nor	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
till	O
now	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
a	O
Robery	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
24.	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Kift	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Vaugham	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Stamper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Stone	O
.	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
17.	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
May	O
13	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jasper	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
May	O
27	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
First	O
Indictment	O
.	O
William	O
Stamper	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
thirteenth	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
four	O
Men	O
at	O
Stone-bridge	O
,	O
just	O
behind	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
between	O
Shoreditch	B-place
Church	I-place
and	O
Kingsland	B-place
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
your	O
Blood	O
come	O
along	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
R	O
-	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
)	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Be	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
shall	O
hurt	O
your	O
Body	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
me	O
about	O
one	O
Hundred	O
Yards	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
where	O
Jack	B-pers
Catch	I-pers
was	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
an	O
Amethyst	O
Ring	O
with	O
my	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shoes	O
.	O
They	O
cut	O
the	O
String	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
and	O
tyed	O
my	O
Hands	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Legs	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
throw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
lately	O
broke	O
my	O
Arm	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
laid	O
me	O
down	O
gently	O
.	O
R	O
-	O
said	O
,	O
Be	O
easy	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
shall	O
come	O
in	O
five	O
Minutes	O
and	O
release	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
offers	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
spoke	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
Watch	O
Word	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
could	O
do	O
me	O
but	O
little	O
service	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
of	O
all	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
complain	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
mercy	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
fired	O
a	O
Pistol	O
over	O
my	O
Head	O
(	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
a	O
silly	O
Action	O
)	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
tall	O
ill-looking	O
Fellow	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Gang	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Face	O
was	O
muffled	O
-	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
Knife	O
like	O
that	O
as	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
Mac	O
Cray	O
.	O
And	O
R	O
-	O
gave	O
two	O
Pistols	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Wigg	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
R	O
-	O
Head	O
-	O
I	O
lay	O
bound	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
an	O
Hour	O
by	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
made	O
shift	O
to	O
get	O
loose	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
engaged	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
thirteenth	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
They	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
went	O
to	O
The	O
Fox	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Kingsland	O
Road	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
staid	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
duskish	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
Stone	O
Bridge	O
.	O
R	O
-	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
Vaughan	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Punch	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
.	O
They	O
also	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wig	O
,	O
Ring	O
and	O
Money	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shoes	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Crown	O
.	O
But	O
we	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
The	O
Magpye	O
Tavern	O
at	O
Bishop	O
's	O
Gate	O
to	O
share	O
the	O
Booty	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
produced	O
only	O
a	O
half	O
Crown	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
a	O
lying	O
Rogue	O
for	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
Vaughan	O
and	O
R	O
-	O
-	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
Watch	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ring	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Gold	O
for	O
four	O
Shillings	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
five	O
Shillings	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
or	O
six	O
Shillings	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
which	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
odd	O
six	O
Pence	O
)	O
to	O
a	O
Gold-Smith	O
in	O
White	O
Chapple	O
-	O
and	O
the	O
Buckles	O
.	O
-	O
Kist	O
.	O
Talk	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
stand	O
-playing	O
with	O
your	O
Hat	O
-	O
such	O
a	O
Rogue	O
as	O
you	O
,	O
will	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Cotterel	O
.	O
R	O
-	O
carried	O
the	O
Wig	O
to	O
Phillip	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
a	O
Barber	O
in	O
Petticoat	O
Lane	O
(	O
White	O
Chapple	O
)	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
.	O
Lacy	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
Part	O
is	O
Goat	O
's	O
Hair	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
Mohair	O
-	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Devil	O
-	O
By	O
G	O
-	O
the	O
Wig	O
is	O
worth	O
but	O
sixteen	O
Shillings	O
.	O
We	O
threw	O
for	O
the	O
Wig	O
with	O
Box	O
and	O
Dice	O
,	O
and	O
R	O
-	O
had	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
afterwards	O
asked	O
Lacy	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
value	O
such	O
a	O
Wig	O
at	O
but	O
sixteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Answer	O
was	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
R	O
-	O
,	O
bid	O
me	O
say	O
so	O
-	O
Before	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
R	O
-	O
fired	O
a	O
Pistol	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
token	O
for	O
one	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
relieve	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
knew	O
of	O
nobody	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
any	O
such	O
Account	O
.	O
R	O
-	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
Wig	O
of	O
Cotterel	O
.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
.	O
R	O
-	O
and	O
Cotterel	O
brought	O
the	O
Wig	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
much	O
rumpled	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
judge	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
it	O
-	O
But	O
afterwards	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
once	O
worth	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Pound	O
.	O
R	O
-	O
Here	O
is	O
my	O
Landlord	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
lodg	O
'd	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
can	O
prove	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
never	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
Money	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
last	O
April	O
-	O
and	O
to	O
swear	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
Kist	O
and	O
Cotterel	O
for	O
their	O
shares	O
of	O
the	O
Wig	O
.	O
R	O
-	O
You	O
may	O
see	O
by	O
his	O
Face	O
that	O
he	O
swears	O
falsely	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
your	O
own	O
Witness	O
.	O
Kist	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
that	O
Rogue	O
Cotterel	O
,	O
his	O
own	O
Rod	O
will	O
whip	O
him	O
-	O
And	O
as	O
to	O
my	O
dying	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
pleasure	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
only	O
sorry	O
that	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Villain	O
-	O
But	O
he	O
'll	O
come	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
appearing	O
some	O
favourable	O
Circumstances	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
of	O
R	O
-	O
the	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
Mercy	O
.	O
25.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stamp	B-pers
Brookshank	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hester	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
June	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
Edward	B-pers
Omsby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Lilly	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
And	O
27	O
.	O
28.	O
Martha	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Strutton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Branan	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
afterwards	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lilly	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
twentieth	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Omsby	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Denmark	B-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Ratcliff	I-place
Highway	I-place
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Cup-board	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
my	O
Tankard	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
some	O
People	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
if	O
they	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
that	O
Cup-board	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
I	O
mist	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
within	O
that	O
time	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
ye	O
know	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
?	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
I	O
been	O
in	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
M.	O
Lilly	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Richard	O
Lilly	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
Omsby	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Oration	O
about	O
the	O
Tankard	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Girl	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
People	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
stradling	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Pox	O
-	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tankard	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Shop-board	O
till	O
near	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
-	O
Omsby	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smitherman	I-pers
,	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Martha	B-pers
Strutton	I-pers
these	O
ten	O
Years	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twentieth	O
of	O
June	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
this	O
Tankard	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
Eagle	O
Street	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
to	O
pledge	O
for	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house-keeper	O
at	O
The	O
Fountain	O
in	O
Tothill	O
Street	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
my	O
Servant	O
thither	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
You	O
need	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
called	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Omsby	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
cryed	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
Little	O
Queen	O
Street	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Branan	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
for	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
against	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
Shop	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Branan	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Gonson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Tankard	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
Omsby	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
ran	O
another	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
.	O
Omsby	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
handle	O
the	O
Tankard	O
?	O
R	O
Smitherman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Omsby	O
Did	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
Tankard	O
in	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
R.	O
Smitherman	O
.	O
You	O
came	O
in	O
as	O
the	O
Owner	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
five	O
Guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
Woman	O
had	O
asked	O
but	O
for	O
four	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Omsby	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
come	O
in	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
?	O
R.	O
Smitherman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Omsby	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
some	O
dispute	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
I	O
own	O
that	O
I	O
desired	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
-	O
Was	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Box	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
?	O
R.	O
Smitherman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Omsby	O
.	O
Why	O
was	O
I	O
carried	O
into	O
a	O
different	O
Box	O
?	O
R.	O
Smitherman	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
other	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
I	O
took	O
you	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Omsby	O
about	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
this	O
Tankard	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
The	O
Fountain	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
but	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
some	O
Money	O
for	O
his	O
Brewer	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
Years	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
believing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
pledge	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
known	O
.	O
The	O
Pawn-broker	O
asking	O
several	O
Questions	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
Omsby	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Since	O
he	O
makes	O
such	O
a	O
rent	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
bring	O
me	O
the	O
Tankard	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
pawn	O
it	O
any	O
where	O
.	O
So	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Branan	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
ye	O
my	O
Word	O
.	O
William	O
Belt	O
.	O
and	O
others	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
heard	O
Omsby	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
innocent	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tozer	I-pers
.	O
Being	O
near	O
the	O
Pawn-brokers	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
Omsby	O
running	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
;	O
several	O
Questions	O
were	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
dull	O
and	O
would	O
say	O
nothing	O
-	O
He	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
Witnesses	O
appeared	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
Strutton	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
many	O
for	O
Branan	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
good	O
Characters	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Edward	B-pers
Omsby	I-pers
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
But	O
acquitted	O
the	O
two	O
Accessaries/	O
.	O
29	O
,	O
30.	O
Edward	B-pers
Stavely	I-pers
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Stavely	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Perrier	I-pers
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31	O
,	O
32.	O
Nightingale	B-pers
Meads	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Tippet	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
.	O
Meads	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifty	O
four	O
Pound	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
fixt	O
to	O
the	O
Buildings	O
of	O
James	B-pers
and	I-pers
John	I-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
Esqs	O
;	O
May	O
21	O
.	O
And	O
Tippet	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
33.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
He	O
and	O
Meads	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Ducks	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mole	I-pers
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
and	O
Tippet	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
All	O
Guilty	O
.	O
34.	O
Nathan	B-pers
Winnington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
with	O
Nightingale	B-pers
Meads	I-pers
,	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
and	O
three	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Drewster	I-pers
,	O
May	O
9	O
.	O
All	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Winnington	O
,	O
Elliot	O
,	O
and	O
Meads	O
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Geese	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
May	O
19	O
.	O
All	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Elliot	O
and	O
Meads	O
were	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
Pound	O
of	O
old	O
Iron	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
Esqs	O
,	O
May	O
19	O
.	O
But	O
they	O
being	O
convicted	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
Indictments	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
thought	O
necessary	O
to	O
try	O
them	O
on	O
this	O
.	O
[	O
Nightingale	O
,	O
Tippet	O
,	O
Winnington	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Elliot	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
Callico	O
Printer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Stamp	O
,	O
to	O
resemble	O
a	O
certain	O
Stamp	O
,	O
provided	O
to	O
stamp	O
Vellum	O
,	O
Parchment	O
,	O
and	O
Paper	O
,	O
chargeable	O
by	O
certain	O
Statutes	O
with	O
the	O
Duties	O
of	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
May	O
30	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Elihu	O
Bridoak	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
since	O
1733	O
-	O
About	O
the	O
twenty	O
sixth	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1734	O
.	O
I	O
by	O
his	O
Direction	O
,	O
purchased	O
two	O
Treble	O
six	O
Penny	O
Stamps	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
before	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
a	O
Counterfeit	O
so	O
exact	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
from	O
the	O
true	O
Stamp	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
assist	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
half	O
the	O
Profit	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
had	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
New	O
street	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
hired	O
by	O
his	O
Orders	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
only	O
to	O
Coin	O
Money	O
there	O
-	O
He	O
melted	O
a	O
Composition	O
of	O
Metal	O
in	O
a	O
Crucible	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
cast	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
Stamp	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
repaired	O
it	O
fit	O
for	O
use	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
stampt	O
near	O
two	O
Ream	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Paper	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
three	O
Impressions	O
on	O
some	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
two	O
on	O
others	O
-	O
In	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
by	O
his	O
Orders	O
for	O
two	O
other	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
I	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
cast	O
another	O
Stamp	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
new	O
ones	O
and	O
stampt	O
several	O
Papers	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
The	O
Stamps	O
have	O
usually	O
some	O
particular	O
Letter	O
on	O
them	O
-	O
What	O
Letters	O
had	O
those	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
?	O
Bridoak	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
was	O
Y	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
AA	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
made	O
others	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
twelve	O
Penny	O
Stamp	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
House	O
at	O
Lambeth-marsh	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
House	O
in	O
St.George	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
partly	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
partly	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
's	O
-	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Goal	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
at	O
Lambeth-marsh	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
St.George	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
all	O
his	O
Implements	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
produced	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
gave	O
Information	O
to	O
the	O
Stamp	O
Office	O
.	O
Mr	O
Lunnies	O
,	O
the	O
Messenger	O
,	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
Presses	O
one	O
for	O
Coining	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
for	O
Stamping	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Dies	O
for	O
half	O
Pence	O
and	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lunnies	I-pers
.	O
We	O
found	O
two	O
Presses	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
fixt	O
to	O
a	O
Block	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Block	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
Dies	O
for	O
half	O
Pence	O
,	O
a	O
Head	O
and	O
a	O
Britannia	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
This	O
Stamp	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Tin	O
Box	O
,	O
two	O
for	O
two	O
Shillings	O
and	O
three	O
Pence	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
twelve	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
for	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
this	O
Stamp	O
AA	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
stamp	O
Paper	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stamp	O
this	O
Paper	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
with	O
the	O
Letter	O
Y	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
other	O
Stamps	O
with	O
T	O
and	O
R.	O
Thomas	O
Hodson	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
eight	O
Stamps	O
from	O
between	O
the	O
Wall	O
and	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
four	O
six	O
Penny	O
Stamps	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
make	O
three	O
of	O
these	O
;	O
Y	O
,	O
AA	O
,	O
and	O
O	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Penny	O
Stamp	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rollos	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
engraved	O
for	O
the	O
Stamp	O
Office	O
about	O
thirty	O
three	O
Years	O
.	O
The	O
Stamps	O
now	O
produced	O
are	O
Couterfeit	O
;	O
ours	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
are	O
all	O
of	O
Steel	O
,	O
but	O
these	O
I	O
believe	O
are	O
a	O
composition	O
of	O
-	O
and	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
Paper	O
was	O
not	O
stampt	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
this	O
counterfeit	O
Stamp	O
Y.	O
Mr.	O
Lunnies	O
.	O
This	O
other	O
Press	O
is	O
for	O
stamping	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
fixt	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
nor	O
put	O
together	O
as	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Block	O
is	O
-	O
And	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Fly	O
of	O
the	O
Stamp	O
Engine	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
their	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
,	O
Smith	O
.	O
This	O
Screw	O
and	O
Box	O
which	O
belongs	O
to	O
this	O
Press	O
I	O
made	O
by	O
Bridoak	O
's	O
Order	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
orders	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Block	O
that	O
the	O
Iron	O
is	O
fixt	O
on	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
What	O
name	O
did	O
he	O
call	O
it	O
by	O
?	O
Boddington	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
it	O
no	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
chalked	O
out	O
the	O
Parts	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
my	O
direction	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Buttons	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
found	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
We	O
mention	O
this	O
,	O
only	O
to	O
shew	O
that	O
that	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Stamps	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
was	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
to	O
hold	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
the	O
Instrument	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
Label	O
the	O
Parchment	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Punches	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rollos	O
.	O
These	O
Puncheons	O
are	O
to	O
repair	O
the	O
Stamps	O
after	O
they	O
are	O
cast	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
sink	O
the	O
Leaves	O
of	O
the	O
Roses	O
-	O
These	O
are	O
Letters	O
-	O
This	O
represents	O
the	O
Seed	O
in	O
the	O
Rose	O
of	O
the	O
six	O
Penny	O
Stamp	O
-	O
This	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
ornament	O
round	O
the	O
Hoop	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
for	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
Leaf	O
of	O
the	O
Rose	O
within	O
the	O
Garrer	O
-	O
This	O
,	O
a	O
Flower	O
de	O
Luce	O
in	O
the	O
Imperial	O
Crown	O
-	O
This	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
inner	O
Leaf	O
of	O
the	O
Roses	O
-	O
And	O
here	O
is	O
another	O
Ornament	O
for	O
the	O
Hoop	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Boddington	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
you	O
Orders	O
to	O
make	O
that	O
Engine	O
;	O
did	O
I	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
for	O
my	O
self	O
?	O
J.	O
Boddington	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Lancashire	O
to	O
make	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Buttons	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
come	O
to	O
examine	O
it	O
?	O
J.	O
Boddington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
one	O
Watts	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Boddington	O
's	O
Brother	O
-	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
Screw	O
Press	O
on	O
the	O
Block	O
for	O
Bridoak	O
?	O
George	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
of	O
this	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
is	O
Three	O
Threads	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
made	O
part	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
Two	O
Threads	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
often	O
make	O
such	O
things	O
?	O
G	O
Boddington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
several	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
use	O
?	O
G.	O
Boddington	O
.	O
They	O
may	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
what	O
use	O
they	O
please	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
commonly	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
for	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Buttons	O
-	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Being	O
told	O
that	O
Bridoak	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Thus	O
our	O
Acquantance	O
begun	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
set	O
up	O
one	O
Watts	O
to	O
make	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Buttons	O
at	O
Warrington	O
in	O
Lancashire	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
trust	O
Watts	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
a	O
Press	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
assist	O
in	O
the	O
management	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
worth	O
my	O
while	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
employed	O
Bridoak	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
-	O
And	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Lunnies	O
what	O
Ship	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Goods	O
in	O
for	O
Liverpool	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
examine	O
into	O
the	O
Truth	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lunnies	O
.	O
Yes	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
natural	O
for	O
a	O
guilty	O
Man	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
discovered	O
,	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
blame	O
on	O
another	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
what	O
Bridoak	O
has	O
done	O
by	O
me	O
-	O
I	O
shall	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
Presses	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
-	O
Call	O
John	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Wilden	I-pers
.	O
John	O
Roach	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
hired	O
me	O
and	O
Wilden	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
heavy	O
-	O
from	O
a	O
Stationer	O
's	O
in	O
Butcherhall	O
Lane	O
-	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
square	O
Stones	O
from	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
New-Street	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
to	O
White	O
Fryer	O
's	O
Stairs	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
carryed	O
them	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Old	O
Barge	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
them	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Wilden	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
These	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
Watts	O
-	O
Let	O
them	O
prove	O
that	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
-	O
Call	O
Mrs.	O
Hollings	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hollings	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Feather	O
on	O
the	O
Broad	O
Wall	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Bridoak	O
and	O
Watts	O
were	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Bridoak	O
make	O
a	O
Bargain	O
with	O
one	O
Sharp	O
for	O
my	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Broad	O
Wall	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Hollings	O
.	O
But	O
Wattt	O
came	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
not	O
Sharp	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
your	O
House	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
to	O
shew	O
that	O
I	O
employed	O
Bridoak	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
-	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
I	O
say	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
Watts	O
-	O
Let	O
them	O
call	O
the	O
Landlord	O
to	O
prove	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Watts	O
's	O
House	O
or	O
mine	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wigly	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
marsh	O
(	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
Bridoak	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
thereupon	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
he	O
surrendered	O
and	O
informed	O
against	O
me	O
-	O
Who	O
is	O
there	O
to	O
prove	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
me	O
but	O
he	O
-	O
And	O
he	O
owns	O
himse	O
'	O
f	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
-	O
Had	O
I	O
been	O
concerned	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
got	O
Money	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
-	O
But	O
I	O
was	O
reduced	O
to	O
such	O
streights	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
sell	O
my	O
Wig	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Law-suit	O
he	O
managed	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Prove	O
the	O
Law-suit	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
will	O
-	O
Call	O
Giles	O
Bradshaw	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
.	O
Bridoak	O
brought	O
an	O
Officer	O
and	O
arrested	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Suit	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
Bridoak	O
was	O
not	O
an	O
Attorney	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
act	O
as	O
a	O
Solliciter	O
?	O
G	O
Bradshaw	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
a	O
Solliciter	O
is	O
-	O
But	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Receipt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wigly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Landlord	O
in	O
Lambeth	O
Parish	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
rented	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
me	O
at	O
five	O
Pound	O
a	O
Year	O
-	O
Then	O
he	O
quitted	O
it	O
and	O
let	O
it	O
Bridoak	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
place	O
that	O
goes	O
off	O
the	O
Broad	O
Wall	O
-	O
Its	O
a	O
mighty	O
promiscuous	O
place	O
,	O
its	O
a	O
Hovel	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
Hog	O
's	O
Sty	O
.	O
Every	O
Door	O
is	O
a	O
Window	O
and	O
every	O
Win-	O
dow	O
is	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
looking	O
into	O
the	O
Windows	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Garden	O
before	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ditch	O
behind	O
;	O
a	O
mighty	O
promiscuous	O
place	O
indeed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
built	O
it	O
himself	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Workman	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
these	O
Contrivances	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Contrivances	O
,	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
Windows	O
?	O
What	O
is	O
there	O
particular	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
J.	O
Wigly	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Forge	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rollos	O
.	O
A	O
Furnace	O
,	O
and	O
Crucibles	O
,	O
and	O
Sand	O
.	O
J.	O
Wigly	O
.	O
He	O
cut	O
Callico-prints	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
Buckles	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
heard	O
him	O
pound	O
.	O
pound	O
,	O
pound-something	O
or	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
Bridoak	O
often	O
went	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
a	O
Flag	O
Basket	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
Lease	O
of	O
this	O
promiscuous	O
;	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
not	O
liking	O
the	O
Company	O
that	O
came	O
after	O
him	O
(	O
a	O
Woman	O
they	O
called	O
Flora	O
,	O
Bridoak	O
,	O
Watt	O
,	O
and	O
Boulter	O
)	O
I	O
refused	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
the	O
Lease	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
old	O
Watts	O
-	O
But	O
Bridoak	O
and	O
Boulter	O
threatned	O
to	O
sue	O
me	O
in	O
Chancery	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Call	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
-	O
Mr.	O
Dell	O
,	O
is	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
uncommon	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
?	O
B.	O
Dell	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
suspicious	O
-	O
Tis	O
a	O
slight	O
House	O
,	O
has	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
little	O
Rooms	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
is	O
a	O
Lost	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Garden	O
with	O
a	O
Gate	O
before	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Field	O
with	O
a	O
Ditch	O
behind	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cut	O
Prints	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
Day	O
after	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
work	O
upon	O
his	O
Prints	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
base	O
Action	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hains	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
civil	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Could	O
not	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Ground	O
into	O
mine	O
?	O
Hains	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Gap	O
on	O
purpose	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
is	O
only	O
fastened	O
by	O
a	O
single	O
Bolt	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
room	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
and	O
push	O
t	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lunnies	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
the	O
Landlord	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lunnies	O
I	O
think	O
his	O
Name	O
is	O
Igby	O
,	O
by	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Church	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Tenant	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Lunnies	O
Old	O
Watts	O
was	O
the	O
Tenant	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
Mr.	O
Bridoak	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
New-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Pauls	O
Alley	O
?	O
Bridoak	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Petty	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
hired	O
a	O
Room	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
Paul	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
Lady-Day	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
cohabited	O
together	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Months	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
there	O
only	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
my	O
Goods	O
into	O
Lancshire	O
-	O
Call	O
Mr.	O
Herbert	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Watts	O
's	O
Landlord	O
-	O
Did	O
not	O
Bridoak	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
House	O
to	O
bid	O
Watts	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
?	O
Edward	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
.	O
Bridoak	O
came	O
to	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
(	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
,	O
a	O
Baker	O
in	O
David-street	O
)	O
to	O
ask	O
if	O
Watts	O
lodged	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Business	O
.	O
Nothing	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
leave	O
a	O
Direction	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
took	O
this	O
Paper	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
for	O
Watts	O
-	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Note	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
these	O
Words	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dean	O
does	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
till	O
he	O
returns	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
apprehend	O
that	O
by	O
my	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
he	O
meant	O
my	O
being	O
in	O
Prison	O
?	O
E.	O
Herbert	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
afterwards	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Story	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Design	O
was	O
to	O
keep	O
Watts	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Florance	B-pers
Cameron	I-pers
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Bridoak	O
what	O
he	O
thought	O
would	O
come	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Trial	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
old	O
Watts	O
is	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
by	O
now	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
him	O
-	O
And	O
if	O
Dean	O
had	O
done	O
as	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Confinement	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
have	O
had	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Bridoak	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
Patterns	O
to	O
cut	O
Wooden-prints	O
for	O
Paper	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
like	O
Post	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
with	O
Crowns	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
However	O
there	O
being	O
one	O
for	O
Daffy	O
's	O
Elixir	O
I	O
begun	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
shuffled	O
off	O
the	O
finishing	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
an	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Law-suit	O
I	O
had	O
employed	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
wanted	O
for	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
36.	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
dead	O
Ducks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dobbs	I-pers
,	O
June	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
14	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Bonnet	I-pers
,	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
38	O
39.	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rachel	B-pers
Gardener	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Assaulting	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dearing	I-pers
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
June	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
40.	O
John	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
November	O
12	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Breadcot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brocaded	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
March	O
28.	O
in	O
the	O
sixth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
And	O
42	O
.	O
43.	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
44.	O
Peter	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Wilfull	O
and	O
Corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
to	O
aggrieve	O
Edward	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
discharge	O
a	O
Rule	O
against	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
for	O
excessive	O
Gaming	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
twenty	O
second	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
make	O
an	O
Affidavit	O
in	O
Writing	O
before	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
Lee	O
in	O
Serjeants	O
Inn	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Affidavit	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
Edward	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
did	O
lose	O
seven	O
Hundred	O
Guineas	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
at	O
Put	O
;	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Warren	O
did	O
look	O
over	O
the	O
said	O
Perkins	O
's	O
Shoulder	O
;	O
or	O
went	O
Partner	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Brown	O
;	O
or	O
did	O
receive	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Perkins	O
three	O
Hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
Guineas	O
for	O
his	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
seven	O
Hundred	O
Guineas	O
;	O
Whereas	O
in	O
Truth	O
and	O
in	O
Fact	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
45.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charlesworth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
extorting	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
-	O
Constable	O
.	O
But	O
no	O
Evidence	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
46	O
John	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Phillip	B-pers
Shirly	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
June	O
29	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shirly	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
The	O
Hoop	B-place
and	I-place
Bunch	I-place
of	I-place
Grapes	I-place
Tavern	I-place
facing	I-place
Beauford	I-place
's	I-place
Building	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Minutes	O
before	O
ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
Passage	O
into	O
my	O
Yard	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
and	O
rung	O
the	O
Bell	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
a	O
Candle	O
to	O
'em	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Port	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Drawer	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
rung	O
again	O
for	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
Coach	O
-	O
Do	O
they	O
take	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Coffee	O
house	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Do	O
they	O
think	O
that	O
out	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
I	O
can	O
afford	O
to	O
fe	O
d	O
a	O
Porter	O
on	O
their	O
Errand	O
?	O
Let	O
'em	O
walk	O
-	O
My	O
Porter	O
however	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
soon	O
after	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
went	O
of	O
several	O
Errands	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
they	O
expected	O
more	O
Company	O
and	O
would	O
stay	O
and	O
sup	O
-	O
They	O
had	O
a	O
cool	O
Tankard	O
-	O
some	O
Steaks	O
-	O
and	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Oat	O
Ale	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
near	O
eleven	O
without	O
paying	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
;	O
and	O
carried	O
off	O
the	O
two	O
Silver	O
Tankards	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
too	O
much	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
carried	O
in	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
turned	O
his	O
Face	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
,	O
Porter	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Men	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Fourteen	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
The	O
Swan	O
Alehouse	O
about	O
three	O
Doors	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Emes	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
perfectly	O
well	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
The	O
Bull	O
Head	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
topping	O
Gentelman	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
this	O
Message	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
but	O
one	O
Tankard	O
.	O
They	O
bid	O
me	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Porter	O
do	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
step	O
to	O
Tom	O
.	O
King	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
(	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Night-house	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
)	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Emes	O
is	O
not	O
theres	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
above	O
three	O
Minutes	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Master	O
carried	O
a	O
Candle	O
into	O
the	O
Fourteen	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Red	O
which	O
I	O
carried	O
to	O
them	O
-	O
They	O
asked-	O
for	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
They	O
ordered	O
a	O
Cool	O
Tankard	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
those	O
Men	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
Its	O
yours	O
if	O
its	O
lost	O
They	O
would	O
fain	O
have	O
made	O
the	O
Cool	O
Tankard	O
themselves	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
I	O
wanted	O
the	O
Strainer	O
and	O
Spoon	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
and	O
Strainer	O
away	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
some	O
Steaks	O
.	O
They	O
bid	O
me	O
give	O
the	O
Steaks	O
to	O
the	O
Cook	O
to	O
set	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Fire	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
yet	O
come	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
indeed	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Speech	O
-	O
Our	O
Porter	O
having	O
subscribed	O
him	O
to	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
that	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Dun	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Flower	O
de	O
luce	O
Court	O
I	O
enquired	O
at	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
thence	O
three	O
Days	O
;	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
a	O
Silver	O
Smith	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
leaned	O
over	O
the	O
Rails	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pursued	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Lion	O
in	O
Fetter	O
Lane	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
our	O
Porter	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
again	O
at	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
But	O
understanding	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Landlady	O
still	O
denyed	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
at	O
last	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
secured	O
-	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
supp	O
'd	O
that	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
in	O
Salisbury	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
Suit	O
of	O
Clothes	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
Salisbury	O
Court	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
?	O
Wilton	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
heard	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Cook	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Fourteen	O
,	O
ordered	O
some	O
Steaks	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
again	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Cool	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
any	O
Oat	O
Ale	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
ordered	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
Fisher	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
a	O
Tankard	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
by	O
his	O
Stature	O
,	O
his	O
Voice	O
,	O
and	O
partly	O
by	O
his	O
Complexion	O
and	O
Dress	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Here	O
,	O
Drawer	O
!	O
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
shall	O
swear	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
retract	O
all	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
said	O
.	O
Wilton	O
.	O
I	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
Cloth	O
for	O
the	O
Steaks	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
in	O
the	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Oat	O
Ale	O
and	O
left	O
both	O
the	O
Tankards	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
side	O
Faces	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
remember	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
Grey	O
Coat	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
now	O
has	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
his	O
Person	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
.	O
At	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
Ten	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
by	O
the	O
Fourteen	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
-	O
He	O
had	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Wig	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Features	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
certain	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
any	O
one	O
can	O
be	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Duncan	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
some	O
Beer	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
fourteen	O
was	O
open	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fourteen	O
with	O
Steaks	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
him	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
opened	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
Man	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Wig	O
,	O
Iron	O
Grey	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
Black	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
view	O
me	O
yesterday	O
in	O
the	O
Bail	O
Dock	O
and	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
my	O
Clothes	O
-	O
last	O
Sunday	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Havers	O
,	O
in	O
Salisbury	O
Court	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
after	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Flower	O
de	O
luce	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Goody	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Havers	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
he	O
learns	O
Gentlemen	O
Languages	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
teach	O
Latin	O
and	O
Greek	O
,	O
but	O
chiefly	O
French	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
bred	O
a	O
Physician	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Havers	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Salisbury	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
once	O
out	O
,	O
till	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eleven	O
.	O
Catherine	O
R	O
per	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Christian	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
(	O
who	O
were	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Havers	O
's	O
House	O
)	O
all	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
particulars	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Goody	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Flower	O
de	O
luce	O
Court	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Fetter	O
Lane	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Lodger	O
;	O
he	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
directly	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Court	O
)	O
for	O
some	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
and	O
returned	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
,	O
Mr.	O
King	O
,	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
Mr	O
Ashton	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
Jewel	O
Office/	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Jekyll	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
sober	O
and	O
worthy	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
appeared	O
ready	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
it	O
unnecessary	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
47.	O
William	B-pers
Byrom	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
June	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
48	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Gilt	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
de	I-pers
St	I-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
49	O
Sarah	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
three	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
five	O
Moidores	O
,	O
six	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Pierce	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dunkerton	I-pers
,	O
October	O
26	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
50.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rome	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Robotham	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Hughs	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Laced	O
Head	O
Cloths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
nine	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
being	O
insufficient	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
51	O
Ann	B-pers
Craft	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
ten	O
pair	O
of	O
Womens	O
Yarn	O
Hose	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Oakey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jul	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
