TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1735.	O
in	O
the	O
Eight	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BELLAMY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1735	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
,	O
M.DCC.XXXV	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BELLAMY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Probyn	O
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
Comyns	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Urlin	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Shellswell	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Dison	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Blackbourn	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Tyre	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ainsworth	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Valentine	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Mark	B-pers
Aldworth	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ayliff	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bignell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Whitton	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Nowles	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Milchet	I-pers
,	O
Gerard	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Archambeau	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
John	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Matthew	I-place
Friday	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
Book-keeper	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
500	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
December	O
27	O
.	O
John	O
Gibson	O
(	O
the	O
Hereford	O
Carrier	O
.	O
)	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
twenty	O
first	O
or	O
twenty	O
second	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
500	O
Guineas	O
of	O
-	O
Clayton	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Receiver	O
General	O
of	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Hereford	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
in	O
my	O
Waggon	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
was	O
sealed	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
delivered	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
who	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
At	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
packing	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
Tom	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
Fetch	O
the	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Seal	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
she	O
roll	O
'd	O
some	O
Straw	O
round	O
it	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
an	O
old	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Saddle	O
Bags	O
.	O
They	O
roll	O
'd	O
more	O
Straw	O
round	O
the	O
Saddle	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
small	O
Pack	O
of	O
Goods	O
and	O
corded	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Pack	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
towards	O
the	O
Fore-end	O
.	O
The	O
Waggon	O
was	O
loaded	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
twelve	O
it	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
My	O
Brother	O
Thomas	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
my	O
self	O
-	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
sennight	O
,	O
my	O
Son	O
In-law	O
,	O
William	O
Mountain	O
(	O
the	O
Monmouth	O
Carrier	O
)	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
My	O
Waggon	O
inns	O
at	O
the	O
Saracen	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
in	I-place
Friday	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
my	O
Book-keeper	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
charge	O
others	O
?	O
J.	O
Gibson	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
John	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Airs	I-pers
,	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Porters	O
who	O
unloaded	O
the	O
Waggon	O
at	O
the	O
Inn	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Passengers	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
?	O
J.	O
Gibson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
But	O
I	O
connot	O
say	O
how	O
many	O
.	O
P.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
send	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
J.	O
Gibson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
usual	O
thing	O
.	O
P.	O
Council	O
.	O
Among	O
the	O
other	O
Particulars	O
in	O
that	O
Bill	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
mention	O
this	O
Money	O
?	O
J.	O
Gibson	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
it	O
proper	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
with	O
advice	O
of	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
?	O
J.	O
Gibson	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
sometimes	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
oftner	O
omitted	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
packed	O
up	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
for	O
London	O
about	O
twelve	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
never	O
stir	O
'd	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
.	O
For	O
though	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
Passengers	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
yet	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
Pack	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Boxes	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
loaded	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
where	O
we	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
a	O
Night	O
for	O
watching	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Inn-Yard	O
(	O
in	O
Friday	O
Street	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
nothing	O
had	O
been	O
removed	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Waggon	O
unloaded	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
tired	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Porters	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
thinking	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Tap-house	O
where	O
I	O
staid	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hours	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
little	O
Parcel	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
searched	O
the	O
Bags	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
but	O
Straw	O
in	O
'em	O
.	O
-	O
Nothing	O
but	O
Straw	O
in	O
'em.	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
in	O
great	O
Surprise	O
,	O
for	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
-	O
Sure	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
mistaken	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Bags	O
lying	O
under	O
his	O
Desk	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
them	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Porters	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
they	O
denyed	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Aires	I-pers
(	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
)	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Saddle	O
Bags	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Pack	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
old	O
pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
Man	O
.	O
For	O
their	O
Method	O
is	O
,	O
to	O
unload	O
the	O
Goods	O
by	O
the	O
Waggon	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
every	O
Parcel	O
single	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Book-keeper	O
,	O
who	O
sits	O
in	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Were	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Journey	O
?	O
T.	O
Gibson	O
.	O
We	O
always	O
have	O
Way-Goods	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
call	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
these	O
we	O
put	O
at	O
the	O
Tail	O
of	O
the	O
Waggon	O
.	O
William	O
Mountain	O
.	O
Being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
twenty	O
second	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
into	O
talk	O
about	O
this	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
hard	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
out	O
who	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
than	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
aware	O
of	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
Men	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
concern	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
describe	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
proper	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
a	O
Man	O
would	O
bring	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
Confession	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
some	O
Person	O
in	O
Goal	O
before	O
the	O
matter	O
all	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
Intelligence	O
?	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
cunning	O
Man	O
at	O
Wickham	O
in	O
Buckinghamshire	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
John	O
Gibson	O
himself	O
cunjure	O
for	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Book	O
and	O
Key	O
?	O
W.	O
Mountain	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
proposed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Wickham	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
cunning	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
.	O
At	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Gibson	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
patience	O
and	O
not	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Goal	O
,	O
for	O
before	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
next	O
Month	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
again	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Aye	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
cunning	O
Man	O
spoke	O
Truth	O
.	O
Fry	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
might	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
cunning	O
Man	O
told	O
him	O
so	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Rustel	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
Night	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
-	O
Council	O
.	O
What	O
Money	O
?	O
The	O
500	O
Guineas	O
that	O
Gibson	O
had	O
lost	O
?	O
Rustel	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Saracen	O
's	O
Head	O
Inn	O
Yard	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Gibson	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
ruin	O
me	O
quite	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
but	O
half	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
that	O
is	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
send	O
me	O
but	O
100	O
Guineas	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
by	O
any	O
Messenger	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
it	O
without	O
asking	O
any	O
Questions	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
answered	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
expect	O
to	O
have	O
your	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
Yard	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
.	O
Then	O
Gibson	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
quarrel	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
100	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
than	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
served	O
him	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
lodges	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lodge	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
.	O
Between	O
Christmas	O
Day	O
and	O
New	O
Year	O
's	O
Day	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
for	O
a	O
Pail	O
of	O
Water	O
,	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
shew	O
me	O
something	O
to	O
grease	O
my	O
Eyes	O
with	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Closer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
great	O
Bag	O
of	O
Money	O
and	O
pour	O
'd	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Lap	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
300	O
Pound	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
all	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
Child	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Merchants	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
all	O
away	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Pad-lock	O
on	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
if	O
any	O
Rogues	O
should	O
hear	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
'll	O
think	O
its	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
knock	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
coming	O
home	O
to	O
Dinner	O
,	O
Edad	O
she	O
calls	O
him	O
in	O
and	O
shews	O
him	O
this	O
Gold	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
loves	O
to	O
have	O
me	O
keep	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
What	O
a-pox	O
do	O
ye	O
do	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
Room	O
?	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
Nursing	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
Ah	O
,	O
pox	O
o	O
'	O
your	O
Pad-lock	O
!	O
the	O
Money	O
's	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
Osborn	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
Tinner	O
ant	O
wass	O
coing	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
put	O
the	O
Prissoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
callt	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
sait	O
Here	O
iss	O
your	O
coot	O
Oman	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
hust	O
her	O
a	O
pit	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
her	O
why	O
a	O
Tiffel	O
she	O
coud	O
n't	O
keep	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Hapitation	O
when	O
I	O
wanted	O
my	O
Tinner	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
Prissoners	O
Wife	O
prought	O
out	O
a	O
pag	O
with	O
a	O
crate	O
teal	O
of	O
coolt	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
crate	O
many	O
Pieces	O
,	O
a	O
crate	O
teal	O
pigger	O
as	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
This	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
Gibson	O
lost	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Osborn	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Ant	O
she	O
pickt	O
out	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
of	O
them	O
crate	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
kafe	O
'em	O
to	O
the	O
Chilt	O
to	O
truntle	O
apout	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Where	O
a	O
Cots	O
Name	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
ket	O
all	O
this	O
Money	O
?	O
O	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
ours	O
,	O
put	O
my	O
Uspant	O
is	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
away	O
for	O
a	O
Merchant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Airs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
unload	O
the	O
Waggon	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Pack	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
which	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
Boots	O
;	O
No	O
says	O
Leach	O
,	O
They	O
are	O
Saddle	O
Bags	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Goddard	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
search	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
in	O
them	O
but	O
a	O
Wad	O
of	O
Straw	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
fastned	O
at	O
top	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
each	O
end	O
of	O
each	O
Bag	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Hole	O
big	O
enough	O
to	O
thrust	O
ones	O
Fist	O
in	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
Stephen	O
Leach	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
given	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
2.	O
Mary	B-pers
Manwaring	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Pennyman	I-pers
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Charles	B-pers
Peel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Carteret	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
for	O
170	O
l.	O
drawn	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
April	O
13	O
,	O
1727.	O
on	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Shewill	I-pers
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Denzil	B-pers
Onslow	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Treasurer	O
of	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
,	O
or	O
order	O
twenty	O
Days	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
for	O
Value	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
;	O
the	O
said	O
Bill	O
being	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Andrew	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
1727	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
causing	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
an	O
Indorsement	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Bill	O
in	O
these	O
Words	O
,	O
Recd	O
.	O
Denzil	O
Onslow	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
publishing	O
the	O
said	O
forged	O
Indorsement	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
Receipt	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Bill	O
in	O
these	O
Words	O
,	O
Recd	O
.	O
Denzil	O
Onslow	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
fifth	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
publishing	O
the	O
said	O
Receipt	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
.	O
To	O
all	O
these	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
4.	O
William	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
(	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
)	O
of	O
St.	O
Martins	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
(	O
his	O
own	O
Mother	O
)	O
by	O
wilfully	O
discharging	O
a	O
Musket	O
loaded	O
with	O
Powder	O
and	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Bullet	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
above	O
the	O
right	O
Ear	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
six	O
Inches	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
May	O
8	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
;	O
and	O
thereupon	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
5.	O
Elton	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
Mariner	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
(	O
his	O
Aunt	O
)	O
by	O
striking	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Hatchet	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
hinder	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
breadth	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
April	O
21	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
,	O
to	O
both	O
which	O
Indictments	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
6.	O
Hester	B-pers
Hargrove	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Durdant	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Mob	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
April	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
William	B-pers
Ruberry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Pointer	I-pers
,	O
by	O
knocking	O
her	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Hoe	O
and	O
giving	O
her	O
several	O
Mortal	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
13th	O
and	O
dyed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Newby	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Easter	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
thick	O
set	O
Hedge	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
looking	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Hedge	O
,	O
Pray	O
what	O
's	O
the	O
Matter	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
They	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Man	O
beating	O
a	O
Woman	O
unmercifully	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
farther	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
Ye	O
Villain	O
!	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
beat	O
a	O
Man	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
she	O
were	O
a	O
little	O
apart	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Hoing	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
knock	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Hoe	O
and	O
stamp	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
Groin	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
cut	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
pieces	O
and	O
stamp	O
her	O
Guts	O
out	O
at	O
her	O
Mouth	O
for	O
going	O
upon	O
his	O
Crop	O
.	O
Ye	O
Villain	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
serve	O
a	O
Woman	O
so	O
?	O
Hold	O
your	O
Tongue	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
as	O
much	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
came	O
every	O
Day	O
after	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
Day	O
she	O
dyed	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
her	O
Eye	O
was	O
black	O
and	O
swelled	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
something	O
within	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
should	O
die	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
Fighting	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
complained	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
trod	O
on	O
her	O
Belly	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
she	O
lay	O
a-bed	O
all	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
Ann	O
Newby	O
asked	O
if	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Blood	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
worse	O
than	O
when	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
(	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
know	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
)	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
six	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
ten	O
the	O
same	O
Morning	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
dead	O
in	O
a	O
Stable	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
.	O
She	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
assaulting	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
served	O
at	O
the	O
New	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Kensington	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
whose	O
Name	O
was	O
Will	O
.	O
Ruberry	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Hoe	O
and	O
stampt	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
whipt	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
before	O
Justice	O
Vincent	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
made	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
paying	O
her	O
six	O
Shillings	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Noon	O
the	O
Beadle	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
Body	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
lower	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
which	O
we	O
call	O
the	O
Pubis	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Bruise	O
externally	O
.	O
And	O
opening	O
the	O
Part	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
and	O
Matter	O
about	O
the	O
Gut	O
,	O
we	O
call	O
the	O
Rectum	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
distemper	O
'd	O
pocky	O
Body	O
.	O
Jury-man	O
.	O
Might	O
that	O
Blood	O
be	O
occasion	O
'd	O
by	O
Blows	O
?	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Blows	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
the	O
Vessels	O
breaking	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
in	O
Easter	O
Week	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
Betty	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
quarrel	O
'd	O
in	O
Holland	O
Walk	O
.	O
The	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
held	O
up	O
a	O
Knife	O
at	O
Morris	O
,	O
and	O
Morris	O
hit	O
her	O
a	O
slap	O
o'the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
into	O
Fits	O
and	O
foam	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Mouth	O
.	O
Fox	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
subject	O
to	O
Fits	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Chowny	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
'em	O
a	O
scolding	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lying	O
on	O
her	O
Back	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
Betty	O
Morris	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
ye	O
beat	O
her	O
for	O
?	O
Says	O
Betty	O
,	O
she	O
threatned	O
my	O
Life	O
and	O
bit	O
my	O
Finger	O
off	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
.	O
At	O
seven	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
Gin	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
light	O
her	O
Pipe	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
other	O
Company	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
such	O
Cattle	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
drunken	O
quarrelsome	O
Creature	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
-	O
Gains	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
Harrison	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
laborious	O
careful	O
honest	O
quiet	O
Man	O
.	O
and	O
not	O
inclinable	O
to	O
be	O
quarrelsome	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
9.	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Goat	O
's	O
Hair	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bosanquet	I-pers
,	O
May	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10	O
,	O
11.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hunton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
9	O
.	O
Mary	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
Margaret	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gillam	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Gwillim	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Loaves	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
April	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
13.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
d.	O
3/4	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
,	O
April	O
19	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
14.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hyfield	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ham	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crapper	I-pers
,	O
May	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Richard	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Hats	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
April	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Mary	B-pers
Doderidge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
17.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Potlids	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Beef	O
Fork	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
April	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
William	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Stamp	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
thirty	O
six	O
Chrystal	O
Stones	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Volaire	I-pers
,	O
January	O
8	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
four	O
Chrystal	O
Stones	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Duval	I-pers
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Volaire	I-pers
.	O
Dat	O
is	O
de	O
Man	O
vid	O
de	O
Cap	O
.	O
He	O
come	O
and	O
aska	O
me	O
to	O
use	O
mine	O
Tools	O
in	O
de	O
Lapidary	O
Business	O
for	O
two	O
Shillings	O
in	O
de	O
Veek	O
.	O
He	O
vark	O
vid	O
mine	O
Tool	O
,	O
van	O
,	O
two	O
Veek	O
,	O
and	O
den	O
he	O
no	O
vark	O
any	O
longer	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
lose	O
a	O
mine	O
Brass	O
Stamp	O
and	O
tree	O
Dozen	O
of	O
mine	O
Stones	O
-	O
da	O
vare	O
de	O
Oval	O
Chrystal	O
Stones	O
-	O
Den	O
I	O
no	O
can	O
tell	O
vat	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
de	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
Monsieur	O
Duval	O
give	O
a	O
me	O
notice	O
dat	O
if	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Shustice	O
Deveil	O
I	O
fall	O
hear	O
of	O
mine	O
Tings	O
.	O
And	O
ven	O
I	O
go	O
dare	O
,	O
de	O
Prisonnaar	O
make	O
de	O
Confessiong	O
dat	O
he	O
steal	O
mine	O
Stamp	O
and	O
mine	O
Stones	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Duval	I-pers
.	O
De	O
Prisonnaar	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
de	O
New-Year-Day	O
,	O
and	O
aska	O
me	O
to	O
vark	O
upon	O
mine	O
Tool	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
say	O
Monsieur	O
Volaire	O
ave	O
turn	O
him	O
ava	O
.	O
Vell	O
,	O
I	O
say	O
,	O
Go	O
up	O
and	O
vark	O
for	O
two	O
Shilling	O
de	O
Veek	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
is	O
de	O
common	O
price	O
for	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
de	O
Master	O
's	O
Tools	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
vark	O
a	O
leetle	O
vile	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
two	O
Dozen	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
Chrystal	O
Stones	O
.	O
I	O
aska	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
take	O
adem	O
.	O
He	O
tella	O
me	O
no	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
Vy	O
I	O
ave	O
no	O
Teef	O
come	O
to	O
mine	O
Ouse	O
but	O
you	O
.	O
Vell	O
he	O
can	O
tell	O
noting	O
of	O
de	O
Matter	O
.	O
Den	O
he	O
vark	O
a	O
leetle	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
den	O
I	O
miss	O
Von	O
Vastcoat	O
,	O
von	O
Shart	O
,	O
and	O
von	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Vell	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
be	O
no	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
you	O
be	O
de	O
Teef	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
no	O
longer	O
stay	O
in	O
mine	O
Ouse	O
.	O
Den	O
he	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
Ale	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
mine	O
Vife	O
lose	O
von	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
Vare	O
is	O
mine	O
Box	O
?	O
Your	O
Box	O
?	O
he	O
say	O
,	O
Vat	O
you	O
make	O
a	O
Rogue	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
-	O
Rogue	O
?	O
Vy	O
you	O
be	O
de	O
Rogue	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
mine	O
Box-Pox	O
o	O
'	O
your	O
Box	O
!	O
Vy	O
a	O
diable	O
you	O
make	O
adis	O
Noise	O
about	O
de	O
lousy	O
Box	O
?	O
I	O
vell	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
Ha'penny	O
for	O
your	O
Box	O
-	O
I	O
will	O
ave	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
Ha'penny	O
,	O
you	O
Rogue	O
!	O
Vat	O
ave	O
you	O
do	O
vid	O
mine	O
Husband	O
's	O
Vastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Shart	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
oder	O
Tings	O
?	O
-	O
Vat	O
Tings	O
?	O
-	O
Vy	O
his	O
Stamp	O
and	O
his	O
Stones	O
;	O
you	O
be	O
de	O
fine	O
Rogue	O
indeed	O
!	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
make	O
Vark	O
vid	O
mine	O
Usband	O
's	O
Tool	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
vid	O
his	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
dat	O
he	O
have	O
.	O
Vell	O
,	O
after	O
dis	O
,	O
ve	O
fesh	O
the	O
Coonstable	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
den	O
he	O
confess	O
de	O
Vastcoat	O
and	O
de	O
Shart	O
,	O
and	O
de	O
Stamp	O
and	O
de	O
Stones	O
,	O
and	O
dat	O
he	O
sell	O
de	O
Stones	O
to	O
Monsieur	O
Treneau	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Treneau	I-pers
(	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
)	O
About	O
last	O
Christmas	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Stones	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
twenty	O
Pence	O
a	O
Dozen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Pragnell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Duval	O
's	O
Wife	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Shirt	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
off	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
creditable	O
People	O
to	O
appear	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
happen	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
whereas	O
at	O
the	O
Sessions	O
held	O
here	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
was	O
convicted	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
,	O
January	O
16	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
fourteen	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Anterack	I-pers
,	O
January	O
18	O
.	O
He	O
the	O
said	O
Patrick	O
Lambert	O
did	O
afterwards	O
receive	O
the	O
same	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Record	O
of	O
the	O
Conviction	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
was	O
read	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Merchant	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
neither	O
know	O
who	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
.	O
Morgan	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Compton	O
Street	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Kinswoman	O
Mary	O
brought	O
down	O
the	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Merchant	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
Yards	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
Minutes	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
same	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Merchant	O
's	O
-	O
And	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
fourteen	O
Pound	O
Leaden	O
Weight	O
carried	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Anterack	O
's	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
delivered	O
back	O
;	O
for	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
absconded	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Anterack	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
fourteen	O
Pound	O
Leaden	O
Weight	O
;	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Saxon	I-pers
who	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
in	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
swore	O
that	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
Weight	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Weight	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
mine	O
.	O
Mr	O
J.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
Jenkins	O
was	O
convicted	O
on	O
Saxon	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
absconded	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
four	O
Months	O
.	O
Saxon	O
being	O
very	O
sick	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
I	O
discharged	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
afterwards	O
came	O
voluntarily	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bound	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
forty	O
Pounds	O
for	O
Saxon	O
's	O
Appearance	O
-	O
There	O
lies	O
the	O
Recognizance	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barly	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Bail	O
for	O
Saxon	O
told	O
me	O
yesterday	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sent	O
a	O
Man	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
bribe	O
Saxon	O
to	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
's	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
Saxon	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
found	O
Major	O
Barnwell	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Parlor	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Be	O
easy	O
,	O
be	O
favourable	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
Man	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
ye	O
what	O
ye	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
you	O
live	O
-	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
's	O
Face	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
M.	O
Barnwell	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
Sir	O
?	O
You	O
ought	O
to	O
know	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
Offence	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
screen	O
any	O
Person	O
from	O
Justice	O
.	O
Major	O
Barnwell	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
intended	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
innocent	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
too	O
busy-You	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
indicted	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barly	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
did	O
receive	O
a	O
Pestle	O
and	O
Mortar	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
one	O
and	O
twenty	O
Pence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Thief	O
selling	O
Lead	O
there	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
convicted	O
about	O
five	O
Years	O
ago	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Pump	O
that	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
transported	O
.	O
Dideric	B-pers
Hindson	I-pers
.	O
A	O
dud	O
leef	O
two	O
,	O
tree	O
Year	O
in	O
his	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
wrong	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
De	O
People	O
I	O
am	O
acquainted	O
vid	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
-	O
and	O
some	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
no	O
wonder	O
at	O
dat	O
,	O
for	O
da	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
too	O
.	O
Caleb	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
His	O
Character	O
is	O
honest	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Eve	I-pers
.	O
He	O
's	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
for	O
ought	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
honestly	O
-	O
Tho	O
'	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
once	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Desumble	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Major	O
Barnwell	O
.	O
He	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
extraordinary	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
Man	O
without	O
Enemies	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
20	O
,	O
21	O
,	O
22	O
,	O
23.	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
*	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Godson	I-pers
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Charles	B-pers
Stockton	I-pers
alias	O
Stogdon	O
,	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Benyan	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Power	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
9	O
s	O
.	O
May	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
for	O
robbing	O
Abigail	B-pers
Bingo	I-pers
in	O
St.	O
Peter	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
,	O
Number	O
I	O
.	O
Part	O
2	O
.	O
Page	O
3	O
.	O
But	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
Robberies	O
in	O
Surry	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
down	O
to	O
Kingston	O
to	O
be	O
tryed	O
at	O
the	O
Assizes	O
held	O
there	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
when	O
no	O
Bill	O
being	O
found	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Power	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
thirteenth	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
Lamb	B-place
's	I-place
Conduit	I-place
with	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Lad	O
(	O
William	B-pers
Howson	I-pers
)	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
other	O
Fellows	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
(	O
in	O
a	O
Jockey	O
's	O
Black	O
Cap	O
)	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
and	O
collar	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
falling	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Sutton	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
it	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
Thereupon	O
Hoxson	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Red-Lyon-Street	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
help	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
Sutton	O
beat	O
me	O
violently	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Godson	O
step	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
dropt	O
your	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Company	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
a	O
Brick-layer	O
said	O
,	O
Ye	O
Dogs	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
rob	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
o	O
'	O
Day	O
?	O
I	O
'll	O
run	O
my	O
Trowel	O
in	O
your	O
Guts	O
.	O
One	O
Man	O
collar	O
'd	O
Sutton	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Howson	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Master	O
,	O
(	O
James	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Poulterer	O
in	O
Holborn	O
)	O
sent	O
into	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
Street	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
make	O
me	O
drink	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
a	O
Pond	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
four	O
Fellows	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
He	O
's	O
drunk	O
.	O
Damn	O
'em	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
What	O
would	O
they	O
be	O
at	O
?	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
Black	O
Cap	O
,	O
Will	O
ye	O
fight	O
?	O
and	O
so	O
stripping	O
back	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
Then	O
Sutton	O
took	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
hurt	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
drink	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
drunk	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
walk	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Elkins	O
towards	O
Pancras	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
We	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
Sutton	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Sutton	O
damn	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
for	O
saying	O
so	O
.	O
Godson	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Sutton	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
abusing	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
He	O
answered	O
he	O
would	O
serve	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Struggles	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
Sutton	O
fell	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
his	O
Family	O
.	O
Sutton	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
insulted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
Coat	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
.	O
Plunket	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
made	O
any	O
resistance	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Elkins	O
.	O
Going	O
into	O
Lamb	O
's	O
Conduit-Fields	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
for	O
a	O
Shower	O
of	O
Rains	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
and	O
saw	O
four	O
Men	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
a	O
Man	O
has	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
murdered	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
towards	O
them	O
with	O
my	O
Trowel	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
Plunket	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Pistols	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
staid	O
,	O
and	O
Sutton	O
collar	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Grass	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
by	O
the	O
New	O
Burying	O
Ground	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
Bowling	O
Green	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
five	O
People	O
in	O
contest	O
.	O
Two	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
each	O
others	O
Collar	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
help	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
barbarously	O
used	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
-	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
-	O
A	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Trowel	O
-	O
Sutton	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Stables	O
next	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
with	O
other	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Men	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
sneaking	O
along	O
by	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
Ditch	O
he	O
looked	O
pale	O
and	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
stopt	O
him	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
.	O
Then	O
Sutton	O
's	O
Confession	O
taken	O
May	O
14.	O
before	O
John	B-pers
Poulson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
was	O
proved	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
following	O
effect	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Godson	O
,	O
Stockton	O
and	O
Benyan	O
,	O
met	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
at	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Sun	O
and	O
Horshoe	O
in	O
Dyer	O
's	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Fie'ds	O
and	O
rob	O
.	O
From	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
opposite	O
Brandy	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
thence	O
to	O
an	O
infamous	O
House	O
the	O
Two	O
Fighting	O
Cocks	O
at	O
the	O
Brill	O
,	O
kept	O
by	O
Taylor	O
alias	O
Pritchard	O
.	O
Going	O
thence	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
:	O
One	O
of	O
us	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Black	O
Cap	O
)	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Waistcoat	O
Pocket	O
;	O
but	O
People	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
String	O
hanging	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
threw	O
the	O
Watch	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Godson	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
might	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
our	O
Company	O
.	O
Sutton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
when	O
I	O
made	O
that	O
Confession	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Thief	O
Takers	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Mr.Justice	O
Polson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
sober	O
-	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
be	O
deceived	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
Examination	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
an	O
Information	O
-	O
He	O
read	O
it	O
over	O
himself	O
before	O
he	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Godson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
and	O
lived	O
at	O
Rochester	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Brother-Craft	O
in	O
Phoenix	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
I	O
met	O
Sutton	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
formerly	O
done	O
Work	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Family	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Sun	O
and	O
Horshoe	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
Acquaintance	O
:	O
We	O
drank	O
together	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
Hound	O
's	O
Ditch	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
their	O
persuasions	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
there	O
before	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
haste	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
before	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
one	O
of	O
Sutton	O
's	O
Acquaintance	O
(	O
in	O
a	O
Black	O
Cap	O
;	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
Sutton	O
stept	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
ye	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
fight	O
.	O
Presently	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
at	O
hearing	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
and	O
trembled	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
a	O
Watch	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
.	O
Godson	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Journey-man	O
at	O
Rochester	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
back	O
again	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
I	O
entrusted	O
him	O
to	O
cut	O
out	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
just	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Godson	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Sutton	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
24.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
first	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
at	O
Edgware	B-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
four	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
four	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
twelve	O
Napkins	O
,	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
six	O
Towels	O
,	O
six	O
Pillowbiers	O
,	O
six	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Dimity	O
Waste	O
Coat	O
,	O
fifteen	O
Guineas	O
,	O
three	O
Moidores	O
and	O
thirty	O
Shillings	O
Feb.	O
4	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
2d	O
.	O
For	O
assaulting	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
.	O
3d	O
.	O
For	O
Assaulting	O
,	O
Ravishing	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
Will	O
,	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
4th	O
.	O
For	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bay	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
.	O
5th	O
.	O
For	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
la	I-place
Bonne	I-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
Feb.	O
7	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
6th	O
.	O
For	O
Assaulting	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
Feb.	O
7	O
.	O
First	O
,	O
Second	O
,	O
and	O
Third	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Elder	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Edgware	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Somebody	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
Name	O
.	O
My	O
Servant	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Peats	I-pers
,	O
unbolted	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
five	O
Men	O
rush	O
'd	O
in	O
with	O
ten	O
Pistols	O
,	O
each	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
having	O
one	O
in	O
each	O
Hand	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
positively	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
among	O
them	O
pretty	O
much	O
like	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
swore	O
they	O
'd	O
kill	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
'em	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
six-and-thirty	O
.	O
Shilling	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
They	O
broke	O
the	O
two	O
Buttons	O
off	O
my	O
Breeches	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
wanted	O
more	O
Money	O
.	O
They	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Door	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
with	O
two	O
Handles	O
,	O
four	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
-	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
another	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
below	O
Stairs	O
-	O
still	O
they	O
wanted	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
.	O
My	O
Breeches	O
being	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
set	O
my	O
bare	O
backside	O
on	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
burnt	O
indeed	O
,	O
but	O
sorely	O
scalded	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
a	O
Case	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
rip	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
Bill	O
to	O
chop	O
my	O
Legs	O
off	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
confess	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
Back	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Maid	O
was	O
beating	O
up	O
Butter	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Kettle	O
off	O
the	O
Fire	O
with	O
two	O
Pails	O
of	O
Water	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
threw	O
the	O
Water	O
all	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
happened	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
quite	O
scalding	O
hot	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
between	O
twenty	O
and	O
thirty	O
Pounds	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
lost	O
-	O
They	O
took	O
my	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Table	O
Cloths	O
,	O
Napkins	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
best	O
Linnen	O
I	O
had	O
-	O
They	O
broke	O
my	O
Head	O
with	O
their	O
Pistols	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
blood	O
run	O
down	O
and	O
matted	O
my	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
live	O
till	O
Morning	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
where	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
-	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
over	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
pull	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Capes	O
of	O
their	O
Coats	O
-	O
At	O
their	O
first	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
broke	O
a	O
Fowling	O
Piece	O
which	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
serve	O
my	O
son	O
Joseph	O
just	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
served	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
my	O
Boy	O
shew	O
them	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
having	O
another	O
Son	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
to	O
venture	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
staid	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
for	O
his	O
coming	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
tyed	O
my	O
Hands	O
and	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hands	O
and	O
Legs	O
of	O
my	O
Man	O
and	O
Maid	O
and	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
leaving	O
us	O
lying	O
upon	O
our	O
Backs	O
,	O
they	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
-	O
They	O
took	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
about	O
sixty	O
Pounds	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
went	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
February	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Rowlets	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
Inn	O
in	O
the	O
Broad	O
Way	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
Horse	O
and	O
Gregory	O
's	O
stood	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
at	O
Edgware	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
shod	O
this	O
Farmer	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
)	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
worth	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
his	O
Advice	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
thither	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Rose	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
;	O
Turpin	O
and	O
Fielder	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
us	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Pots	O
at	O
the	O
Bowl	O
and	O
Skettle	O
on	O
the	O
Hill	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Edgware	O
.	O
Thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
at	O
Stanmore	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
drank	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
eat	O
Bacon	O
and	O
Eggs	O
for	O
Supper	O
.	O
We	O
set	O
out	O
again	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
wanted	O
but	O
a	O
small	O
matter	O
of	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
rode	O
into	O
the	O
Farmer	O
(	O
Lawrence	O
's	O
)	O
Grounds	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
tyed	O
up	O
our	O
Horses	O
within	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Hearing	O
the	O
Boy	O
calling	O
up	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
we	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
Fielder	O
jumpt	O
over	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
half	O
Door	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Sheep-boy	O
,	O
and	O
tyed	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
and	O
knock	O
,	O
and	O
answer	O
to	O
any	O
Body	O
that	O
asked	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
knock	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
servant	O
Man	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
Rose	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
two	O
Pistols	O
each	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
Turpin	O
and	O
Fielder	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
a-piece	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
rush	O
'd	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
bound	O
the	O
Boy	O
again	O
(	O
for	O
we	O
had	O
unbound	O
him	O
)	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
bonnd	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
over	O
them	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
others	O
carried	O
up	O
the	O
Old	O
Man	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
shew	O
them	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
two	O
Half	O
Crowns	O
and	O
eighteen	O
Pence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
Ye	O
,	O
shew	O
me	O
where	O
your	O
Master	O
's	O
Money	O
is	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
Curtesy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
made	O
her	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
cryed	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
But	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
Men	O
has	O
lain	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
by	O
force	O
?	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
We	O
put	O
the	O
Linnen	O
in	O
Sacks	O
-	O
the	O
Plate	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
put	O
in	O
their	O
Pockets	O
-	O
and	O
carried	O
all	O
to	O
our	O
Horses	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Day	O
we	O
divided	O
our	O
Booty	O
.	O
Rose	O
gave	O
us	O
fifteen	O
Shillings	O
for	O
all	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
likewise	O
bought	O
of	O
us	O
the	O
two	O
handled	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
now	O
for	O
how	O
much	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Rose	O
made	O
them	O
off	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
twenty	O
times	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
the	O
Maid	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
by	O
force	O
?	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bolted	O
the	O
Garret	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
a	O
Pistol	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
while	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
deny	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
that	O
Day	O
sennight	O
.	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
when	O
we	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
perhaps	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
cheated	O
me	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
out	O
of	O
sixty	O
Pounds	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
four	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
share	O
of	O
whatever	O
was	O
taken	O
-	O
though	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
went	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
just	O
within	O
the	O
Door	O
where	O
I	O
stood	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
no	O
Sacks	O
carried	O
out	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Street	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
House	O
.	O
when	O
the	O
Rogues	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
five	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
Rankshatteld	O
(	O
Ransacked	O
)	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
were	O
tyed	O
in	O
the	O
Parlor	O
.	O
But	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Wheeler	O
went	O
formost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
after	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
'd	O
Rankshattle	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
.	O
Wheeler	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Foot	O
of	O
the	O
Garret	O
Stairs	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
forced	O
me	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
bolted	O
the	O
Garret	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
yield	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
one	O
Pistol	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
a	O
Chest	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
force	O
you	O
?	O
Were	O
you	O
drest	O
or	O
undrest	O
?	O
D.	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drest	O
.	O
He	O
pull	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
Coats	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
what	O
he	O
-	O
and	O
-	O
into	O
me	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
ever	O
he	O
could	O
for	O
the	O
Life	O
and	O
Soul	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
perceive	O
-	O
?	O
D.	O
Street	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
was	O
lain	O
with	O
before	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
's	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
Men	O
has	O
lain	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Nine	O
Pin	O
and	O
Bowl	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Edgware	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Wheeler	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
drank	O
together	O
.	O
They	O
staid	O
about	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
five	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
whither	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ironmonger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
at	O
Stanmore	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
February	O
five	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
Wheeler	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
another	O
.	O
They	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Minutes	O
past	O
seven	O
.	O
They	O
turned	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Farmer	O
Lawrence	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
But	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Smith	O
at	O
Edgware	O
and	O
shod	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Horses	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
on	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
others	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
thought	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
think	O
so	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Because	O
you	O
paid	O
every	O
body	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
very	O
rich	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
too	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
twenty	O
five	O
Shillings	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
He	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
six	O
Months	O
at	O
Edgware	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shod	O
Farmer	O
Lawrence	O
's	O
Horses	O
at	O
both	O
Houses	O
.	O
Archelaus	O
Pullen	O
.	O
The	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
the	O
Girl	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
either	O
as	O
willing	O
as	O
he	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
Pistols	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
likewise	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
nor	O
one	O
Friend	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
must	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	O
Francis	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Francis	O
,	O
were	O
called	O
and	O
appeared	O
.	O
+	O
+	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Fielder	O
,	O
Rose	O
,	O
Walker	O
,	O
and	O
Bush	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Burglary	O
and	O
Robbery	O
,	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
Number	O
3	O
.	O
Page	O
56	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
'	O
l	O
give	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
no	O
farther	O
trouble	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
Guineas	O
for	O
my	O
Share	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
stealing	O
the	O
Horse	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
of	O
that	O
too	O
-	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
Gold	O
Watches	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
Sir	O
Simeon	B-pers
Stewart	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
in	O
Ham	O
Shire	O
,	O
ought	O
they	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
into	O
Court	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
for	O
which	O
you	O
are	O
indicted	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
One	O
was	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Osbaston	I-pers
's	O
Watch	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
Gold	O
Case	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Shagreen	O
Case	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
before	O
this	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
can	O
make	O
no	O
Order	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
(	O
which	O
cost	O
me	O
18	O
s.	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
all	O
my	O
Linnen	O
,	O
in	O
Winchester	O
Goal	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
six	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
25.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lattimore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
White	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Beckley	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	O
Beckley	O
,	O
March	O
5	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Beckley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
from	O
a	O
Relation	O
at	O
Cheshunt	B-place
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
had	O
bought	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
deliver	O
the	O
Horses	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Cheshunt	O
Marsh	O
?	O
Beckley	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
next	O
Door	O
Neighbour	O
in	O
Carbuncle	O
Street	O
in	O
Chesunt	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
had	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
afterwards	O
,	O
Beckley	O
claimed	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
Gray	O
Horse	O
twelve	O
Hands	O
high	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
Enfield	O
for	O
15	O
s.	O
before	O
Christmas	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Horses	O
in	O
the	O
Marsh	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
who	O
gave	O
you	O
leave	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Really	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
that	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Taverner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Tenant	O
at	O
forty	O
five	O
Shillings	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
/	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
make	O
his	O
Confession	O
of	O
Justice	O
Brown	O
Enfield	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
twenty	O
sixth	O
April	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
was	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
Effect	O
:	O
'	O
That	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
ago	O
he	O
stole	O
a	O
Grey	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
to	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
for	O
six	O
Shillings	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
Shilling	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
ten	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
stole	O
a	O
Black	O
Horse	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
him	O
for	O
twenty	O
one	O
Shillings	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stanly	O
at	O
Newington	O
Butts	O
.	O
'	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
both	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
26	O
,	O
27.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Sparnell	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Frock	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Abel	I-pers
,	O
April	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
28.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
April	O
27	O
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29	O
,	O
30.	O
Robert	B-pers
Landsman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
with	O
Frances	B-pers
Macdonal	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mackenzy	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
Highway	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
Pence	O
,	O
May	O
1	O
.	O
W.	O
Mackenzy	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
both	O
Pensioners	O
in	O
Chelsea	O
College	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
Year	O
.	O
On	O
May	O
Day	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Quarter	O
past	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
the	O
five	O
Fields	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
over	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mackenzy	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
got	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
borrow	O
it	O
of	O
ye	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Robert	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
Money	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ll	O
have	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
People	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Women	O
's	O
Clothes	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
by	O
his	O
Beard	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mole	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
Women	O
held	O
me	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
-	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
likewise	O
took	O
Macdonal	O
,	O
his	O
pretended	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
raised	O
a	O
hundred	O
Mob	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
his	O
Money	O
nor	O
nothing	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
for	O
robbing	O
me	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Poland	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
Serj	O
.	O
Mackenzy	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
Now	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
Mackenzy	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
will	O
ye	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
That	O
's	O
a	O
damned	O
Lye	O
.	O
C.	O
Poland	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
have	O
Money	O
?	O
says	O
I.	O
Aye	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
Guineas	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
Mackenzy	O
should	O
swear	O
me	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Horrocks	I-pers
.	O
On	O
May	O
Day	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
arrested	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
for	O
a	O
hundred	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
his	O
Bail	O
.	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
.	O
And	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
-	O
or	O
Mistress	O
,	O
Macdonal	O
-	O
Mackenzy	O
.	O
She	O
's	O
as	O
much	O
his	O
Wife	O
as	O
mine-she	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Crown	O
Office	O
.	O
Horrocks	O
.	O
Be	O
she	O
his	O
Wife	O
or	O
be	O
she	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
at	O
five	O
or	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
she	O
crost	O
over	O
the	O
Field	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
why	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
Mackenzy	O
?	O
and	O
who	O
was	O
Bail	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
for	O
says	O
he	O
.	O
all	O
his	O
Money	O
is	O
exhausted	O
John	B-pers
Low	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Aberry	O
Farm	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
past	O
by	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
Horrocks	O
staid	O
there	O
to	O
rest	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
:	O
But	O
I	O
neither	O
heard	O
nor	O
saw	O
any	O
Robbery	O
enacted	O
that	O
Evening./	O
Defence	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
On	O
May	O
Day	O
about	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
arrested	O
Mackenzy	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
clandestinately	O
,	O
and	O
leaving	O
him	O
nothing	O
but	O
two	O
Children	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harps	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
to	O
satisfy	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Minister	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
Affidavit	O
that	O
he	O
married	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Frances	B-pers
Macdonal	I-pers
-	O
and	O
so	O
Mackenzy	O
was	O
arrested	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
makes	O
Cabbage	O
Nets	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
harmless	O
old	O
Man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bensy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Justice	O
Man	O
's	O
Office	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
Mackenzy	O
for	O
taking	O
away	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
by	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Order	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
Mackenzy	O
had	O
sworn	O
against	O
several	O
Persons	O
innocently	O
and	O
returned	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Blassman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
about	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Comrade	O
William	B-pers
Giddy	I-pers
,	O
about	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
not	O
a	O
Word	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Giddy	I-pers
.	O
That	O
's	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
Hands	O
and	O
come	O
safe	O
home	O
.	O
Mackenzy	O
.	O
What	O
occasion	O
had	O
I	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
appeal	O
to	O
them	O
two	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Friends	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Macdonal	O
indicted	O
her	O
Husband	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
first	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
Wives	O
alive	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
help	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
,	O
Last	O
Midsummer	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
Robbery	O
against	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Son	O
(	O
a	O
Child	O
of	O
thirteen	O
Years	O
old	O
)	O
and	O
has	O
brought	O
us	O
into	O
a	O
Law	O
for	O
near	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
ruin	O
'd	O
us	O
-	O
And	O
just	O
now	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
swear	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
broke	O
my	O
Articles	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
31.	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coffee	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l	O
a	O
Silver	O
Milk	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
Rachel	O
,	O
Lady	O
Morgan	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
April	O
11	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pantry	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
(	O
with	O
the	O
Lady	O
's	O
Arms	O
on	O
it	O
)	O
for	O
four	O
Shillings	O
ten	O
Pence	O
an	O
Ounce	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Boucher	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Smith	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Wheat-sheaf	O
in	O
Tavistock	O
Street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
John	B-pers
Joyner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifty	O
two	O
Hundred	O
and	O
twenty	O
five	O
Pound	O
of	O
Logwood	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sidebotham	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
And	O
33.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stedman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Bromley	I-place
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
two	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stol'n	O
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
And	O
.	O
34.	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
White	B-place
Chapple	I-place
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
fifty	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stol'n	O
,	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
that	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Logwood	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Sidebotham	O
and	O
Wright	O
,	O
was	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ware	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Farmer	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Joyner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Ballast-man	O
,	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Stedman	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Hand	O
in	O
Hand	O
at	O
Bow	O
Creek	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
remarkable	O
Boat	O
(	O
both	O
ends	O
being	O
alike	O
)	O
loaded	O
with	O
Logwood	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
Stedman	O
's	O
Back	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
sixteenth	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
That	O
Joyner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Logwood	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
Joyner	O
's	O
Mate	O
(	O
Richard	B-pers
Bogue	I-pers
)	O
had	O
carried	O
the	O
Boat	O
into	O
Bow	B-place
Creek	I-place
.	O
That	O
three	O
Cart	O
Loads	O
of	O
Logwood	O
were	O
carried	O
from	O
Stedman	O
's	O
(	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
Joyner	O
and	O
Bogue	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bedford	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Grey-hound	B-place
against	I-place
White	I-place
Chappel	I-place
Church	I-place
on	O
the	O
seventeenth	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
besides	O
one	O
Load	O
from	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Old	O
Gravel	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Load	O
from	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
two	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
of	O
Logwood	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
,	O
part	O
in	O
Stedman	O
's	O
Brew-house	O
,	O
and	O
Part	O
in	O
his	O
Stable	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Proof	O
that	O
this	O
Logwood	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
Joyner	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Joyner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
.	O
And	O
.	O
35.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Easton	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
Hundred	O
and	O
twenty	O
five	O
Pound	O
of	O
Logwood	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sidebotham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
April	O
27	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
I	O
live	O
at	O
Lime	B-place
Kiln	I-place
Dock	I-place
.	O
My	O
Warehouse	O
and	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
are	O
Contigous	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
both	O
under	O
one	O
Roof	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Roofs	O
join	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Door	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
into	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
considerable	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Logwood	O
belonging	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sidebotham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
twenty	O
seventh	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
standing	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
the	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
he	O
stept	O
into	O
a	O
Ballast	O
Lighter	O
that	O
was	O
moor	O
'd	O
under	O
the	O
Crane	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
fifty	O
two	O
Sticks	O
of	O
Logwood	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Water	O
Side	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Lighter	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
they	O
were	O
driven	O
thither	O
by	O
Stress	O
of	O
Weather	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Wind	O
stiring	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
left	O
their	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
Door	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Justice	O
they	O
denied	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
yet	O
Joyner	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
confest	O
that	O
they	O
moor	O
'd	O
the	O
Lighter	O
there	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
About	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
just	O
High	O
Water	O
,	O
my	O
Boat	O
got	O
a	O
Shore	O
by	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
over	O
set	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Ballast	O
Lighter	O
coming	O
up	O
with	O
two	O
Men	O
in	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
good	O
Design	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
lay	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
Boat	O
to	O
watch	O
them	O
.	O
Presently	O
they	O
moor	O
'd	O
the	O
Lighter	O
under	O
the	O
Crane	O
and	O
both	O
came	O
ashore	O
,	O
and	O
whispered	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
bring	O
out	O
Logwood	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Water	O
Side	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
went	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Moon-light	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
then	O
distinguish	O
their	O
Faces	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Dock	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Lighter	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
Men	O
that	O
opened	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Woods	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
very	O
plainly	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
and	O
no	O
others	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Lighter	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
jump	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Wharf	O
into	O
the	O
Lighter	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
.	O
Easton	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
other	O
Lighter	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Chalk	O
Lighter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Eriff	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
Lewis	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
Ware	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
in	O
my	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Logwood	O
rattle	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Light	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
jump	O
off	O
the	O
Wharf	O
into	O
the	O
Lighter	O
.	O
Joyner	O
crept	O
under	O
the	O
Foresail	O
,	O
and	O
Easton	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Windless	O
,	O
both	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
asleep	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
Foresail	O
off	O
Joyner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
hastily	O
what	O
's	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
what	O
's	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
-	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
Joyner	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Key	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Ware	O
House	O
Door	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Key	O
as	O
locked	O
his	O
Oars	O
.	O
Joyner	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
no	O
Oars	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Jones	O
.	O
May	O
be	O
so	O
-	O
But	O
you	O
said	O
so	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
.	O
J.	O
Swainson	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
fifty	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Logwood	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Redwood	O
,	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ware	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
at	O
the	O
Edge	O
of	O
the	O
Wharf	O
.	O
The	O
Logwood	O
weigh	O
'd	O
fifteen	O
Hundred	O
,	O
one	O
Quarter	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
one	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
worth	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
a	O
Hundred	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Lighter	O
Man	O
(	O
Easton	O
's	O
Godfather	O
,	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Mires	I-pers
of	O
Lime	O
House	O
(	O
with	O
whom	O
Easton	O
lodged	O
,	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pardo	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Caves	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Easton	O
was	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
they	O
added	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
say	O
nothing	O
in	O
favour	O
of	O
Joyner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Joyner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
Barrels	O
of	O
Tar	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Josiah	B-pers
Jetsom	I-pers
,	O
April	O
17	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
being	O
convicted	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
Indictments	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
it	O
unnecessary	O
to	O
try	O
him	O
on	O
this	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36	O
,	O
37.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pinchbeck	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	O
Pinchbeck	O
,	O
and	O
Joice	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Susan	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Pinchbeck	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
thirteen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
March	O
8	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
ow	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Mrs.	O
Pinchbeck	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Field	B-place
Lane	I-place
to	O
pay	O
her	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Part	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
approve	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
Money	O
about	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
Her	O
Maid	O
Joice	O
Hunt	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
five	O
Shillings	O
more	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Then	O
Pinchbeck	O
bid	O
her	O
Maid	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
'd	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
Old	O
Bitch	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
thirteen	O
Shillings	O
and	O
two	O
Thimbles	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
what	O
the	O
Old	O
bitch	O
has	O
got	O
in	O
her	O
Bosom	O
.	O
And	O
not	O
content	O
with	O
hunting	O
in	O
my	O
Bosom	O
as	O
low	O
as	O
my	O
Wake	O
,	O
she	O
punch	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Bruised	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
with	O
in	O
an	O
Inch	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Parlor	O
above	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Bristol	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
was	O
missing	O
above	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mother	O
,	O
where	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
?	O
She	O
burst	O
out	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Pinchbecks	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
picked	O
her	O
Pocket	O
of	O
all	O
her	O
Money	O
-	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
died	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
six	O
Months	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
miscarried	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Pinchbeck	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
subsisted	O
this	O
Woman	O
these	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
relieve	O
the	O
Widow	O
and	O
the	O
Fatherless	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lent	O
at	O
times	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
Pounds	O
and	O
never	O
took	O
a	O
Farthing	O
Interest	O
.	O
S.	O
Wright	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
sold	O
Wine	O
and	O
-	O
Pinchbeck	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
thirty	O
Shillings	O
when	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Boy	O
'Prentice	O
to	O
a	O
Weaver	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
seven	O
Pound	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
a	O
Loom	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
seven	O
Years	O
in	O
paying	O
me	O
four	O
Pound	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
-	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
thirty	O
Shillings	O
but	O
last	O
Christmas	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
beg	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
four	O
Pound	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
paid	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
arrested	O
by	O
a	O
Tally	O
Man	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
her	O
Son	O
came	O
and	O
intruded	O
on	O
my	O
Goodness	O
for	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
more	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
twenty	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
towards	O
the	O
five	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
the	O
rest	O
Weekly	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
me	O
nineteen	O
Shillings	O
on	O
the	O
Day	O
she	O
says	O
I	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
But	O
she	O
brought	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
thirteen	O
Shillings	O
which	O
she	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
telling	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Hold	O
!	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
you	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
catch	O
'd	O
it	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
a	O
Crown	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
there	O
's	O
too	O
much	O
?	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
eighteen	O
Shillings	O
.	O
God	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
and	O
catches	O
up	O
a	O
Quart	O
Pot	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
split	O
your	O
Scull	O
.	O
But	O
my	O
Maid	O
stepping	O
between	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
no	O
Mischief	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
eighth	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
sixteenth	O
,	O
I	O
arrested	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
Lawyer	O
Theobald	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Head	O
to	O
prosecute	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
on	O
the	O
nineteenth	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
S.	O
Wright	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
lent	O
me	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
spend	O
good	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Brandy	O
and	O
Wine	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
She	O
keeps	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Draper	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
S.	O
Wright	O
.	O
She	O
's	O
a	O
Tally	O
Woman	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Just	O
.	O
Robe	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
a	O
Warrant	O
from	O
Ald	O
.	O
Brocas	O
for	O
violently	O
assaulting	O
and	O
beating	O
Susan	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
and	O
taking	O
thirteen	O
Shillings	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
her	O
above	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
Wright	O
nor	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
appearing	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
good	O
Bail	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
the	O
Recognizance	O
to	O
Hick	O
's	O
Hall	O
-	O
Theobald	O
afterwards	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
threatned	O
me	O
for	O
taking	O
Bail	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Case	O
William	B-pers
Dakin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
thirteen	O
Years	O
,	O
her	O
Circumstances	O
are	O
such	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
act	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
Principles	O
are	O
such	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Dr.	O
-	O
She	O
lives	O
just	O
by	O
me	O
in	O
Field	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Character	O
as	O
any	O
Woman	O
in	O
England	O
-	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
Patient	O
these	O
twenty	O
Years	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Roundtree	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
large	O
Dealings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
their	O
Indictment	O
.	O
38.	O
John	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Curtains	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Bassan	I-pers
,	O
April	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39.	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Firkin	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Butterwick	I-pers
,	O
May	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
Mary	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Dish	O
,	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
May	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41.	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Men	O
's	O
Pumps	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
.	O
No	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
42.	O
William	B-pers
Byrom	I-pers
*	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shovel	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
his	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
tryed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sir	O
Fisher	O
Tench	O
in	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
tried	O
in	O
January	O
,	O
1733-4.	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Laurence	B-pers
Evers	I-pers
near	O
Moor	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shovel	O
in	O
New	B-place
Broad	I-place
Street	I-place
.	O
About	O
ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Parlor	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
little	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lying	O
on	O
his	O
Face	O
on	O
the	O
Parlor	O
Stairs	O
,	O
his	O
Feet	O
were	O
four	O
Steps	O
from	O
the	O
bottom	O
.	O
He	O
turned	O
his	O
face	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
Candlestick	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
was	O
fast	O
,	O
I	O
seemed	O
to	O
take	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
call	O
my	O
Fellow	O
Servants	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Door	O
being	O
still	O
locked	O
and	O
chain	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Dining	O
Room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
fronting	O
the	O
Street	O
:	O
The	O
Sashes	O
of	O
this	O
Room	O
were	O
then	O
all	O
three	O
drawn	O
up	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
one	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
shut	O
down	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hours	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
concluded	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
called	O
Thieves	O
!	O
and	O
some	O
body	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
's	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
this	O
is	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cresswell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
(	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
)	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jump	O
from	O
the	O
Lamp	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
-	O
The	O
Lamp	O
was	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
or	O
three	O
Quarters	O
from	O
the	O
Dining	O
Room	O
Window	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
hurt	O
himself	O
with	O
the	O
Fall	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
lay	O
there	O
till	O
a	O
Man	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Green	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
Dark	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Black	O
Wig	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
Light	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
?	O
E.	O
Cresswell	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
preserve	O
(	O
observe	O
)	O
him	O
by	O
Day	O
Light	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Light	O
at	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
-	O
And	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
next	O
Morning	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
dress	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Townshend	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
along	O
Broad	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
tumbled	O
over	O
a	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
were	O
crying	O
Thieves	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
them	O
bring	O
a	O
Light	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
drunk	O
from	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
in	O
Moor	O
Fields	O
;	O
I	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Broad	O
Street	O
;	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
Senses	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Compton	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
not	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Disturbance	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Archbole	I-pers
alias	O
Young	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hound	O
's	O
Ditch	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
that	O
Night	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cooms	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Wind	O
Mill	O
Hill	O
-	O
Cooms	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
Opening	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
drunk	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Bishop	O
's	O
Gate	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Merry-making	O
all	O
Day	O
in	O
Moor	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Bishop	O
's	O
Gate	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
at	O
past	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Clock	O
strike	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
Hour	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Clock	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
43.	O
Sarah	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
violently	O
and	O
inhumanely	O
beating	O
and	O
wounding	O
Daniel	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	O
Owen	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watch	O
Man	O
by	O
St	O
Paul	O
's	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
Mr.	O
Atkins	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
.	O
She	O
run	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Paul	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
:	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
Gate	O
.	O
she	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
hearty	O
Knocks	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
my	O
Nose	O
bleed	O
-	O
But	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
served	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Fellow	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
what	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
Orders	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
enough	O
.	O
Well	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
quietly	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
Ye	O
for	O
B	O
-	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
ll	O
lug	O
ye	O
along	O
as	O
I	O
think	O
fit	O
.	O
You	O
dirty	O
Dog	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
ye	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
as	O
I	O
please	O
-	O
Why	O
how	O
now	O
ye	O
F	O
-	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
resist	O
Authority	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Servant	O
-	O
You	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
ye	O
Scrub	O
Rascal	O
?	O
-	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
a	O
Knock	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
to	O
strike	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
if	O
he	O
pleas	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
assured	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
striking	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
his	O
Authority	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
harm	O
did	O
I	O
do	O
him	O
?	O
Let	O
him	O
shew	O
his	O
Marks	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
any	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
fined	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
44	O
,	O
45	O
,	O
46.	O
John	B-pers
Nottingham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrgove	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Shillings	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marseder	I-pers
,	O
April	O
29	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Marseder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Barkham	O
Wood	O
beyond	O
Stanmore	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
sold	O
my	O
Eggs	O
:	O
and	O
riding	O
homewards	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
three	O
Men	O
a	O
Horse-back	O
upon	O
Golder	B-place
's	I-place
Green	I-place
.	O
One	O
rid	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
others	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
file	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
Dame	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
sell	O
?	O
Butter	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
two	O
Pound	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
sixteen	O
Pence	O
-	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
it	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Sister	O
;	O
but	O
can	O
you	O
change	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
Friend	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
change	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
five	O
Shillings	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Lap	O
-	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
Shilling	O
for	O
the	O
Butter	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
just	O
such	O
a	O
Shilling	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
for	O
Eggs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
for	O
I	O
doubted	O
the	O
Goodness	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
this	O
Shilling	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
confirmed	O
in	O
it	O
by	O
missing	O
the	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Quinny	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Woman	O
the	O
Shilling	O
for	O
the	O
Butter	O
and	O
that	O
Yorkshire	O
Tom	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Booker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hargrove	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Yorkshire	O
Tom	O
,	O
took	O
four	O
Shillings	O
six	O
Pence	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
two	O
Comrades	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
they	O
bought	O
the	O
Butter	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Brandy	O
.	O
They	O
gave	O
my	O
Wife	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
change	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
Change	O
.	O
They	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
their	O
Horses	O
a	O
Mouthful	O
of	O
Hay	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
Yorkshire	O
Tom	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
no	O
need	O
to	O
change	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Brandy	O
,	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
Gold	O
again	O
.	O
Aye	O
,	O
says	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
When	O
he	O
gives	O
me	O
the	O
Silver	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
Silver	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Wife	O
telling	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
wanted	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
examining	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Three	O
or	O
four	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Butcher	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
in	O
his	O
'Prenticeship	O
,	O
which	O
expired	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
47.	O
Charles	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
.	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
Shilling	O
and	O
six	O
Pence	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
April	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
48.	O
John	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Indictment	O
being	O
defective	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
49.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charlesworth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Defect	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
50.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wolf	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
in	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
detestable	O
Sin	O
of	O
Sodomy	O
,	O
April	O
10	O
.	O
John	O
Holloway	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Skipworth	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Brandy	O
Merchant	O
in	O
Goswell	O
Street	O
,	O
near	O
Old	O
Street	O
.	O
On	O
Easter	O
Thursday	O
my	O
Master	O
sent	O
me	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
into	O
Bishop's-Gate	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Helmet	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
round	O
the	O
Wastes	O
,	O
and	O
tickled	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
