TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1735.	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Eighth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	O
BELLAMY	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1735	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXV	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
EDWARD	B-pers
BELLAMY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Hardwick	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Comyns	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Durnford	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Osborn	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Quilter	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Nowles	I-pers
,	O
Coles	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Ilive	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Drayton	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sallis	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hayley	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Osgood	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burchett	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Ann	B-pers
Abrams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Tedder	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
and	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
October	O
4	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
2.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lekeux	I-pers
,	O
September	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
George	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clear	I-pers
,	O
October	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Berkley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lindo	I-pers
,	O
October	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5	O
,	O
6	O
,	O
7.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
Spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
:	O
Margaret	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
both	O
her	O
Hands	O
about	O
the	O
Neck	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Catherine	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
choaking	O
and	O
strangling	O
her	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
choaking	O
and	O
strangling	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
Rebecca	O
and	O
Margaret	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
Spinsters	O
,	O
by	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
and	O
abetting	O
the	O
said	O
Margaret	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
Widow	O
(	O
their	O
Mother	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
,	O
September	O
16	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Denmark	B-place
Court	I-place
.	O
Three	O
Weeks	O
and	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
lett	O
a	O
Room	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
backwards	O
to	O
Margaret	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
Her	O
two	O
Daughters	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
)	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
another	O
Daughter	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
Merchant	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
seldom	O
had	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
her	O
above	O
once	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
Daughter	O
alive	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Betty	B-pers
Camay	I-pers
,	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
almost	O
every	O
Day	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
seventeenth	O
of	O
September	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
a	O
Boy	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Coffin	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
mistook	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
for	O
Margaret	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
my	O
Lodger	O
,	O
had	O
ordered	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
for	O
a	O
Maid	O
who	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
and	O
died	O
suddenly	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
her	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Packthread	O
and	O
a	O
Stick	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Staple	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Lock	O
;	O
I	O
bounced	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
behind	O
it	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lay	O
dead	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
covered	O
all	O
but	O
her	O
Face	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
Flock	O
Bed	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
living	O
Person	O
there	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Furniture	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
a	O
Stool	O
or	O
a	O
Chair	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
Boy	O
.	O
He	O
waited	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
by-and-by	O
Margaret	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
Rebecca	O
her	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
are	O
got	O
here	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
body	O
dead	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
.	O
She	O
answered	O
,	O
What	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
she	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
acquainted	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
Truly	O
,	O
says	O
her	O
Daughter	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Impudence	O
to	O
ask	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
's	O
dead	O
in	O
our	O
Room	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
nor	O
never	O
shall	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
business	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
they	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
went	O
up	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Searchers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Guard	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
ever	O
had	O
any	O
Furniture	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
bring	O
any	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Searchers	O
came	O
about	O
Candle-light	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Door	O
was	O
then	O
fastened	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
open	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
Coffin	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pan	O
whelmed	O
on	O
the	O
Lid	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
and	O
Daughter	O
were	O
then	O
gone	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
they	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Daughter	O
Peggy	O
,	O
and	O
Betty	B-pers
Caway	I-pers
came	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Hy	O
!	O
Hy	O
!	O
says	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Impudence	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
?	O
The	O
Searchers	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
's	O
being	O
dead	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
dear	O
Child	O
,	O
her	O
own	O
dear	O
Kitty	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
died	O
of	O
Convulsion	O
Fits	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
bloody	O
Rag	O
pinned	O
about	O
her	O
Neck	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
black	O
Marks	O
about	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
a	O
Bruise	O
on	O
her	O
Temple	O
,	O
another	O
on	O
her	O
Cheek	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
her	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
her	O
Breast	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
was	O
very	O
fair	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Searchers	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
die	O
of	O
Convulsions	O
,	O
because	O
her	O
Nails	O
were	O
white	O
and	O
clear	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
place	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
first	O
lay	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
mopt	O
up	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
bloody	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
in	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Mother	O
,	O
Why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
acquaint	O
us	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
's	O
being	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
disturb	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
round	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
only	O
a	O
Flock	O
Bed	O
no	O
bigger	O
than	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
all	O
their	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
for	O
my	O
Rent	O
.	O
The	O
eldest	O
Daughter	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
designed	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
any	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
wiped	O
the	O
Purging	O
at	O
the	O
Deceas'd	O
's	O
Nose	O
and	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
she	O
bled	O
fresh	O
Blood	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
a	O
Vein	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
no	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Twentyman	I-pers
,	O
Searcher	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
first	O
by	O
Candle-light	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
bled	O
so	O
much	O
at	O
her	O
Mouth	O
and	O
Nose	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
observe	O
the	O
Marks	O
about	O
her	O
Neck	O
;	O
but	O
next	O
Morning	O
we	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
bruised	O
much	O
under	O
the	O
right	O
Ear	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Skin	O
was	O
raised	O
and	O
several	O
Bruises	O
about	O
the	O
Neck	O
and	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
was	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Hands	O
and	O
Fingers	O
were	O
white	O
and	O
open	O
.	O
Her	O
Mother	O
said	O
she	O
died	O
of	O
Convulsion	O
Fits	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
strangled	O
.	O
For	O
in	O
Convulsion	O
Fits	O
,	O
the	O
Nails	O
and	O
Fingers	O
will	O
be	O
black	O
thus	O
far	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bowels	O
will	O
presently	O
turn	O
green	O
-	O
I	O
advised	O
them	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
who	O
had	O
more	O
Skill	O
than	O
I.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Caway	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
worked	O
at	O
my	O
Mothers	O
at	O
stiching	O
of	O
Stays	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
death	O
,	O
her	O
Mother	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sick	O
with	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
from	O
her	O
Service	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
black	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
beat	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
The	O
Saturday	O
before	O
the	O
Deceased	O
died	O
,	O
her	O
Sister	O
Peggy	O
(	O
the	O
Girl	O
there	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Mother	O
had	O
been	O
beating	O
her	O
Sister	O
Kitty	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Beck	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
crying	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
You	O
never	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Creature	O
as	O
my	O
Mother	O
,	O
I	O
lifted	O
Kitty	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
set	O
her	O
to	O
lean	O
against	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mother	O
knocked	O
her	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
with	O
her	O
Fist	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
all	O
along	O
of	O
you	O
!	O
and	O
Kitty	O
looked	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
?	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
old	O
Flock	O
Bed	O
which	O
my	O
Mother	O
gave	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Charity	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
Furniture	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
Forehead	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
,	O
what	O
must	O
I	O
do	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
afterwards	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
Word	O
she	O
spoke	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
on	O
Monday	O
(	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
)	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
dozing	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
troubled	O
with	O
any	O
Distemper	O
-	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
two	O
of	O
Ward	O
's	O
Pills	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
lying	O
dead	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
Her	O
Mother	O
said	O
she	O
died	O
in	O
Fits	O
,	O
and	O
wiped	O
her	O
Nose	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
more	O
she	O
wiped	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
clear	O
Blood	O
came	O
.	O
They	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Coffin	O
,	O
and	O
mop	O
'd	O
up	O
some	O
blood	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Mothers	O
and	O
drank	O
Tea	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
Candle-light	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
People	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
their	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
hundred	O
People	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
Goods	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
robbed	O
.	O
Beck	O
wiped	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
Blood	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mouth	O
and	O
Nose	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Edward	O
's	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
backward	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
under	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lay	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
thirteenth	O
of	O
September	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
thump	O
as	O
if	O
some	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
Shriek	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
a	O
shuffling	O
of	O
Feet	O
as	O
if	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
had	O
been	O
shuffling	O
one	O
from	O
another	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Cadogan	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Girl	O
Peggy	O
was	O
examined	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
Roundhouse	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
no	O
Confession	O
,	O
but	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
good	O
God	O
!	O
what	O
would	O
become	O
of	O
my	O
poor	O
Mother	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Wilkie	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
death	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
I	O
viewed	O
the	O
Body	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Work	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
Neck	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Mark	O
of	O
Fingers	O
;	O
the	O
Skin	O
was	O
quite	O
rubbed	O
off	O
across	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
one	O
Mark	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
there	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
Circle	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
by	O
a	O
violent	O
Pressure	O
on	O
the	O
Gullet	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
judge	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
strangled	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Bruise	O
on	O
her	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
material	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
form	O
no	O
Judgment	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
having	O
had	O
Fits	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
she	O
have	O
been	O
strangled	O
without	O
leaving	O
a	O
Mark	O
quite	O
round	O
her	O
Neck	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Wilkie	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
for	O
by	O
pressing	O
the	O
Gullet	O
the	O
Vessels	O
would	O
be	O
obstructed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
strangled	O
of	O
course	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Beckington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Se'nnight	O
before	O
her	O
death	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
by	O
her	O
eldest	O
Sister	O
,	O
who	O
led	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Her	O
Face	O
was	O
half	O
muffled	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
black	O
Eye	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
made	O
their	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
lived	O
at	O
John	B-pers
Caldecot	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
Lane	O
.	O
She	O
,	O
having	O
two	O
Fits	O
there	O
,	O
would	O
leave	O
her	O
Service	O
and	O
come	O
home	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sick	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
one	O
Fit	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
every	O
Night	O
after	O
.	O
But	O
on	O
Sunday	O
she	O
had	O
Ten	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
Thirteen	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Metcalf	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
who	O
blooded	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
blooded	O
by	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
in	O
Princes	O
Street	O
.	O
Rebecca	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
home	O
vastly	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cover	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
burnt	O
some	O
Gin	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
Fit	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
her	O
Stays	O
for	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
some	O
Broth	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
afterwards	O
grew	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
died	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
8.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hansel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sears	I-pers
,	O
August	O
2	O
.	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
Thomas	B-pers
Petty	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
9.	O
Ann	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Porringers	O
,	O
three	O
Shirts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Enoch	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
,	O
September	O
9	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
11	O
,	O
12.	O
George	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
*	O
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
+	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Beesly	I-pers
++	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
In	O
December	O
last	O
George	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
but	O
not	O
then	O
taken	O
)	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
John	O
for	O
robbing	O
Abigail	B-pers
Bingo	I-pers
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
four	O
Street-Robbers	O
in	O
Sept.	O
1732	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
tryed	O
(	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
)	O
in	O
Sept.	O
1733	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Philip	B-pers
Turft	I-pers
in	O
Marybone	O
fields	O
;	O
but	O
acquitted	O
.	O
+	O
Beesly	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
in	O
White.chapel.fields	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
++	O
In	O
January	O
1732-3	O
,	O
S	O
-	O
Goodman	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Ackers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wetton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
.	O
And	O
in	O
June	O
1733	O
he	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
but	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
and	O
Laurence	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Street-Robbery	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
.	O
Some	O
Time	O
in	O
June	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Will	O
.	O
Beesly	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
Chelsea	B-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Sutton	O
and	O
Beesly	O
knocked	O
down	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
Sutton	O
afterwards	O
gave	O
me	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
for	O
my	O
Share	O
of	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
ready	O
to	O
assist	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Goodman	O
?	O
Winn	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
too	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
their	O
Design	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
Night	O
)	O
nor	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Sutton	O
.	O
What	O
Places	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Winn	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
directly	O
from	O
my	O
Mistress	O
(	O
Mrs.	O
How	O
's	O
)	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
again	O
-	O
We	O
afterwards	O
agreed	O
to	O
rob	O
my	O
Mistress	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Sutton	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
George	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
's	O
Mother	O
)	O
from	O
May	O
to	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
Time	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
after	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
afterwards	O
without	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Wainscot	O
Partition	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Son	O
George	O
never	O
was	O
from	O
home	O
after	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
all	O
the	O
Months	O
of	O
June	O
and	O
July	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
an	O
unhappy	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
often	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
too	O
much	O
Cause	O
to	O
remember	O
the	O
Time	O
I	O
speak	O
of	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
poor	O
unfortunate	O
Brother	O
was	O
executed	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Badham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Joiner's-street	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
Cyder	O
and	O
Dorchester-Beer	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Goodman	O
is	O
my	O
Brother-in	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
with	O
my	O
Mother	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
sick	O
that	O
Day	O
as	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
was	O
hanged	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
ill	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Weeks	O
after	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Son	O
was	O
ill	O
for	O
three	O
Weeks	O
after	O
Sutton	O
was	O
hanged	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
six	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
after	O
Candle-lighting	O
in	O
all	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Goodman	O
and	O
found	O
Sutton	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Transportation	O
.	O
13.	O
Mary	B-pers
Loyd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Brilliant	O
Diamond	O
and	O
six	O
Sparks	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
One	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
Garnets	O
;	O
and	O
an	O
Agate	O
Snuff-box	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Brim	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
Oxenham	I-pers
;	O
and	O
two	O
Aprons	O
,	O
two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Cath	B-pers
Rochford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Tho	O
.	O
Oxenham	O
.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Oxenham	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Days	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
I	O
lost	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Box	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
found	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
in	O
Westminster	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
confessed	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Cath.Rochford	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Oxenham	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dehane	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
such	O
Goods	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
offered	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
broken	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
Ear-rings	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Dowler	I-pers
.	O
She	O
brought	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Farley	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
sweeping	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
fine	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
Molly	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
the	O
Times	O
are	O
well	O
mended	O
.	O
Aye	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
last	O
Night	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
French	O
-	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
lye	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
stript	O
the	O
Rascal	O
naked	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
14.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Head-cloths	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
several	O
Persons	O
,	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
William	B-pers
Topping	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16	O
,	O
17.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rose	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Bromingham	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
;	O
Bromingham	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Hurling	O
Stick	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
and	O
Bruise	O
near	O
the	O
Right	O
Eye	O
,	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
and	O
Bruise	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
7th	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
And	O
Abraham	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
and	O
Rose	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
by	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
abetting	O
the	O
said	O
Bromingham	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Murder	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Nurse	O
at	O
the	O
Hospital	O
at	O
Hyde-Park	O
Corner	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
Hospital	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
Sept.	O
2	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
four	O
Men	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
wounded	O
him	O
so	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
Handsaw	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
no	O
Affront	O
,	O
and	O
neither	O
touched	O
them	O
nor	O
spoke	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
following	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
our	O
Work	O
at	O
Chelsea	B-place
between	O
Seven	O
and	O
Eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
over-taken	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
three	O
others	O
near	O
Bloody-bridge	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
a	O
Word	O
was	O
spoken	O
,	O
but	O
Webb	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
lying	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
killed	O
my	O
Master	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
him	O
dye	O
and	O
be	O
damned	O
:	O
You	O
shall	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
they	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
we	O
had	O
assaulted	O
them	O
.	O
Webb	O
.	O
You	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
Affront	O
.	O
Palmer	O
.	O
We	O
said	O
not	O
a	O
Word	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
they	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Father	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
used	O
in	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
to	O
say	O
by	O
whom	O
.	O
-	O
When	O
Rose	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
she	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
(	O
who	O
was	O
tried	O
and	O
acquitted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
)	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
when	O
my	O
Father	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Mollineux	I-pers
.	O
Webb	O
's	O
Father	O
keeps	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Vine-street	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
this	O
Hand-saw	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Son	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
Chelsea	O
Fields	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Saw	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Middleton	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Fracture	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
the	O
Skull	O
was	O
broke	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pieces	O
forced	O
quite	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Brain	O
by	O
the	O
Violence	O
of	O
the	O
Blow	O
,	O
which	O
without	O
doubt	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Webb	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
with	O
some	O
Company	O
from	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
Palmer	O
affronted	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
Palmer	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
that	O
struck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Saw	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
bid	O
me	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
.	O
Abr	O
.	O
Webb	O
the	O
Elder	O
.	O
My	O
Son	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Saw	O
which	O
was	O
bloody	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Flaningan	I-pers
,	O
Rich	O
.	O
Freeman	O
,	O
Rose	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Flaningan	O
was	O
cut	O
down	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
cross	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
bled	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Rich	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
.	O
Palmer	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
by	O
Justice	O
Manly	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Flaningan	O
,	O
for	O
violently	O
beating	O
and	O
wounding	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
would	O
not	O
bail	O
him	O
till	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
declared	O
that	O
Flaningan	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Danger	O
.	O
Several	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
bore	O
the	O
Characters	O
of	O
sober	O
peaceable	O
Persons	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
18.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
75	O
Yards	O
of	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
5	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
Potter	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
Night	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
,	O
going	O
up	O
Fish-street-hill	B-place
with	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
I	O
pitched	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
Bulk	O
at	O
the	O
Olive	O
Tree	O
,	O
an	O
Oil-shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
Boy	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
Rascal	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
-	O
Do	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
step	O
to	O
the	O
Cross-Keys-Inn	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
Hamper	O
directed	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
keep	O
this	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
your	O
Bundle	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
ye	O
Three-pence	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
Three-pence	O
when	O
you	O
come	O
back	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
Three-pence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Cloth	O
on	O
the	O
Bulk	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
long	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
him	O
to	O
several	O
People	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
follow	O
such	O
Practices	O
,	O
lodged	O
at	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Rose-and-Crown	O
Court	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
plainly	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simmer	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
3	O
.	O
1733	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Marriage	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
poxt	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Wedding	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
she	O
married	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
another	O
Husband	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
since	O
married	O
a	O
third	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
12	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
About	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Magpye	B-place
Tavern	I-place
at	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
half	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
She	O
put	O
one	O
Hand	O
under	O
my	O
Chin	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Come	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
fill	O
my	O
Glass	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
putting	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
French	O
Half	O
Crown	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Landlord	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
only	O
laugh	O
'd	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
French	O
Half	O
Crown	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
threw	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
making	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Landlord	O
pushed	O
her	O
aside	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
carry	O
us	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
lose	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
too	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
laid	O
the	O
Half	O
Crown	O
under	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
humour	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Way	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
very	O
unheathenly	O
to	O
mention	O
;	O
whereof	O
when	O
I	O
refused	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
21.	O
Jane	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
Value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Shop	O
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
22.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Silk	O
Damask	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cosins	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
18	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
23.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
2	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
24.	O
Ann	B-pers
Flowers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
4	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Long	I-pers
Will	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
James	B-pers
des	I-pers
Romains	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
three	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Stones	O
,	O
one	O
Gold	O
Mourning	O
Ring	O
,	O
thirteen	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
twelve	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
seven	O
Knives	O
with	O
Silver	O
Handles	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Soop	O
Ladle	O
,	O
four	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
eight	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Pistols	O
mounted	O
with	O
Silver	O
and	O
Steel	O
,	O
one	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
one	O
Silk	O
Damask	O
Night	O
Gown	O
,	O
twenty	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
six	O
Holland	O
Sheets	O
,	O
fifty	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
seventeen	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
des	I-pers
Romaine	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
And	O
four	O
Silk	O
Damask	O
Gowns	O
,	O
three	O
Silk	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
ten	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
four	O
Suits	O
of	O
Laced	O
Head	O
Clothes	O
,	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
set	O
with	O
Bristol	O
Stones	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
des	I-pers
Romaine	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
October	O
25	O
.	O
1733	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Col.	O
Des	O
Romaine	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty	O
fifth	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1733.	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
My	O
Maid	O
who	O
was	O
below	O
,	O
not	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
unbolted	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
thrust	O
his	O
Foot	O
between	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
the	O
Threshold	O
,	O
and	O
seizing	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
swore	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
dead	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
pushed	O
the	O
Door	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
with	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
cryed	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
call	O
my	O
Men	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Pistols	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
by	O
this	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Rogues	O
think	O
I	O
had	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
But	O
presently	O
I	O
was	O
struck	O
across	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Cutlace	O
.	O
I	O
still	O
kept	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
him	O
,	O
beat	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
:	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
received	O
such	O
a	O
Blow	O
with	O
the	O
Butt	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
my	O
Eye	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Men	O
rushed	O
in	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
rifled	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
two	O
Rings	O
,	O
about	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
While	O
they	O
were	O
searching	O
my	O
right	O
Pockets	O
,	O
I	O
slipt	O
a	O
Purse	O
with	O
six	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
left	O
Fob	O
and	O
thrust	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
Matt	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
They	O
tyed	O
my	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
me	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
discover	O
where	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
They	O
opened	O
my	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Plate	O
.	O
The	O
Trunk	O
had	O
a	O
double	O
Cover	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
forty	O
five	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
open	O
the	O
upper	O
Cover	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
hopes	O
that	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
two	O
Pistols	O
and	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Closet	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
Blade	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
others	O
opposed	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
took	O
me	O
down	O
Stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Parlor	O
Door	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Maid	O
lying	O
with	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
turned	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fourth	O
Man	O
putting	O
up	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
tall	O
,	O
and	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Blood	O
run	O
over	O
my	O
Eyes	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
hardly	O
see	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
tyed	O
my	O
Hands	O
behind	O
me	O
so	O
hard	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Cord	O
was	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
Flesh	O
of	O
my	O
Wrists	O
,	O
which	O
put	O
me	O
to	O
such	O
violent	O
Pain	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
Torture	O
of	O
putting	O
the	O
Question	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Marks	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Cords	O
remained	O
in	O
my	O
Wrists	O
for	O
a	O
Year	O
after	O
.	O
They	O
put	O
a	O
Napkin	O
over	O
my	O
Face	O
and	O
the	O
Maids	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
Gown	O
over	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
this	O
Condition	O
I	O
remained	O
from	O
eight	O
at	O
Night	O
till	O
three	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
They	O
bound	O
the	O
Maid	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Parlor	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
feel	O
her	O
move	O
,	O
and	O
hear	O
them	O
go	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
broke	O
the	O
Blow	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
ye	O
old	O
Rogue	O
!	O
You	O
told	O
us	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
.	O
By	O
which	O
I	O
concluded	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
Guineas	O
in	O
my	O
Trunk	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
abuse	O
me	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
kill	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
put	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Misery	O
.	O
Presently	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
Hanger	O
put	O
under	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
to	O
my	O
Neck	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
my	O
Maid	O
cried	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
not	O
kill	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
rather	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O
Between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
hearing	O
no	O
Noise	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Maid	O
that	O
I	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
feared	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
me	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
not	O
to	O
hazard	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
ventured	O
to	O
move	O
about	O
till	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
Back	O
towards	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
with	O
much	O
Difficulty	O
untyed	O
my	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
thus	O
got	O
loose	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Passage	O
.	O
I	O
perceived	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
the	O
Fore	O
Parlor	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
first	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
Apprehensions	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
yet	O
gone	O
.	O
But	O
hearing	O
nothing	O
stit	O
,	O
I	O
ventured	O
forward	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
left	O
ajar	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
Brown	O
and	O
Whitlock	O
*	O
(	O
who	O
were	O
since	O
executed	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Jail	O
,	O
agreed	O
to	O
rob	O
Mr.	O
Sherrack	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Jeweller	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
Brown	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
acquitted	O
at	O
Croydon	O
Assizes	O
,	O
and	O
Whitlock	O
was	O
acquitted	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
We	O
committed	O
several	O
Robberies	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
And	O
Brown	O
and	O
I	O
meeting	O
afterwards	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
we	O
happened	O
to	O
quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
parted	O
without	O
doing	O
any	O
business	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
going	O
into	O
Southwark	O
met	O
with	O
Whitlock	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
Pepper	O
Alley	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
Brown	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Brown	O
and	O
I	O
both	O
lodged	O
at	O
one	O
White	O
's	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
the	O
Hand-and-Flower	O
in	O
the	O
Grainge	O
near	O
Barnaby	O
Street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty	O
fifth	O
of	O
October	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
met	O
at	O
White	O
's	O
and	O
agreed	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Jeweller	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
wanted	O
another	O
Hand	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Long	O
Will	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
Long	O
Will	O
,	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Simon	I-pers
who	O
is	O
hanged	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
Friend	O
of	O
ours	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Gasley	I-pers
(	O
Garscee	O
)	O
who	O
kept	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
in	O
Tyburn	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
off	O
dealling	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
venture	O
again	O
.	O
Brown	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
Long	O
Will	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
Gassy	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
his	O
Mothers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
step	O
and	O
fetch	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
we	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
together	O
above	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
Lay	O
we	O
were	O
upon	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Objection	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Arms	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
about	O
seven	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Jeweller	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Grate	O
in	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
look	O
through	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
never	O
take	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
do	O
Business	O
if	O
we	O
can	O
.	O
Ring	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
will	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
rung	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Servant	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
Madam	O
de	O
Batt	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
answered	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
just	O
gone	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
consulted	O
what	O
do	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Col.	O
Romaine	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
.	O
Brown	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
foremost	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
put	O
back	O
the	O
Bolt	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
Door	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
knocked	O
.	O
The	O
Colonel	O
himself	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thrust	O
my	O
Foot	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
the	O
Threshold	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
a	O
Cutlace	O
.	O
He	O
cryed	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
his	O
Maid	O
to	O
bid	O
his	O
Men	O
bring	O
the	O
Pistols	O
.	O
But	O
we	O
forced	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
tying	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
Whitlock	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
why	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
sooner	O
.	O
We	O
risled	O
him	O
and	O
bound	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Parlor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
tyed	O
her	O
Hands	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
and	O
Brown	O
and	O
Whitlock	O
took	O
the	O
Colonel	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
shew	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
Maid	O
.	O
We	O
began	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
a	O
Chest	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
untie	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
the	O
Keys	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Pearl	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Money	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
found	O
any	O
they	O
sunk	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
another	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
the	O
Beds	O
up	O
to	O
examine	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
a	O
rough	O
Draught	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
there	O
-	O
*	O
See	O
their	O
Trial	O
in	O
December	O
1733	O
.	O
+	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
John	O
Gassey	O
in	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
for	O
July	O
1722	O
.	O
-	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
a	O
rough	O
Draught	O
?	O
Mitchel	O
.	O
We	O
gave	O
a	O
look	O
round	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Chamber	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
Head	O
Clothes	O
and	O
other	O
Women	O
's	O
Apparel	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Colonel	O
,	O
bound	O
his	O
Hands	O
again	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Coming	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
Maid	O
lying	O
with	O
her	O
Coats	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
putting	O
up	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
you	O
Rogue	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
ought	O
to	O
think	O
of	O
other	O
things	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
as	O
this	O
.	O
And	O
turning	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
has	O
he	O
hurt	O
ye	O
?	O
She	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
cryed	O
.	O
Whitlock	O
often	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Colonel	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
discover	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
cut	O
his	O
Throat	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
we	O
brought	O
the	O
Things	O
all	O
into	O
one	O
Room	O
and	O
packed	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Plate	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
what	O
Goods	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
till	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
Water	O
to	O
Pepper	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
White	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Grange	O
,	O
where	O
Brown	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
our	O
Wives	O
lodged	O
.	O
Brown	O
's	O
Wife	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
opened	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Linnen	O
.	O
Brown	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Whitelock	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Plate	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Bodenham	I-pers
*	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
all	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
twenty	O
five	O
Pound	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
his	O
Share	O
of	O
this	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
more	O
for	O
his	O
Snack	O
in	O
the	O
Brocades	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
then	O
near	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
return	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
any	O
Fact	O
besides	O
this	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Bodenham	O
in	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
for	O
December	O
1733	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Prove	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
Company	O
.	O
Mitchel	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
can	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
Mitchel	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
that	O
Morning	O
with	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
Whitlock	O
and	O
Brown	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
brocaded	O
Silk	O
Clothes	O
,	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Laced	O
Head	O
Clothes	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
Silver-handled	O
Knives	O
,	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
a	O
Silver-hilted	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
being	O
quite	O
light	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
you	O
by	O
your	O
Tongue	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
your	O
Name	O
Blackwell	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
Geese	O
and	O
Rabbitt	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
you	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
these	O
Goods	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
my	O
Husband	O
answered	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Smuggling	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
he	O
and	O
Brown	O
and	O
Whitlock	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
Colonel	O
Romaines	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
eighteen	O
or	O
nineteen	O
Years	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty	O
ninth	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Horseback	O
and	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Earl	O
's	O
Court	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
.	O
One	O
Sarah	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
was	O
persuading	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
go	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
There	O
's	O
Will	O
.	O
Kirk	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
but	O
little	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
hearing	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
into	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
Sarah	O
Burgess	O
's	O
Door	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Colstair	O
's	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Brocks	O
(	O
Brogdon	O
Poplet	O
's	O
)	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Long	O
Will	O
.	O
was	O
hard	O
by	O
and	O
we	O
might	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
Brock	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
his	O
while	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
forty	O
Pound	O
for	O
taking	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Redgate	I-pers
,	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
proper	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
till	O
that	O
Man	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
followed	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
till	O
coming	O
towards	O
the	O
Vine	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
wished	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
hold	O
by	O
the	O
Horse	O
's	O
Main	O
.	O
Never	O
fear	O
,	O
Cockey	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
my	O
Eyes	O
I	O
shall	O
do	O
well	O
enough	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
being	O
gone	O
,	O
we	O
pulled	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
off	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
cried	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
!	O
my	O
Glass	O
is	O
run	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
my	O
Eyes	O
!	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
Pistol	O
and	O
Powder	O
and	O
Ball	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
me	O
but	O
down-right	O
Work	O
.	O
Kirk	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eighteen	O
or	O
nineteen	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
sometimes	O
went	O
with	O
an	O
Orange-Barrow	O
with	O
Twenty-one	O
at	O
three	O
Throws	O
.	O
And	O
sometimes	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
Thimble	O
and	O
Button	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
26	O
,	O
27	O
,	O
28.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Cammel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Marman	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Eastwood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
29	O
Shillings	O
,	O
Septemb	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29.	O
George	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Stamper	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Stone	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
May	O
13	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stamper	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Shacklewel	O
,	O
four	O
Men	O
stopt	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Causeway	O
between	O
Shoreditch	B-place
Church	I-place
and	O
Kingsland	B-place
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
seized	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
-	O
What	O
are	O
ye	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
no-body	O
to	O
oppose	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
;	O
take	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
abuse	O
me	O
Damn	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
speak	O
another	O
Word	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
Brains	O
out	O
-	O
Come	O
along	O
,	O
They	O
led	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
where	O
Jack	B-pers
Catch	I-pers
was	O
hanged	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shoes	O
,	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bound	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
me	O
they	O
would	O
send	O
some	O
body	O
to	O
relieve	O
me	O
in	O
five	O
Minutes	O
,	O
they	O
fired	O
a	O
Pistol	O
over	O
my	O
Head	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
there	O
an	O
Hour	O
by	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Clock	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
heard	O
strike	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
my	O
Buckles	O
I	O
had	O
lain	O
longer	O
;	O
for	O
having	O
got	O
my	O
Shoes	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
at	O
last	O
got	O
my	O
Legs	O
loose	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
Morpeth	O
and	O
Kiff	O
,	O
were	O
convicted	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
both	O
executed	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cotterel	I-pers
.	O
Morpeth	O
,	O
Kiff	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Kingsland-Road	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
till	O
the	O
Dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
by	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
at	O
Stone-bridge	O
.	O
Morpeth	O
stopt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
started	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Punch	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
:	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
down	O
a	O
Lane	O
and	O
rifled	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wig	O
,	O
Watch	O
,	O
Ring	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
Buckles	O
.	O
We	O
tied	O
his	O
Legs	O
and	O
Arms	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
released	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
us	O
how	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
And	O
Morpeth	O
fired	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
Sign	O
for	O
one	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
Relies	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
only	O
said	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
easy	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Magpye	O
Tavern	O
at	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
produced	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
and	O
two	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
They	O
swore	O
then	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
a	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
People	O
often	O
pretend	O
to	O
have	O
lost	O
more	O
than	O
they	O
really	O
have	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Ring	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
Watch	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Ring	O
(	O
having	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
Stone	O
out	O
because	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
in	O
it	O
)	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
forget	O
which	O
-	O
The	O
Buckles	O
were	O
sold	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
to	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Moses	O
and	O
Aaron	O
Alley	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
The	O
Wig	O
was	O
valued	O
by	O
Philip	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
a	O
Barber	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
at	O
16	O
s.	O
We	O
flung	O
Dice	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Morpeth	O
won	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Claxton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
Back	O
Lane	O
by	O
Whetstone	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
they	O
hanged	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
for	O
his	O
Good	O
,	O
for	O
then	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
no	O
more	O
Mischief	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
my	O
Eyes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
cast	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
sha'n't	O
be	O
jamm	O
'd	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
good	O
Friends	O
who	O
can	O
save	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
they	O
wo	O
n't	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
damn	O
'd	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
left	O
him	O
3500	O
l.	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Aunt	O
allows	O
him	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Midshipman	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Tilbury	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
idle	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Water-Lane	O
,	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
He	O
continued	O
with	O
me	O
Three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
last	O
May	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
appeared	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
civil	O
and	O
sedate	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
swear	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
nor	O
saw	O
any	O
Company	O
come	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Three	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
deposed	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
30.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Joyce	B-pers
Cordwell	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hodgkin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
at	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Storke	I-pers
the	O
Minister	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1724	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
what	O
Month	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
do	O
n't	O
always	O
set	O
the	O
Months	O
down	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Minister	O
James	B-pers
Storke	I-pers
lived	O
with	O
me	O
eighteen	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
his	O
Register-Book	O
.	O
Joyce	B-pers
Cordwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Shrove	O
Tuesday	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
Lime-house	I-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
this	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Work-house	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
called	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
was	O
No	O
Woman	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
contradicted	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hewet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Brass	O
Locks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susan	B-pers
Farforth	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hooker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pounds	O
and	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Plate	O
Brass	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
23	O
Brass	O
Ballances	O
,	O
Value	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
16	O
Steel	O
Verges	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
7	O
Setts	O
of	O
Steel	O
Works	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
steel	O
File	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Shop	O
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
.	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
About	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
had	O
stole	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
in	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
Workmen	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
such	O
Goods	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
long	O
Hesitation	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
desiring	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
16	O
Verges	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Mouth	O
(	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
of	O
no	O
greater	O
Bulk	O
than	O
a	O
Chew	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
)	O
17	O
Studs	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
23	O
Ballances	O
,	O
10	O
Setts	O
of	O
Steel	O
Works	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Watch	O
-	O
Movements	O
,	O
three	O
Pounds	O
and	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
File	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pockets	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
ashamed	O
of	O
and	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Jail	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
you	O
the	O
Minute	O
you	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
defraud	O
you	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cushion	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
for	O
some	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
Ballances	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
Parcel	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
missing	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
.	O
Next	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
Verges	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
out	O
32	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
several	O
into	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
27	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
besides	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Dozen	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
ten	O
Steel	O
Works	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
Excuse	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
-	O
All	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bought	O
came	O
but	O
to	O
Nine-pence	O
Half-penny	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Milburn	I-pers
confirmed	O
Mr.King	O
's	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
dealt	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Years	O
at	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
as	O
usual	O
to	O
buy	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
in	O
Drink	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
what	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
buy	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
trusted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
these	O
Watches	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
honestly	O
returned	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Goods	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Westley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Grout	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
they	O
had	O
heard	O
any	O
III	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
Ten	O
Pence	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
Richard	B-pers
Peacod	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Girdle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Buckle	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
October	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Tea-spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
35.	O
Julian	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
*	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Ravishing	O
and	O
Carnally	O
Knowing	O
Susan	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
of	O
Eleven	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
April	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
In	O
September	O
1731	O
,	O
Brown	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
Street-Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Evidences	O
for	O
Mac	O
Cray	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
Night	O
my	O
Mother	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
keeps	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Plum-tree	B-place
Court	I-place
in	I-place
Dyot-street	I-place
,	O
-	O
for	O
two	O
Red	O
Herrings	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
me	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
one	O
for	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
came	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
into	O
his	O
Back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
me	O
a	O
Red	O
Herring	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
Anniseed	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
drink	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
set	O
me	O
on	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
up	O
my	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
and	O
-	O
I	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
nasty	O
Rogue	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Hush	O
!	O
hush	O
!	O
I	O
do	O
so	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
promise	O
to	O
tell	O
no	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
Monday	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Bathaway	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
sore	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
about	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
my	O
Mother	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Vat'our	O
it	O
vas	O
ven	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
mine	O
Shop	O
?	O
Susan	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
What	O
Hour	O
?	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
or	O
second	O
Time	O
of	O
your	O
being	O
there	O
?	O
Susan	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
Ten	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
He	O
shut	O
the	O
Hatch	O
and	O
bolted	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
Room	O
he	O
latched	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
vas	O
in	O
mine	O
Shop	O
but	O
von	O
Time	O
dat	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
complain	O
before	O
Monday	O
?	O
Susan	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
Because	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
my	O
Mother	O
would	O
beat	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
your	O
Oath	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
consent	O
?	O
Susan	O
Marshall	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
aloud	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ven	O
you	O
come	O
again	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
?	O
Susan	O
Marshall	O
.	O
Not	O
till	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
come	O
on	O
de	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
used	O
you	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
?	O
Were	O
you	O
sent	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
?	O
Susan	O
Marshall	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
Play-fellows	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bathaway	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Habitation	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
two	O
Herrings	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
her	O
come	O
again	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
one	O
for	O
herself	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
up	O
her	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
speak	O
it	O
-	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
must	O
-	O
And	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
very	O
loud	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
heard	O
her	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
examining	O
we	O
found	O
that	O
some	O
Man	O
had	O
abused	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Marshall	O
.	O
My	O
Girl	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
used	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Manner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
frighted	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
medling	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
send	O
a	O
Surshon	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Marshall	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
complain	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Marshall	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
done	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
preferred	O
a	O
Bill	O
for	O
an	O
Attempt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
a	O
Bill	O
afterwards	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
for	O
a	O
Rape	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Marshall	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Attorney	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Midwife	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
Girl	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
torn	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
foul	O
Distemper	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
fancy	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
clapt	O
,	O
by	O
what	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
Linnen	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
enter	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
Smart	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
Linnen	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
discolour	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Running	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
some	O
doubt	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
Disorder	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
Medicines	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
French	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Distemper	O
submitted	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
,	O
Apothecary	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
by	O
her	O
Linnen	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Disorder	O
was	O
Venereal	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
an	O
Action	O
against	O
deem	O
in	O
de	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
for	O
Scandal	O
,	O
and	O
den	O
dey	O
indict	O
me	O
for	O
dis	O
Rape	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
eleventh	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
little	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Shop	O
from	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
till	O
eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
except	O
twice	O
or	O
thrice	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
just	O
stept	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
Room	O
and	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
But	O
from	O
nine	O
at	O
Night	O
to	O
eleven	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
once	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
came	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
for	O
two	O
Herrings	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
she	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
little	O
Room	O
.	O
And	O
Mrs.	O
Tomson	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
,	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
from	O
eight	O
till	O
past	O
ten	O
:	O
Next	O
Day	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Spanish	O
Embastinder	O
's	O
Silver	O
Smith	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
over	O
Sea	O
)	O
were	O
sitting	O
in	O
that	O
Room	O
,	O
this	O
Girl	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
of	O
Gin	O
;	O
they	O
laughed	O
and	O
talked	O
how	O
they	O
had	O
served	O
two	O
Boys	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Girl	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
his	O
Shins	O
with	O
the	O
Fire-shovel	O
,	O
I	O
love	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
like	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
that	O
Day	O
for	O
Gin	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
let	O
them	O
Girls	O
drink	O
Gin	O
?	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
you	O
deny	O
them	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
.	O
So	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
his	O
Cellar	O
under	O
that	O
little	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
Noise	O
that	O
Night	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Girl	O
on	O
the	O
fifteenth	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
.	O
Because	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Dram	O
of	O
Anniseed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
pretty	O
Baby	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
to	O
nurse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
will	O
be	O
better	O
than	O
crying	O
out	O
.	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
May	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Parents	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lately	O
had	O
a	O
Clap	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Ferris	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Fullerton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
general	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Suky	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
was	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
every	O
body	O
for	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
Impudence	O
.	O
In	O
reply	O
to	O
which	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
Suky	O
Marshall	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
like	O
Impudence	O
or	O
Forwardness	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
modest	O
,	O
virtuous	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
litigious	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
36	O
,	O
37.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Darling	I-pers
:	O
Armstrong	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Calf	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
Leg	O
of	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
September	O
24	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
:	O
And	O
Price	O
,	O
by	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
and	O
abetting	O
Armstrong	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Humphries	O
's	O
Brandy	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
Winford	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
should	O
come	O
in	O
but	O
this	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
Now	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
a	O
mighty	O
joaking	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
curried	O
a	O
clean	O
Heel	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
like	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
like	O
an	O
Irish	O
Leg	O
,	O
as	O
thick	O
at	O
bottom	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
at	O
top	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
she	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
Leg	O
and	O
kicked	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Parts	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hit	O
her	O
a	O
Box	O
on	O
the	O
Ear	O
.	O
She	O
reel	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Call	O
my	O
Cosin	O
,	O
call	O
my	O
Cousin	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
at	O
a	O
Gin	O
shop	O
next	O
Door	O
.	O
So	O
came	O
her	O
Cousin	O
(	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Armstrong	O
)	O
with	O
an	O
Oyster	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
'd	O
cut	O
his	O
Nose	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
laughed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
sure	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
serve	O
me	O
so	O
?	O
She	O
swore	O
yes	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
Irish	O
Thief	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Push	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
pushed	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
turned	O
short	O
and	O
stabbed	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
saw	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
he	O
knocked	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
beating	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
cut	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Leg	O
.	O
And	O
her	O
Aunt	O
Price	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Kill	O
him	O
Betty	O
,	O
kill	O
him	O
.	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
till	O
all	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
before	O
the	O
Stab	O
.	O
Harry	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
past	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
Armstrong	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
He	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Wrist	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
being	O
stronger	O
than	O
he	O
,	O
shifted	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
left	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
darted	O
the	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Leg	O
,	O
and	O
Price	O
came	O
and	O
hung	O
round	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Kill	O
him	O
,	O
kill	O
him	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Sallet	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
the	O
same	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
in	O
Baker	O
's	O
Arms	O
Alley	O
,	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
,	O
when	O
Armstrong	O
came	O
in	O
very	O
dirty	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
tumbling	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Mud	O
.	O
She	O
answered	O
,	O
A	O
little	O
Irish	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
struck	O
my	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Breast	O
thus	O
far	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wish	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Heart	O
's	O
Blood	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Winford	O
Street	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
in	O
my	O
Arms	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Farwell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
who	O
sat	O
on	O
a	O
Bench	O
.	O
Price	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
cleaver	O
Legs	O
,	O
as	O
thick	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
as	O
top	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
touched	O
the	O
String	O
of	O
her	O
Shoe	O
.	O
She	O
kicked	O
his	O
Privities	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Box	O
on	O
the	O
Ear	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
for	O
her	O
Cousin	O
Armstrong	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
cut	O
his	O
Nose	O
off	O
.	O
Arm-Strong	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stabbed	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Shoe	O
full	O
of	O
Blood	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
in	O
four	O
Minutes	O
,	O
which	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Wound	O
near	O
the	O
Armpit	O
which	O
past	O
obliquely	O
towards	O
the	O
Sternum	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
penetration	O
in	O
the	O
Cavity	O
of	O
the	O
Thorax	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
another	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
deep	O
in	O
the	O
Calf	O
of	O
his	O
Leg	O
.	O
I	O
drest	O
his	O
Wounds	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
trivial	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
due	O
care	O
,	O
the	O
Hemorrhage	O
of	O
Blood	O
from	O
the	O
Calf	O
of	O
his	O
Leg	O
contributed	O
to	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
harrasded	O
about	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
And	O
his	O
Animal	O
Spirits	O
being	O
exhausted	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
be	O
suffocated	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
having	O
his	O
Head	O
laid	O
in	O
a	O
proper	O
position	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
he	O
fought	O
with	O
a	O
Sailor	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
hasten	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
-	O
Wallis	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sailor	O
coming	O
by	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Blows	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
People	O
saying	O
,	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
ashamed	O
to	O
fight	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
is	O
stabbed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Sailor	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
Window	O
and	O
saw	O
Armstrong	O
push	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Wrists	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
loose	O
and	O
stabbed	O
him	O
thus	O
down	O
the	O
Breast	O
;	O
I	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
Beat	O
her	O
,	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
her	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
.	O
A	O
Sailor	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
ye	O
!	O
what	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
beat	O
a	O
Woman	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
quitted	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Blows	O
past	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Sailor	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
beat	O
a	O
wounded	O
Man	O
.	O
Price	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
up	O
my	O
Coats	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
for	O
ye	O
Blockhead	O
?	O
is	O
there	O
not	O
Wench	O
enough	O
for	O
ye	O
?	O
What	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
do	O
ye	O
stomach	O
it	O
?	O
My	O
Cousin	O
having	O
been	O
opening	O
Oysters	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
but	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Cousin	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a	O
beating	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
off	O
.	O
Armstrong	O
.	O
Hearing	O
my	O
Aunt	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
foolish	O
Irish	O
Dog	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
twice	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
up	O
my	O
Coats	O
.	O
Two	O
Surgeons	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
mortal	O
.	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
living	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
due	O
care	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Armstrong	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
38.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cullen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
in	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
;	O
three	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
two	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Laced	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tostick	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
October	O
13	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
M.	O
Yates	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mistress	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
to	O
Dance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Chocolate-house	O
-	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
concealed	O
himself	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Family	O
sat	O
up	O
till	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Maid	O
's	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Tostick	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
there	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lady	O
went	O
from	O
our	O
House	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
account	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
we	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
five	O
that	O
Morning	O
.	O
Upon	O
searching	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
ten	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
two	O
Salts	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Cloth	O
up	O
the	O
Chimney	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
our	O
House	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
that	O
he	O
returned	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
he	O
first	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
past	O
through	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
waited	O
till	O
the	O
Family	O
was	O
abed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
(	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
open	O
)	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
He	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
Mistress	O
eight	O
Months	O
ago	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Leadbeater	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Footman	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Brooks	O
in	O
Great	O
Pultney-Street	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
without	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
young	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
39	O
Ann	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howorth	I-pers
,	O
January	O
4	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howorth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
forty	O
Pound	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Bank	O
Note	O
for	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
in	O
Gold	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Peter	O
Street	O
,	O
Soho	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
-	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Church	B-place
Lane	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
where	O
we	O
drank	O
Ale	O
and	O
Brandy	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
growing	O
late	O
we	O
concluded	O
that	O
one	O
Bed	O
should	O
serve	O
us	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
giving	O
the	O
Landlady	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
she	O
locked	O
us	O
both	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
awaked	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
self	O
disordered	O
in	O
a	O
strange	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
Clothes	O
half	O
on	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
Days	O
Work	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Washing	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
my	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
some	O
Guineas	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
knocked	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Landlady	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
mist	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
enquiring	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
a	O
Ginshop	O
;	O
she	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
pretended	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
upon	O
that	O
same	O
Account	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Mob	O
rescued	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
indeed	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Business	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
care	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Neighbourhood	O
and	O
degraded	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Whitesides	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Power	O
I	O
would	O
prosecute	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
Assurance	O
in	O
divulging	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
again	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
hoped	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
me	O
no	O
harm	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
drunk	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
awaked	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
self	O
locked	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
-	O
And	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
seven	O
Guineas	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
has	O
brought	O
on	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
40.	O
John	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Sauce	O
Pan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Coffee	O
Mil	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
October	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41.	O
Frances	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
from	O
Henry	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
October	O
6	O
.	O
Henry	O
Dun	O
.	O
Having	O
been	O
taking	O
a	O
Bottle	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
merry	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
Charing	B-place
Cross	I-place
about	O
twelve	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
an	O
Alley	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
stood	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
felt	O
for	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
then	O
safe	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
parted	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
felt	O
again	O
for	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
described	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
Night	O
following	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
Direction	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn-brokers	O
;	O
she	O
says	O
indeed	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
common	O
Pretence	O
of	O
such	O
Creatures	O
to	O
make	O
People	O
ashamed	O
to	O
prosecute	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
others	O
will	O
follow	O
my	O
Example	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
offered	O
such	O
unseemly	O
things	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
shame	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
oblige	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
pledge	O
his	O
Watch	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
supposed	O
I	O
was	O
commonly	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
redeem	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
42.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Had	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Richard	B-pers
Marston	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Wallet	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stick	O
value	O
two	O
Pence	O
,	O
July	O
5	O
.	O
But	O
it	O
appearing	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
granted	O
him	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
his	O
Indictment	O
.	O
43	O
,	O
44.	O
James	B-pers
Farthing	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Farthing	I-pers
his	O
Son	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brown	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
September	O
27	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
45.	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
,	O
August	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
46.	O
James	B-pers
Barns	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Lions	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
her	O
of	O
five	O
Pence	O
,	O
September	O
22	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
47.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Quaif	I-pers
,	O
September	O
22	O
.	O
And	O
48.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Quaif	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
met	O
Newman	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
in	O
Queen	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
Yard	I-place
in	I-place
Tyburn	I-place
Road	I-place
.	O
She	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
up	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
over	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
what	O
a	O
Creature	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Quart	O
of	O
Gin	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
had	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
them	O
.	O
49.	O
William	B-pers
Gibbens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
three	O
Portugal	O
Pieces	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
-	O
Graham	O
.	O
About	O
Eleven	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
an	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
.	O
His	O
Face	O
and	O
Hands	O
were	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
his	O
Landlord	O
had	O
abused	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lodging	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
your	O
Fault	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
civil	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
one	O
Night	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
Countryman	O
,	O
and	O
destitute	O
of	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
I	O
at	O
last	O
consented	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
Bed-fellow	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
undress	O
'd	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Money	O
was	O
tied	O
fast	O
in	O
the	O
Tail	O
of	O
my	O
Shirt	O
.	O
My	O
other	O
Bed-fellow	O
and	O
I	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
Brewhouse	O
three	O
Doors	O
from	O
my	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
early	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
farther	O
Side	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
needs	O
lie	O
next	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
In	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
my	O
other	O
Bed-fellow	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Tail	O
of	O
my	O
Shirt	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
above	O
two	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
over-slept	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Brewhouse	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
dress	O
'd	O
myself	O
in	O
such	O
haste	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
whether	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
safe	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
immediately	O
leave	O
the	O
Work	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Street-Door	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
serve	O
me	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
civil	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
answered	O
;	O
What	O
a	O
Noise	O
you	O
make	O
,	O
hold	O
your	O
Tongue	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
'll	O
get	O
your	O
Money	O
again	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
search	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
Landlady	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
keep	O
the	O
Door	O
till	O
I	O
fetched	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
right	O
Name	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Beau	O
Nash	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
than	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
.	O
50	O
Thomas	B-pers
Devenish	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
Backmaker	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
a	O
Promissory	O
Note	O
(	O
dated	O
May	O
25	O
,	O
1735	O
.	O
Signed	O
with	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Devenish	I-pers
,	O
and	O
purporting	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Devenish	O
promised	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
or	O
Order	O
,	O
One	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
)	O
he	O
did	O
forge	O
an	O
Indorsement	O
in	O
these	O
Words	O
and	O
Figures	O
,	O
May	O
29	O
,	O
1735	O
.	O
Pay	O
the	O
Contents	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
or	O
Order	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
utter	O
and	O
publish	O
the	O
said	O
Forged	O
Writing	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
Green	O
and	O
Morris	O
,	O
June	O
29	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Note	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
first	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Northall	I-pers
a	O
Scrivener	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
Sessions	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
Money	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
try	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
indors	O
'd	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
who	O
Morris	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
Northall	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
Morris	O
was	O
a	O
Smith	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
End	O
of	O
Broad-Street	O
.	O
Northall	O
came	O
several	O
Times	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
Devenish	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
Note	O
belonged	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
must	O
pay	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Name	O
at	O
Bottom	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
directed	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
that	O
Morris	O
was	O
a	O
Smith	O
in	O
Broad	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
that	O
Direction	O
was	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
dealt	O
with	O
Morris	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
owe	O
Morris	O
such	O
a	O
considerable	O
Sum	O
.	O
His	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
a	O
Back-maker	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
owing	O
for	O
Nails	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Back-making	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Sum	O
was	O
not	O
considerable	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
his	O
Dealing	O
.	O
This	O
Account	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
natural	O
enough	O
;	O
