TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
May	O
1736.	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
WILLIAMS	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1736	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXVI	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Hardwick	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Cummins	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Say	I-pers
,	O
+	O
Challenged	O
by	O
Hen	O
.	O
Justice	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
sworn	O
in	O
his	O
Place	O
on	O
at	O
Tryal	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hewett	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boon	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Petty	I-pers
,	O
Benj	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
Enoch	B-pers
Gregg	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Chitty	I-pers
,	O
++	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
,	O
++	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Sam	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
instead	O
of	O
Theoph	O
.	O
Lightfoot	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
taken	O
ill.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Aimes	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Saugill	I-pers
.	O
1	O
,	O
2.	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Wharton	B-pers
Rutlis	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Casements	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Grate	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
March	O
30	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ketterich	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Casements	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Ketterich	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
an	O
Old-Iron	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Sea-cole	O
Lane	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Men	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Terrill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Casements	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Dean	O
lived	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Meeting	O
House	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
Lead	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
Indictment	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
Window	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Casements	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Monnear	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
an	O
Old-Iron	O
Stall	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Sea-cole-Lane	O
,	O
for	O
Three	O
Farthings	O
or	O
a	O
Penny	O
a	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
among	O
us	O
.	O
John	O
Dean	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Walnut-tree	O
Plank	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Feet	O
of	O
inch	O
Wainscot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
March	O
30	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
,	I-place
by	I-place
St.	I-place
Pauls	I-place
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Ketterich	O
's	O
Account	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Terrill	O
and	O
examined	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
Account	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
stolen	O
the	O
Planks	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
Walnut-tree	O
to	O
one	O
Bunyan	O
a	O
Turner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wainscot	O
to	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Rams	I-pers
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Work-shop	O
in	O
Black-Swan-Alley	B-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Directions	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Terrill	I-pers
.	O
'T	O
is	O
all	O
right	O
;	O
my	O
Uncle	O
Dean	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Walnut-tree	O
Plank	O
out	O
of	O
Newman	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Bunyan	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
7	O
d.	O
a	O
Foot	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
two	O
Wainscot	O
Boards	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Rams	O
:	O
Uncle	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Bunyan	O
and	O
Rams	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
Pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
fixed	O
to	O
an	O
empty	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ketterich	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
March	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anns	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
suspected	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
them	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Cellar-stairs	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
George	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
,	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
(	O
with	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Dillon	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
26	O
,	O
1735	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
10s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
aforesaid	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Time	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
my	O
Servant	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
the	O
Bake-house	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
for	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
him	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
long	O
Pole	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Man	O
fired	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
Arm	O
and	O
Breast	O
.	O
A	O
Second	O
fir	O
'd	O
and	O
wounded	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
backwards	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
Persons	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
their	O
Arms	O
,	O
unbottoned	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
my	O
Man	O
into	O
the	O
Bake-house	O
,	O
tied	O
his	O
Handkerchief	O
over	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
his	O
Hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
him	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
swearing	O
with	O
horrid	O
Oaths	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
a	O
Word	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
Brains	O
out	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
others	O
got	O
Candles	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
many	O
more	O
Things	O
than	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
was	O
Valuable	O
they	O
took	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Bridgewater	O
in	O
Somersetshire	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Mayor	O
and	O
Alderman	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Rogues	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Director	O
in	O
the	O
Affair	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
they	O
broke	O
any	O
Lock	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
that	O
is	O
next	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
broke	O
several	O
Locks	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Bridgewater	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
Confession	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
being	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
Parish	O
of	O
Bridgewater	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
taken	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
1735	O
,	O
before	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Hosee	I-pers
,	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
Sam	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Borough	O
,	O
who	O
says	O
,	O
'That	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
24	O
or	O
25	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
'	O
born	O
at	O
Dublin	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
a	O
Joyner	O
;	O
'	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
London	O
about	O
last	O
'	O
March	O
was	O
twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
'	O
one	O
King	O
,	O
a	O
Joyner	O
,	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
lodged	O
'	O
in	O
Newtoner	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Fitzgerald	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
at	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
other	O
Houses	O
near	O
'	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
except	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
'	O
three	O
Weeks	O
that	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
one	O
Conolly	O
;	O
'	O
that	O
about	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
March	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
'	O
Bristol	O
,	O
staid	O
there	O
three	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
in	O
'	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
White	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
Shipping	O
'	O
there	O
for	O
Dublin	O
,	O
with	O
Patrick	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
'	O
Edward	B-pers
Dillon	I-pers
.	O
Dillon	O
came	O
into	O
Bristol	O
in	O
Company	O
'	O
with	O
this	O
Examinant	O
,	O
and	O
Hall	O
came	O
to	O
'	O
Bristol	O
some	O
Days	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
'	O
expose	O
to	O
Sale	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
any	O
Person	O
whatever	O
.	O
'	O
That	O
in	O
August	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
England	O
,	O
'	O
went	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
his	O
'	O
Trade	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
Confession	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
as	O
aforesaid	O
:	O
Who	O
saith	O
,	O
'That	O
notwithstanding	O
his	O
former	O
'	O
Examination	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
'	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
hopes	O
that	O
his	O
'	O
Majesty	O
will	O
shew	O
him	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
admit	O
him	O
to	O
'	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Farther	O
confesseth	O
,	O
and	O
faith	O
,	O
'	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
assisting	O
to	O
'	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Dillon	I-pers
and	O
Row	O
,	O
in	O
'	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
'	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
'	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
the	O
'	O
said	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
two	O
'	O
gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
several	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
'	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
Spoon	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
'	O
Money	O
divided	O
between	O
them	O
and	O
this	O
Examinant	O
:	O
'	O
That	O
Hall	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Gibson	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
Service	O
:	O
That	O
Hall	O
,	O
Row	O
and	O
'	O
Dillon	O
being	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
,	O
Hall	O
proposed	O
'	O
the	O
committing	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
'	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
try	O
to	O
get	O
Money	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
'	O
had	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
how	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
'	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Matter	O
being	O
agreed	O
upon	O
,	O
'	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
they	O
'	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
Hall	O
led	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Back-door	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
that	O
Gibson	O
and	O
his	O
Man	O
were	O
up	O
at	O
'	O
Baking	O
;	O
the	O
Man	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bake-house	O
;	O
'	O
He	O
this	O
Examinant	O
,	O
rush	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
said	O
'	O
Bakehouse	O
and	O
secured	O
Gibson	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
'	O
rifled	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Row	O
,	O
Hall	O
'	O
and	O
Dillon	O
,	O
are	O
all	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
about	O
Dublin	O
.	O
'	O
Signed	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
George	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
Bryan	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Work	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
for	O
the	O
Scovel	O
to	O
sweep	O
the	O
Oven	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
hung	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
an	O
Oven	O
facing	O
the	O
Bake-house	O
:	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
Scovel	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Men	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Number	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
surprised	O
:	O
They	O
rush	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
silenced	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
threatning	O
to	O
blow	O
my	O
Brains	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
put	O
a	O
Sword	O
to	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
Pistols	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
two	O
Pistols	O
discharged	O
at	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
cry	O
out	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
Doors	O
.	O
Q	O
When	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
you	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
whether	O
I	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
Door	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
broke	O
several	O
Locks	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
particularly	O
,	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
large	O
Locks	O
on	O
the	O
Doors	O
of	O
the	O
Rooms	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
5.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Books	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Adventures	O
of	O
Telemacus	O
,	O
2	O
vol	O
.	O
of	O
Persian	O
Letters	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Book	O
called	O
a	O
Voyage	O
to	O
Barbary	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bailey	O
's	O
English	O
Dictionary	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Banner	I-pers
,	O
April	O
26	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cope	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Loggan	I-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
April	O
13	O
.	O
Edward	O
Loggan	O
Bird	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
6	O
Weeks	O
,	O
or	O
2	O
Months	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Spoon	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
other	O
of	O
my	O
Servants	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn-brokers	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kay	I-pers
.	O
Tuesday	O
13	O
April	O
a	O
Person	O
brought	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
ACL	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Family	O
Spoon	O
,	O
so	O
enquired	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Cope	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
see	O
this	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Cope	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Spoon	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
her	O
Character	O
;	O
she	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Say	O
's	O
the	O
Undertaker	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
nothing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Griffin	O
Tavern	O
,	O
Holborn	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
Bird	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Spoon	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
upon	O
this	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
Spoon	O
(	O
three	O
Months	O
before	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
)	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
by	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
8s	O
.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Wattis	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Manichee	I-pers
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
and	O
Reputation	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
8.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Laffar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Vannier	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Gotier	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
39s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Mary	B-pers
Denny	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Dwelling-House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Ferret	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
29	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
Ferret	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
observed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
followed	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11	O
,	O
12.	O
Martha	B-pers
Hadley	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Douglas	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Redhead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-Le-Strand	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
without	O
a	O
Lid	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alex	B-pers
.	I-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
April	O
26	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
swear	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Tankard	O
;	O
Hadley	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
about	O
five	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Birchmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Pawn-Broker	O
,	O
on	O
Easter	O
Monday	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
(	O
Hadley	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Name	O
is	O
Martha	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Turnball-Street	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
marked	O
AMM	O
.	O
these	O
Letters	O
ca	O
n't	O
stand	O
for	O
your	O
Name	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
satisfied	O
't	O
is	O
your	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
the	O
Tankard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Money	O
they	O
wanted	O
upon	O
it	O
)	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
liv	O
'd	O
;	O
they	O
carried	O
me	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
;	O
now	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
satisfied	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Habitation	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
if	O
Martha	O
Warren	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
ad	O
lived	O
there	O
several	O
Years	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
very	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
advertised	O
it	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
Morning	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Papers	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
was	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
describing	O
this	O
Tankard	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Owner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Turnimill	O
street	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
this	O
Mrs.	O
Warren	O
,	O
Somebody	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
Hadley	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
I	O
wanted	O
:	O
She	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
Stays	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Means	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy	O
shop	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
whence	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Justice	O
Robe	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
39s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Jane	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
32s	O
.	O
the	O
Moneys	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
14.	O
William	B-pers
Whale	I-pers
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
b.	O
of	O
Lead	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
Iron	O
Casement	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
John	B-pers
Standland	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Iron	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Martin	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Dennet	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
February	O
3d	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Dennet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
Poultrey	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
rushed	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
each	O
side	O
:	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
go	O
up	O
towards	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
towards	O
the	O
Exchange	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
has	O
my	O
Name	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Saunders	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
exactly	O
against	O
Stocks	O
Market	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
left	O
Side	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Mary	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alban	I-place
Wood-Street	I-place
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
being	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Coombes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Yards	O
of	O
Taffety	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
and	O
Eudasia	B-pers
Street	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Vedast	I-place
Foster-lane	I-place
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Silk	O
and	O
Cotton	O
wove	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Tea	O
pot	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Tea-kettle	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
one	O
black	O
Callimanco	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Riding-hood	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winder	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
William	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
London	I-place
Wall	I-place
,	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Terris	I-pers
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Butolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margarets	I-place
New	I-place
Fish-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Tea-spoon	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Sladen	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
23.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Collard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Christopher	I-place
's	I-place
Parish	I-place
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
Chain	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Seal	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
March	O
the	O
first	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
St.	O
David	O
's	O
Day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Dinner	O
at	O
Merchant-Taylor	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Welch	O
Society	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Threadneedle-street	B-place
,	O
within	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Hall	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
rushing	O
with	O
his	O
Belly	O
against	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
held	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
rent	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
how	O
far	O
distant	O
I	O
was	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
The	O
very	O
instant	O
I	O
felt	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
'till	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
secure	O
the	O
Man	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
without	O
losing	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
this	O
Arm	O
,	O
by	O
pulling	O
and	O
haling	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Strafford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
sells	O
Fish	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
sells	O
Greens	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
him	O
in	O
Angel-Alley	O
in	O
Moor-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bowl	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
sells	O
Fish	O
,	O
Oranges	O
and	O
Lemons	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
hear	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Long	O
Will	O
?	O
Bowl	O
No	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Boston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
do	O
an	O
ill	O
Thing	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
sell	O
Fish	O
and	O
Oranges	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
otherwise	O
,	O
let	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
say	O
say	O
against	O
it	O
Richard	B-pers
Arding	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
was	O
but	O
small	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Trifle	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
sold	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
a	O
Barrow	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
24.	O
Martha	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
double	O
channel	O
'd	O
Pumps	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
John	O
Davis	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
Measure	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
desired	O
she	O
might	O
wait	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
Girl	O
she	O
expected	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
she	O
sat	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Customer	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
fitting	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
young	O
Shop-keeper	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
losing	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Neighbours	O
of	O
my	O
Loss	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pierce	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
double-channell	O
'd	O
Pumps	O
sold	O
with	O
the	O
Name	O
Wright	O
in	O
the	O
Inside	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
that	O
Name	O
.	O
-	O
Pierce	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Pumps	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
ask	O
'd	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
Pumps	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Shoe-maker	O
in	O
Tooley-street	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
appeared	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
Living	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25	O
,	O
26.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tooting	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Coral	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Razors	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Snute	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
Hinds	I-pers
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
William	O
Snute	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Tooting	O
is	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
about	O
11	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
those	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Girl	O
confessed	O
she	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
King	B-place
David	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
sells	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
has	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
these	O
two	O
Years	O
.	O
-	O
Clymore	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
follow	O
this	O
Girl	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
finding	O
out	O
the	O
Woman	O
;	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
receive	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Girl	O
confess	O
it	O
before	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
27.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lyell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wellsted	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Wig	O
was	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
borrowed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
my	O
Apartment	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
Complaint	O
to	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Peruke-maker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
a	O
Wig	O
to	O
be	O
buckled	O
,	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
before	O
all	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Wig	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
buckle	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
it	O
lie	O
at	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
should	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
When	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Bannisters	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
28	O
:	O
Frances	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pottage	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Holcraft	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Mary	O
Holcraft	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Room	O
ready	O
furnished	O
at	O
two	O
Shillings	O
a	O
Week	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
there	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
Weeks	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
paying	O
her	O
Rent	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
Warning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
my	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
:	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
persuading	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
:	O
At	O
last	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Collier	O
in	O
Denmark-street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
but	O
two	O
Plates	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Holcraft	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Collier	O
in	O
Denmark-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Licence	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Collier	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
:	O
She	O
has	O
brought	O
these	O
very	O
Goods	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
redeem	O
'd	O
them	O
again	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Licence	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Tost	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
Colliers	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
Things	O
without	O
our	O
searching	O
:	O
The	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
present	O
.	O
The	O
Creature	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
formerly	O
a	O
Servant	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Gentlewoman	O
my	O
Landlady	O
)	O
used	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
work	O
(	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
Washing	O
)	O
but	O
happening	O
to	O
miscarry	O
about	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
those	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
redeemed	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
stay	O
but	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
Thing	O
should	O
be	O
replaced	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29	O
,	O
30	O
,	O
31	O
Eliz	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Eliz	B-pers
Venus	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Abigal	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Shovel	O
,	O
two	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
fifteen	O
Glass	O
Bottles	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Reaping	O
Hook	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Door	O
burst	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
we	O
caught	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
suspected	O
them	O
of	O
bursting	O
it	O
open	O
again	O
:	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
owned	O
that	O
Hart	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
us	O
where	O
we	O
should	O
find	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
all	O
but	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
the	O
Bottles	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
As	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
had	O
complained	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Matthews	O
,	O
and	O
Venus	O
on	O
the	O
Premisses	O
:	O
On	O
Venus	O
's	O
Information	O
I	O
took	O
Hart	O
;	O
Venus	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
Hart	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Places	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
confess	O
'd	O
this	O
before	O
Justice	O
Midford	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
guilty	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32	O
,	O
33	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Warming-pan	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rachael	B-pers
Wheelwright	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Lodging	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Rachael	B-pers
Wheelwright	I-pers
.	O
They	O
hired	O
the	O
Lodging	O
of	O
me	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
their	O
Possession	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
Warning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
many	O
Words	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
Colonel	O
Davy	O
's	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seized	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Baby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
bring	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davy	O
's	O
to	O
pledge	O
and	O
in	O
particular	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
or	O
three	O
Shillings	O
on	O
the	O
Warming-pan	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Williams	O
Mrs.	O
Alice	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
knows	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
redeem	O
the	O
Goods	O
Alice	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Wheelwright	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
let	O
her	O
Room	O
to	O
a	O
Whore	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
impudent	O
one	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
was	O
seduced	O
by	O
this	O
vile	O
Siut	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Imeson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Imeson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
hired	O
as	O
my	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
Spoon	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
She	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
her	O
Confession	O
after	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Higginson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
offered	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
some	O
Questions	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
trembled	O
and	O
quak	O
'd	O
exceedingly	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
Practices	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
carried	O
me	O
herself	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Grahan	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bolster	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Pillow-beers	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodging	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Bushton	I-pers
,	O
March	O
24	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Bushton	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
took	O
the	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Having	O
missed	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
two	O
Places	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dorman	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Sheet	O
and	O
two	O
Pillow-beers	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
no	O
Questions	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
used	O
our	O
Shop	O
many	O
Years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
People	O
of	O
your	O
Trade	O
are	O
not	O
apt	O
to	O
ask	O
Questions	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gilner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lent	O
a	O
Shilling	O
upon	O
the	O
Bolster	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37.	O
William	B-pers
Fowkes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
blue	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Shoulder-knot	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
Wast-coat	O
faced	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
and	O
one	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Vanderbank	I-pers
,	O
April	O
22	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Stables	O
bolted	O
on	O
the	O
Inside	O
:	O
We	O
borrowed	O
a	O
Ladder	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Livery-coat	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Lace	O
ripp	O
'd	O
off	O
the	O
Wastcoat	O
;	O
upon	O
searching	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
hid	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Stalls	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Livery-coat	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Shoulder-knot	O
and	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
Bag	O
that	O
hung	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Shirt	O
and	O
3	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Hay-lost	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
covered	O
with	O
the	O
Litter	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Mangers	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Coat	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hickford	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Thief	O
was	O
found	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
Answer	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
Coat	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Horseman	O
's	O
Coat	O
over	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
the	O
Shoulder-knot	O
and	O
the	O
Lace	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
Charge	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
me	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
come	O
it	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
indict	O
them	O
?	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nixon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Stedman	I-pers
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
nine	O
Cloath	O
Coats	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
eight	O
Drugget	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
value	O
28s	O
.	O
three	O
Cloath	O
Wastcoats	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Drugget	O
Wastcoats	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
my	O
Shop	O
is	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Stedman	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
all	O
fast	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Groove	O
of	O
the	O
Shutters	O
cut	O
,	O
the	O
Shutter	O
stuck	O
up	O
in	O
its	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
Goods	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
a	O
Door	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
shop	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Shop	O
is	O
made	O
intire	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Door	O
but	O
that	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Door	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
~	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
Christmas	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
dead	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Slide	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
this	O
Woman	O
's	O
Shutters	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
:	O
We	O
took	O
away	O
19	O
Coats	O
,	O
two	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
;	O
seventeen	O
of	O
the	O
Coats	O
were	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
Direction	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
we	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
we	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
~	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
was	O
try	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
in	O
January	O
Sessions	O
;	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Book	O
,	O
p.	O
50	O
.	O
Numb	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
swears	O
this	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
Revence	O
of	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
We	O
fell	O
out	O
at	O
Cricket	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
,	O
I	O
beat	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
two	O
afterwards	O
he	O
got	O
me	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Sam	B-pers
Breere	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Agnes	B-pers
Craven	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Behalf	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
.	O
The	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
had	O
18	O
Garments	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
some	O
Coats	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Waistcoats	O
.	O
Dodd	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
the	O
Goods	O
'till	O
they	O
should	O
satisfy	O
me	O
as	O
to	O
their	O
Characters	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
would	O
fetch	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
knew	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
By	O
Dodd	O
's	O
Information	O
Harris	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
I	O
remember	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Lads	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Nixon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
39s	O
39	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cocks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
eight	O
Hens	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
.	O
John	O
Peacock	O
The	O
Fowls	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
Yard	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
Night	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
:	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
my	O
Pales	O
were	O
broke	O
and	O
the	O
Fowls	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Change	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
left	O
Notice	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Dodd	O
was	O
seen	O
with	O
a	O
Sack	O
full	O
of	O
Fowls	O
:	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
:	O
He	O
would	O
own	O
nothing	O
till	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
little	O
Boy	O
Dobson	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Directions	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
Nixon	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
of	O
my	O
Fowls	O
alive	O
at	O
one	O
Nevet	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
&	O
ack	O
lane	O
,	O
Well-street	O
.	O
Nevet	O
denied	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
searching	O
with	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
five	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
.	O
The	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
Dobson	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Armitage	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
Nixon	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
there	O
was	O
Fowls	O
in	O
this	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Pales	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
Cocks	O
and	O
8	O
Hens	O
;	O
5	O
of	O
which	O
we	O
sold	O
to	O
Nevet	O
alive	O
;	O
2	O
we	O
sold	O
dead	O
over	O
against	O
Nevet	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
two	O
we	O
sold	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
we	O
gave	O
away	O
:	O
When	O
the	O
Fowls	O
were	O
disposed	O
of	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
into	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
Hog	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
eat	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
Nevet	O
appeared	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
examined	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
understanding	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
an	O
Accessary	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
they	O
must	O
not	O
regard	O
his	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Dobson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Dodd	O
and	O
Nixon	O
in	O
Well	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
drink	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Gin	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Fowls	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
but	O
that	O
my	O
Child	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Years	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Spolston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
may	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
Mother	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
a	O
little	O
short	O
witted	O
.	O
Nixon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Dobson	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
William	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
March	O
15	O
on	O
Catherine	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
wilfully	O
,	O
maliciously	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Feet	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Skelton	O
did	O
cast	O
and	O
throw	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Skelton	O
so	O
lying	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Stevens	O
did	O
divers	O
Times	O
strike	O
and	O
kick	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Face	O
,	O
Stomach	O
.	O
Belly	O
and	O
Sides	O
,	O
several	O
Mortal	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
from	O
the	O
15th	O
to	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
she	O
languished	O
and	O
languishingly	O
liv	O
'd	O
and	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
died	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
Six	O
Weeks	O
:	O
On	O
Monday	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
beat	O
her	O
and	O
stamped	O
on	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
drag	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Hair	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Provocation	O
given	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
darning	O
a	O
Stocking	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
and	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
stamped	O
upon	O
her	O
right	O
Side	O
,	O
so	O
violently	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Blood	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Nose	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
stamped	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
drag	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
stamp	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Dear	O
,	O
God	O
,	O
save	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
killed	O
me	O
!	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Relation	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Skelton	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
Bedfellows	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
Bridges-street	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
co-habited	O
with	O
her	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
sell	O
Oranges	O
just	O
by	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Play-house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
pull	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
the	O
Door	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
heard	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Katey	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
used	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
at	O
two	O
a-Clock	O
and	O
whipt	O
her	O
so	O
violently	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Scourges	O
were	O
on	O
her	O
Face	O
when	O
the	O
Coroner	O
sat	O
on	O
her	O
Body	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
dying	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
9	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
died	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
10	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
Jenny	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
sitting	O
upright	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
dying	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
f	O
r	O
a	O
Minister	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
starv	O
'd	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
Gill	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
Jenny	O
Hall	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Genoa	O
Arms	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
had	O
killed	O
and	O
murdered	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
wo	O
n't	O
do	O
me	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
World	O
will	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
a	O
free	O
Place	O
,	O
from	O
Head	O
to	O
Foot	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
black	O
as	O
the	O
Gentlemens	O
Gowns	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
any	O
Physician	O
or	O
Surgeon	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Coldham	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
:	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
any	O
one	O
come	O
near	O
her	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
alive	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Stevens	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
the	O
Deceased	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Minister	O
sent	O
for	O
:	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
Kate	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
,	O
say	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Minister	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
too	O
;	O
if	O
she	O
dies	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
buried	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Vinegar-Yard	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Senses	O
between	O
whiles	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
lay	O
across	O
the	O
Feet	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
burning	O
in	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
what	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
me	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
whereabouts	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
From	O
two	O
a-Clock	O
to	O
8	O
a-Clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
beat	O
her	O
several	O
Times	O
in	O
the	O
Brandy-shop	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
locked	O
her	O
in	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Help	O
!	O
Murder	O
!	O
Sarah	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Farthing	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
small	O
Beer	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
tapp	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
Will	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Punch	O
in	O
the	O
Eye	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Blow	O
might	O
do	O
her	O
a	O
Prejudice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
tap	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
given	O
with	O
Violence	O
?	O
Whitehead	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Hand	O
is	O
heavy	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
that	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Kate	O
come	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
Kate	O
,	O
go	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
said	O
fye	O
upon	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
stand	O
by	O
and	O
see	O
a	O
Woman	O
beat	O
;	O
why	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
if	O
we	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
he	O
'll	O
beat	O
us	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
Will	O
.	O
Stevens	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
her	O
down	O
and	O
trampled	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
been	O
myself	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
laid	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Coldham	O
had	O
opened	O
her	O
;	O
her	O
Side	O
very	O
black	O
and	O
bruised	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Plaister	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
other	O
Parts	O
of	O
her	O
Body	O
was	O
much	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
poor	O
Eye	O
sunk	O
in	O
her	O
head	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
if	O
you	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
falling	O
down	O
Stairs	O
drunk	O
?	O
Whitehead	O
.	O
No	O
never	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
once	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
her	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
put-her	O
Finger	O
and	O
Thumb	O
out	O
of	O
joint	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
on	O
Friday	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
poor	O
Creature	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
hot	O
,	O
with	O
Sugar	O
and	O
Nutmeg	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Fellow	O
has	O
murdered	O
you	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
.	O
Says	O
she	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
long	O
for	O
this	O
World	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
World	O
will	O
see	O
this	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
she	O
died	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Plaister	O
off	O
her	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
free	O
Place	O
from	O
the	O
Crown	O
of	O
her	O
Head	O
to	O
the	O
Sole	O
of	O
her	O
Feet	O
,	O
all	O
black	O
as	O
a	O
Shoe	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stripes	O
in	O
her	O
Fore-head	O
were	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
my	O
little	O
Finger	O
;	O
both	O
Sides	O
were	O
black	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
was	O
blackest	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
Arms	O
whaled	O
as	O
thick	O
as	O
a	O
Cane	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
beat	O
her	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
no	O
Christian	O
Creature	O
could	O
have	O
lived	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
,	O
I	O
says	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Katey	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
Will	O
Stevens	O
was	O
hanging	O
over	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
want	O
something	O
under	O
your	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
her	O
Petticoat	O
behind	O
her	O
Head	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Occasion	O
for	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Fellow	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Play-house	O
Passage	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
Jenny	O
Hill	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
her	O
hands	O
were	O
very	O
cold	O
and	O
she	O
in	O
a	O
clammy	O
Sweat	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
desired	O
Stevens	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
some	O
Small-beer	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Sage	O
Tea	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
help	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
made	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
aired	O
her	O
Sheets	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
to	O
Bed	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
faint	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Hands	O
round	O
my	O
Wast	O
,	O
gritted	O
her	O
Teeth	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
low	O
Voice	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
her	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Plaister	O
on	O
her	O
Right-side	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Body	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
Bruises	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
not	O
in	O
her	O
Senses	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Jenny	O
Hall	O
had	O
bepissed	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
burning	O
.	O
She	O
died	O
with	O
her	O
Head	O
in	O
my	O
Bosom	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Rialton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
sit	O
up	O
there	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
for	O
Stevens	O
had	O
threatned	O
to	O
murder	O
her	O
;	O
this	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Kitty	O
,	O
be	O
persuaded	O
and	O
go	O
home	O
:	O
if	O
I	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
murder	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Will	O
.	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Broom	O
stick	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
her	O
fetch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
out	O
her	O
Finger	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Fool	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
Aye	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
fine	O
talking	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
Fathers	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
get	O
me	O
away	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
threatned	O
to	O
murder	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
enough	O
already	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
one	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Kate	B-pers
Plump	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
full	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
I	O
viewed	O
her	O
Body	O
;	O
her	O
Right-side	O
and	O
Shoulder	O
were	O
very	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
left	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
right	O
Finger	O
and	O
Arm	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
she	O
was	O
waiting	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
for	O
Stevens	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
:	O
He	O
bid	O
her	O
get	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
Blows	O
,	O
not	O
very	O
unmercifull	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
black	O
Eye	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
must	O
abuse	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
Blows	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
hear	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
together	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
Strokes	O
on	O
the	O
Forehead	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
Eye	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
looked	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Dr.	O
Coldham	O
was	O
my	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
for	O
being	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
no	O
,	O
Griffiths	O
,	O
I	O
wont	O
belie	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
against	O
my	O
doing	O
good	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
she	O
fell	O
before	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
Pains	O
were	O
too	O
great	O
to	O
bear	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
occasioned	O
her	O
Pains	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
who	O
laid	O
her	O
out	O
would	O
see	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Coldham	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Church	O
Wardens	O
of	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
Parish	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
I	O
viewed	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
several	O
Bruises	O
on	O
her	O
Arms	O
and	O
Sides	O
;	O
I	O
cut	O
into	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
went	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
Fat	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
mortal	O
.	O
On	O
opening	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Lobes	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
adhered	O
to	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
Lobe	O
was	O
formed	O
a	O
large	O
Ulcer	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Collection	O
of	O
Matter	O
;	O
the	O
Liver	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
parboil	O
'd	O
Complection	O
,	O
and	O
larger	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
the	O
Stomach	O
much	O
diminished	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tone	O
entirely	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
was	O
from	O
a	O
Complication	O
of	O
Disorders	O
occasioned	O
by	O
irregular	O
living	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hicks	O
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
Mr.	O
Coldham	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Opinion	O
.	O
Jane	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
two	O
Days	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
complain	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
never	O
easy	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
Night	O
she	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
murdered	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
giving	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
quiet	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
deposing	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
excessively	O
addicted	O
to	O
drinking	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
that	O
Catherine	O
Skelton	O
died	O
a	O
natural	O
Death	O
.	O
41.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
4	O
Pillowbeers	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
acquitted	O
.	O
42.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
Necklace	O
,	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Coral	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Mops	O
,	O
4	O
Brushes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Master	O
,	O
April	O
27	O
.	O
acquitted	O
.	O
44.	O
William	B-pers
Basset	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
3	O
Pillowbeers	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ursula	B-pers
Upton	I-pers
,	O
March	O
6	O
.	O
acquitted	O
.	O
45.	O
Ann	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Men	O
's	O
Shoes	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
acquitted	O
.	O
46.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Leman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
white	O
Stuff	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
April	O
17	O
.	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
47.	O
Catherine	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Shoes	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
48.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cockran	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Shirt	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Terril	I-pers
;	O
and	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Tollery	I-pers
,	O
January	O
30	O
.	O
acquitted	O
.	O
49.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Diamond	O
Ear-rings	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
3	O
Shirts	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
silver	O
Nossels	O
for	O
Candlesticks	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Moneys	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Challoner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Geary	I-pers
,	O
April	O
16	O
.	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
silver	O
Candlesticks	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
silver	O
Sockets	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
5	O
silver	O
gilt	O
Spoons	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
Damask	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
stitch	O
'd	O
Bed	O
Quilt	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
December	O
31	O
.	O
guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
51.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Toney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Montrose	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
House	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Colebrook	I-pers
,	O
April	O
23	O
.	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
52.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
the	O
Honourable	O
John	B-pers
Cambpel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
commonly	O
call	O
'd	O
Lord	O
Glenorchey	O
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
guilty	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
53.	O
Evan	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cross-cut	O
Saw	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
54.	O
Mary	B-pers
Yardley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Butter	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Wooden	O
half	O
Firkin	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
55.	O
Ann	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Frisket	I-pers
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Key	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Gerier	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
56.	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drugget	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Monday	I-pers
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
57.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Leaden	O
Pipe	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Brass	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
58.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Matteir	I-pers
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
59.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stavel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
a	O
Stone	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
Brass	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Watch-string	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Percival	B-pers
Luttock	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Percival	B-pers
Luttock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
by	O
James	B-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
busy	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
take	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
a	O
gain	O
:	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
feeling	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
Brandy	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
Stairs	O
:	O
The	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
and	O
got	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Friends	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
:	O
Before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Watch	O
at	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
in	O
Tyburn-Road	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
do	O
something	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
to	O
mention	O
;	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
so	O
many	O
Lies	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pyke	I-pers
.	O
The	O
young	O
Man	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Woman	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
this	O
Woman	O
in	O
Tyburn-Road	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Swinney	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barling	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
or	O
sold	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
five	O
Shillings	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
as	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Money	O
first	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
bit	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Times	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
hold	O
the	O
Watch	O
till	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
:	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
60.	O
Matthias	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
two	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chettle	I-pers
.	O
and	O
a	O
Tea-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Lace	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Lydia	B-pers
Dowell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Sedgewich	I-pers
,	O
March	O
11	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Chettle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
lost	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
from	O
Goldsmith's-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Spoons	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Tankard	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hilder	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
Lodging	O
.	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
Drawers	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Tankard	O
and	O
the	O
Lace	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Dowell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Sedgewich	O
:	O
The	O
Things	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
at	O
5	O
a-Clock	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
Servants	O
might	O
find	O
it	O
:	O
About	O
7	O
a-Clock	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Key	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
knew	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
My	O
Felow	O
Servant	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Lock	O
would	O
push	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Remembrance	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Cloaths	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
Questions	O
because	O
as	O
there	O
were	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
going	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Urton	I-pers
.	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
two	O
Spoons	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
seeing	O
a	O
Crest	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
stopt	O
them	O
:	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
Counsellor	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
(	O
Bennet	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
Drury-Lane	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
telling	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
a	O
Guinea	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Bill	O
from	O
Gold-smith's-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
the	O
Money	O
again	O
and	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
my	O
Trouble	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appeared	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fact	O
being	O
clear	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
61.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Pater-noster	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silk	O
Gowns	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
eighteen	O
Pair	O
of	O
Men	O
's	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Pair	O
of	O
Womans	O
ditto	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
January	O
2	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Lawson	O
.	O
Rents	O
being	O
high	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
Room	O
,	O
am	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
lay	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
upon	O
Shelves	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
:	O
The	O
Gloves	O
are	O
Goods	O
I	O
sell	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
:	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
coming	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Farthing	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Candle	O
on	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
blown	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
about	O
30	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Nathan	B-pers
Cokran	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Black	O
boy	O
Alley	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
the	O
Evening	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
Kate	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
came	O
to	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
some	O
check	O
'd	O
Linnen	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Arms	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
long	O
enough	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
alongg	O
we	O
saw	O
this	O
Shop	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Farthing	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
waited	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
'till	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
backward	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
blew	O
out	O
the	O
Candle	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Bundles	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
more	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
an	O
odd	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
30	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
Sheets	O
to	O
Whitehead	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
wanted	O
Sheets	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
allowed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
her	O
Share	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cockran	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
Kate	O
's	O
Room	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
my	O
Husband	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Business	O
with	O
that	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
one	O
Cambrick	O
laced	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gabb	I-pers
;	O
and	O
fourteen	O
Yards	O
of	O
Burdet	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
and	O
a	O
Cloath	O
short	O
Cloak	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
January	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
62	O
,	O
63.	O
John	B-pers
Talton	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bully	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
Colt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
26	O
.	O
Talton	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
myself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
before	O
Justice	O
Joyner	O
,	O
concerning	O
these	O
Horses	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
of	O
an	O
Information	O
at	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
wanted	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
Evidence	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
an	O
old	O
black	O
Golding	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
Colt	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Farm	O
Yard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Penn	B-place
in	I-place
Buckinghamshire	I-place
:	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
till	O
Yesterday	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Biddlecomb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
old'Black	O
Horse	O
of	O
Talton	O
at	O
the	O
Blazing-Star	O
in	O
Old-Street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Still	I-pers
;	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Horse	O
now	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
wantted	O
one	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
a	O
Mill	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
taking	O
to	O
the	O
Work	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
him	O
again	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
Owner	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
Horses	O
at	O
the	O
Blazing-Star	O
:	O
Talton	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
unwilling	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
the	O
Colt	O
.	O
Biddlecomb	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
a	O
Bargain	O
for	O
the	O
old	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Talton	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
a	O
Halter	O
on	O
him	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
cheapened	O
the	O
Horses	O
of	O
Talton	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
7	O
Guineas	O
for	O
the	O
Colt	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
Guineas	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Blazing-Star	O
,	O
Feb.	O
26	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
Horses	O
that	O
Page	O
owne	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Knight	O
.	O
The	O
Horses	O
being	O
lost	O
from	O
Penn	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Page	O
to	O
advertise	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
printed	O
500	O
Bills	O
,	O
and	O
distributed	O
them	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
and	O
proper	O
Placs	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Notice	O
that	O
the	O
old	O
Horse	O
had	O
been	O
put	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Blazing-Star	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
view	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
Oath	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
believed	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
Page	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
had	O
Information	O
that	O
the	O
Colt	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
at	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
keeps	O
the	O
Pound	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
at	O
the	O
Blazing-Star	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
Horse	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
House	O
who	O
bought	O
him	O
,	O
next	O
Door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
Blazing-Star	O
.	O
Having	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Countess	O
of	O
Harold	O
's	O
Turkeys	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
down	O
to	O
Justice	O
Chandler	O
about	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Horses	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
Talton	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
Examination	O
,	O
Bully	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Talton	O
made	O
a	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
read	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
sign	O
it	O
.	O
Read	O
the	O
Confession	O
.	O
The	O
Information	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Talton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Reading	O
in	O
Berkshire	O
,	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
taken	O
on	O
Oath	O
this	O
Day	O
before	O
me	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
.	O
Who	O
saith	O
,	O
'That	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bully	I-pers
was	O
concerned	O
'	O
with	O
this	O
Informant	O
and	O
Leonarnd	O
Talton	O
,	O
'	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
Horse	O
and	O
a	O
Colt	O
at	O
Penn	O
in	O
'	O
Buckinghamshire	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
.	O
'	O
Talton	O
gave	O
a	O
long	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
nothing	O
Material	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
Talton	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Bully	O
acquitted	O
.	O
64.	O
Robert	B-pers
Keeble	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Tibley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Border	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carwell	I-pers
,	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
65.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Pyle	I-pers
,	O
May	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
66.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Cloth	O
Cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
March	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
67.	O
Moses	B-pers
Gladwin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dobey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
Shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
Ribbons	O
:	O
I	O
shewed	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
would	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
Handkerchiefs	O
:	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
a	O
Dozen	O
that	O
were	O
just	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
clap	O
three	O
Lustring	O
ones	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
great	O
Coats	O
on	O
,	O
besides	O
his	O
Wastcoat	O
:	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
;	O
why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
I	O
would	O
steal	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
reaching	O
over	O
the	O
Computer	O
,	O
I	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
dropt	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
:	O
His	O
Companion	O
immediately	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Handkerchiefs	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
?	O
Dobey	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
his	O
Companion	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Face	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
three	O
odd	O
ones	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Elsteb	I-pers
.	O
While	O
my	O
Fellow-Servant	O
was	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Handkerchiefs	O
drop	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Great	O
Coat	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
stand	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
this	O
?	O
Elstob	O
.	O
By	O
your	O
side	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Hark	O
'	O
e	O
,	O
my	O
Boy	O
,	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
grudge	O
going	O
to	O
Hell	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
swear	O
so	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
they	O
valued	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
30	O
s	O
and	O
now	O
they	O
value	O
them	O
at	O
40	O
s.	O
which	O
shews	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
malicious	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
after	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
Things	O
they	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
68	O
,	O
69.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ellard	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Exton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
six	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
two	O
Dimitty	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
Quilted	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
March	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Exton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
Door	O
latched	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
wash	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
was	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gold	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
.	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
,	O
March	O
4.	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
my	O
Fire-side	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
out-cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Angel-Alley	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
:	O
On	O
hearing	O
the	O
Noise	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Woman	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
calling	O
him	O
Rogue	O
and	O
Thief	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
up	O
comes	O
Ellard	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
Freeman	O
,	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
punch	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Guts	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Caddet	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
:	O
Ellard	O
would	O
get	O
in	O
between	O
Freeman	O
and	O
me	O
:	O
Says	O
Freeman	O
,	O
you	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Bundle	O
;	O
then	O
Ellard	O
took	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
tript	O
up	O
Freeman	O
's	O
Heels	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
sprung	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
he	O
ran	O
:	O
Ellard	O
ran	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
Caddet	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
.	O
With	O
much	O
Trouble	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
assist	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
Freeman	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
that	O
Day	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
perfectly	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
on	O
Freeman	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
on	O
Ellard	O
.	O
Exton	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Caddet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Haines	O
has	O
given	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
Freeman	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
black	O
Wig	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Ellard	O
,	O
the	O
Butcher	O
,	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
Washerwoman	O
in	O
Crutched	B-place
Fryars	I-place
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
.	O
Bollinbrook	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
try	O
'd	O
here	O
before	O
,	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
.	O
Freeman	O
.	O
How	O
she	O
talks	O
of	O
my	O
Wife	O
?	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
married	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
over	O
the	O
Water	O
for	O
some	O
Silk	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Weaver	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
Home	O
about	O
11	O
a-Clock	O
by	O
St.	O
Helen	O
's	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
a	O
Turning	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
Occasions	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
kick	O
'd	O
against	O
this	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Ellard	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
prove	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Butchers-Arms	O
in	O
Spittle-Fields	O
Market	O
fron	O
4	O
to	O
11	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
At	O
11	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Angel-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
Kit	O
.	O
Freeman	O
beating	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
hold	O
the	O
Bundle	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dan	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kimbell	I-pers
,	O
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Kimbell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Wint	I-pers
,	O
positively	O
swore	O
that	O
Ellard	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Butchers-Arms	O
from	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
till	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
spoke	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
was	O
called	O
by	O
Freeman	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
good	O
Account	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Freeman	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Ellard	O
acquitted	O
.	O
70.	O
John	B-pers
Maccoon	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Maccools	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Birchman	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
driving	O
two	O
Horses	O
drawing	O
a	O
certain	O
Cart	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Maccoon	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
near	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Cart	O
so	O
drawn	O
,	O
to	O
and	O
against	O
a	O
certain	O
Wheelbarrow	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
said	O
Birchman	O
stood	O
between	O
the	O
Handles	O
,	O
did	O
drive	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Wheelbarrow	O
did	O
cast	O
down	O
;	O
by	O
Reason	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Brichman	O
was	O
cast	O
and	O
thrown	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Maccoon	O
so	O
driving	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Birchman	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
and	O
Bruise	O
did	O
give	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murder	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ridley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Accident	O
this	O
very	O
Day	O
three	O
Weeks	O
.	O
The	O
Cart	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
to	O
prevent	O
its	O
being	O
run	O
over	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Wheelbarrow	O
stood	O
between	O
the	O
Posts	O
,	O
the	O
Handles	O
toward	O
one	O
Post	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Barrow	O
toward	O
another	O
:	O
The	O
Cart	O
came	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
Posts	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
just	O
Time	O
to	O
clap	O
the	O
Child	O
between	O
the	O
Handles	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
save	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Cart	O
run	O
so	O
near	O
the	O
Posts	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Barrow	O
was	O
overturn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
with	O
its	O
Head	O
under	O
the	O
Wheel	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Skull	O
crack	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Wheel	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
quite	O
over	O
it	O
;	O
It	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Kindall	I-pers
.	O
As	O
the	O
Cart	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
towards	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Prince's-Street	O
asked	O
the	O
Carman	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Jobb	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
to	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
Cart	O
go	O
on	O
by	O
it	O
self	O
.	O
The	O
Wheelbarrow	O
stood	O
between	O
the	O
Posts	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
two	O
thirds	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
beyond	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Cart-way	O
.	O
The	O
Mother	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
my	O
Child	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
young	O
Child	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
met	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
do	O
not	O
be	O
frighted	O
!	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
Child	O
is	O
kill	O
'd	O
!	O
they	O
had	O
set	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
Threshold	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
its	O
poor	O
Jaws	O
fell	O
in	O
my	O
Arms	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
71.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Broadfield	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Bradford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cotton	O
Check	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Bence	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
72.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Hugh	B-pers
Evanson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
March	O
8	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Evanson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
Bloomsbury	B-place
and	O
Castle-Street	B-place
,	O
by	O
2	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-brokers	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
stop	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baxter	O
,	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Woman	O
near	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
73	O
,	O
74	O
,	O
75	O
,	O
76	O
,	O
77.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Malden	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Morgan	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Holbert	I-pers
and	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
;	O
8	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
;	O
3	O
Check	O
Aprons	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hilder	I-pers
,	O
Check	O
Aprons	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Seal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
1	O
Shirt	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
February	O
29	O
.	O
And	O
Mary	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
1	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
I	O
Mary	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
last	O
Day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
dead	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Washer-woman	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
I	O
bolted	O
my	O
Doors	O
and	O
Windows	O
fast	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
wrenched	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pins	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
key	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
cut	O
the	O
Shutter	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Casement	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
washed	O
them	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
must	O
be	O
all	O
wet	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
these	O
People	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Malden	I-pers
came	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
to	O
walk	O
several	O
times	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
,	O
viewing	O
(	O
I	O
suppose	O
)	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
Warrant	O
I	O
searched	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
at	O
Holloway	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
Holbert	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Malden	I-pers
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
