TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1735-6.	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
WILLIAMS	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1735-6	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XXXV	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLIAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
Reynolds	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lee	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Lluellin	I-pers
,	O
Joel	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Vezey	B-pers
Hastlefoot	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Shuckburgh	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tiller	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gillmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hawksworth	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Maccartney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
Steel	O
Hilt	O
,	O
inlaid	O
with	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Bennet	B-pers
Swain	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
6	O
.	O
Bennet	B-pers
Swain	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
Crowd	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
twitching	O
at	O
my	O
Side	O
;	O
I	O
clapt	O
my	O
Hand	O
on	O
my	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Sword	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
taken	O
in	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
dodging	O
between	O
the	O
Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bricklayer	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
thro	O
'	O
Castle-Alley	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
something	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
Alehouse	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Janeway	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Cry	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
Back-door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
past	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
something	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
into	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
as	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
View	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Sword	O
,	O
4	O
Steps	O
from	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Church	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
Custody	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
Bailiffs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
he	O
gave	O
for	O
his	O
running	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
,	O
hearing	O
the	O
Cry	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
run	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
ran	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
were	O
pursuing	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bragg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
running	O
in	O
Bartholomew-Lane	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
saw	O
what	O
the	O
Matter	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
Sword	O
being	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Swain	O
declared	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
that	O
was	O
Material	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Martha	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchres	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pound	O
of	O
Starch	O
8	O
d.	O
-	O
2	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
value	O
9s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
-	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Nutmegs	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
-	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Cloves	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
-	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Mace	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
-	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Green	O
Tea	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
-	O
half	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Bohea-Tea	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cromwell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Cromwell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
some	O
Goods	O
in	O
my	O
Way	O
,	O
were	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
this	O
Mrs.	O
Bee	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Stanley	O
lodges	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Goods	O
at	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Bees	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
Stanley	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
Information	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Bee	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stanley	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
one	O
Day	O
brought	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
However	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
signifies	O
it	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Nutmegs	O
,	O
Tea	O
,	O
Sugar	O
,	O
Cloves	O
,	O
Mace	O
,	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
Starch	O
,	O
Blue	O
,	O
Fig-blue	O
,	O
Powder-blue	O
:	O
The	O
Bundle	O
was	O
as	O
thick	O
as	O
a	O
little	O
Child	O
:	O
As	O
for	O
the	O
Quantities	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Things	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
thinking	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
stoln	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
so	O
silly	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
no	O
Questions	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
say	O
afterwards	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
by	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
-	O
some	O
at	O
one	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
never	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Cromwell	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cromwell	O
to	O
New	O
.	O
Prison	O
,	O
on	O
Christmas-Day	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Men	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Supper	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
those	O
Opportunities	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Cromwell	O
's	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
consequently	O
must	O
have	O
such	O
Things	O
in	O
her	O
Custody	O
as	O
were	O
necessary	O
for	O
Pickling	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
perhaps	O
she	O
might	O
take	O
a	O
Nutmeg	O
or	O
some	O
Spice	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
for	O
that	O
Purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Charles	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
East-cheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
11s	O
.	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
4	O
Stocks	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
8	O
d.	O
2	O
Night-caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
January	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Grant	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
received	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
4	O
Stocks	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Night-caps	O
,	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
as	O
this	O
Man	O
came	O
begging	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
They	O
lay	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
engaged	O
in	O
Business	O
with	O
my	O
Back	O
to	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
advanced	O
almost	O
within	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
very	O
watchful	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
mistaken	O
as	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Minutes	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
the	O
Servants	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Upon	O
enquiry	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
imagined	O
that	O
this	O
Man	O
must	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shirts	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
resign	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
Excuse	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
and	O
had	O
forgot	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
else	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
came	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
this	O
Shirt	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Will	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
natur	O
'd	O
Manner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4	O
,	O
5.	O
Ann	B-pers
Collard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
White	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Silver	O
3	O
pronged	O
Forks	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Kendrick	B-pers
Edisbury	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
January	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Joan	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
We	O
had	O
the	O
Spoons	O
and	O
the	O
Forks	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
of	O
January	O
after	O
3	O
of	O
the	O
Clock	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Scullery	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
at	O
ten	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
'till	O
now	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gager	I-pers
.	O
He	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
with	O
Relation	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
nothing	O
that	O
effected	O
them	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Newshum	I-pers
.	O
These	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
to	O
be	O
valu	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Wife	O
seeing	O
the	O
Crest	O
rubb	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
White	O
pretended	O
most	O
Claim	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Collard	O
said	O
nothing	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
the	O
Marks	O
being	O
taken	O
out	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
White	O
that	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
3	O
Letters	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
White	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
the	O
right	O
Owner	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
Moor-lane	O
.	O
Defence	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Market	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
Collard	O
's	O
Husband	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
Spoons	O
and	O
Forks	O
to	O
borrow	O
Money	O
upon	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
pretend	O
to	O
borrow	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Nan	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
kick	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
Gentlemans	O
in	O
Barbican	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
valued	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
Money	O
to	O
be	O
lent	O
upon	O
them	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
.	O
Very	O
well	O
Dame	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
backwards	O
.	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
Nan	O
,	O
wo	O
n't	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
weigh	O
'em	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
two	O
Ounce	O
Weight	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
must	O
stay	O
'till	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
talked	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
must	O
stop	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
Man	O
we	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
to	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
to	O
her	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
'till	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
us	O
up	O
.	O
We	O
neither	O
of	O
us	O
fled	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
White	O
call	O
'd	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
in	O
her	O
Behalf	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
and	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
.	O
Collard	O
's	O
Defence	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
brought	O
these	O
Things	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
all	O
they	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
never	O
since	O
been	O
heard	O
of	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Rainbow	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Panton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
gave	O
Collard	O
the	O
general	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
6	O
,	O
7.	O
Richard	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Beshaw	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Dye	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Iron	O
Crows	O
,	O
value	O
7s	O
.	O
54	O
House-lines	O
.	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
45	O
Strands	O
for	O
Hand-lines	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
Pounds	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Hemp	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	I-pers
Senr	I-pers
.	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	I-pers
Junr	I-pers
.	O
December	O
23	O
d	O
.	O
Richard	O
Baker	O
,	O
Senr	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
a	O
Ware-house	O
which	O
belongs	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Son	O
;	O
we	O
make	O
Lines	O
and	O
Twine	O
in	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Iron	O
Crows	O
,	O
we	O
stick	O
into	O
the	O
Ground	O
to	O
fasten	O
our	O
Lines	O
to	O
.	O
All	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
is	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
24th	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
which	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Iron	O
Crows	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
Lines	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
might	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
willing	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
should	O
have	O
found	O
the	O
Bill	O
against	O
the	O
Persons	O
where	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
We	O
miss	O
'd	O
our	O
Goods	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
'till	O
some	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Charnock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
Dun	O
,	O
Beshaw	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
from	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
in	O
Winford	O
street	O
that	O
Night	O
:	O
Says	O
Dun	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
round	O
Ratcliff-high-way	O
;	O
the	O
back	O
Yards	O
there	O
are	O
good	O
Places	O
to	O
get	O
wet	O
Linnen	O
from	O
:	O
We	O
went	O
round	O
Ratcliff-high-way	B-place
,	O
cross	O
'd	O
Sun-tavern-fields	B-place
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
's	O
Shed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Place	O
is	O
this	O
Shed	O
?	O
Richard	O
Baker	O
Junr	O
,	O
'T	O
is	O
built	O
as	O
strong	O
as	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
could	O
build	O
it	O
:	O
We	O
have	O
abundance	O
of	O
Goods	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
use	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
Ware-house	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
Work-house	O
.	O
Charnock	O
.	O
We	O
propos	O
'd	O
getting	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
's	O
Shed	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Iron	O
Bolts	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
Beshaw	O
took	O
a	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
2	O
Iron	O
Crows	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Beshaw	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Shed	O
Door	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
2	O
Crows	O
out	O
to	O
Beshaw	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Beshaw	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Dun	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stood	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
Shakesby	O
's	O
Walks	O
,	O
while	O
Beshaw	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
more	O
Bolts	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
Balls	O
of	O
Line	O
in	O
the	O
Shed	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
Hand-Line	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
House-Line	O
,	O
and	O
thirteen	O
Pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Hemp	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
together	O
;	O
Beshaw	O
carried	O
one	O
Bottom	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
other	O
and	O
the	O
Hemp	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
in	O
Hare	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Dun	O
and	O
Beshaw	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Bolts	O
,	O
(	O
Iron	O
Crows	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
knocked	O
my	O
Mother	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Yard	O
,	O
dug	O
a	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
buried	O
one	O
Bottom	O
of	O
Line	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Bottom	O
,	O
in	O
single	O
Lines	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
spare	O
Time	O
.	O
Beshaw	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
call	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Brandy-shop	O
?	O
Charnock	O
,	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
have	O
done	O
many	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
meet	O
with	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
,	O
jun	O
.	O
The	O
Crow	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
the	O
unfinished	O
Lines	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
two	O
Men	O
here	O
who	O
made	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
will	O
swear	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
Property	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
Charnock	O
were	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Philips	O
.	O
Charnock	O
begg	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
(	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
years	O
ago	O
)	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Knowlon	I-pers
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
on	O
Christmas-Eve	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
our	O
Work	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Shed	O
robb	O
'd	O
:	O
We	O
made	O
Holiday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
two	O
Mates	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
Discovery	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Hemp	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
Shakesby	O
's	O
Walks	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
where	O
we	O
suspected	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
we	O
met	O
,	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
our	O
Master	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
Things	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
at	O
Bigg	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
a	O
Cask-Head	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Skains	O
of	O
House-Lines	O
in	O
Bigg	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
:	O
Whereof	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
desired	O
Biggs	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
up	O
Brick-Lane	O
we	O
met	O
Charnock	O
.	O
Whom	O
we	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Penn'orth	O
of	O
Gin	O
together	O
,	O
whereof	O
we	O
turned	O
up	O
to	O
Bigg	O
's	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
desired	O
Biggs	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
brought	O
those	O
Lines	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Business	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Mates	O
there	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
stept	O
down	O
to	O
Justice	O
Philips	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
word	O
was	O
brought	O
down	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
Lines	O
was	O
in	O
Bigg	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
he	O
(	O
Charnock	O
)	O
was	O
brought	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
Bolts	O
we	O
should	O
find	O
at	O
Webb	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
against	O
Spittle-fields	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Lines	O
were	O
at	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
was	O
dug	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lines	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
whereof	O
we	O
searching	O
farther	O
found	O
a	O
Ball	O
of	O
Line	O
buried	O
at	O
their	O
Vault-door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Line	O
was	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Hemp	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
best	O
had	O
been	O
spun	O
up	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Osgood	I-pers
.	O
Gave	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
as	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
Charnock	O
's	O
Information	O
that	O
Dun	O
and	O
Beshaw	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
to	O
Justice	O
Philips	O
.	O
Dun	O
confess	O
'd	O
himself	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Shed	O
;	O
and	O
Beshaw	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Shed	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
Charnock	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
retired	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
having	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Beshaw	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Pierre	B-pers
le	I-pers
Blanc	I-pers
in	O
an	O
open	O
Place	O
(	O
called	O
Buttermilk-Alley	B-place
)	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Jonneau	O
was	O
sworn	O
his	O
Interpreter	O
.	O
Pierre	O
le	O
Blanc	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
five	O
Weeks	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
thro	O
'	O
Butter-milk-Alley	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Hat	O
taken	O
away	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
running	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
they	O
came	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Charnock	I-pers
.	O
Robinson	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
Beshaw	O
and	O
Tame	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Brandy-shop	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
't	O
is	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
)	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Hat	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Liquor	O
;	O
Beshaw	O
went	O
about	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
,	O
to	O
Pick	O
Pockets	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
get	O
nothing	O
;	O
D	O
-	O
m	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
Beshaw	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
go	O
into	O
Spittle	O
fields	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
many	O
an	O
old	O
Frenchman	O
's	O
Hat	O
:	O
We	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
down	O
Buttermilk-Alley	O
,	O
Beshaw	O
took	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
D-m	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
his	O
Hat	O
;	O
then	O
Will	O
Tame	O
went	O
thro	O
'	O
an	O
Alley	O
into	O
Phoenix	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
former	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Hat	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
2s	O
.	O
-	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
Charnock	O
and	O
himself	O
had	O
not	O
an	O
equal	O
Share	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
met	O
them	O
again	O
that	O
Night	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
Robinson	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
;	O
they	O
knew	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
before	O
Justice	O
Philips	O
,	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
Hat	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
and	O
Buttermilk-Alley	O
both	O
in	O
one	O
Night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turford	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
Robinson	O
's	O
owning	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
.	O
Justice	O
Philips	O
.	O
Robinson	O
owned	O
this	O
Fact	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Michael	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Wroth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hornsey	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Gillow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
6	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gillow	I-pers
;	O
1	O
Silver	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
,	O
value	O
20s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
and	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Francis	O
Gillow	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
these	O
6	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Candle-stick	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Highgate	B-place
.	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Gonson	I-pers
in	O
Gray's-Inn	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
Things	O
in	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
Goodmorrow	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
spend	O
a	O
Penny	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
.	O
There	O
is	O
my	O
Name	O
on	O
the	O
Tobacco-Box	O
;	O
Mr	O
Gillow	O
is	O
a	O
Brewer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Clerk	O
.	O
My	O
Box	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Scrutore	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Gillow	O
's	O
Parlour	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
the	O
Robbery	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Scrutore	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
on	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Presence	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
detected	O
him	O
was	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
Rogue	O
as	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
together	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wetherhead	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
3s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Alexander	O
Smith	O
.	O
Coming	O
out	O
of	O
Good-men's-Fields	B-place
Play-House	I-place
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
Assistants	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
me	O
violently	O
on	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
clapt	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
Money	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Purse	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
with	O
12	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
5	O
Moidore	O
Piece	O
;	O
he	O
try	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
seized	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
cryed	O
out	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Huddy	O
's	O
Tavern	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
him	O
stripp	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
Watch	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
Clothes	O
on	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
retaken	O
presently	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Huddy	I-pers
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Smith	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
into	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
(	O
assisted	O
by	O
his	O
Friend	O
)	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
They	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
usual	O
for	O
these	O
Fellows	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
what	O
they	O
steal	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
way	O
,	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
3	O
Men	O
searched	O
,	O
who	O
followed	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchin	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
slipp	O
'd	O
off	O
.	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
cape	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
Pity	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
he	O
changed	O
his	O
Note	O
-	O
And	O
said	O
who	O
dared	O
detain	O
him	O
without	O
a	O
Peace	O
Officer	O
?	O
-	O
And	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
about	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
desperate	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
detained	O
him	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
sometimes	O
plies	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Watch	O
:	O
The	O
Captain	O
described	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Place	O
were	O
the	O
Fellow	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
answers	O
to	O
the	O
Account	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
gave	O
of	O
his	O
losing	O
it	O
.	O
Kemp	B-pers
Outoloni	I-pers
,	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Play-House	O
,	O
and	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Heatly	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Play-house	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
Out-cry	O
,	O
-	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
I	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
with	O
a	O
lighted	O
Link	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
full	O
Stop	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Huddy	O
's	O
Drawer	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
.	O
and	O
returning	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Play-house	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Play-house-Door	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
Watch	O
,	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Huddy	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Nothing	O
material	O
being	O
offered	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10	O
11.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
Jordan	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Sparkes	I-pers
,	O
January	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
8th	O
Year	O
of	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
:	O
And	O
Elizabeth	O
Bowen	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Mary	O
Sparkes	O
.	O
About	O
12	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Jordan	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
my	O
Aunts	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Draws	O
.	O
I	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
:	O
So	O
I	O
troubled	O
my	O
Head	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
'till	O
I	O
accidentally	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Bowen	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
12	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
prove	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
suffer	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Jordan	O
,	O
and	O
Bowen	O
produced	O
a	O
different	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
saw	O
first	O
.	O
Jordan	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
Bowen	O
,	O
for	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
1s	O
.	O
8d	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
it	O
while	O
Jordan	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Sparkes	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Sparkes	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
'till	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Warrant	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	O
Barret	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Sparkes	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Bowen	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
right	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
produced	O
another	O
.	O
Jordan	O
owned	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
Bowen	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
a	O
Gown	O
.	O
Rachel	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Jordan	O
tell	O
Bowen	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
Bowen	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
appearing	O
to	O
Bowen	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
Jordan	O
found	O
Guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bulker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gwillim	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gwillim	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
(	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Pointer	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
robbing	O
George	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Cloath	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Gwillin	O
.	O
On	O
New	O
Year	O
's	O
Day	O
at	O
Night	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
Halfway-house	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Star-light	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
a	O
Clock	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
above	O
ten	O
Yards	O
beyond	O
the	O
Halfway-house	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
You	O
are	O
soon	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Club	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Club	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
wrenched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
twice	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
tumbled	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
Wig	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
18d	O
.	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Wig	O
cost	O
me	O
3l	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
strip	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
hit	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
stripped	O
me	O
naked	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
nothing	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Stockings	O
and	O
Garters	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
3	O
Fields	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
in	O
this	O
Condition	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
no	O
one	O
but	O
an	O
Oyster-man	O
,	O
who	O
sprung	O
with	O
Surprize	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
walked	O
over	O
some	O
Fields	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
my	O
Breeches	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Grey	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
seated	O
;	O
my	O
Knee	O
Buckels	O
were	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
two	O
odd	O
Mettal	O
Buckels	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
Pipe-picker	O
in	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
this	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Breeches	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
with	O
my	O
Breeches	O
;	O
the	O
Things	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
frequented	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
in	O
Love-Lane	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
End	O
of	O
Old-Gravel-Lane	O
.	O
On	O
New-Year's-Day	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
new	O
pair	O
of	O
Trowsers	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
rolled	O
up	O
about	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Rope	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
about	O
his	O
Wast	O
pretty	O
tight	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
tucked	O
his	O
Hair	O
under	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Tom	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
this	O
very	O
Night	O
either	O
to	O
win	O
the	O
Saddle	O
,	O
or	O
lose	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Bird's-Ey	O
'd	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
;	O
a	O
white	O
Coat	O
with	O
open	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
flowered	O
Wast-Coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Grey	O
Breeches	O
,	O
with	O
Knee	O
Buckels	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Notice	O
enough	O
of	O
the	O
Breeches	O
and	O
Knee	O
Buckels	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
again	O
:	O
(	O
Then	O
they	O
were	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
to	O
these	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
these	O
Buckels	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
Shirt	O
,	O
pieced	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
Flap	O
.	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
Tom	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
these	O
Cloaths	O
?	O
't	O
is	O
pity	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
charged	O
with	O
an	O
Officer	O
:	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Blood	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
of	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
sha	O
n't	O
tell	O
who	O
did	O
your	O
Business	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Gwillim	O
.	O
A	O
whitish	O
Coat	O
and	O
black	O
flowered	O
Calamanco	O
Wastcoat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Badger	I-pers
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
only	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lilly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
likewise	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
Breeches	O
and	O
Buckles	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
odd	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
White	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Yellow	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Pockets	O
this	O
Pipe-picker	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
You	O
Rogue	O
,	O
says	O
Mr.	O
Gwillim	O
,	O
this	O
confutes	O
you	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Farmer	O
bid	O
him	O
pull	O
off	O
the	O
Breeches	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
to	O
put	O
ou	O
?	O
No	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
without	O
you	O
'll	O
let	O
me	O
send	O
for	O
my	O
Trowsers	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Clemency	O
Sutton	O
to	O
prove	O
his	O
buying	O
the	O
Breeches	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
;	O
but	O
no	O
one	O
appearing	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
one	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
as	O
above	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Fd	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
from	O
Work	O
at	O
Lime-house-Hole	O
,	O
December	O
30	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
thro	O
'	O
Stepney	B-place
;	O
my	O
Mother	O
lives	O
near	O
the	O
Half-way-house	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
called	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Men	O
talking	O
at	O
Torkington	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
Corner	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
run	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Corner	O
to	O
get	O
there	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Posts	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
White-Chappel	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
readiest	O
Way	O
.	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Ragg-Fair	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
Way	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Stepney	O
:	O
He	O
kept	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
Blows	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
Blow	O
brought	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
holding	O
his	O
Stick	O
a	O
cross	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
labouring	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
to	O
have	O
dropped	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
8	O
d.	O
from	O
me	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Boot	O
sleeve	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Waistcoat	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
leave	O
him	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
pull	O
off	O
my	O
Breeches	O
.	O
then	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
pull	O
off	O
my	O
Shirt	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
for	O
nothing	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
insisted	O
on	O
having	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Shoes	O
too	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
begged	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
me	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Knock	O
or	O
two	O
over	O
the	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
run	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
turn	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
shoot	O
me	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
School	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
had	O
not	O
his	O
Hat	O
been	O
flapped	O
over	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
till	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
Tap	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
Nick-Name	O
(	O
Joaney	O
)	O
I	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
mind	O
now	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
appeared	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
nothing	O
material	O
to	O
say	O
He	O
was	O
one	O
who	O
assisted	O
in	O
takeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
13	O
Simon	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Liberty	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leaden	O
Glue-pot	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
,	O
December	O
17	O
.	O
Eades	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Glew	O
.	O
pot	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Leaf	O
of	O
a	O
Table	O
to	O
glue	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
that	O
works	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
borrow	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
only	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
this	O
purpose	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shop	O
is	O
in	O
Smock-Alley	B-place
,	I-place
Petticoat-Lane	I-place
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
14.	O
George	B-pers
Fairclough	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stratford-Bow	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Hens	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Jaggar	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
caught	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Fowls	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15	O
,	O
16.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
Eliz	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
Iron	O
Pinns	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Suannah	B-pers
Wadcock	I-pers
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Satchwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
rent	O
the	O
Tenter-Grounds	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
several	O
Pinns	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
my	O
Man	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
Clark	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Wroth	O
;	O
they	O
confess	O
'd	O
and	O
signed	O
their	O
Confession	O
in	O
my	O
Presence	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Luke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
Clark	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Holmes	O
,	O
but	O
from	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
Clark	O
guilty	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
acquitted	O
Holmes	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Pearl	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Clogs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Mob	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Having	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
we	O
enquired	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Coat	O
at	O
the	O
Black-dog	O
in	O
Long-alley	O
;	O
we	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
a	O
Green	O
Grocer	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Caffoy	O
Seat	O
for	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Calamanco	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Edw	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
.	O
Our	O
Chair	O
was	O
robbed	O
at	O
the	O
Cardigan-Head	B-place
Tavern	I-place
Door	O
.	O
One	O
Brown	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
this	O
Woman	O
near	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
denied	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Search-warrant	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
my	O
Partner	O
.	O
Ant.Ivory	O
.	O
We	O
reat	O
the	O
Chair	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
.	O
My	O
Partner	O
being	O
gone	O
for	O
a	O
Search-warrant	O
,	O
she	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ditchbourn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Hatt	O
,	O
laced	O
with	O
Silver	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
-	O
and	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
Wm	O
.	O
Mason	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
:	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
-	O
Glayton	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
Stockings	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
-	O
She	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
(	O
committed	O
)	O
us	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Robert	B-pers
Willkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St	I-place
Katherines	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Wm	O
.	O
Walters	O
.	O
His	O
Father	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Closet	O
and	O
get	O
some	O
Victuals	O
if	O
he	O
pleased	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
eaten	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
Excuse	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
his	O
Mother	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
missed	O
the	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Father	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
Search	O
of	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Rogue	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
Spoon	O
for	O
5	O
Shillings	O
.	O
His	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Bernard	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22	O
Sarah	B-pers
Matts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Bick	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
1	O
Iron	O
Jack	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Job	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Job	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Evening	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Bick-iron	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
turned	O
him	O
away	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
Information	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
Jack	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
work	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hilder	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Toucher	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Bick-Iron	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Pound	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Jack	O
and	O
borrowed	O
2	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d.	O
24.	O
Charles	B-pers
Francus	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Woman	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fithian	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Fithian	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
my	O
Shoes	O
which	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
were	O
given	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Mobb	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Feezer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Kennel	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Branson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
Standbank	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
14	O
.	O
Wm	O
.	O
Standbank	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
blind	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
Small-coal	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
my	O
House-keeper	O
to	O
lay	O
up	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Times	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Branson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Standbank	O
's	O
House-keeper	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
Creature	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
did	O
a	O
Jobb	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
14th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
wrapped	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hilder	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
blue	O
Apron	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Husband	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
slipped	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
haste	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Apron	O
to	O
tye	O
about	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
Brass	O
Hilt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Scabbard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Henry	O
Anderson	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
Push	O
against	O
my	O
Hip	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
Sword	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
:	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Blows	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
let	O
it	O
go	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
swore	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dodds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
(	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Putt	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Hatt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Wilson	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Putt	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
from	O
the	O
shovel	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
in	O
New	B-place
Rag-Fair	I-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
a	O
single	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
clapped	O
a	O
Pistol	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
)	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
ye	O
,	O
Stand	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Hammer	O
,	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Friend	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
Three	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Man	O
,	O
to	O
assist	O
my	O
Friend	O
.	O
I	O
struck	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
twice	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
my	O
Hatt	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
swears	O
is	O
false	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Putt	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
mortal	O
dark	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
bid	O
Putt	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
two	O
Men	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
sad	O
Blow	O
.	O
Putt	O
,	O
Putt	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
3	O
Men	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Hatt	O
and	O
this	O
Cap	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
Friends	O
Hatt	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
that	O
Hatt	O
's	O
coming	O
to	O
light	O
that	O
has	O
brought	O
us	O
to	O
this	O
Trouble	O
.	O
Nan	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
.	O
December	O
27	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Sprats	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ingram	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
Tommy	B-pers
Dodds	I-pers
was	O
there	O
with	O
Jemmy	O
Bailey	O
-	O
't	O
is	O
in	O
Well	O
street	O
-	O
and	O
two	O
young	O
Women	O
were	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Aunt	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
Pot-full	O
of	O
Sprats	O
to	O
boil	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
eaten	O
the	O
Sprats	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
Women	O
wanted	O
a	O
Dram	O
.	O
Jemmy	O
Baily	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
nor	O
Dodds	O
neither	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
young	O
Women	O
gave	O
me	O
Three-half-pence	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
Gin	O
after	O
our	O
Sprats	O
:	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Ingram	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
Gin	O
come	O
there	O
,	O
nor	O
let	O
them	O
sing	O
a	O
Song	O
.	O
So	O
Jemmy	O
Baily	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Dodds	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
young	O
Women	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Distiller	O
's	O
and	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
;	O
we	O
paid	O
Three-halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
scor	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
Three-half	O
pence	O
.	O
We	O
stayed	O
there	O
till	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
Women	O
would	O
stay	O
no	O
longer	O
;	O
so	O
Dodds	O
,	O
and	O
Baily	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
Home	O
into	O
Hogg-yard	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
this	O
Place	O
,	O
Jemmy	O
Baily	O
dropped	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Shovel	O
,	O
and	O
Dodds	O
and	O
I	O
stayed	O
at	O
his	O
Aunt	O
's	O
Door	O
;	O
we	O
talked	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
comes	O
Jemmy	O
Baily	O
;	O
Who	O
's	O
here	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
Nan	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
,	O
says	O
Dodds	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Shovel	O
,	O
says	O
Jemmy	O
Baily	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
Gentlemen	O
paying	O
their	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
-	O
they	O
have	O
Money	O
-	O
Money	O
we	O
want	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
must	O
have	O
.	O
So	O
Baily	O
,	O
and	O
Dodds	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
-	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
stop-ped	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
came	O
by	O
;	O
they	O
turned	O
up	O
between	O
Nightingal-lane	O
and	O
Ragg	O
Fair	O
.	O
Jemmy	O
Baily	O
followed	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Red	O
Rug-Coat	O
a	O
Blow	O
;	O
the	O
Man	O
turned	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
had	O
got	O
Dodd	O
's	O
Hammer	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
his	O
Head	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
two	O
Places	O
.	O
Baily	O
got	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
Hatt	O
,	O
but	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
Dodds	O
lost	O
his	O
Hatt	O
and	O
Cap	O
in	O
the	O
Fray	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
Dodds	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
all	O
over	O
Gore-Blood	O
,	O
and	O
Hatt	O
,	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
Hammer	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Jemmy	O
Baily	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
lost	O
your	O
Hatt	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
better	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
Dodds	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Glass-house	O
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
2	O
s.	O
upon	O
the	O
Hatt	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Gin	O
upon	O
it	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
;	O
and	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
Dodds	O
order	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
sell	O
the	O
Hatt	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Hatt	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
from	O
Reynold	O
's	O
and	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
to	O
sell	O
-	O
He	O
seeing	O
the	O
Blood	O
in	O
the	O
Inside	O
,	O
stopt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
't	O
was	O
Dodds	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Hatt	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
Hoy	O
borrowed	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
this	O
Hatt	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
6	O
d	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
sold	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
acquainting	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Grounds	O
of	O
his	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
Hoy	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
corroborated	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Informant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
this	O
same	O
Story	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
for	O
Dodds	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Confession	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Hatter	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Hatt	O
go	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
't	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
for	O
4s	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Blood	O
in	O
the	O
Inside	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
recollecting	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
I	O
stept	O
after	O
her	O
to	O
Harris	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
we	O
made	O
this	O
Discovery	O
,	O
and	O
Hoy	O
made	O
herself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
several	O
to	O
his	O
Reputation	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
28.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sears	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
6s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smallman	I-pers
,	O
December	O
18	O
last	O
.	O
John	O
Smallman	O
,	O
December	O
18.	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
somebody	O
reach	O
over	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
Gown	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
pursued	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
:	O
the	O
Gown	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
necessary	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
conceal	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
and	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Zaccheus	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
James	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Talmash	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
violently	O
throwing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Step-Ladder	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Yard	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Keaton	I-pers
in	O
Long-Acre	B-place
;	O
by	O
Reason	O
of	O
which	O
throwing	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
said	O
Talmash	O
Duke	O
Ford	O
received	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
languished	O
from	O
the	O
3d	O
to	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
for	O
throwing	O
the	O
Deceased	O
from	O
a	O
Ladder	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
informed	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Possibility	O
of	O
removing	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Information	O
under	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
perfectly	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
Hours	O
to	O
live	O
.	O
I	O
presented	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
wilfully	O
threw	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Ladder	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
Read	O
the	O
Information	O
.	O
The	O
Information	O
of	O
Tallmash	O
Duke	O
Ford	O
taken	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
1735.	O
Who	O
being	O
on	O
Oath	O
,	O
deposeth	O
,	O
that	O
James	O
Davison	O
threw	O
him	O
off	O
a	O
Ladder	O
,	O
whereby	O
his	O
Skull	O
was	O
so	O
fractured	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Hopes	O
of	O
Life	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
wilfully	O
and	O
maliciously	O
.	O
Taken	O
before	O
me	O
T.	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
and	O
Year	O
aforesaid	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
died	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
declared	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wilfully	O
and	O
maliciously	O
threw	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Ladder	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
injured	O
him	O
once	O
before	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bowcher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
looked	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ill	O
of	O
this	O
Wound	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Coldham	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
3d	O
or	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
.	O
Upon	O
Examination	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Skull	O
fractured	O
,	O
and	O
tho	O
'	O
all	O
possible	O
Care	O
was	O
taken	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
he	O
died	O
;	O
the	O
Fracture	O
being	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
time	O
you	O
dressed	O
him	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Keaton	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cooley	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
bled	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Arms	O
,	O
while	O
you	O
drest	O
him	O
:	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
make	O
any	O
such	O
Declaration	O
then	O
?	O
Coldham	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Glanfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
when	O
the	O
Accident	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
Word	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Brains	O
were	O
knocked	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
Davison	O
threw	O
him	O
off	O
the	O
Ladder	O
.	O
The	O
Morning	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
Hurt	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
sociable	O
,	O
and	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
Beer	O
together	O
that	O
very	O
Afternoon	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
behaved	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
two	O
Fellow-servants	O
could	O
do	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lent	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
pawned	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
paid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
not	O
frequently	O
in	O
Liquor	O
?	O
Glandfield	O
.	O
Yes	O
James	B-pers
Macmullan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
the	O
Shed	O
,	O
erected	O
for	O
priming	O
Cloath	O
for	O
Painters	O
.	O
We	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
Ladder	O
with	O
Bevill-Steps	O
,	O
14	O
Foot	O
high	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
Minutes	O
before	O
the	O
Accident	O
happened	O
,	O
talking	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
Friendly	O
Manner	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Business	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
the	O
Ladder	O
stand	O
?	O
Macmullan	O
.	O
It	O
bore	O
against	O
the	O
Bracimer	O
of	O
the	O
Building	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
aslant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
not	O
the	O
Deceased	O
speak	O
to	O
you	O
without	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
Ladder	O
?	O
Macmullan	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
had	O
private	O
Business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
necessary	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
that	O
Ladder	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
on	O
a	O
Level	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Macmullan	O
.	O
Yes	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
in	O
private	O
,	O
without	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Ladder	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Accident	O
happened	O
?	O
Macmullan	O
.	O
Yes	O
he	O
fell	O
before	O
the	O
Ladder	O
fell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Ladder	O
's	O
falling	O
?	O
Macmullan	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
coming	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
the	O
Ladder	O
's	O
falling	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Saturday	O
before	O
the	O
Accident	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
Deceased	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Day	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
happened	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
have	O
pawned	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
to	O
have	O
paid	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
my	O
Master	O
to	O
employ	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
Keaton	O
.	O
I	O
visited	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
his	O
illness	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
till	O
that	O
Night	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
then	O
?	O
Macmullan	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
been	O
read	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Ladder	O
fell	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
round	O
Ladder	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Head	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hands	O
:	O
O	O
!	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
poor	O
Boy	O
has	O
killed	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
immediately	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Coldham	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
both	O
14	O
Years	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
about	O
24	O
or	O
26	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
behave	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Coldham	O
came	O
?	O
Macmullan	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
assisted	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
third	O
Dressing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
Ladder	O
was	O
standing	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
slip	O
'd	O
away	O
from	O
its	O
Footing	O
.	O
Macmullan	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
am	O
on	O
my	O
Oath	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
it	O
slip	O
'd	O
from	O
its	O
Footing	O
:	O
it	O
bore	O
on	O
a	O
White	O
Lead	O
Barrel	O
3	O
Foot	O
high	O
,	O
after	O
it	O
fell	O
;	O
one	O
Part	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Part	O
on	O
the	O
Barrel	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
large	O
Grinding-stone	O
on	O
the	O
Barrel-head	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
the	O
Ladder	O
fall	O
upon	O
that	O
?	O
Macmullan	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
on	O
that	O
Stone	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Duffrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
two	O
Nights	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
James	O
Davison	O
threw	O
him	O
off	O
of	O
the	O
Ladder	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
Macmullan	O
;	O
and	O
disputing	O
about	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
but	O
few	O
Words	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
flung	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
designedly	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Wm	O
.	O
Williams	O
.	O
The	O
Ladder	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Ladder	O
,	O
every	O
Step	O
about	O
6	O
Inches	O
and	O
half	O
wide	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
it	O
willfully	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
not	O
all	O
declared	O
so	O
.	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
declare	O
so	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Assistant	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
carried	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
New-gate	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
Newgate	O
to	O
Tyburn	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
Master	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
the	O
Charges	O
upon	O
Duke	O
Ford	O
's	O
Account	O
.	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
quit	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Sutherland	O
Ford	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Brother	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
when	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
Davison	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
rap	O
out	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
talk	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
owed	O
the	O
Deceased	O
any	O
Ill-will	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
so	O
ill	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
half	O
the	O
Questions	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Keaton	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
Breakfast	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
.	O
Mr.	O
R.	O
Keaton	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
9	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
diligent	O
Man	O
,	O
not	O
given	O
to	O
quarrel	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
-	O
Keaton	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
Years	O
:	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
quiet	O
,	O
sober	O
,	O
careful	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
Servant	O
as	O
any	O
we	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
requested	O
Mr.	O
Keaton	O
never	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Deceased	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Drinking	O
and	O
Quarrelling	O
.	O
And	O
several	O
others	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
is	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
de	O
sire	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
called	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Beaumont	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
Duke	O
Ford	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
him	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
Condition	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
Information	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
delirious	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
him	O
then	O
Incurable	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gomond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
delirious	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
attended	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
that	O
Tallmarsh	O
Duke	O
Ford	O
's	O
Death	O
was	O
Accidental	O
.	O
30.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Coral	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
1	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
1	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Geo	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
short	O
Cloak	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
appearing	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
disordered	O
in	O
her	O
Mind	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
her	O
.	O
31.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Waring	O
Apparel	O
,	O
on	O
Jan.	O
2	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joshua	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
offered	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Places	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Knife	O
Blades	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hen	B-pers
.	I-pers
Willoughbey	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shop	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
and	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
Susan	B-pers
Fidzar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Leather	O
Watch-string	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hearley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Headley	I-pers
.	O
About	O
Friday	O
was	O
Fort-night	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
in	O
an	O
Alley	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	B-place
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
must	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
:	O
She	O
made	O
a	O
Bargain	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
give	O
her	O
6d	O
.	O
to	O
be	O
great	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
10	O
Minutes	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
an	O
Excuse	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Chairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
?	O
Headley	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
by	O
ourselves	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Woman	O
by	O
themselves	O
:	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
middling	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Room	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
were	O
as	O
far	O
assunder	O
,	O
as	O
from	O
hence	O
to	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
this	O
Court	O
.	O
-	O
Yes	O
-	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
other	O
Company	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
very	O
Minute	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
about	O
5	O
Minutes	O
before	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
felt	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
for	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
after	O
my	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
34.	O
Barnaby	B-pers
Roebick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
18d	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Negroe	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Queen-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
from	O
my	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
quick	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
my	O
Hat	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
close	O
at	O
his	O
Heels	O
to	O
an	O
Alley	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
Bow-Lane	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
a	O
Light	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
never	O
once	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
baptiz	O
'd	O
?	O
Farrow	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
-	O
my	O
Lord	O
Grantham	O
was	O
my	O
Godfather	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Cranwell	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
Evidence	O
confirmed	O
Farrow	O
's	O
.	O
Sir	O
William	O
Billars	O
's	O
Clark	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Keepers	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Billars	I-pers
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36.	O
John	B-pers
Courtney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Ounce	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37.	O
William	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gray	B-pers
Munshal	I-pers
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fact	O
being	O
plainly	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38.	O
William	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Hats	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Vibart	I-pers
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Robert	O
Vibart	O
.	O
Having	O
lost	O
four	O
Hats	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
desire	O
the	O
Shop-Keepers	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
should	O
offer	O
to	O
Sale	O
such	O
Hats	O
as	O
I	O
described	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
was	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Seeing	O
the	O
Fellow	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Hat	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vibart	I-pers
's	O
Evidence	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4s	O
.	O
10s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelburga	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Twist	I-pers
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
be	O
changed	O
for	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Guinea	O
to	O
this	O
Bed-ford	O
to	O
get	O
changed	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
intrust	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Bedford	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
must	O
be	O
acquitted	O
of	O
this	O
Indictment	O
.	O
40.	O
George	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Katherine	I-place
Coleman	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Harefinch	I-pers
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Silk	O
Dyer	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
this	O
Gown	O
off	O
the	O
Pole	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
Christmas	O
;	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
we	O
dy	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
two	O
Breadths	O
of	O
Burdett	O
,	O
an	O
Olive	O
Colour	O
,	O
the	O
Burdett	O
was	O
marked	O
in	O
the	O
Sleeve	O
with	O
a	O
(	O
D	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
made	O
up	O
?	O
Robins	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
sewed	O
together	O
for	O
the	O
Conveniency	O
of	O
Dying	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
about	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
sewed	O
it	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
indicted	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
.	O
Robins	O
.	O
We	O
always	O
call	O
such	O
Things	O
Gowns	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
general	O
Course	O
of	O
your	O
Business	O
called	O
Gowns	O
?	O
Robins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
never	O
any	O
Thing	O
else	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
Term	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Gown	O
again	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
unfinished	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
used	O
till	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
Waterers	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
sent	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
Trade	O
to	O
have	O
such	O
Things	O
stopp	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
their	O
Hands	O
.	O
Word	O
was	O
sent	O
me	O
by	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
watered	O
such	O
Goods	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
swore	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Widegate-Alley	O
.	O
Bishops-gate-street	O
,	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
be	O
watered	O
one	O
Evening	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
done	O
,	O
they	O
lay	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
this	O
Notice	O
and	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
:	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
Mark	O
(	O
D	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
Sleeve	O
:	O
This	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
either	O
on	O
Saturday	O
or	O
Monday	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
swear	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
Things	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
answered	O
his	O
Description	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
common	O
Course	O
of	O
your	O
Business	O
can	O
you	O
water	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
in	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Hours	O
?	O
Bryan	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
if	O
Necessity	O
requires	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
have	O
Work	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
done	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Bryan	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
fetched	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
his	O
Servant	O
with	O
this	O
Notice	O
?	O
Bryan	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Monday	O
was	O
Se'nnight	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
them	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
got	O
them	O
done	O
.	O
Several	O
Persons	O
appearing	O
on	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
41.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Starling	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
Silver	O
top	O
of	O
a	O
Chocolate	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
17s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
17	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
42.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gagg	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wast-coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Towle	I-pers
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
January	O
.	O
Matthew	O
Towle	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Coventry	B-place
Court	I-place
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Asctell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
(	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
)	O
and	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
more	O
,	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
afterward	O
.	O
Towle	O
made	O
enquiry	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
then	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
examined	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
I	O
secured	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Towle	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Philips	O
gave	O
her	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
produce	O
this	O
Philips	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
asked	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
Money	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
her	O
own	O
Account	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43.	O
Isabel	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
Yards	O
of	O
striped	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
December	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
David	O
Davis	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
left	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
by	O
Mr.	O
More	O
:	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
behind	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
five	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
Lodger	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
at	O
the	O
Pawn-brokers	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
her	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Goods	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
Affidavit	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
's	O
.	O
-	O
Hayton	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
this	O
Parcel	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
suspicion	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
confessed	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
44.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hazledine	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Shirts	O
,	O
3	O
Sheets	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Maccartney	I-pers
,	O
December	O
18	O
.	O
last	O
.	O
Jacob	O
Adams	O
.	O
I	O
caught	O
this	O
Man	O
taking	O
the	O
Linnen	O
off	O
the	O
Lines	O
in	O
my	O
Yard	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Linnen	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
-	O
You	O
are	O
mistaken	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Maccartney	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
while	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Linnen	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
's	O
Evidence	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Purpose	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45.	O
Esther	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
44	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Turvey	I-pers
,	O
October	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
46	O
,	O
47	O
,	O
48.	O
William	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
18	O
pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
4	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
;	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Boiler	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Dr.	O
John	B-pers
Heyling	I-pers
,	O
and	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Heylin	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
;	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
49.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Precious	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
3	O
Wast-coats	O
,	O
1	O
Hood	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
Yard	O
of	O
Damask	O
,	O
4	O
Linnen	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Creedland	I-pers
,	O
January	O
the	O
4th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50.	O
Robert	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Jane	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Lodgers	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
took	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
the	O
Ring	O
off	O
my	O
Finger	O
without	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
immediately	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
the	O
Ring	O
the	O
Moment	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
was	O
always	O
fond	O
and	O
friendly	O
;	O
she	O
lent	O
me	O
the	O
Ring	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
get	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
cruel	O
Case	O
-	O
but	O
-	O
Women	O
's	O
Words	O
!	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Huggins	I-pers
was	I-pers
a	I-pers
second	I-pers
time	I-pers
indicted	I-pers
(	I-pers
with	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hurgins	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
October	O
10	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
old	O
Hood	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
swore	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
51.	O
William	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
49	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Goods	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Callan	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Matthias	B-pers
Prime	I-pers
.	O
December	O
12	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Callan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Prime	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Grafton	B-place
street	I-place
.	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
this	O
thing	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Trunk	O
,	O
a	O
Purse	O
with	O
50	O
Guineas	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
change	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
rest	O
I	O
tyed	O
up	O
and	O
layed	O
down	O
upon	O
an	O
Oak	O
Table	O
in	O
my	O
forward	O
Room	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
covered	O
the	O
Purse	O
with	O
a	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Washer-womans	O
for	O
some	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
bid	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
expected	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
arrested	O
,	O
to	O
lock	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
Stair-head	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
locked	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
this	O
Man	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
there	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
?	O
What	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
-	O
away	O
flew	O
the	O
Lock	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
seeing	O
the	O
Door	O
fly	O
open	O
,	O
was	O
so	O
astonished	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Wits	O
-	O
he	O
layed	O
his	O
Hands	O
on	O
my	O
Brothers	O
,	O
and	O
shoving	O
over	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
Table	O
stood	O
,	O
he	O
spy	O
'd	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
nearer	O
the	O
Table	O
than	O
I	O
,	O
he	O
snatched	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Well	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
arrest	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
rob	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
how	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Purse	O
;	O
you	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
covered	O
.	O
Callan	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
shoved	O
the	O
Linnen	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Fellows	O
gathered	O
close	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
!	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
!	O
You	O
Bitch	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
say	O
a	O
Word	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
cut	O
your	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
he	O
pulled	O
a	O
long	O
Knife	O
-	O
Woman	O
!	O
Woman	O
!	O
says	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
hold	O
your	O
Tongue	O
,	O
or	O
we	O
shall	O
all	O
be	O
murdered	O
!	O
I	O
dropped	O
back	O
on	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
power	O
to	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
more	O
-	O
My	O
Money	O
lost	O
,	O
my	O
Life	O
in	O
danger	O
-	O
Then	O
away	O
he	O
hurried	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Brother	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
In	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Minutes	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Folks	O
below	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
,	O
which	O
way	O
are	O
the	O
Fellows	O
gone	O
?	O
They	O
directed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
locked	O
up	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
