TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
Country	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Friday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1736	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
THOMPSON	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1736	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
,	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXVII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
;	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
Lee	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Cummins	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middle-sex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Amsley	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Trimmer	I-pers
John	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
.	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Hearsay	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Knightley	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Lathwaite	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Gillmore	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Low	I-pers
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hammersley	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pint	O
Mug	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
,	O
December	O
20	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
(	O
her	O
Name	O
is	O
Susannah	O
Draper	O
,	O
she	O
keeps	O
the	O
Globe-Tavern	B-place
in	I-place
Fleet-Street	I-place
)	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
fetch	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Cook	O
to	O
dress	O
him	O
a	O
Beef	O
Stake	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Cook	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Mug	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
Boys	O
standing	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
while	O
the	O
Boy	O
took	O
the	O
Mug	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
IDS	O
.	O
and	O
is	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
:	O
The	O
Fellow	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
stole	O
about	O
five	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
To	O
excuse	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
seem	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
capable	O
of	O
committing	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
Mug	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
my	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
how	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
Word	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
They	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
lay	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
wonder	O
'd	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
John	O
Draper	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
resistance	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
neither	O
paid	O
for	O
his	O
Wine	O
,	O
nor	O
his	O
Beef-Stake	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Tilman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Cook	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Mug	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
coming	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
dress	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Beef-Stake	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
Beer	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Mug	O
;	O
he	O
drank	O
up	O
the	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
to	O
the	O
Larder	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
(	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
)	O
put	O
the	O
Mug	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stop	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
my	O
young	O
Master	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Boy	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
I	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Neveil	I-pers
The	O
Prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
Mother	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Vintner	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
or	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
robb	O
'd	O
any	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
Pin	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
keeps	O
Burton	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
Years	O
.	O
His	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Gillender	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
over-against	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
reckon	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
enquired	O
of	O
several	O
People	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
has	O
liv	O
'd	O
and	O
have	O
heard	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
very	O
earnestly	O
recommended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Favour	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Intercession	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
seven	O
Years	O
.	O
2.	O
William	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
'live	O
Pigs	O
,	O
fed	O
for	O
Pork	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
September	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
January	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
4.	O
James	B-pers
Cray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Stone	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
clunch	O
Stone	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Jelf	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
5.	O
Martha	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tisbury	I-pers
,	O
December	O
30	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6	O
,	O
7	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Insome	I-pers
and	O
Esther	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
14	O
.	O
James	O
Powel	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
Dec.	O
14	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
light	O
on	O
this	O
Creature	O
,	O
(	O
Clare	O
Dickenson	O
)	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
?	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Insome	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
't	O
is	O
Insome	O
's	O
House	O
or	O
Robert	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Watch	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Drams	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
neither	O
Money	O
nor	O
Watch	O
.	O
Clare	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
I	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
Redding	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Insome	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
Redding	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
truly	O
they	O
wonder	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
pick	O
up	O
such	O
a	O
nasty	O
black-guard	O
Creature	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
:	O
But	O
we	O
had	O
three	O
Quarterns	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
Insome	O
I	O
am	O
same	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Redding	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
so	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
they	O
stripp	O
'd	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
so	O
improperly	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
Midwife	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
ill	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
not	O
mind	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
got	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
us	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
we	O
were	O
but	O
gone	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
safe	O
enough	O
.	O
They	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
Black-guard	O
,	O
and	O
wonder	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
dirty	O
Wretch	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
Where	O
does	O
Redding	O
live	O
?	O
Dickenson	O
.	O
Over-against	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Church	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Sign	O
.	O
Insome	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
I	O
did	O
bring	O
them	O
their	O
Liquor	O
;	O
but	O
ask	O
her	O
if	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Dickenson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
you	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
then	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
Candle	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
wonder	O
'd	O
how	O
any	O
body	O
could	O
pick	O
up	O
such	O
a	O
Black-guard	O
,	O
dirty	O
Bitch	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Insome	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
brought	O
the	O
Creature	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
:	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
Liquour	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
his	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
it	O
in	O
our	O
House	O
;	O
why	O
then	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
it	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
Creature	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
sadly	O
;	O
Redding	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
could	O
charge	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
charge	O
no	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
Dickenson	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barringer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
Man	O
and	O
Dickenson	O
out	O
of	O
Redding	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
Silver	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
value	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
but	O
get	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
We	O
search	O
'd	O
Dickenson	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
:	O
there	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
saw	O
Insome	O
take	O
it	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
Redding	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
In	O
Redding	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
Fact	O
on	O
Clare	O
Dickenson	O
only	O
Thomas	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
crying	O
,	O
-	O
past	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
Watch	O
!	O
but	O
please	O
your	O
Honour	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
other	O
Watchman	O
.	O
This	O
Gentlewoman	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
Night	O
Walker	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
beating	O
the	O
Creature	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
mad	O
:	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
-	O
do	O
n't	O
beat	O
her	O
so	O
,	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
charge	O
us	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
her	O
according	O
to	O
Law	O
,	O
please	O
your	O
Honour	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
We	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
Women	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
Women	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
)	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
were	O
then	O
Present	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
Appear	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Characters	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
8.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dowgard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Seventy-three	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Sea-Coal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
and	O
Deborah	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
December	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
John	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
Chains	O
,	O
used	O
for	O
Horse	O
Harness	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Stable	O
,	O
Dec.	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
John	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Ickenham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
open	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Bags	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
one	O
Quart	O
of	O
Peas	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Haydon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Bottle	O
of	O
spirituous	O
Liquors	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
Haydon	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
from	O
Uxbridge	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Road	O
near	O
the	O
Cart	O
Road	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Stile	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
who	O
's	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Name	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
darted	O
his	O
Stick	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
cut	O
a	O
great	O
Gash	O
in	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
backwards	O
:	O
Then	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
Stile	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
making	O
another	O
Blow	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
slipp	O
'd	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
avoided	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
and	O
got	O
two	O
Men	O
to	O
search	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Wife	O
how	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Congregation	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Sweat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
(	O
as	O
how	O
)	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
but	O
a	O
Mile	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
lame	O
of	O
one	O
Hand	O
;	O
he	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
gone	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
on	O
his	O
Account	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
Goods	O
again	O
?	O
Haydon	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Dog-house	O
of	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bolton	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
20	O
Pole	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
acted	O
very	O
Ugly	O
by	O
me	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
for	O
robbing	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
Malice	O
!	O
Haydon	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
,	O
not	O
I.	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
:	O
When	O
Haydon	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Heat	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
sweat	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
sweat	O
very	O
much	O
when	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
one	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
lame	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
often	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
lame	O
Hand	O
:	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
ago	O
he	O
got	O
his	O
Bread	O
by	O
his	O
Labour	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
he	O
's	O
kept	O
by	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
is	O
lame	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
his	O
Leg	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
lame	O
indeed	O
,	O
at	O
some	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
others	O
,	O
he	O
walks	O
better	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
dishonest	O
by	O
me	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
,	O
but	O
John	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
Character	O
.	O
Another	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Parish	O
will	O
give	O
Haydon	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
.	O
Another	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Principle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
never	O
catch	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
any	O
ill	O
demeanour	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
often	O
out	O
o'Nights	O
pretty	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
looks	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
easy	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lame	O
Man	O
:	O
My	O
right	O
Hand	O
is	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
right	O
Leg	O
and	O
Thigh	O
is	O
not	O
bigger	O
than	O
my	O
Wrist	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
past	O
my	O
Labour	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
work	O
for	O
my	O
Bread	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
Assistance	O
from	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
they	O
have	O
done	O
this	O
out	O
of	O
Spite	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
11.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lillyman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Meage	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
January	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
Philip	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Box-iron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
six	O
Padlocks	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
Keys	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
November	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
William	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bob	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Mary	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
Headcloths	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
suit	O
of	O
Fringed	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Smock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lydall	I-pers
,	O
January	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15	O
,	O
16	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
and	O
Hugh	B-pers
Macmahon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancrass	B-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
open	O
Field	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
two	O
camblet	O
Cloaks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
callamanco	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
linnen	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
a	O
linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eunace	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
December	O
8	O
.	O
And	O
17	O
,	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Cloak	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Smith	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
Cart	O
almost	O
asleep	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
ask	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
drove	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
was	O
:	O
They	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
spoke	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Tilt	O
off	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Money	O
they	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
:	O
My	O
Husband	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
clapp	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
in	O
the	O
Cart	O
;	O
what	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
hit	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
how	O
much	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
pull	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
stripped	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
Gown	O
,	O
three	O
Cloaks	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
my	O
Maid	O
's	O
(	O
Eunace	O
Newman	O
)	O
a	O
linnen	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
Shoes	O
off	O
my	O
Feet	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
hide	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
abuse	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
Home	O
with	O
our	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Men	O
assaulted	O
us	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Cart	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
:	O
I	O
remember	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
red	O
Coat	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
there	O
?	O
Francis	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Ryan	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
off	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
several	O
knocks	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
One	O
had	O
a	O
red	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Ryan	O
cry	O
'd	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
several	O
Blows	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
how	O
much	O
that	O
was	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
meaning	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
another	O
?	O
-	O
Hah	O
!	O
How	O
many	O
of	O
us	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
?	O
F.	O
Smith	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
of	O
you	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
And	O
pray	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
F.	O
Smith	O
.	O
You	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
With	O
humble	O
Submission	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
why	O
should	O
he	O
know	O
me	O
in	O
particular	O
?	O
F.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Because	O
you	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
ugly	O
Knocks	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
With	O
humble	O
Submission	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
why	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
any	O
Notice	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
F.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Why	O
you	O
damn	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
turn	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
you	O
that	O
pull	O
'd	O
my	O
great	O
Coat	O
over	O
my	O
Back	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
And	O
will	O
you	O
swear	O
it	O
?	O
F.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
With	O
humble	O
Submission	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
inform	O
your	O
self	O
about	O
that	O
Fellow	O
.	O
F.	O
Smith	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
nothing	O
but	O
our	O
Money	O
from	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
made	O
us	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
plunder	O
'd	O
the	O
Cart	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
F.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Cart	O
stripp	O
'd	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
with	O
a	O
safe	O
Conscience	O
swear	O
that	O
Ryan	O
was	O
among	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
;	O
they	O
d	O
-	O
'd	O
us	O
when	O
they	O
drove	O
us	O
up	O
the	O
Field	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
go	O
faster	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Business	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
Questions	O
.	O
F.	O
Smith	O
.	O
My	O
great	O
Coat	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
from	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cloak	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
my	O
Maid	O
will	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
with	O
humble	O
Submission	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
the	O
Reason	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
particular	O
Marks	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
before	O
three	O
more	O
?	O
with	O
humble	O
Submission	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
why	O
does	O
he	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
F.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
by	O
your	O
Voice	O
,	O
your	O
Nose	O
,	O
your	O
black	O
Hair	O
,	O
by	O
your	O
laying	O
so	O
violently	O
upon	O
me	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
cover	O
'd	O
all	O
over	O
with	O
Blood	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
by	O
your	O
Boldness	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
strutting	O
Manner	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
with	O
humble	O
Submission	O
,	O
that	O
Fellow	O
will	O
swear	O
that	O
a	O
Cow	O
is	O
a	O
Jack-ass	O
.	O
With	O
humble	O
Submission	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
understand	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
are	O
,	O
not	O
I	O
,	O
the	O
Thief-takers	O
instruct	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
every	O
Thing	O
.	O
F.	O
Smith	O
.	O
He	O
clapp	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
lye	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
bound	O
us	O
;	O
they	O
ty	O
'd	O
my	O
Hands	O
behind	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
strong	O
penny	O
Cord	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Legs	O
they	O
fasten	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Hands	O
.	O
Before	O
they	O
bound	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Shoes	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Wife	O
does	O
.	O
S.	O
Smith	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
last	O
December	O
.	O
Q	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Ryan	O
.	O
With	O
humble	O
Submission	O
,	O
he	O
swears	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Ditch	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Cart	O
;	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Fore-horse	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
stirr	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
Copses	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
that	O
Man	O
(	O
Ryan	O
)	O
that	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
With	O
humble	O
Submission	O
,	O
inform	O
your	O
self	O
what	O
this	O
Fellow	O
has	O
sworn	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
these	O
Evidences	O
.	O
Nash	O
.	O
I	O
swear	O
you	O
abus	O
'd	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
his	O
coat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
hope	O
(	O
help	O
'd	O
)	O
to	O
pull	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
22	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
my	O
Knife	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ditch	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
You	O
swore	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Viel	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
that	O
knock	O
'd	O
you	O
down	O
.	O
Terence	B-pers
O'Bryan	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Macmahon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
and	O
I	O
,	O
met	O
this	O
same	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
High	O
Road	O
,	O
between	O
Tottenham	B-place
and	O
the	O
quarter	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Hampstead	B-place
Road	I-place
:	O
we	O
stopp	O
'd	O
his	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Man	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Shilling	O
and	O
some	O
Brass	O
,	O
about	O
16	O
d.	O
in	O
all	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
understand	O
,	O
that	O
same	O
Hugh	O
Macmahon	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
Macdonald	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Cloth	O
that	O
cover	O
'd	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
stripp	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Pocket	O
from	O
the	O
Woman	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
made	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
justly	O
tell	O
whether	O
they	O
took	O
any	O
Cloaths	O
from	O
the	O
Woman	O
'till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Field	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
her	O
Cloak	O
,	O
her	O
Gown	O
,	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Shoes	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Macmahon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
at	O
present	O
-	O
Ryan	O
.	O
At	O
present	O
,	O
-	O
Hah	O
!	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
Company	O
at	O
present	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
Ryan	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gown	O
on	O
Ellen	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
that	O
goes	O
under	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Ryan	O
's	O
Wife	O
.	O
That	O
very	O
same	O
Night	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Ryan	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Gown	O
he	O
gave	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
say	O
whether	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
stole	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
Coleman	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Lacey	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
Coleman	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
subject	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
-	O
when	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
we	O
could	O
come	O
by	O
them	O
no	O
other	O
Way	O
but	O
by	O
robbing	O
on	O
the	O
High-way	O
.	O
Macmahon	O
.	O
Please	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
ask	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
has	O
known	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
About	O
Three	O
Months	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Macmahon	O
.	O
Very	O
well	O
:	O
where	O
,	O
(	O
with	O
Submission	O
)	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
first	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
Not	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
France	O
.	O
I	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
this	O
Country	O
at	O
London	O
:	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
was	O
at	O
Ryan	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
Macmahon	O
.	O
Very	O
well	O
,	O
please	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
over	O
against	O
my	O
Room	O
in	O
Newtoner's-Lane	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
was	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Court	O
and	O
your	O
Lordship	O
will	O
all	O
know	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
will	O
prove	O
this	O
Man	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Perjury	O
[	O
perjur	O
'd	O
]	O
before	O
the	O
whole	O
Court	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
Occasion	O
did	O
I	O
become	O
acquainted	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Ryan	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Intention	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
robbing	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
Macmahon	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
ask	O
me	O
?	O
Ryan	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
with	O
humble	O
Submission	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
capable	O
of	O
swearing	O
,	O
-	O
pray	O
how	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
me	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Ryan	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Regiment	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
Recruits	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Regiment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
Garrison	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
's	O
Service	O
at	O
St.	O
Omers	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
With	O
humble	O
Submission	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
have	O
Access	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
-	O
out	O
and	O
in	O
,	O
above	O
any	O
other	O
?	O
Eunace	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
swear	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Cloak	O
;	O
my	O
Mistress	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Owen	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
Ryan	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
for	O
Robberies	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
.	O
Ryan	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
upon	O
him	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
(	O
't	O
was	O
here	O
produced	O
)	O
't	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
at	O
Colonel	O
Williamson	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
positively	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Colonel	O
's	O
Custody	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
't	O
is	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
Colonel	O
's	O
Seal	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
S.	O
Smith	O
.	O
This	O
very	O
Handkerchief	O
they	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
Neck	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
.	O
Griffith	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
left	O
with	O
Colonel	O
Williamson	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
Governor	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
seal	O
'd	O
.	O
Col.	O
Williamson	O
.	O
This	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
Ryan	O
in	O
my	O
Presence	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Shoes	O
;	O
this	O
Hat	O
was	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
too	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Presence	O
.	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
Scrutore	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
seal	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Griffith	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Governor	O
had	O
committed	O
Ryan	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
Coleman	O
in	O
Custody	O
on	O
a	O
different	O
Warrant	O
for	O
receiving	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
to	O
be	O
examin	O
'd	O
.	O
Next	O
Day	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Colonel	O
Deacon	O
inform	O
'd	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Cloak	O
on	O
Coleman	O
's	O
Back	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
Smith	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Eunace	O
Newman	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Cloak	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
lent	O
my	O
Mistress	O
.	O
Ryan	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
With	O
humble	O
Submission	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
all	O
false	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
sworn	O
about	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
the	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Governor	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
.	O
Inform	O
your	O
self	O
how	O
she	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
C.	O
Why	O
she	O
says	O
you	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
cursed	O
Lie	O
,	O
with	O
humble	O
Submission	O
;	O
my	O
Moan	O
is	O
,	O
-	O
shall	O
this	O
Woman	O
here	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
Coleman	O
)	O
answer	O
for	O
this	O
?	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
deny	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Transgressor	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
's	O
no	O
Reason	O
an	O
innocent	O
Person	O
should	O
lose	O
her	O
Life	O
by	O
the	O
Liar	O
and	O
the	O
Perjuror	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
deny	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
Transgressor	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Grace	O
of	O
God	O
I	O
shall	O
suffer	O
.	O
Macmahon	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
over	O
from	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
O'Bryan	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
Six	O
Men	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
into	O
the	O
French	O
Service	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
Two	O
Days	O
before	O
Allhallontide	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
toward	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
young	O
Fellows	O
in	O
my	O
Company	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
one	O
Garvey	O
can	O
justify	O
that	O
he	O
lent	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
France	O
or	O
Flanders	O
,	O
about	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
Days	O
after	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Man	O
swears	O
I	O
did	O
these	O
Things	O
.	O
Lord	O
!	O
see	O
what	O
difference	O
there	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Talk	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
Money	O
too	O
,	O
keeps	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
and	O
Magpye	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
look	O
into	O
his	O
Manners	O
,	O
-	O
why	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
is	O
striving	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
Life	O
away	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Friends	O
to	O
stand	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Ellen	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
acquainted	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
I	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
Flanders	O
.	O
Coleman	O
.	O
Examine	O
him	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
pray	O
examine	O
him	O
over	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
serv	O
'd	O
the	O
Counsellors	O
in	O
Lincolns-Inn	O
and	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Council	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
with	O
Flowers	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
What	O
she	O
has	O
done	O
was	O
by	O
my	O
Order	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
her	O
Husband	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
Robbery	O
she	O
has	O
committed	O
.	O
Ryan	O
and	O
Macmahon	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Coleman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18	O
,	O
19.	O
James	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Falconer	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
North	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Stock	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Nov.	O
7.	O
James	B-pers
North	I-pers
.	O
About	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Nov.	O
7	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Highgate	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
three	O
Men	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
.	O
They	O
rifled	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
five	O
Penn'orth	O
of	O
half	O
Pence	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Silver	O
among	O
the	O
Half-pence	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
One	O
Man	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
hoarse	O
Voice	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
spare	O
Man	O
,	O
a	O
low	O
Voice	O
,	O
and	O
pale	O
Complection	O
;	O
the	O
Moon	O
was	O
over-cast	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
dark	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Men	O
;	O
but	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
Hat	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
O'Bryan	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
own	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
put	O
on	O
these	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
in	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
the	O
Ditch	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
you	O
was	O
first	O
assaulted	O
?	O
North	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Highgate	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
over	O
two	O
great	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
Gateway	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
Field	O
.	O
My	O
Money	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
Field	O
.	O
Two	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
,	O
seemingly	O
to	O
keep	O
Guard	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
With	O
humble	O
Submission	O
-	O
keep	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Custody	O
.	O
O'Bryan	O
is	O
instructed	O
in	O
all	O
Villainy	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
the	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
C.	O
(	O
To	O
O'Bryan	O
)	O
Take	O
care	O
you	O
speak	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
remember	O
you	O
are	O
upon	O
your	O
Oath	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
robbed	O
a	O
Man	O
near	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
.	O
Ryan	O
and	O
Falconer	O
led	O
him	O
cross	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
Fitzgerald	O
stood	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
Ditch	O
and	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
Field	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Hand	O
going	O
to	O
Highgate	O
.	O
Ryan	O
commanded	O
me	O
to	O
stand	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
with	O
Arms	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
stripp	O
'd	O
naked	O
,	O
but	O
Ryan	O
commanded	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
stipp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Ryan	O
,	O
Falconer	O
,	O
and	O
Fitzgerald	O
,	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
Ryan	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
and	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Hat	O
.	O
North	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Hat	O
I	O
lost	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Ditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
upon	O
this	O
Robbery	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
As	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
understand	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
between	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
and	O
Highgate	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
?	O
O	O
Bryan	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Ryan	O
and	O
Falconer	O
first	O
;	O
they	O
laid	O
Hands	O
on	O
the	O
Man	O
first	O
.	O
Fitzgerald	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
present	O
Time	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
with	O
humble	O
Submission	O
-	O
look	O
in	O
that	O
Fellow	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
talks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to'em	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
They	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Breeches	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
took	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
Hedge	O
and	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
over	O
one	O
Field	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
they	O
chang	O
'd	O
Cloaths	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Ryan	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
Two	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Three	O
Pence	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
but	O
the	O
Hat	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
they	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
ty	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Garters	O
.	O
North	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
my	O
Garters	O
off	O
my	O
right	O
Leg	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ty	O
'd	O
my	O
Hands	O
prodigious	O
hard	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
Only	O
compare	O
his	O
Affidavit	O
now	O
with	O
what	O
he	O
produced	O
before	O
his	O
Worship	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Governor	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
.	O
Fitzgerald	O
.	O
Ryan	O
can	O
clear	O
me	O
.	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Fitzgerald	O
these	O
12	O
Months	O
Counsel	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
last	O
in	O
France	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
Months	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
remember	O
your	O
telling	O
any	O
one	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
France	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Garvey	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Antony	O
Ellis	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Francis	O
Allen	O
,	O
or	O
Elizabeth	O
Broughton	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
meeting	O
Garvey	O
's	O
Wife	O
in	O
Flanders	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
this	O
same	O
Woman	O
kill	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Now	O
she	O
is	O
come	O
to	O
swear	O
falsly	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
vile	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
a	O
House	O
for	O
Thieves	O
,	O
Highway	O
Robbers	O
,	O
Pickpockets	O
and	O
Rogues	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Garvey	O
's	O
being	O
in	O
Flanders	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
lending	O
her	O
Money	O
in	O
Flanders	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
receiving	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Token	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
within	O
these	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Months	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Fitzgerald	O
lately	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
Sherlock	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
one	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
at	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Night	O
that	O
the	O
Robery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
Cosgrave	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Princes-Street	O
;	O
and	O
Ryan	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
Fitzgerald	O
and	O
Falconer	O
were	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
behind	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bedford	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
to	O
object	O
against	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
-	O
Hear	O
his	O
Objections	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
the	O
Affidavit	O
he	O
made	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Governor	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
produced	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Examination	O
I	O
took	O
,	O
which	O
O'Bryan	O
sign	O
'd	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Clerk	O
Reads	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Information	O
of	O
Terence	O
O'Bryan	O
,	O
taken	O
before	O
me	O
Thomas	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
Jan.	O
9	O
,	O
1736-7.	O
Who	O
being	O
on	O
Oath	O
says	O
,	O
That	O
James	O
Ryan	O
,	O
Gerrard	O
Fitzgerald	O
,	O
and	O
James	O
Falconer	O
,	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Falconer	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
three	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
says	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
told	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
out	O
of	O
Ryan	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
He	O
did	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Examination	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
set	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
Ryan	O
's	O
Room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
what	O
Place	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
when	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
from	O
Cosgrave	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Princes	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
Fitzgerald	O
and	O
Falconer	O
were	O
to	O
meet	O
as	O
behind	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bedford	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
free	O
Evidence	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
laid	O
to	O
my	O
Charge	O
-	O
What	O
Need	O
have	O
I	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
their	O
Lives	O
?	O
Counsel	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
O'Bryan	O
swears	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
.	O
C.	O
He	O
swears	O
that	O
three	O
Men	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
Eliz	B-pers
Garvey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Horshoe	O
and	O
Magpie	O
in	O
Drury	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
O'Bryan	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
frequent	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
for	O
France	O
.	O
Col.	O
De	O
Veil	O
knows	O
't	O
was	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
Hawkins	O
and	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
O'Bryan	O
at	O
Arras	O
in	O
Flanders	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
or	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Carravan	O
and	O
seeing	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
you	O
will	O
perhaps	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
dear	O
Place	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
this	O
Pocket-Piece	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
Husband	O
as	O
a	O
Token	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
deliver	O
'd	O
O'Bryan	O
the	O
Pocket-Piece	O
upon	O
this	O
Occasion	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
from	O
France	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
15th	O
or	O
16th	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
cold	O
,	O
being	O
just	O
come	O
off	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
France	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
my	O
Mistress	O
on	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
giving	O
my	O
Master	O
the	O
Pocket	O
Piece	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
my	O
Master	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Discourse	O
together	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
Half	O
Guinea	O
came	O
to	O
.	O
He	O
owes	O
3s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
upon	O
our	O
Score	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Horshoe-and-Magpie	O
in	O
Drury	O
lane	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Oct.	O
27	O
.	O
O'Bryan	O
left	O
my	O
House	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
France	O
;	O
on	O
Nov.	O
16	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Debt	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
this	O
Memorandum	O
the	O
Day	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
.	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
France	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Clark	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
from	O
his	O
telling	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Fitzgerald	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
Know	O
he	O
works	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
Bread	O
,	O
at	O
labouring	O
among	O
the	O
Bricklayers	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Red	O
Bull	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Vine-street	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Browlter	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
Fitzgerald	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
O'Bryan	O
)	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
last	O
go	O
to	O
France	O
?	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
Half	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
but	O
towards	O
Dover	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
meet	O
Garvis	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
,	O
at	O
Arras	O
in	O
Flanders	O
.	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
lend	O
her	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Token	O
she	O
speaks	O
of	O
;	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
ever	O
declare	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
,	O
That	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
look	O
in	O
their	O
Characters	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Longbottom	I-pers
.	O
When	O
we	O
enquired	O
after	O
Falconer	O
,	O
Barnes	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
Vere	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
House	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
Labourers	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
hard	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
smelt	O
a	O
Snitch	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
come	O
out	O
for	O
no	O
Body	O
-	O
Barnes	O
I	O
took	O
Fitzgerald	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
Rescue	O
of	O
Casey	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
reputed	O
Thief	O
and	O
Pick	O
Pocket	O
at	O
the	O
Play-houses	O
.	O
When	O
Longbottom	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
perswading	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
smelt	O
a	O
Snitch	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
Richard	B-pers
Eustace	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Lyon-by	O
Hicks-Hall	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Keate	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bignal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
New	O
Prison	O
;	O
and	O
O'Bryan	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Papers	O
of	O
Tothill	O
fields	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
I	O
spake	O
to	O
O'Bryan	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
in	O
Flanders	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
remember	O
'd	O
his	O
meeting	O
between	O
Arras	O
and	O
Bethune	O
in	O
Flanders	O
Yes	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silver	O
to	O
return	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
before	O
November	O
.	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
New	O
Prison	O
;	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
heard	O
any	O
such	O
Discourse	O
:	O
-	O
'T	O
is	O
all	O
false	O
.	O
Barnes	O
.	O
Among	O
all	O
these	O
People	O
that	O
have	O
sworn	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
not	O
one	O
but	O
what	O
are	O
Irish	O
.	O
All	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
20.	O
James	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
Garret	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hugh	B-pers
Macmahon	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edmund	B-pers
Rowbottom	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckskin	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
Nov.	O
20	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examin	O
'd	O
apart	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Rowbottom	I-pers
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
Men	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
beyond	O
the	O
Half-way-House	O
going	O
to	O
Hampstead	B-place
.	O
They	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Shirt	O
,	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
Buckles	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
they	O
bound	O
my	O
Hands	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
left	O
Leg	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Hands	O
then	O
they	O
ty	O
'd	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
over	O
my	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
rolled	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
Ditch	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
was	O
there	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Rowbottom	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
two	O
led	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
followed	O
me	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Moon-light	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
kept	O
an	O
old	O
Hat	O
over	O
my	O
Face	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
much	O
of	O
a	O
Size	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
taller	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
With	O
humble	O
Submission	O
,	O
-	O
these	O
Thief-catchers	O
have	O
instructed	O
him	O
too	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
Villanies	O
.	O
Terence	B-pers
O'Bryan	I-pers
.	O
Ryan	O
,	O
Farrel	O
,	O
Macmahon	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Macdonal	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
Intention	O
to	O
rob	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
:	O
We	O
went	O
above	O
the	O
Half-way-House	O
into	O
the	O
Foot-Road	O
.	O
We	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Path	O
,	O
so	O
Ryan	O
,	O
Farrel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
farthest	O
from	O
the	O
Road	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
and	O
two	O
Six-pences	O
This	O
was	O
beyond	O
Mother	O
Redcap	O
's	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
Ryan	O
bid	O
him	O
deliver	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
commanded	O
Farrel	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Ditch	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
poor	O
Servant	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
resistance	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wig	O
,	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
Shirt	O
,	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Buckles	O
.	O
The	O
Stockings	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Ryan	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Man	O
has	O
sworn	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
next	O
?	O
O	O
Bryan	O
.	O
We	O
bound	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Penny	O
Cord	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
;	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
were	O
ty	O
'd	O
behind	O
him	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Legs	O
.	O
Ryan	O
,	O
Farrel	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
bound	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
High	O
Road	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
With	O
what	O
intent	O
did	O
they	O
stand	O
there	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
For	O
fear	O
any	O
enterprize	O
should	O
come	O
upon	O
us	O
:	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
Macmahon	O
and	O
Macdonald	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
and	O
join	O
'd	O
us	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
Observe	O
how	O
often	O
he	O
convinces	O
(	O
contradict	O
)	O
his	O
own	O
Story	O
.	O
O	O
Bryan	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
brought	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
to	O
Ryan	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
Let	O
his	O
Informations	O
before	O
Col.	O
De-Viel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Governor	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
be	O
produc	O
'd	O
then	O
we	O
'll	O
stand	O
in	O
our	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
alledge	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Behalf	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trangress	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Sin	O
and	O
a	O
Shame	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
a	O
Villain	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
.	O
Owen	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Col.	O
Williamson	O
O	O
Bryan	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Ryan	O
had	O
the	O
Stockings	O
on	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Buckles	O
in	O
his	O
Shoes	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
Rowbottom	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Ryan	O
in	O
Newgate	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
here	O
they	O
are	O
.	O
Rowbottom	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Stockings	O
and	O
Buckles	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Griffith	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
him	O
another	O
Pair	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
pull	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
my	O
Shirt	O
,	O
when	O
these	O
Fellows	O
swear	O
so	O
.	O
Col.	O
Williamson	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
O'Bryan	O
's	O
Information	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
Sign	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Information	O
of	O
Terence	B-pers
O'Bryan	I-pers
,	O
taken	O
before	O
Col.	O
Williamson	O
.	O
Who	O
saith	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Macmahon	I-pers
,	O
Garret	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
,	O
were	O
out	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
since	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
particularly	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
stripping	O
him	O
and	O
tying	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Manner	O
he	O
deposed	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Fruer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
for	O
which	O
Fact	O
at	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
the	O
said	O
Fruer	O
was	O
condemned	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
farther	O
saith	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Fruer	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Robbery	O
,	O
nor	O
doth	O
he	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
farther	O
saith	O
,	O
that	O
among	O
the	O
Things	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buckles	O
,	O
both	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
by	O
O'Bryan	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
by	O
Short	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Buckles	O
and	O
Knife	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
that	O
Macdonald	O
was	O
not	O
assisting	O
in	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
within	O
Call	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
assistance	O
should	O
be	O
wanted	O
.	O
He	O
farther	O
faith	O
,	O
that	O
James	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
about	O
two	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
single	O
Man	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
between	O
Highgate	O
and	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
,	O
which	O
Man	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
Ryan	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
Fitzgerald	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
stripp	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Skin	O
,	O
ty	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
was	O
about	O
9s	O
.	O
as	O
Ryan	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
Falconer	O
is	O
a	O
thick	O
Man	O
,	O
about	O
36	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
wears	O
a	O
Wig	O
but	O
often	O
a	O
Cap	O
:	O
Fitzgerald	O
is	O
about	O
23	O
Years	O
old	O
a	O
tight	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
Wig	O
.	O
Col.	O
Williamson	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
several	O
Depositions	O
,	O
some	O
Robberies	O
he	O
forgot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
recollected	O
them	O
by	O
piece	O
meal	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
one	O
after	O
another	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
another	O
Information	O
.	O
-	O
Terence	O
O'Bryan	O
farther	O
deposeth	O
,	O
that	O
Garret	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
a	O
Robbery	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
by	O
robbing	O
,	O
stripping	O
,	O
and	O
binding	O
a	O
Man	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
Farrel	O
is	O
a	O
tall	O
,	O
lusty	O
Fellow	O
,	O
full	O
Face	O
,	O
black	O
Hair	O
,	O
wears	O
a	O
red	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
about	O
28	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
He	O
farther	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
Dun	O
and	O
Lacey	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
above	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
in	O
enlisting	O
Men	O
for	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
.	O
Farrel	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
bring	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
elsewhere	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
doing	O
Work	O
for	O
honest	O
Victuals	O
.	O
-	O
Pray	O
from	O
whence	O
did	O
we	O
descend	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
O'Bryan	O
From	O
one	O
Dive	O
's	O
House	O
four	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
Lacey	O
and	O
Dun	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Rowbottom	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
Robbery	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Ryan	O
,	O
Farrel	O
,	O
Macmahon	O
,	O
and	O
Macdonald	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Lacey	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Reason	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
mark	O
'd	O
.	O
Lacey	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
waiting	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
Dives	O
is	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
Guards	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
Newtoners-Lane	O
.	O
Farrel	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
this	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
recruit	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
France	O
.	O
Farrel	O
.	O
I	O
serve	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
-	O
God	O
bless	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Rogue	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
serve	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
France	O
.	O
Ryan	O
.	O
With	O
humble	O
Submission	O
,	O
-	O
this	O
Rogue	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
rightly	O
tell	O
it	O
you	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
Coats	O
of	O
other	O
People	O
's	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
Col.	O
Williamson	O
.	O
O'Bryan	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
Officers	O
,	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
having	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Tea	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Colonel	O
Deacon	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
a	O
Man	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Gaol	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
Liberty	O
,	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
naughty	O
Person	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Pistol	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
my	O
Assistance	O
to	O
examine	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
appear	O
'd	O
nothing	O
against	O
him	O
but	O
his	O
having	O
two	O
Coats	O
and	O
a	O
loaded	O
Pistol	O
,	O
made	O
us	O
suspect	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
naughty	O
Fellow	O
.	O
I	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
commit	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
to	O
describe	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Coats	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
discover	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
make	O
no	O
Discovery	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
made	O
his	O
Mittimus	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
Proof	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
he	O
would	O
become	O
a	O
frank	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
declared	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
's	O
Service	O
.	O
Farrel	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
nothing	O
against	O
me	O
but	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
Shoul	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
all	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
the	O
Sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
.	O
Eliz	O
Dorrel	O
.	O
Farrel	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
mean	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
He	O
us	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
he	O
abided	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
betimes	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
with	O
his	O
Knot	O
and	O
Basket	O
to	O
Market	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
came	O
Home	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
stirr	O
'd	O
out	O
an	O
Hour	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
stirr	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
to	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
from	O
Market	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
never	O
in	O
all	O
this	O
Time	O
stirr	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
neither	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoons	O
nor	O
in	O
the	O
Evenings	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
he	O
spend	O
his	O
Time	O
?	O
Dorrel	O
.	O
In	O
cleaning	O
the	O
Knives	O
,	O
or	O
fetching	O
me	O
Water	O
,	O
or	O
playing	O
with	O
the	O
Children	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
any	O
Evening	O
all	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
he	O
then	O
?	O
Dorrel	O
.	O
At	O
Home	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
on	O
my	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Virtue	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
suspect	O
(	O
inspect	O
)	O
into	O
Days	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
true	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
my	O
self	O
sometimes	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
was	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
?	O
Dorrel	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
Sunday	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
?	O
Dorrel	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
-	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Virtue	O
of	O
my	O
Oath	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
miss	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
the	O
26th	O
nor	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
has	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
O'Callan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
him	O
every	O
Morning	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
Market	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Market	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
all	O
the	O
Week	O
;	O
on	O
Sundays	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
Shoe	O
blacking	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
always	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
(	O
no	O
)	O
more	O
.	O
All	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
21	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Gulliforth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Callamanco	O
Stay	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Amber	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
December	O
2	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22	O
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
24	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	O
Manning	O
,	O
Dec	O
20	O
Guilty	O
on	O
both	O
Indictments	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23	O
,	O
24	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Moulding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Gew	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Pig	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
23	O
.	O
in	O
his	O
Stable	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25	O
,	O
26	O
,	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Dodds	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dodds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
edg	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
Lace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
29	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Book	O
,	O
1736	O
,	O
Page	O
50	O
.	O
27	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
belonging	O
to	O
Philip	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
Earl	O
of	O
Chesterfield	O
,	O
Dec.	O
29	O
.	O
then	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
Building	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Felony	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28	O
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Strangbridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s	O
and	O
6	O
d	O
in	O
Monies	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Franklyn	I-pers
,	O
Dec	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30	O
,	O
Elleaner	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sprouting	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Michael	O
Bread-street	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Tortoise-shell	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
rimm	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Bourcher	B-pers
Dorrel	I-pers
,	O
December	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
,	O
January	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33	O
,	O
34	O
,	O
35	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
Victualler	O
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Baws	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
Cordwainer	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
Brandy-man	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
Misdemeanor	O
,	O
in	O
contriving	O
and	O
conspiring	O
falsly	O
to	O
charge	O
John	B-pers
Drinkwater	I-pers
with	O
a	O
Felony	O
and	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
April	O
16	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
8th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
having	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
they	O
proceeded	O
to	O
call	O
their	O
Witnesses	O
John	O
Drinkwater	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
six	O
Months	O
with	O
Warwick	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
Sheer	O
Lane	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
disorderly	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
scarce	O
a	O
Night	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
Gentlemens	O
Pockets	O
were	O
pick	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
He	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
the	O
Profits	O
of	O
his	O
House	O
would	O
maintain	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
myself	O
safe	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
away	O
sooner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
sworn	O
into	O
a	O
Goal	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1735	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Wills	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Curtis	O
and	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
and	O
Pye	O
and	O
Williams	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
all	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
stealing	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
Warwick	O
ordered	O
me	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
immediately	O
enter	O
'd	O
an	O
Action	O
against	O
me	O
for	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
arrested	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
Wood	O
street	O
Compter	O
directly	O
:	O
Then	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
Wife	O
from	O
assisting	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
arrested	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
Action	O
,	O
at	O
somebody	O
's	O
suit	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
she	O
'd	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
lodged	O
in	O
Wood	O
street	O
Compter	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
detain	O
'd	O
by	O
Virtue	O
of	O
a	O
Warrant	O
of	O
Detainer	O
,	O
from	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Oath	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Baws	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
it	O
here	O
,	O
somewhere	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
had	O
notice	O
,	O
that	O
Warwick	O
had	O
withdrawn	O
his	O
Action	O
for	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
remove	O
to	O
Chelmsford	O
Jail	O
in	O
Essex	O
;	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Compter	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
of	O
April	O
:	O
They	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
betimes	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
Chelmsford	O
Jail	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Ray	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Chelmsford	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Conspiracy	O
,	O
came	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
to	O
the	O
Compter-Gate	O
to	O
attend	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
five	O
Miles	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
Warwick	O
,	O
Joyce	O
,	O
Meads	O
and	O
Wills	O
,	O
waited	O
for	O
my	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
the	O
People	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Essex	O
Gang	O
,	O
and	O
Broomhall	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
Stick	O
to	O
defend	O
my	O
self	O
with	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Jail	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
the	O
People	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
several	O
Jails	O
already	O
;	O
so	O
upon	O
this	O
Account	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
used	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
loaded	O
with	O
the	O
heaviest	O
Irons	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Jail	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
here	O
confin	O
'd	O
and	O
iron	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
Assizes	O
in	O
July	O
following	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Week	O
before	O
the	O
Assizes	O
,	O
Wills	O
and	O
Warwick	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
agree	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
Joyce	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Angel	O
Tavern	O
by	O
Temple	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
agree	O
likewise	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
say	O
'd	O
they	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
cruelly	O
and	O
wrongfully	O
charged	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
punish	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
be	O
discharged	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
with	O
them	O
'till	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
Justice	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
another	O
Jayl	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
my	O
Wife	O
should	O
be	O
in	O
Jayl	O
too	O
.	O
Warwick	O
say	O
'd	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
Wills	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
Letter	O
,	O
informing	O
me	O
,	O
That	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
in	O
Prison	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
Jayl	O
on	O
a	O
Charge	O
of	O
Perjury	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
acquitted	O
or	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Assizes	O
?	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
No	O
body	O
appear	O
'd	O
against	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Assizes	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
mov	O
'd	O
from	O
Chelmsford	O
to	O
Hartford	O
Jayl	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Campbel	O
,	O
who	O
calls	O
himself	O
an	O
Attorney	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
them	O
declare	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
?	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
Fit	O
of	O
Sickness	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
preferr	O
'd	O
a	O
Bill	O
against	O
Wills	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
Warwick	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
and	O
threaten	O
'd	O
me	O
-	O
C.	O
They	O
are	O
indicted	O
for	O
conspiring	O
to	O
charge	O
you	O
with	O
robbing	O
Baws	O
,	O
-	O
speak	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
apprehended	O
Baws	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
cruel	O
Thing	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
privy	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
Conspiracy	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
-	O
they	O
got	O
some	O
body	O
to	O
personate	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
threaten	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Since	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
often	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Matter	O
up	O
,	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
not	O
in	O
Person	O
,	O
)	O
but	O
I	O
always	O
shunn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
always	O
avoided	O
them	O
.	O
Counsel	O
Def	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
this	O
Discourse	O
with	O
Baws	O
?	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
At	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Best	O
's	O
in	O
Sheer-Lane	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Mr	O
Wills	O
present	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
attending	O
the	O
Society	O
for	O
Reformation	O
of	O
Manners	O
at	O
Bow	O
Church	O
.	O
Warwick	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
me	O
Letters	O
from	O
Chelmsford	O
?	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
produce	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
send	O
him	O
some	O
Letters	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
cruel	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
discharge	O
my	O
Wife	O
;	O
but	O
never	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Warwick	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Company	O
present	O
when	O
I	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
Chelmsford	O
Jayl	O
about	O
discharging	O
you	O
?	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
every	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
your	O
Company	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
but	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
Wills	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
.	O
Counsel	O
Def	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
willingly	O
ask	O
you	O
any	O
Questions	O
,	O
to	O
draw	O
you	O
into	O
Difficulties	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
consider	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
upon	O
your	O
Oath	O
.	O
-	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
others	O
into	O
this	O
Indictment	O
?	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
none	O
but	O
what	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
.	O
Counsel	O
Def	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Money	O
from	O
others	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
their	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
?	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
Never	O
,	O
one	O
Farthing	O
Counsel	O
Def	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
send	O
to	O
Wills	O
by	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
offer	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
you	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Release	O
?	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
Not	O
for	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
such	O
Sum	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
spoke	O
to	O
,	O
by	O
several	O
People	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
divers	O
Sums	O
Counsel	O
Def	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
send	O
one	O
Lydia	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
to	O
Wills	O
?	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
Never	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Counsel	O
Def	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
Money	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
Farthing	O
of	O
her	O
Money	O
;	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
ever	O
send	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
Wills	O
.	O
Morris	O
and	O
Atkins	O
has	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
them	O
first	O
.	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
's	O
Clerk	O
has	O
asked	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
never	O
agree	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Counsel	O
Def	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
threaten	O
to	O
put	O
others	O
into	O
this	O
Conspiracy	O
?	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
this	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
in	O
Hartfordshire	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Counsel	O
Def	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
declared	O
you	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
if	O
you	O
could	O
?	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
mention	O
'd	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
such	O
Subject	O
.	O
Counsel	O
Def	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
said	O
you	O
would	O
hang	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Defendants	O
?	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
Warwick	O
would	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
prodigious	O
Rogue	O
always	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Counsel	O
Def	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
threaten	O
to	O
put	O
Lydia	O
Clark	O
into	O
this	O
Conspiracy	O
?	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Warwick	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Bill	O
when	O
Sayer	O
indicted	O
me	O
for	O
two	O
Robberies	O
in	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
that	O
Trial	O
he	O
declared	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
hang	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
transport	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
keep	O
me	O
in	O
Jayl	O
for	O
Life	O
.	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Sayer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Wills	O
and	O
Warwick	O
-	O
Baws	O
I	O
know	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Action	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
Yard	O
19	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
alter	O
'd	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Joyner	O
,	O
Shop	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Coffee-house	O
.	O
Warwick	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
four	O
Months	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1735	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
Warwick	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drunk	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
a-bed	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
Drinkwater	O
's	O
Watch	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
God	O
to	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
must	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
keep	O
him	O
poor	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Drinkwater	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
the	O
four	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
Warwick	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
arrested	O
Drinkwater	O
in	O
an	O
Action	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
People	O
enough	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
(	O
Drinkwater	O
)	O
was	O
arrested	O
for	O
Debt	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Tibbalds	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
informed	O
Warwick	O
,	O
that	O
Drinkwater	O
was	O
making	O
an	O
Information	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
Robberies	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
Account	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
contriv	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
After	O
many	O
Consultations	O
,	O
(	O
at	O
which	O
Warwick	O
,	O
Wills	O
,	O
Clark	O
,	O
Pritchard	O
,	O
Curtis	O
,	O
Joyce	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
present	O
,	O
)	O
Joyce	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Baws	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
every	O
thing	O
upon	O
this	O
terrible	O
Occasion	O
.	O
The	O
Substance	O
of	O
the	O
Discourse	O
was	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Robbery	O
sworn	O
against	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
Pritchard	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
their	O
Company	O
when	O
Baws	O
was	O
first	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
;	O
and	O
Warwick	O
asked	O
Baws	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
undertake	O
to	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
Drinkwater	O
;	O
Baws	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
:	O
Then	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
much	O
Money	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
give	O
him	O
20	O
s.	O
Whether	O
it	O
was	O
Warwick	O
or	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
that	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Question	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
.	O
They	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
next	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
whole	O
Affair	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
to	O
Warwick	O
's	O
Management	O
,	O
-	O
Baws	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
chose	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
somewhere	O
about	O
Ham	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
best	O
acquainted	O
with	O
that	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
he	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
20	O
s.	O
for	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
swear	O
to	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
believe	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
am	O
poor	O
in	O
Apparel	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
will	O
know	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
much	O
Money	O
to	O
lose	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Time	O
they	O
made	O
this	O
Agreement	O
with	O
Baws	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
seven	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
collected	O
3	O
s	O
a-piece	O
;	O
Warwick	O
,	O
Wills	O
,	O
Clark	O
,	O
Williams	O
,	O
Joyce	O
,	O
and	O
Curtis	O
laid	O
down	O
3s	O
.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
Pritchard	O
being	O
absent	O
,	O
they	O
laid	O
down	O
3s	O
.	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
sad	O
Thing	O
to	O
hang	O
a	O
Man	O
wrongfully	O
,	O
and	O
Warwick	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Sin	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
hang	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
agreed	O
thus	O
far	O
,	O
Baws	O
and	O
Joyce	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Justice	O
Newton	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Warrant	O
of	O
Detainer	O
against	O
Drinkwater	O
,	O
but	O
Justice	O
Newton	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Warwick	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
this	O
will	O
hang	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
slept	O
in	O
my	O
Bed	O
'till	O
I	O
made	O
Oath	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Ayres	O
,	O
in	O
June	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Chelmsford	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
Expence	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
Drinkwater	O
upon	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
Campbel	O
the	O
Lawyer	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
afterwards	O
)	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Hertford	O
Goal	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
never	O
pretended	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
.	O
Sayer	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
must	O
do	O
it	O
to	O
save	O
their	O
own	O
Lives	O
.	O
They	O
talked	O
to	O
Baws	O
about	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Assizes	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
better	O
rigg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
be	O
well	O
drest	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
paid	O
3	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
round	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
laid	O
down	O
3s	O
.	O
for	O
Pritchard	O
;	O
the	O
odd	O
Shilling	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
a	O
Dinner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Warrant	O
of	O
Detainer	O
,	O
what	O
happen	O
'd	O
next	O
?	O
Sayer	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Warrant	O
to	O
detain	O
him	O
,	O
Baws	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
very	O
proper	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
Sight	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
.	O
Warwick	O
describ	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
his	O
Speech	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
Thing	O
,	O
very	O
particularly	O
;	O
but	O
Baws	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
six	O
agreed	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
Letter	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Drinkwater	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
Baws	O
came	O
there	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
answer	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
all	O
agreed	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
see	O
him	O
when	O
they	O
remov	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Chelmsford	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Business	O
was	O
to	O
get	O
an	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
cost	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
all	O
agreed	O
to	O
club	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Pray	O
what	O
is	O
Warwick	O
?	O
Warwick	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
-	O
Acquaintance	O
-	O
of	O
hers	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
cohabited	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
.	O
You	O
'll	O
please	O
to	O
take	O
Notice	O
that	O
all	O
this	O
which	O
she	O
swears	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
are	O
now	O
indicted	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
a	O
Trial	O
in	O
this	O
Court	O
some	O
Time	O
ago	O
;	O
this	O
Woman	O
tried	O
Warwick	O
for	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
with	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
in	O
St.	O
Clements	O
Church	O
Yard	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Warwick	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
her	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
liv	O
'd	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
no	O
Felony	O
.	O
Sayer	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
-	O
Counc	O
.	O
Def	O
You	O
have	O
told	O
a	O
very	O
long	O
Story	O
,	O
Madam	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
have	O
an	O
excellent	O
Memory	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
any	O
Body	O
talk	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
Money	O
but	O
Baws	O
and	O
Warwick	O
?	O
Sayer	O
All	O
the	O
Persons	O
I	O
have	O
nam	O
'd	O
were	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
join	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
in	O
my	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Clements	O
Churchyard	O
.	O
Counc.Def	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Sayer	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Drinkwater	I-pers
.	O
When	O
my	O
Husband	O
was	O
arrested	O
in	O
Warwick	O
's	O
sham	O
Action	O
,	O
Joyce	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
assisted	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
arrested	O
before	O
the	O
Week	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
I	O
was	O
arrested	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
Lydia	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
alias	O
Clark	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
Assizes	O
,	O
they	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Warwick	O
said	O
they	O
must	O
confine	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Husband	O
might	O
be	O
starv	O
'd	O
in	O
Goal	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Officers	O
House	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
sign	O
a	O
Bond	O
,	O
and	O
oblige	O
my	O
self	O
not	O
to	O
assist	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Plaintiffs	O
should	O
discharge	O
me	O
.	O
Wills	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
drinking	O
Punch	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lepards	O
in	O
Wharton-Court	O
,	O
Holborn	O
,	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
Bars	O
,	O
nearer	O
London	O
then	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
thank	O
my	O
Black-guard	O
Husband	O
for	O
my	O
being	O
arrested	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
big	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
an	O
Hour	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
hurry	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Their	O
Intent	O
was	O
to	O
distress	O
my	O
Husband	O
in	O
Jayl	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
sign	O
Releases	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
prosecured	O
for	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Warwick	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
what	O
's	O
her	O
Way	O
of	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
?	O
C.	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
is	O
a	O
Sadler	O
by	O
Trade	O
;	O
and	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Jayl	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
supported	O
by	O
Friends	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
9	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
12	O
Months	O
in	O
Jayl	O
.	O
Warwick	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
common	O
Prostitute	O
?	O
Counc	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
And	O
pray	O
what	O
are	O
we	O
to	O
ask	O
you	O
?	O
Mr.	O
North	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
April	O
16	O
.	O
1735	O
,	O
when	O
Drinkwater	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
one	O
Christopher	B-pers
Baws	I-pers
came	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
positively	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
looking	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
this	O
distance	O
of	O
Time	O
,	O
nor	O
can	O
I	O
say	O
positively	O
whether	O
his	O
Information	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
these	O
Memorandums	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Book	O
.	O
The	O
Party	O
accused	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
brought	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
I	O
believe	O
of	O
it	O
's	O
not	O
being	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Def	O
If	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Information	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
that	O
only	O
must	O
be	O
read	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
If	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Information	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
now	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
and	O
shall	O
we	O
not	O
read	O
there	O
Minutes	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
Ground	O
and	O
Substance	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
then	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Information	O
,	O
that	O
Information	O
was	O
fram	O
'd	O
?	O
Mr.	O
North	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
is	O
a	O
competent	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
,	O
usual	O
Course	O
of	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
North	O
.	O
Baws	O
swore	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
that	O
Drinkwater	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
forget	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
but	O
't	O
was	O
somewhere	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Words	O
in	O
my	O
Memorandum	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Warrant	O
of	O
Detainer	O
granted	O
,	O
and	O
Baws	O
enter	O
'd	O
into	O
a	O
Recognizance	O
of	O
40	O
l	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
next	O
Assizes	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Baws	O
till	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
Drinkwater	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
recollect	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
this	O
Transaction	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Person	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
answers	O
the	O
Description	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Keeper	O
of	O
Woodstreet	O
Compter	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Warrant	O
of	O
Detainer	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
Drinkwater	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
Custody	O
on	O
an	O
Action	O
for	O
Debt	O
.	O
Mr.	O
North	O
The	O
Body	O
of	O
this	O
Warrant	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
Writing	O
,	O
the	O
Signing	O
was	O
by	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
into	O
Baws	O
Hands	O
.	O
London	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
Woodstreet	O
Compter	O
.	O
Detain	O
in	O
your	O
Custody	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
John	O
Drinkwater	O
,	O
charged	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
Oath	O
of	O
Christopher	O
Baws	O
,	O
for	O
assaulting	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
him	O
keep	O
in	O
safe	O
Custody	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
shall	O
be	O
discharged	O
by	O
due	O
Course	O
of	O
Law	O
:	O
given	O
under	O
my	O
Hand	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
April	O
16	O
,	O
1735.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Drinkwater	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
us	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
or	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Action	O
was	O
discharged	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Detainer	O
came	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
came	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
Essex	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ray	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Virtue	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Chelmsford	O
.	O
Warwick	O
and	O
Wills	O
I	O
met	O
at	O
Stratford	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
towards	O
London	O
.	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
they	O
both	O
go	O
some	O
Miles	O
with	O
us	O
hallowing	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
a	O
Yard	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
Drinkwater	O
lives	O
upon	O
the	O
Reversion	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
Sharper	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
Strumpet	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
give	O
no	O
Credit	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
should	O
be	O
asham	O
'd	O
of	O
being	O
seen	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Wills	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Fet	O
er-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
for	O
John	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Warwick	O
,	O
Wills	O
,	O
Joyce	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
present	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Baws	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
bring	O
an	O
Habeas	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Paper	O
he	O
sign	O
'd	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Clerk	O
reads	O
.	O
Christopher	O
-	O
Baws	O
his	O
Mark	O
.	O
Witness	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
hereby	O
authorize	O
you	O
to	O
bring	O
an	O
Habeas	O
Corpus	O
for	O
John	O
Drinkwater	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
charged	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
Warrant	O
of	O
Detainer	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
Compter	O
.	O
For	O
your	O
so	O
doing	O
this	O
shall	O
be	O
your	O
sufficient	O
Warrant	O
.	O
Ray	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Expence	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
apprehend	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
joyn	O
'd	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
all	O
;	O
Warwick	O
,	O
Wills	O
,	O
Joyce	O
,	O
Meads	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Broomhall	I-pers
.	O
Drinkwater	O
became	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Warwick	O
's	O
Suit	O
for	O
