TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminor	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1736	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
THOMPSON	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1736	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXVII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Page	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Fortescue	B-pers
Aland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burchet	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Lester	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bignal	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mussin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Fowl	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Tyers	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Brock	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hasswittle	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pyke	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roice	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fullforth	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Lebeck	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thornhill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Sugar	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
and	O
Zachary	B-pers
Borian	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
Jan	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
John	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Butolph	I-place
,	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
Feb.	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Soames	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
China	O
Punch-bowl	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Picture	O
with	O
cut	O
Work	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
Copper	O
Sauce-pans	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
small	O
Looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Box-iron	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
,	O
December	O
16	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
4	O
,	O
5.	O
Henry	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Anne	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
their	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
Day	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Whitesides	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Henry	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
a	O
certain	O
Pavement	O
of	O
Stones	O
,	O
did	O
cast	O
and	O
throw	O
down	O
the	O
said	O
Whitesides	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
such	O
casting	O
and	O
throwing	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Whitesides	O
,	O
did	O
receive	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
and	O
Bruise	O
,	O
which	O
fractured	O
his	O
Skull	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
and	O
Bruise	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Whitesides	O
did	O
languish	O
,	O
and	O
languishingly	O
lived	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
committing	O
this	O
Felony	O
,	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
comforting	O
the	O
said	O
Dodson	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
feloniously	O
staying	O
the	O
said	O
Whitesides	O
.	O
Mr.	O
How	O
.	O
January	O
14	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
George	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
with	O
my	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Hubbub	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Carter	O
beating	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
likewise	O
my	O
Servant	O
)	O
that	O
somebody	O
was	O
beating	O
the	O
Boy	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
Carter	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
beat	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
tripped	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
resolved	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Deveil	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
before	O
some	O
other	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
haul	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
walk	O
very	O
civilly	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
would-not	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Minute	O
I	O
had	O
loosen	O
'd	O
my	O
Hold	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Dodson	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Deceased	O
seeing	O
Carter	O
run	O
,	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
if	O
Dodson	O
had	O
not	O
with	O
a	O
Jostle	O
thrown	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
Carter	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
informed	O
that	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Leeson	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
I	O
met	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
immediately	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Servant	O
was	O
Speechless	O
and	O
his	O
Skull	O
broke	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
till	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
had	O
his	O
Senses	O
all	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Dodson	O
throw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
down	O
?	O
How	O
.	O
When	O
Carter	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
passed	O
Dodson	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Hunch	O
,	O
which	O
turned	O
him	O
quite	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
falling	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
(	O
Dodson	O
)	O
put	O
out	O
his	O
Foot	O
and	O
trip	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
a	O
Trice	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cajor	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'Clock	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
)	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Bustle	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
-	O
't	O
was	O
in	O
Sidney	B-place
's	I-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
by	I-place
Leicester-Fields	I-place
,	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Carter	O
beating	O
George	O
Hart	O
.	O
Mr.	O
How	O
(	O
Hart	O
's	O
Master	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Carter	O
why	O
he	O
beat	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
he	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
Mr.	O
How	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Carter	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
held	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
walk	O
very	O
civilly	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
Mr.	O
How	O
let	O
him	O
loose	O
,	O
away	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
Whitesides	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
passing	O
by	O
Dodson	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Jostle	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
which	O
turned	O
him	O
quite	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
backwards	O
with	O
his	O
Head	O
upon	O
the	O
Pavestones	O
;	O
I	O
helped	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stunn	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Fall	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Head	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
.	O
This	O
happened	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
following	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
sat	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
.	O
How	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
Health	O
when	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
out	O
on	O
this	O
Occasion	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
sedate	O
,	O
good	O
Servant	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
Man	O
could	O
have	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
but	O
once	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
this	O
Hurt	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hulet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
immediately	O
after	O
the	O
Fall	O
;	O
the	O
Blood	O
ran	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sighed	O
and	O
sweat	O
extreamly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
Agony	O
with	O
the	O
Pain	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
lifted	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
sit	O
still	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Minutes	O
he	O
walked	O
Home	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
.	O
As	O
Mr.	O
How	O
was	O
bringing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Carter	O
through	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
walk	O
without	O
being	O
held	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Minutes	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Jostle	O
,	O
which	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
sure	O
whether	O
he	O
jostled	O
him	O
down	O
or	O
tripped	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Falling	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ormered	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
Skull	O
fractured	O
and	O
a	O
Concussion	O
upon	O
the	O
Brain	O
,	O
he	O
languished	O
till	O
Monday	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
I	O
performed	O
the	O
Operation	O
of	O
the	O
Trepan	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
his	O
Death	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Skull	O
.	O
The	O
Fall	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Dodson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Leeson	O
,	O
and	O
Carter	O
is	O
my	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
How	O
's	O
Apprentice	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
Whig	O
upon	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
Carter	O
struck	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Fray	O
began	O
.	O
Mr.	O
How	O
came	O
and	O
hauled	O
Carter	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
let	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Liberty	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
ran	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
a	O
Bulk	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
threw	O
himself	O
down	O
.	O
Carter	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
touch	O
the	O
Wig	O
with	O
my	O
Hand	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
flew	O
upon	O
me	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
found	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Death	O
Accidental	O
.	O
6.	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Sturgeon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in-the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dally	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Feuase	I-pers
,	O
January	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
8.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles's-in-the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Cosby	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
February	O
7	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Eleven	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
January	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Stormy	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11	O
,	O
12.	O
James	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plucknet	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
24	O
.	O
And	O
Margaret	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
James	B-pers
Furnace	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin's-in-the-Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Glass	O
Decanters	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Levet	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
1	O
.	O
And	O
Margaret	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
one	O
Decanter	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Furnace	O
and	O
Stanley	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
Fox	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Sheers	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
28	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Portugal	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catherine	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Paul	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
3d	O
.	O
and	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Two-pence	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
July	O
11	O
,	O
1734	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
This	O
(	O
here	O
)	O
Man	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Friend	O
;	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1734	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Beal	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Gardiner	O
,	O
in	O
Ratcliffe-Highway	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
would	O
see	O
me	O
Home	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
in	O
Kent	O
Street	O
Road	O
;	O
they	O
pretended	O
they	O
would	O
see	O
me	O
safe	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
within	O
a	O
Stone	O
's	O
Cast	O
of	O
East-Smithfield	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shoved	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Knive	O
and	O
Five	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Two-pence	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
over-against	O
a	O
Distiller	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
Light	O
or	O
Dark	O
when	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
Cross	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
Dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
first	O
after	O
this	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
?	O
Cross	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Barnaby-street	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
speaking	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
discover	O
my	O
Mind	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
since	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
Knife	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Cross	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
consider	O
-	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
possible	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
Cross	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
this	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
that	O
Day	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Beal	O
's	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gathering	O
Cucumbers	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
End	O
of	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Friend	O
,	O
would	O
conduct	O
me	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Pray	O
where	O
did	O
I	O
work	O
?	O
Cross	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Beal	O
's	O
a	O
Gardiner	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Does	O
not	O
your	O
Father	O
go	O
by	O
some	O
other	O
Name	O
?	O
Cross	O
.	O
My	O
Name	O
is	O
Paul	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Father	O
's	O
Name	O
is	O
Hercules	O
Cross	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Paul	O
!	O
-	O
O	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Name	O
Paul	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Beal	O
's	O
when	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
nor	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Paul	O
,	O
I	O
declare	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
fuddled	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
sad	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Women	O
there	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
their	O
Company	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
17.	O
George	B-pers
Presgrove	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Geare	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Brass	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Midwinter	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
Mob	O
and	O
three	O
Slips	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stibbs	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
20.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
Neck	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
Jaw	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
lunatick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
spoke	O
for	O
many	O
Months	O
past	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
back	O
to	O
Newgate	O
'till	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
otherwise	O
be	O
disposed	O
of	O
.	O
21.	O
William	B-pers
Maw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
upon	O
Charles	B-pers
Dubois	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Iron	O
and	O
Steel	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
,	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
beat	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
below	O
the	O
Collar	O
Bone	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
3	O
4ths	O
of	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
By	O
Reason	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
he	O
languished	O
,	O
and	O
languishingly	O
lived	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
20th	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
for	O
Stabbing	O
)	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
Jan	O
20.	O
on	O
Charles	O
Dubois	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Fury	O
of	O
his	O
Mind	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
below	O
the	O
Collar	O
Bone	O
did	O
stab	O
;	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
Weapon	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
giving	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
as	O
above	O
)	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
20th	O
to	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Wound	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
by	O
Virtue	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sturgeon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
my	O
Fellow	O
Watchman	O
.	O
The	O
Night	O
this	O
Murder	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
giving	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Twelve	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
my	O
self	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
who	O
comes	O
there	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
-	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
sure	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
)	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Cask	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
Damn	O
thee	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
what	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
thee	O
?	O
He	O
pass	O
'd	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
no	O
Harm	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
no	O
Words	O
in	O
Anger	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
damn	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
damn	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
fell	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Paces	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
pursuing	O
her	O
,	O
my	O
Partner	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
O	O
Lord	O
,	O
Watch	O
!	O
Watch	O
!	O
the	O
Rogue	O
has	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
!	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
secure	O
her	O
till	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
tripping	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
round	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
-	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sure	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
of	O
Heaven	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
or	O
the	O
Deceased	O
give	O
any	O
Provocation	O
?	O
Sturgeon	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a'miss	O
(	O
an	O
amiss	O
)	O
Word	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
Mouths	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Provocation	O
given	O
,	O
excepting	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Blow	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Deceased	O
?	O
Sturgeon	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
quarrelsome	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
careful	O
good	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
send	O
for	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
Guard	O
all	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
C.	O
That	O
's	O
an	O
old	O
Story	O
,	O
indeed	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dubois	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Widow	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
Death-bed	O
he	O
declared	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
assisting	O
this	O
Watchman	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stabbed	O
by	O
a	O
Soldier	O
with	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
from	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
to	O
Friday	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
declar	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
murder	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Edmunds	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
One	O
,	O
to	O
dress	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wound	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
imagine	O
it	O
was	O
mortal	O
;	O
but	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
After	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
left	O
Lobe	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
was	O
penetrated	O
;	O
this	O
occasion	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Effusion	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
Guard	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
Corporal	O
:	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
upon	O
Duty	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Wife	O
I	O
must	O
return	O
to	O
my	O
Duty	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
promis	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
home	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Guard-Room	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Corporal	O
not	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
King-Street	B-place
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
20	O
Yards	O
from	O
King-Street	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Pole	O
,	O
struck	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
we	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
struck	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Mob	O
parted	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Fountain	O
in	O
King-Street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
drank	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Pints	O
of	O
Beer	O
with	O
one	O
Lamb	O
,	O
who	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
Trade	O
of	O
Shoe-mending	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
a	O
Night-Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Lawyer	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
Paper	O
would	O
satisfy	O
the	O
Court	O
'till	O
To-morrow	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Fellow	O
Soldier	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
upon	O
Guard	O
that	O
Night	O
after	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
in	O
King-Street	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Barrel	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulders	O
then	O
:	O
His	O
Nose	O
was	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Blow	O
between	O
his	O
Eyes	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
fighting	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
with	O
whom	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Cellar	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
murder	O
'd	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
laughed	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
so	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
Corporal	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
About	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Guard-Room	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
not	O
,	O
'till	O
almost	O
4	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
King-Street	O
.	O
He	O
drew	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
something	O
would	O
have	O
attended	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
smil	O
'd	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Aye	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
would	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Church-lane	O
.	O
On	O
Jan.	O
14	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
Night	O
about	O
Ten	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
come	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
,	O
about	O
Eight	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
their	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
Time	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Cut	O
cross	O
his	O
Nose	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
two	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
resticall	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
play	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
Relation	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
-	O
no	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
-	O
this	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
do	O
for	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
without	O
he	O
would	O
procure	O
her	O
some	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
she	O
meant	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
say	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
know	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
and	O
make	O
Answer	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Woman	O
did	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
-	O
this	O
Woman	O
she	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Proviso	O
he	O
would	O
produce	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
and	O
make	O
Answer	O
,	O
his	O
Substance	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bed	O
to	O
lye	O
upon	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
would	O
signify	O
nothing	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
all	O
I	O
do	O
know	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
22.	O
Jeffery	B-pers
Morat	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Murat	I-pers
,	O
(	O
a	O
Negro	O
)	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Peregrine	B-pers
Bertie	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
commonly	O
call	O
'd	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Lindsey	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
thence	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Breast	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Peregrine	O
Bertie	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Feb	O
1	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Hannah	B-pers
Emberton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Peregrine	B-pers
Bertie	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
commonly	O
call	O
'd	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Lindsey	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Stuff	O
and	O
Silk	O
Pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Corkscrew	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
Three-pence	O
Half-penny	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Hannah	O
Emberton	O
to	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Feb	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
having	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Honour	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
Lord	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Examination	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
him	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
read	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
set	O
his	O
Mark	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Lord	O
Carpenter	O
sign	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Confession	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
The	O
Examination	O
of	O
Jeffery	O
Murat	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Morat	O
,	O
taken	O
and	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
George	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
1	O
.	O
1736.	O
``	O
Who	O
confesseth	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
his	O
``	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Manchester	O
;	O
that	O
meeting	O
``	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	O
a	O
Shooe-Boy	O
,	O
``	O
before	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
they	O
continued	O
together	O
``	O
till	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
``	O
agreed	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
the	O
Marquis	O
``	O
of	O
Lindsey	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Garden	O
``	O
Wall	O
,	O
opened	O
a	O
back	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
unbolted	O
``	O
the	O
Shutters	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
lay	O
conceal	O
'd	O
``	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
House	O
till	O
Morning	O
;	O
then	O
``	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
a	O
Beaufet	O
,	O
and	O
``	O
stole	O
from	O
thence	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
;	O
``	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Library	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
Beaufet	O
,	O
``	O
they	O
stole	O
2	O
Guineas	O
.	O
That	O
afterwards	O
they	O
``	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
``	O
Cloaths	O
of	O
Hannah	O
Emberton	O
,	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
``	O
said	O
House	O
:	O
But	O
hearing	O
her	O
come	O
in	O
about	O
``	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
this	O
Examinant	O
hid	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
``	O
afterwards	O
knocked	O
the	O
said	O
Hannah	O
down	O
with	O
``	O
an	O
Iron	O
Poker	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
``	O
he	O
owns	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
)	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
``	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
several	O
Wounds	O
;	O
``	O
that	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
up	O
the	O
``	O
Chimney	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
``	O
Pocket	O
Three-pence	O
Half-penny	O
.	O
Hannah	O
Emberton	O
appeared	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
weak	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
following	O
Evidence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
these	O
five	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Dutchess	O
of	O
Manchester	O
's	O
Black	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Door	O
broke	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
frighted	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
the	O
Study	O
Door	O
bolted	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
Thank	O
God	O
they	O
have	O
got	O
no	O
further	O
;	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
Courage	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Hall	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
attack	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
lock	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
and	O
spare	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
he	O
commanded	O
me	O
to	O
deliver	O
up	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
throw	O
them	O
somewhere	O
where	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
again	O
;	O
Oh	O
!	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
Keys	O
too	O
:	O
I	O
begged	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
kill	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
shut	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
He	O
must	O
kill	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
quickly	O
over	O
;	O
we	O
struggled	O
together	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
got	O
me	O
down	O
and	O
stabbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
my	O
Hands	O
sadly	O
as	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
save	O
myself	O
.	O
He	O
cut	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Hair	O
's	O
Breadth	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
stabbed	O
me	O
before	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
and	O
whetted	O
his	O
Knife	O
;	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
use	O
it	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
God	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
Leave	O
;	O
he	O
finding	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
dead	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
five	O
Blows	O
with	O
a	O
Scrubbing-Brush	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
this	O
perceiving	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Life	O
in	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
as	O
many	O
more	O
with	O
the	O
Brush	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
lay	O
for	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
Pockets	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
from	O
about	O
my	O
Neck	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
me	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
no	O
Life	O
in	O
me	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
shift	O
to	O
lift	O
up	O
my	O
Hand	O
and	O
undo	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
weak	O
that	O
my	O
Head	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
-	O
thus	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Morning	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
attacked	O
you	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Emberton	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
that	O
he	O
began	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
butchering	O
about	O
me	O
two	O
Hours	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
,	O
I	O
broke	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Squares	O
in	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
out	O
my	O
bloody	O
Hand	O
and	O
my	O
bloody	O
Hair	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
People	O
gathered	O
about	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
I	O
broke	O
down	O
the	O
Blind	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
sat	O
;	O
he	O
certainly	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
Silver	O
Thimble	O
and	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Emberton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nobody	O
besides	O
himself	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jennings	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Marquis	O
of	O
Lindsey	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Sash	O
break	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Bloody	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Murder	O
!	O
By	O
that	O
Time	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
Sash	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
tumble	O
herself	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
I	O
prevented	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
some	O
Chair-Men	O
and	O
their	O
Poles	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
perceive	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
there	O
lay	O
an	O
Iron	O
Poker	O
broke	O
in	O
Half	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Penknife	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
the	O
House	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
afterwards	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Chimnies	O
;	O
we	O
flung	O
Brickbats	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Tops	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
fall	O
through	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
searched	O
that	O
Chimney	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
into	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
smoaked	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
Straw	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Thimble	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Three-pence	O
Half-penny	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
Carpenter	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
examine	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
Examination	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
Chimney-Sweeper	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
in	O
Grosvenor-Square	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlefolks	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Chimnies	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Boys	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
Chimney	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
smoaked	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
straw	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
set	O
on	O
Fire	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
People	O
surrounded	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
on	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
23.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shrewsbury	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Threwsbury	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
it	O
a	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
it	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bay	O
.	O
This	O
Accident	O
happened	O
in	O
Moorfields	B-place
on	O
Friday	O
7-night	O
last	O
,	O
Application	O
was	O
made	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
a	O
Murder	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
Overseer	O
of	O
the	O
Poor	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
Guard	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
brought	O
a	O
skillful	O
Mid-wife	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
poor	O
Creature	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
sitting	O
upright	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Book	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tears	O
ran	O
plentifully	O
down	O
her	O
Face	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
searched	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
is	O
common	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
Vault	O
to	O
be	O
emptied	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
Contents	O
were	O
well	O
examined	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Midwife	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
examine	O
the	O
Woman	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
without	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
searched	O
the	O
Room	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
she	O
did	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
other	O
Woman	O
here	O
only	O
emptied	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Justice	O
discharged	O
her	O
because	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
all	O
on	O
herself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
on	O
the	O
Child	O
?	O
Mr	O
.	O
Boy	O
.	O
Only	O
the	O
Head	O
cut	O
about	O
half	O
off	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Midwife	O
.	O
The	O
Parish	O
Officer	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
enquired	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
no	O
direct	O
Answer	O
,	O
but	O
sat	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Bed	O
crying	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Book	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
nothing	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
this	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Bell	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
her	O
Orders	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
Bell	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
,	O
and	O
Bell	O
being	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
perswade	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
Examination	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
nothing	O
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
but	O
the	O
After-birth	O
;	O
for	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
she	O
threw	O
down	O
there	O
herself	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
Bell	O
had	O
inform	O
'd	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Child	O
into	O
the	O
Vault	O
:	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
in	O
my	O
Information	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
dead	O
when	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
havock	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Vault	O
was	O
raked	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
After-burthen	O
:	O
Still	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Child	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
empty	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Child	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
there	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
one	O
born	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Beadle	O
and	O
other	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
in	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
Bed	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
Rags	O
stain	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
-	O
at	O
the	O
Feet	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Box	O
with	O
more	O
Rags	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Condition	O
:	O
I	O
shook	O
them	O
all	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
Child	O
:	O
In	O
another	O
Box	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
that	O
put	O
me	O
upon	O
enquiring	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
only	O
put	O
some	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Nook	O
which	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
behind	O
a	O
small	O
Trunk	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
sew	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Cloth	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hole	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
swoon	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
recover	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
several	O
Questions	O
,	O
-	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
cut	O
her	O
Child	O
's	O
Throat	O
so	O
barbarously	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
in	O
her	O
present	O
Condition	O
have	O
Strength	O
to	O
sew	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
Devil	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
Strength	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
God	O
.	O
The	O
Lord	O
have	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Throat	O
cut	O
very	O
much	O
?	O
Palmer	O
It	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
cut	O
worse	O
,	O
unless	O
it	O
's	O
Head	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
quite	O
off	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
This	O
Bell	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Land-lady	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
her	O
come	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Mop	O
and	O
a	O
Pail	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Mary	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Key	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
ail	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Spots	O
of	O
Blood	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
Women	O
are	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
disorder	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
my	O
Landlady	O
Bell	O
is	O
coming	O
to	O
wipe	O
them	O
up	O
In	O
the	O
Closet	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Pan	O
full	O
of	O
Cloths	O
,	O
not	O
very	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
;	O
-	O
what	O
's	O
all	O
this	O
Mary	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
?	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
miscarry	O
'd	O
and	O
was	O
three	O
Months	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
some	O
hot	O
Watergruel	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
to	O
eat	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
settle	O
my	O
self	O
to	O
my	O
Work	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
in	O
my	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
(	O
to	O
make	O
short	O
of	O
my	O
Story	O
)	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
rest	O
'till	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
some	O
farther	O
Enquiry	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
Miscarriage	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Bell	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
.	O
The	O
Vault	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
last	O
in	O
a	O
Nook	O
,	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Chimney	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
't	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
Judgement	O
't	O
was	O
at	O
it	O
's	O
full	O
Growth	O
.	O
Midwife	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
at	O
it	O
's	O
full	O
Growth	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
Hair	O
and	O
Nails	O
perfect	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
larger	O
Child	O
than	O
is	O
common	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
that	O
Night	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Blood	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
frighted	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
mis-carried	O
,	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
no	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
down	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
some	O
hot	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
C.	O
You	O
have	O
behav	O
'd	O
very	O
ill	O
in	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
deserve	O
to	O
be	O
severely	O
reprimanded	O
.	O
You	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
Symptoms	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
being	O
deliver	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
instead	O
of	O
making	O
a	O
Discovery	O
,	O
you	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
Your	O
Proceeding	O
was	O
very	O
shameful	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
are	O
as	O
much	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Murder	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
her	O
self	O
,	O
-	O
Get	O
you	O
gone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
24.	O
Charles	B-pers
Orchard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Elly	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
2	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
Oct	O
,	O
26	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Elly	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
over-against	O
the	O
Danes	O
Church	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	B-place
,	O
for	O
a	O
Halt-penny	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half-pen'orth	O
of	O
Small	O
Beer	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
2	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
in	O
Change	O
of	O
a	O
Half-Crown	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
two	O
Fellows	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
them	O
to	O
come	O
near	O
me	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Trowel	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
Trowel	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Fingers	O
was	O
so	O
chopp	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Hospital	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
it	O
cut	O
off	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
2	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Trowel	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
attack	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
?	O
Elly	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
a	O
Watch-house	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
challeng	O
'd	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Holderness	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Standard	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Harris	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Information	O
concerning	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
robbing	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
:	O
At	O
his	O
Request	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
Thieves	O
are	O
entertain	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
Well-street	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
other	O
Fellows	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Holderness	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
was	O
directed	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
struggled	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
a	O
few	O
Blows	O
were	O
exchang	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
informing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
House-breaking	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
Jail	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
lodged	O
the	O
Evidence	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
desire	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
to	O
permit	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
for	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
hang	O
five	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
knock	O
down	O
the	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
put	O
all	O
the	O
Robberies	O
in	O
his	O
Information	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
committed	O
a	O
Robbery	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
between	O
Rag-Fair	O
and	O
the	O
Tripe-house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
mentioned	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Warrener	I-pers
.	O
To	O
prevent	O
Harris	O
's	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
swear	O
the	O
Peace	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
into	O
Custody	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Clerk	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
an	O
Information	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
Paper	O
)	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Ratcliffs	O
Highway	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
Pardon	O
:	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
chopp	O
'd	O
off	O
her	O
Finger	O
with	O
his	O
Trowel	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Trowel	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
:	O
The	O
Woman	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Trowel	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
her	O
Landlady	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
cut	O
her	O
Finger	O
with	O
the	O
Pitcher	O
:	O
All	O
these	O
People	O
swear	O
only	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
25.	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
about	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
no	O
one	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4l	O
.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
Six	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Dram	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Knee	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
2	O
Lancets	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
2	O
Knives	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Cook	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Meat	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
at	O
Wapping	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
House	O
safe	O
,	O
both	O
Windows	O
and	O
Doors	O
were	O
fast	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
Saturday	O
before	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
that	O
he	O
commited	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
finding	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
returning	O
Home	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
(	O
the	O
Gold-smith	O
)	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
my	O
Man	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Blackwall	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
bound	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
no	O
longer	O
ago	O
than	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
a	O
Month	O
.	O
Jonah	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
brought	O
all	O
this	O
Plate	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
What	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
with	O
this	O
Tankard	O
(	O
bruised	O
in	O
this	O
Manner	O
)	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
first	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Taylor	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
,	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
all	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Orchard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Lermit	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
three	O
Frize	O
Coats	O
,	O
three	O
Frize	O
Jackets	O
,	O
sixteen	O
Yards	O
of	O
Frize	O
,	O
five	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
German	O
Serge	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
Yards	O
of	O
Flannel	O
Baize	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Night-Time	O
,	O
January	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26	O
,	O
27.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Maynard	B-pers
Gearing	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l	O
a	O
Chrystal	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Ruby	O
Seal	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
and	O
twelve	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Oct.	O
28	O
.	O
And	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gearing	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
Home	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
9	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
East	O
Side	O
of	O
Soho	B-place
Square	I-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
two	O
Fellows	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
seized	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
stood	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
Side	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
make	O
no	O
Noise	O
but	O
deliver	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
Purses	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Value	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
that	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
(	O
whom	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
was	O
Bob	O
the	O
Glazier	O
)	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
stopped	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
his	O
Companion	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
;	O
Damn	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
stab	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
it	O
dark	O
and	O
dirty	O
I	O
gave	O
over	O
,	O
flattering	O
myself	O
that	O
my	O
Watch	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
but	O
from	O
the	O
Size	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
his	O
outward	O
Appearance	O
,	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
again	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
James-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Bob	O
the	O
Glazier	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
two	O
Pots	O
of	O
Beer	O
and	O
Ale	O
;	O
I	O
drank	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
and	O
Bob	O
the	O
Glazier	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
one	O
Bob	O
Fields	O
at	O
Cow-Cross	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
redeemed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Holland	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Goodman	O
in	O
Short's-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
lived	O
like	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Holland	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
carried	O
the	O
Woman-Prisoner	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
fourteen	O
Guineas	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Description	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Sam	O
Goodman	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
upon	O
my	O
Word	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
Margaret	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
Whore	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
common	O
Bawdy-houses	O
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Trouble	O
with	O
Sutton	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
cast	O
here	O
for	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Transportation	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Holland	O
.	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
Cooper	O
's	O
Mate	O
in	O
the	O
Lethieulier	O
an	O
India	O
Ship	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Ship	O
had	O
got	O
all	O
it	O
's	O
Hands	O
aboard	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Cooper	O
by	O
Trade	O
and	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
Cyder	O
and	O
Dorchester	O
Beer	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
Company	O
with	O
Sutton	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Sutton	O
returned	O
from	O
Transportation	O
I	O
got	O
rid	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
himself	O
a	O
Ship	O
and	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Holland	O
,	O
for	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
with	O
Sutton	O
before	O
,	O
so	O
now	O
they	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
whenever	O
they	O
please	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
that	O
stands	O
by	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
is	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
And	O
she	O
is	O
George	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
's	O
Wife	O
too	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brother	O
.	O
I	O
deal	O
for	O
some	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
a	O
Year	O
in	O
Cyder	O
and	O
Dorchester	O
Beer	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
all	O
this	O
Money	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
this	O
very	O
Morning	O
:	O
-	O
Please	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
these	O
Papers	O
.	O
C.	O
You	O
may	O
deal	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
never	O
the	O
honester	O
at	O
last	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Goodman	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
call	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
my	O
good	O
Character	O
now	O
.	O
C.	O
Aye	O
!	O
and	O
perhaps	O
they	O
'll	O
be	O
such	O
Persons	O
as	O
stand	O
by	O
you	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Years	O
.	O
C.	O
And	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
Witness	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
his	O
Brother	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Family	O
.	O
C.	O
That	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
the	O
better	O
.	O
Witness	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
something	O
of	O
Value	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
A	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Goodman	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
Evidence	O
in	O
this	O
very	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
committed	O
him	O
with	O
Beezly	O
and	O
Sutton	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
try	O
'd	O
with	O
Sutton	O
,	O
when	O
Sutton	O
was	O
convicted	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
vile	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Minute	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
by	O
Goodman	O
's	O
and	O
Bob	O
the	O
Glasier	O
's	O
Description	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
vastly	O
much	O
the	O
Look	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
Soho	O
square	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
.	O
Goodman	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
attack	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
Bob	O
the	O
Glasier	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
Bob	O
stole	O
out	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
unknown	O
to	O
Goodman	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
some	O
Shillings	O
instead	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Goodman	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Trick	O
,	O
and	O
resolved	O
to	O
redeem	O
the	O
Watch	O
unknown	O
to	O
Bob	O
:	O
So	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Bess	O
,	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Holland	O
together	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
28.	O
David	B-pers
Fossey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
with	O
2	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
Box	O
with	O
a	O
Stone	O
Lid	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Stormy	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woollen	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Archibald	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30.	O
James	B-pers
Brady	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Thornborough	I-pers
.	O
A	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Buckskin	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Fustian	O
Frock	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Manlove	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Oram	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Morshed	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
32.	O
John	B-pers
Pardieu	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
4	O
Silver	O
Soop	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
a	O
Silk	O
Scarf	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Silk	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
11	O
Pair	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
15	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
20	O
linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
12	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Olivier	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
22	O
.	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
33.	O
Moses	B-pers
Jessup	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
C.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
l	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
Grace	O
John	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Mountague	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
And	O
34.	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
14	O
C	O
Weight	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
35	O
,	O
36.	O
Philip	B-pers
Dwyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Bryan	B-pers
Macgrass	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
procuring	O
Richard	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Subject	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
to	O
enlist	O
and	O
enter	O
himself	O
into	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Foreign	O
Prince	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
leave	O
of	O
our	O
present	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
under	O
his	O
Sign	O
Manual	O
first	O
had	O
and	O
obtained	O
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
having	O
opened	O
the	O
Indictment	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
I	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
about	O
3	O
Years	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
In	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Dwyer	O
,	O
being	O
introduced	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
Partners	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Who	O
brought	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
One	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
them	O
first	O
at	O
the	O
Rising	O
Sun	O
in	O
Duke	O
Street	O
,	O
by	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
one	O
Serjeant	O
Archdeacon	O
,	O
by	O
William	O
Clark	O
's	O
Direction	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
with	O
fifteen	O
Recruits	O
for	O
France	O
.	O
Clark	O
met	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
come	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
Passage	O
this	O
Time	O
:	O
But	O
if	O
I	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
come	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
;	O
for	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
Gentlemen	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
must	O
do	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
What	O
pass	O
'd	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Dwyer	O
first	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
Brother	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
would	O
direct	O
me	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Dwyer	O
where	O
Archdeacon	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
last	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
come	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
in	O
Pawn	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
without	O
my	O
Things	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
Uncle	O
in	O
France	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Priest	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
redeem	O
me	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Occasion	O
of	O
Redemption	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
Friend	O
there	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
have	O
your	O
Liberty	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
your	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
such	O
Thing	O
as	O
having	O
them	O
redeem	O
'd	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
once	O
very	O
ill	O
us	O
'd	O
about	O
some	O
Cloaths	O
that	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
for	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
Escape	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
Coffee-House	O
Then	O
we	O
talked	O
of	O
the	O
Pay	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
Seven	O
Pence	O
Half-penny	O
a	O
Day	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Whose	O
Service	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
France	O
's	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Dunkirk	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
Seven	O
Pence	O
Half	O
penny	O
a	O
Day	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Macmillan	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sat	O
himself	O
down	O
to	O
hear	O
what	O
pass	O
'd	O
.	O
Dwyer	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
too	O
low	O
for	O
the	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
War	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
no	O
Men	O
under	O
his	O
(	O
Dwyer	O
's	O
)	O
Size	O
;	O
but	O
Macmillan	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wore	O
a	O
low	O
Shoe	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
wears	O
other	O
Shoes	O
he	O
'll	O
do	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
So	O
if	O
you	O
wore	O
high	O
heel	O
'd	O
Shoes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Macgrass	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
Not	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
afterward	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
They	O
agreed	O
to	O
send	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Brettle	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
get	O
a	O
Note	O
from	O
them	O
to	O
that	O
Purpose	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
pawned	O
in	O
my	O
Name	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
abroad	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
left	O
in	O
Clark	O
's	O
Name	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
labouring	O
to	O
delude	O
more	O
People	O
into	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
France	O
.	O
Councel	O
Was	O
any	O
Thing	O
sign	O
'd	O
between	O
you	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
Not	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
several	O
Meetings	O
together	O
after	O
this	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Dwyer	O
brought	O
his	O
Captain	O
;	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Captain	O
Linderkin	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
Will	O
.	O
Clark	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Macgrass	O
were	O
present	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Agreement	O
drawn	O
in	O
Writing	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Note	O
wrote	O
by	O
Dwyer	O
,	O
and	O
Clark	O
,	O
and	O
Macgrass	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Note	O
sure	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
Bryan	O
,	O
Macgrass	O
,	O
and	O
William	O
Clark	O
signed	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
present	O
(	O
same	O
)	O
Time	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Dwyer	O
write	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
Macgrass	O
to	O
sign	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
suppos	O
'd	O
't	O
was	O
no	O
Harm	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
sign	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
-	O
only	O
he	O
knew	O
on	O
what	O
Account	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
redeem	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
the	O
Note	O
was	O
made	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
believe	O
him	O
innocent	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
never	O
propos	O
'd	O
any	O
Thing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
Affair	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
This	O
Note	O
is	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Promissory	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Singular	O
Number	O
,	O
-	O
my	O
Objection	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
two	O
Men	O
have	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Note	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
A	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	O
Murphey	O
,	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
alter	O
'd	O
into	O
William	O
Clark	O
's	O
Name	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
deliver	O
'd	O
free	O
of	O
all	O
Charges	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Agreement	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Dwyer	I-pers
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
venture	O
to	O
mention	O
what	O
that	O
Agreement	O
was	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
to	O
alter	O
the	O
Name	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Dwyer	O
and	O
Macgrass	O
,	O
and	O
Will	O
.	O
Clark	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Name	O
was	O
changed	O
:	O
Clark	O
wrote	O
his	O
Name	O
upon	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Card	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Agreement	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
Paper	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
To	O
procure	O
a	O
Man	O
or	O
two	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
Macgrass	O
present	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
when	O
Dwyer	O
and	O
you	O
talk	O
'd	O
about	O
your	O
being	O
enlisted	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Dwyer	O
told	O
Macgrass	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
young	O
Man	O
(	O
meaning	O
me	O
)	O
had	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
Times	O
are	O
hard	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
are	O
in	O
Pawn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
will	O
have	O
Security	O
they	O
shall	O
be	O
sent	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pronounce	O
the	O
Agreement	O
,	O
made	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
Macgrass	O
was	O
his	O
Friend	O
(	O
at	O
present	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
tell	O
him	O
the	O
Agreement	O
we	O
were	O
upon	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
Macgrass	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
propos	O
'd	O
about	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
France	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
procure	O
a	O
Man	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
mention	O
made	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
were	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
pass	O
Muster	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
in	O
Buckley	O
's	O
Regiment	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
You	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
Seven-pence	O
Half-penny	O
a	O
Day	O
;	O
what	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
that	O
Pay	O
for	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
To	O
serve	O
like	O
another	O
Man	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
to	O
serve	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
you	O
not	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
so	O
tight	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
-	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
Seven-pence	O
Half-penny	O
a	O
Day	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
private	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Duty	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
Soldier	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
work	O
at	O
my	O
Trade	O
every	O
Day	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
could	O
get	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
muster	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
might	O
follow	O
your	O
own	O
Business	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
wrote	O
the	O
Note	O
about	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
every	O
Thing	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
serv	O
'd	O
but	O
like	O
a	O
common	O
Soldier	O
:	O
Friends	O
we	O
met	O
(	O
says	O
I	O
)	O
and	O
Friends	O
we	O
'll	O
part	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
good	O
Friends	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
two	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
.	O
Councel	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
you	O
this	O
Question	O
,	O
-	O
Was	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
hired	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
with	O
encouragement	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
you	O
might	O
get	O
some	O
body	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Regiment	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
and	O
appear	O
for	O
some	O
body	O
else	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
follow	O
my	O
Business	O
Councel	O
.	O
Pray	O
mind	O
the	O
Question	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
and	O
appear	O
for	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
your	O
self	O
?	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
Occasion	O
to	O
be	O
absent	O
,	O
you	O
might	O
have	O
some	O
body	O
to	O
Muster	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
Murphey	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
appear	O
in	O
a	O
Muster	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Dwyer	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
enlist	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
serv	O
'd	O
as	O
other	O
Men	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
would	O
part	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
pass	O
Muster	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
my	O
Trade	O
too	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
Macgrass	O
hear	O
all	O
this	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
.	O
Macgrass	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
propose	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
all	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
procure	O
a	O
Man	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
get	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
clear	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
one	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
another	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
France	O
:	O
For	O
it	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
Men	O
to	O
enlist	O
in	O
the	O
Regiment	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
my	O
Passage	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
France	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
And	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
mention	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
Man	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
stay	O
there	O
yourself	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
not	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Why	O
what	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
7	O
Pence	O
Half-penny	O
a	O
Day	O
for	O
?	O
Murphey	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
follow	O
my	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
pass	O
Muster	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
Case	O
of	O
Necessity	O
.	O
Macgrass	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
Dwyer	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
all	O
this	O
Discourse	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Concern	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Agreement	O
was	O
reduced	O
to	O
Writing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
signed	O
it	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Macmillon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Rising-Sun	O
by	O
the	O
Romish	O
Chapel	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
when	O
Dwyer	O
and	O
Murphey	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
Side	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Brettle	O
.	O
-	O
Councel	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Dwyer	O
say	O
to	O
Murphey	O
?	O
Macmillon	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
Brettle	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Rising-Sun	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
News-Paper	O
(	O
the	O
Penny-Post	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
think	O
I	O
minded	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
seemed	O
Intent	O
upon	O
the	O
Paper	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Dwyer	O
say	O
,	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
come	O
Yesterday	O
at	O
Five	O
o'Clock	O
?	O
Murphey	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
I	O
come	O
without	O
Cloaths	O
?	O
Dwyer	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
sent	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Murphey	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
Security	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
talked	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
in	O
Irish	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
understand	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
the	O
Man	O
is	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
proper	O
he	O
should	O
leave	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
them	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Aye	O
!	O
but	O
,	O
said	O
Dwyer	O
,	O
he	O
'll	O
have	O
Seven-Pence	O
Half-penny	O
a	O
Day	O
when	O
he	O
comes	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
talk	O
about	O
his	O
Landing	O
somewhere	O
about	O
Calais	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
his	O
Pay	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bonniface	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Dwyer	O
,	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Paper	O
from	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
my	O
Hand	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Paper	O
,	O
he	O
set	O
his	O
Foot	O
upon	O
it	O
and	O
burnt	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
much	O
Difficulty	O
we	O
saved	O
it	O
.	O
Macgrass	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brettle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Murphey	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Dwyer	O
had	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
's	O
Authority	O
about	O
him	O
for	O
enlisting	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
Mr.	O
Ibbot	O
the	O
Messenger	O
with	O
us	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hodges	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Short's-Gardens	O
.	O
Ibbot	O
searched	O
Macgrass	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
searched	O
Dwyer	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
searching	O
Dwyer	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
Dwyer	O
)	O
pulled	O
a	O
Paper	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
set	O
his	O
Foot	O
upon	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Hand	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
Hanger	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
Constable	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
Paper	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
burnt	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
preserved	O
with	O
Difficulty	O
.	O
The	O
Paper	O
was	O
wrote	O
in	O
French	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
English	O
it	O
runs	O
as	O
follows.	O
``	O
The	O
Irish	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Buckley	O
.	O
Soldiers	O
``	O
Furloe	O
.	O
We	O
who	O
have	O
undersigned	O
,	O
to	O
all	O
,	O
``	O
unto	O
whom	O
it	O
may	O
appertain	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
given	O
``	O
Leave	O
to	O
Philip	B-pers
Dwyer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Voluntier	O
in	O
the	O
Colonel	O
's	O
``	O
Company	O
in	O
Buckley	O
's	O
Regiment	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
``	O
to	O
England	O
for	O
6	O
Months	O
,	O
to	O
recruit	O
for	O
the	O
``	O
said	O
Colonel	O
's	O
Company	O
.	O
The	O
said	O
Dwyer	O
``	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Tipperary	O
,	O
aged	O
43	O
Years	O
,	O
five	O
``	O
Feet	O
five	O
Inches	O
high	O
,	O
Chesnut	O
colour	O
'd	O
Hair	O
,	O
``	O
Blue	O
Eyes	O
,	O
short	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
good	O
Legs	O
.	O
Signed	O
.	O
Macgray	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Lieut	O
.	O
Dated	O
at	O
Avence	O
,	O
Counter-sign	O
'd	O
.	O
Macheire	O
,	O
Major	O
.	O
Oct.	O
12	O
,	O
1736	O
.	O
Approv	O
'd	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
.	O
Henezie	O
,	O
Lieut	O
.	O
Col	O
.	O
Enter	O
'd	O
.	O
Dettez	O
,	O
Commissary	O
of	O
War	O
.	O
Dwyer	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
any	O
Money	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
little	O
for	O
his	O
Pay	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
skill	O
in	O
the	O
Irish	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
improve	O
himself	O
in	O
France	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sick	O
when	O
this	O
Furloe	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Soldier	O
's	O
Ease	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
seized	O
,	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
burn	O
the	O
Paper	O
in	O
a	O
surprize	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
me	O
harm	O
.	O
A	O
Juryman	O
.	O
We	O
would	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
giving	O
and	O
receiving	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
is	O
absolutely	O
necessary	O
to	O
the	O
enlisting	O
of	O
Men	O
?	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
Voluntiers	O
are	O
enlisted	O
every	O
Day	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
Farthing	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Act	O
read	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Articles	O
of	O
War	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
assent	O
to	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
to	O
all	O
Intents	O
and	O
Purposes	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Thousand	O
Pounds	O
.	O
Reading	O
the	O
Act	O
,	O
and	O
assenting	O
to	O
the	O
Articles	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
as	O
these	O
,	O
where	O
Persons	O
enlist	O
for	O
Foreign	O
Service	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
37.	O
Ann	B-pers
Shakeshaft	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
C.	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Yarn	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Amos	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
;	O
and	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Yarn	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shoomaker	I-pers
;	O
and	O
26	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Yarn	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
Feb.	O
12	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
38.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stuffin	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Tuffing	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
Oak	O
Pile	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abram	B-pers
Rondeau	I-pers
.	O
Mar	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
39.	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Amy	B-pers
Videau	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Jan	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
Letitia	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Garnet	O
Ear-rings	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
Stone	O
Necklace	O
set	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Saltmarsh	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
41.	O
William	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
half	O
Hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Hen	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moulder	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
42.	O
John	B-pers
Place	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Emanuel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
long	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
29	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Green	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s	O
an	O
Ash	O
colour	O
'd	O
Silk	O
ditto	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abigail	B-pers
Hallet	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
25	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stainthorp	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
3	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
44.	O
Simon	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fosset	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pail	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
brass	O
Bowl	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
14	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
Six	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Tea-pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
half	O
Pint	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Gammon	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
John	O
Fosset	O
.	O
Between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
Feb	O
5.	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
several	O
of	O
my	O
Pales	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
Rogues	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
my	O
Yard	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
Glass	O
from	O
a	O
Window	O
near	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
put	O
their	O
Hands	O
in	O
and	O
unbolted	O
the	O
upper	O
Bolt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bottom	O
Bolt	O
they	O
wrenched	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Batten	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
likewise	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
5	O
of	O
my	O
Plates	O
that	O
very	O
Night	O
in	O
Bullock's-Court	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
next	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
rattling	O
of	O
Pewter	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
5	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
Assistance	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
farther	O
Discovery	O
.	O
We	O
left	O
our	O
Candles	O
and	O
Lanthorns	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
at	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Pales	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
we	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
committed	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
then	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
out	O
the	O
Pewter	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
into	O
Bullock	O
's	O
Yard	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sorrel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
Newman	O
called	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
Newman	O
telling	O
me	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Pewter	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Harrison	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
before	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
himself	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
Sir	O
Richard	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
before	O
his	O
Footman	O
,	O
the	O
Shop-Man	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
fasten	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
Thing	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Peat	I-pers
is	O
my	O
Name	O
all	O
the	O
World	O
over	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
,	O
here	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
-	O
Peat	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
a	O
Hand	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
without	O
their	O
Lanthorns	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
afterwards	O
they	O
caught	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
:	O
He	O
did	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
(	O
by	O
Report	O
)	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
as	O
brave	O
a	O
Thief	O
as	O
any	O
is	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
mighty	O
Obstrepolous	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
punch	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Stomach	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
civil	O
-	O
like	O
an	O
old	O
Soldier	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
have	O
done	O
-	O
all	O
at	O
once	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
with	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
our	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
I	O
stepped	O
up	O
Bullock	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
about	O
Harrison	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hider	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Driver	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Hurt	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
his	O
Father	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Gentry	O
about	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
and	O
Savage-Gardens	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Lord	O
Jesus	O
Christ	O
's	O
Sake	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
Consideration	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
only	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cormeek	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
and	O
Cover	O
,	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dawney	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
12	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
46.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eaustin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
47.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
16	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Malcolm	B-pers
Buchan	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
No	O
one	O
appearing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
48.	O
Susan	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Canvas	O
Bag	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
8	O
Half	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
l	O
16	O
s	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joanna	B-pers
Worthington	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
9	O
.	O
James	O
Bannister	O
.	O
About	O
5	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Worthington	O
's	O
(	O
this	O
old	O
Woman	O
's	O
)	O
House	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hinton	O
a	O
Printer	O
;	O
I	O
waited	O
for	O
him	O
till	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Landlady	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
Lord	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
House	O
40	O
Years	O
and	O
never	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
happen	O
'd	O
before	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
examine	O
her	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
contesting	O
with	O
the	O
old	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
got	O
her	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
awaked	O
and	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
herself	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
Funn	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
good	O
natur	O
'd	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
pallaver	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Watch-house	O
Keeper	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
who	O
I	O
was	O
?	O
With	O
a	O
very	O
reverend	O
Bow	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
with	O
Submission	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
Money	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
your	O
Hands	O
;	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Watchhouse	O
:	O
Well	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
said	O
you	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
Funn	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
Funn	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Purse	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
Justice	O
Lambert	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
Col.	O
Turner	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
what	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
my	O
Landlady	O
's	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
unhappy	O
Woman	O
't	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
pick	O
'd	O
a	O
Pocket	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Worthington	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
that	O
Night	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hinton	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
to	O
wait	O
his	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
falling	O
asleep	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
This	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
foul	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
upon	O
Cure	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
sick	O
People	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
is	O
a	O
vile	O
Creature	O
in	O
her	O
Way	O
,	O
-	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
she	O
have	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
Way	O
of	O
Living	O
again	O
,	O
without	O
robbing	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
She	O
came	O
Home	O
fuddled	O
two	O
Hours	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
never	O
a	O
Lock	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Chamber	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
with	O
his	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
softly	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
make	O
himself	O
easy	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
disputing	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
comes	O
Madam	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
helping	O
us	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
led	O
us	O
from	O
Bagnio	O
to	O
Bagnio	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
knows	O
where	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
indeed	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
brought	O
her	O
Home	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
lye	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
awaked	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
that	O
have	O
done	O
you	O
such	O
Service	O
in	O
curing	O
you	O
and	O
making	O
you	O
right	O
again	O
!	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
Funn	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
'll	O
be	O
very	O
civil	O
I	O
'll	O
get	O
him	O
two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
saucy	O
he	O
shall	O
have	O
none	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watchman	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
us	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
pulled	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
tumbled	O
into	O
the	O
Kennel	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
again	O
like	O
a	O
Cat	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Bag	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
Keeper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
five	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Pray	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
Wingfield	O
the	O
Beadle	O
returned	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
whether	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
ask	O
