TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1737	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
THOMPSON	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1737	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
M	O
,	O
DCC	O
,	O
XXXVII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
THOMPSON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Fortescue	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
Urlin	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
Anthony	B-pers
Plant	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Soame	I-pers
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Bolt	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Lovell	I-pers
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Trimmer	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Strangeways	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Luttman	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hamstone	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Umplehy	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnsen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Queen-hithe	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
four	O
Bushell	O
sack	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pace	I-pers
,	O
March	O
11	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
2.	O
Simon	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
after	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1736	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bow	I-place
,	O
feloniously	O
made	O
and	O
caused	O
to	O
made	O
a	O
certain	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Writing	O
,	O
purporting	O
a	O
Receipt	O
for	O
200	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
following	O
Words	O
,	O
viz.	O
``	O
I	O
do	O
hereby	O
acknowledge	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
``	O
had	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
since	O
I	O
``	O
left	O
the	O
Lady	O
Norton	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
two	O
hundred	O
``	O
Pounds	O
in	O
Money	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
``	O
not	O
to	O
repay	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
rovokes	O
a	O
Deed	O
of	O
``	O
Gift	O
,	O
of	O
five	O
Hundred	O
Pounds	O
in	O
South-Sea	O
.	O
Annuities	O
,	O
``	O
this	O
Day	O
made	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
dated	O
17th	O
Jan.	O
``	O
1728	O
.	O
A	O
Capstick	O
.	O
Witness	O
E.	O
Downs	O
.	O
With	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
John	B-pers
Wigley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Lambeth	O
,	O
and	O
Agnes	B-pers
Capstick	I-pers
,	O
now	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Wigley	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
said	O
Writing	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Stanton	O
publish	O
'd	O
the	O
Day	O
aforesaid	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
3.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Calwell	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Boreman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
One	O
and	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
scarlet	O
short	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
long	O
black	O
silk	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
muslin	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
cambrick	O
Mob	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
Cups	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
striped	O
ticken	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sarah	O
Boreman	O
;	O
and	O
fourteen	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Portugal	O
Gold	O
,	O
at	O
36	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Zaccheus	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
,	O
March	O
11	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Boreman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	B-place
and	I-place
Knot	I-place
,	I-place
on	I-place
Snow-hill	I-place
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Felton	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
this	O
Time	O
Twelvemonth	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
About	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
March	O
11	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
,	O
under	O
my	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
Hoop	O
Petticoat	O
upon	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Stairs	O
,	O
-	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
Chamber	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
't	O
was	O
dark	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
pull	O
out	O
three	O
Drawers	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
took	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
again	O
in	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
swear	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
-	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
two	O
Silver	O
Salts	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
Cups	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
Silk	O
Apron	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
nine	O
Days	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
at	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
The	O
white	O
Hood	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
:	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Boreman	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
Bed-side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
last	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
missed	O
?	O
Boreman	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
Time	O
or	O
Manner	O
of	O
taking	O
these	O
Goods	O
?	O
Boreman	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
'till	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Pockets	O
for	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
Door	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Money	O
lay	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
this	O
that	O
'wak	O
'd	O
me	O
:	O
She	O
opened	O
the	O
Closet	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
brush	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
surprized	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
some	O
body	O
that	O
knew	O
my	O
Room	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
ill	O
Character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Boreman	O
.	O
Nine	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Moment	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
every	O
Thing	O
:	O
She	O
got	O
my	O
Hood	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
her	O
Neck	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Calwell	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
Things	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
:	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Key	O
her	O
self	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Doll	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pieces	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
And	O
have	O
not	O
you	O
lost	O
some	O
Cups	O
and	O
Salts	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
robbed	O
somebody	O
of	O
that	O
Portugal	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
those	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
Parson	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Reason	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Man	O
Boreman	O
.	O
They	O
liv	O
'd	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
in	O
that	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
required	O
so	O
much	O
Violence	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
her	O
Hands	O
alone	O
.	O
Felton	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
ask	O
no	O
Questions	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
desire	O
to	O
clear	O
this	O
innocent	O
Man	O
.	O
Calwell	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
you	O
of	O
a	O
Penny	O
:	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
me	O
?	O
Boreman	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
your	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Calwell	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
not	O
mine	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
before	O
any	O
Thing	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
break	O
any	O
Doors	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
?	O
Boreman	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
outer	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
four	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Shropshire	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Boreman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
one	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
Maid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Soldier	O
in	O
the	O
2d	O
Regiment	O
of	O
Guards	O
,	O
commanded	O
by	O
Capt	O
.	O
Littleer	O
,	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
(	O
a	O
Soldier	O
)	O
was	O
there	O
present	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
Captain	O
Littleer	B-pers
the	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
see	O
Calwell	O
at	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
bring	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
(	O
Calwell	O
)	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
married	O
a	O
Wife	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
why	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
wear	O
fine	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
The	O
Captain	O
insisted	O
on	O
knowing	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
produced	O
this	O
Portugal	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
a	O
Parson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
Money	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pieces	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
in	O
Thieving-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
must	O
enquire	O
for	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Room	O
for	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
must	O
ask	O
for	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Name	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
next	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Row	O
and	O
Alexander	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
Captain	O
Littleer	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
:	O
The	O
Hood	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
she	O
had	O
then	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Row	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Littleer	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
Calwell	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
breaking	O
open	O
a	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
four	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
sent	O
him	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Boswell	O
a	O
Merchant	O
at	O
Bristol	O
.	O
The	O
Captain	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
Calwell	O
)	O
was	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Parade	O
at	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
bring	O
him	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
He	O
fear	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
Roguish	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
clearapos	O
;	O
d	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
declare	O
where	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
us	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
by	O
the	O
Dead	O
Wall	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
Thieving	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
lest	O
the	O
Woman	O
should	O
suspect	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
give	O
my	O
Corporal	O
the	O
Ring	O
off	O
his	O
Finger	O
for	O
a	O
Token	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
her	O
:	O
He	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
at	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Furlow	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Corporal	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Boreman	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Captain	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
Calwell	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
long	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
?	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
at	O
Service	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
11	O
Months	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
.	O
Then	O
Mrs.	O
Boreman	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
her	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
directly	O
,	O
The	O
Devil	O
put	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Boreman	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
?	O
At	O
first	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
there	O
the	O
Cloak	O
and	O
these	O
Silver	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
The	O
Mob	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
her	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Captain	O
asked	O
Calwell	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
36	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hilder	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
five	O
Pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Gold	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Bag	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sav	O
'd	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
?	O
Row	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
a	O
Ground-window	O
,	O
and	O
jumping	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
,	O
a	O
twenty	O
Pound	O
Bag	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
by	O
some	O
People	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
who	O
kick	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
After	O
Justice	O
Hilder	O
had	O
examin	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
Woman	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
Tothill-fields	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Prison	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
a	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Felton	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
say	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
done	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
sold	O
his	O
Blood	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
and	O
others	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
.	O
Calwell	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
Serjeant	O
Row	O
,	O
have	O
not	O
you	O
known	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
Money	O
by	O
Recruiting	O
?	O
Row	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
Town	O
.	O
Calwell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
2	O
Guineas	O
a	O
Week	O
by	O
recruiting	O
in	O
Town	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
Doors	O
fast	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
?	O
Boreman	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
fast	O
after	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
broke	O
about	O
Four	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
Corporal	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Littleer	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Calwell	O
,	O
whereof	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Captain	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
Serjeant	O
Row	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Captain	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
?	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-Lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Threving-lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
his	O
Ring	O
for	O
a	O
Token	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Captain	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
Mrs.	O
Boreman	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
my	O
Assistance	O
in	O
apprehending	O
two	O
Persons	O
she	O
suspected	O
.	O
Calwell	O
was	O
found	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Littleer	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
the	O
Capt	O
.	O
examin	O
'd	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
36	O
Shilling	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Felton	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
the	O
Gold	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Calwell	O
was	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
she	O
took	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Boreman	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Felton	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
is	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
you	O
to	O
clear	O
the	O
Innocent	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
am	O
ready	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
Trial	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
innocent	O
,	O
-	O
He	O
is	O
in	O
Irons	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
had	O
Punishment	O
enough	O
.	O
Felton	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Calwell	O
acquitted	O
.	O
5.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jay	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Olave	I-place
,	I-place
Hart	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Carolina	O
Deer	O
Skins	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Goddin	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
14	O
.	O
Mr.	O
David	O
Goddin	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
French	B-place
Ordinary-Court	I-place
,	I-place
Crouched-Fryars	I-place
:	O
My	O
House	O
having	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
Money	O
and	O
Plate	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
Stole	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
Value	O
;	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
my	O
Warehouses	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
Ambergrease	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
12	O
Carolina	O
Deer-skins	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
Mrs.	O
Tollman	O
may	O
be	O
called	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Tollman	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
O'Brian	I-pers
brought	O
'em	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
them	O
there	O
for	O
his	O
Partner	O
Tom	B-pers
Jay	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
else	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
they	O
were	O
some	O
sort	O
of	O
Skins	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Goddin	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
bid	O
you	O
deliver	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Tollman	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
sometime	O
in	O
February	O
about	O
the	O
Dusk	O
of	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Goddin	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
O'Bryan	O
tell	O
you	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Skins	O
of	O
?	O
Tollman	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
his	O
Uncle	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Pyke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Leatherseller	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
between	O
Norfolk-Street	O
,	O
and	O
Surrey-Street	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
Deer	O
Skins	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
a	O
Sea-faring	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
some	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
.	O
My	O
Answer	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
and	O
liked	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
buy	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Market	O
Price	O
The	O
Day	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Josiah	B-pers
O'Bryan	I-pers
,	O
came	O
with	O
ten	O
Skins	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
O'Bryan	O
,	O
the	O
Sea-faring	O
Man	O
,	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Garret	O
,	O
a	O
Packer	O
in	O
Bell-Alley	O
,	O
Coleman-Street	O
We	O
soon	O
agreed	O
for	O
the	O
Skins	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
for	O
Twenty-eight	O
Shillings	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
the	O
Agreement	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
satisfied	O
about	O
their	O
Property	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
Vouchers	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
O'Bryan	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
a	O
Publican	O
,	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Lyon	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
give	O
some	O
Account	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
Bennet	O
gave	O
me	O
no	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Garret	O
's	O
in	O
Bell	O
Alley	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
his	O
Apprentice	O
was	O
a	O
Dealer	O
in	O
Deer-Skins	O
;	O
Bennet	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Caution	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Garret	O
's	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Garret	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Man	O
O'Brian	O
's	O
being	O
a	O
Dealer	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
Skins	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
O'Bryan	O
were	O
dis-satisfy	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
the	O
Money	O
or	O
the	O
Skins	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
urgent	O
on	O
the	O
Question	O
;	O
either	O
the	O
Money	O
or	O
the	O
Skins	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
prevail	O
on	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
detain	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Man	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
O'Bryan	O
went	O
away	O
very	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
off	O
afterwards	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Bennet	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
my	O
Christian	O
Name	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
Trouble	O
;	O
passing	O
by	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
Trouble	O
,	O
if	O
O'Bryan	O
's	O
Master	O
would	O
appear	O
for	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
the	O
Skins	O
or	O
the	O
Money	O
should	O
be	O
ready	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
Mr.	O
Garret	O
,	O
O'Bryan	O
's	O
Master	O
with	O
his	O
Uncle	O
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
satisfy	O
'd	O
in	O
some	O
Measure	O
about	O
the	O
Skins	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
(	O
they	O
said	O
)	O
bought	O
and	O
truck	O
'd	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
equally	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Cloth	O
.	O
These	O
Gentlemen	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
likewise	O
Mr.	O
Garret	O
's	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
them	O
the	O
Skins	O
?	O
but	O
Mr.	O
O'Bryan	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Trouble	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
pay	O
his	O
Kinsman	O
for	O
them	O
and	O
keep	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
28	O
s.	O
as	O
before	O
we	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Receipt	O
from	O
O'Bryan	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
afterwards	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Court	O
for	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
to	O
be	O
produced	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Price	O
you	O
gave	O
for	O
these	O
Skins	O
,	O
a	O
common	O
Price	O
?	O
Pyke	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
low	O
Price	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
receive	O
any	O
Money	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Pyke	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
when	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
paid	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
known	O
me	O
many	O
Years	O
?	O
Pyke	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Year	O
33	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
pass	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
Overseer	O
of	O
St.	O
Clements	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Master	O
Pyke	O
's	O
Shop	O
when	O
the	O
Skins	O
were	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
doubting	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
their	O
Characters	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Garret	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
along	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Pyke	O
's	O
Christian	O
Name	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
Simon	O
,	O
then	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
I	O
'll	O
arrest	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
Hours	O
Time	O
;	O
for	O
O'Bryan	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
for	O
24	O
s.	O
and	O
we	O
truck	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
these	O
Skins	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Man	O
has	O
bit	O
me	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
even	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
bit	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Cloth	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Pellisent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
know	O
them	O
Skin	O
which	O
be	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
bye	O
them	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Pyke	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Goddin	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
interrogate	O
Mr.	O
Pellisent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
me	O
ask	O
him	O
?	O
It	O
is	O
incumbent	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
shew	O
they	O
were	O
your	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
them	O
.	O
Job	O
How	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
Skins	O
we	O
have	O
sworn	O
to	O
already	O
:	O
When	O
we	O
first	O
rummaged	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
we	O
counted	O
over	O
these	O
Skins	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
hit	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Skin	O
off	O
my	O
Thumb	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
bled	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Blood	O
upon	O
this	O
Skin	O
,	O
-	O
here	O
's	O
more	O
upon	O
this	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
hardly	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
1212	O
of	O
them	O
when	O
we	O
rummag	O
'd	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
rummag	O
'd	O
them	O
the	O
7th	O
or	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
these	O
Skins	O
were	O
missing	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
Master	O
Goddin	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
this	O
Worm-eaten	O
Skin	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
's	O
my	O
Blood	O
upon	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
-	O
that	O
's	O
a	O
Circumstance	O
very	O
plain	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Desnard	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
How	O
's	O
Evidence	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Thing	O
;	O
I	O
recommended	O
the	O
Lad	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pyke	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
his	O
Skins	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
no	O
Property	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
call	O
several	O
People	O
to	O
my	O
Honesty	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sheriff	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Powney	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Addington	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harford	I-pers
,	O
Absalom	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
,	O
appeared	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
6.	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mudd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mudd	I-pers
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
treasonably	O
,	O
and	O
willfully	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
which	O
she	O
held	O
in	O
her	O
Right	O
Hand	O
,	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Back	O
Bone	O
,	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
stab	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
3	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroners	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
the	O
Fury	O
of	O
her	O
Mind	O
,	O
on	O
Thomas	O
Mudd	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Knife	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
held	O
in	O
her	O
Right	O
Hand	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Right	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Back	O
Bone	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
Weapon	O
drawn	O
,	O
nor	O
having	O
first	O
stricken	O
)	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
stab	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Knife	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
3	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
Feb.	O
23.	O
John	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Standridge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
,	O
lives	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
in	O
Carnaby	B-place
Market	I-place
.	O
The	O
23d	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Mudd	I-pers
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Standridge	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
3d	O
Step	O
from	O
the	O
Bottom	O
,	O
Ann	O
Mudd	O
struck	O
him	O
a	O
slap	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
be	O
quiet	O
:	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
by	O
her	O
Side	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
:	O
then	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
3d	O
Step	O
,	O
she	O
struck	O
him	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
be	O
quiet	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
buss	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
both	O
tumbled	O
together	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chair	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
playing	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
happen	O
'd	O
next	O
?	O
Owen	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
got	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
up	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
hurl	O
'd	O
something	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Owen	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
Saucer	O
:	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
stood	O
some	O
Time	O
at	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
immediately	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
stabb	O
'd	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
stabb	O
'd	O
!	O
Mother	O
!	O
Mother	O
!	O
She	O
has	O
done	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
immediately	O
to	O
call	O
Standrige	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
any	O
Instrument	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
after	O
he	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
being	O
stabb	O
'd	O
?	O
Owen	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Distance	O
of	O
Time	O
might	O
there	O
be	O
,	O
between	O
your	O
going	O
to	O
call	O
Standridge	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
Return	O
back	O
?	O
Owen	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
above	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
in	O
his	O
Blood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
Surgeon	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
?	O
Owen	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
Owen	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Minutes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
one	O
Word	O
after	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stabb	O
'd	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Aggleton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
Step	O
from	O
the	O
Bottom	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
him	O
a	O
slap	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
another	O
Blow	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
Step	O
:	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
by	O
her	O
Side	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
fight	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
fight	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
sat	O
her	O
self	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
kiss	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
from	O
the	O
Chair	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
Thing	O
off	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
jobb	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Mother	O
!	O
Mother	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
stabb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
stabb	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
done	O
for	O
me	O
!	O
The	O
very	O
Minute	O
that	O
she	O
jobb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
dropp	O
'd	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
Backside	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
call	O
Standridge	O
's	O
Husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
made	O
this	O
Complaint	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
he	O
fall	O
?	O
Aggleton	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
upon	O
his	O
Back-side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Blood	O
trickle	O
down	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Aggleton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
well	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
?	O
Aggleton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
dy	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lambert	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
Cruel	O
as	O
to	O
Kill	O
her	O
Husband	O
?	O
Why	O
,	O
say	O
'd	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
for	O
Funn	O
The	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Man	O
Dead	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Lambert	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
Funn	O
.	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
her	O
Father	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Maccullough	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
Coroner	O
to	O
view	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Wound	O
between	O
the	O
9th	O
and	O
10th	O
Ribs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Back-bone	O
;	O
the	O
Knife	O
had	O
penetrated	O
into	O
the	O
Cavity	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
;	O
the	O
right	O
Lobe	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
was	O
pierced	O
quite	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
Blood-vessel	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Branch	O
quite	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
8.	O
Charles	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
brass	O
Weight	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Pound	O
brass	O
Weight	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
a	O
half	O
Pound	O
brass	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
Pound	O
brass	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Charles	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Attwood	I-pers
,	O
at	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Drawer	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
35	O
s	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
February	O
18	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Attwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18	O
th	O
of	O
February	O
about	O
seven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Shop	O
Door	O
latched	O
with	O
an	O
iron	O
Latch	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
behind	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Boy	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
Money	O
,	O
Lock	O
and	O
Key	O
,	O
-	O
all	O
was	O
gone	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
.	O
Burn	O
.	O
Pray	O
Mr.	O
Atwood	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Door	O
fast	O
?	O
Atwood	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Burn	O
The	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
broke	O
a	O
Lock	O
in	O
our	O
Lives	O
:	O
We	O
had	O
no	O
Knives	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
open	O
a	O
Door	O
with	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Boy	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
of	O
an	O
Errand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Atwood	O
's	O
Door	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
Night	O
)	O
but	O
Jones	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
stood	O
still	O
:	O
Burn	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Till	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
When	O
Burn	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
Jones	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
:	O
Burn	O
spoke	O
to	O
Ingram	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
enough	O
to	O
hear	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Atwood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
so	O
light	O
at	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
February	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
know	O
their	O
Faces	O
.	O
Walten	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
the	O
Shop	O
Windows	O
were	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
could	O
distinguish	O
their	O
Faces	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
Lights	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Ingram	O
and	O
Jones	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
?	O
Walton	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
3	O
standing	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Burn	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
latch	O
'd	O
or	O
no	O
?	O
Walton	O
'T	O
was	O
a	O
Hatch	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
was	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
lean	O
over	O
it	O
and	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
.	O
Burn	O
.	O
The	O
Door	O
was	O
a	O
Foot	O
open	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
I	O
only	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
Farthing	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
Small-Beer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Till	O
was	O
half	O
in	O
,	O
half	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
lock	O
'd	O
neither	O
.	O
Ingram	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
?	O
Walton	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
all	O
3	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
all	O
their	O
3	O
Faces	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Atwood	O
's	O
Door	O
shut	O
.	O
I	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
and	O
stood	O
still	O
:	O
Burn	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
ran	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Bell-Alley	O
;	O
then	O
Ingram	O
perceiving	O
that	O
Burn	O
's	O
Hand	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
-	O
You	O
Rogue	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
23	O
s.	O
and	O
Eight-pence	O
half-peny	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
,	O
Burn	O
sunk	O
it	O
while	O
his	O
Hand	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
was	O
empty	O
'd	O
into	O
my	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Tobacco-Roll	O
against	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Church	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
we	O
shar	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
6d	O
,	O
less	O
than	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
said	O
6d	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
prevent	O
Disputes	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Loss	O
to	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
some	O
Beef-stakes	O
dressing	O
then	O
for	O
our	O
Suppers	O
,	O
but	O
Ingram	O
's	O
Mother	O
informing	O
us	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Atwood	O
was	O
coming	O
upon	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
without	O
eating	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Hatch	O
latch	O
'd	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
lean	O
'd	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
your	O
Oath	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
lift	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
lean	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
opened	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Light	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
't	O
was	O
Dark	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Burn	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
touched	O
the	O
Latch	O
with	O
my	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
can	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
lift	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
more	O
than	O
3	O
yards	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Burn	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
just	O
stole	O
some	O
brass	O
Weights	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
us	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Charles	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
made	O
the	O
Lob	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
.	O
Burn	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
old	O
Rogue	O
;	O
he	O
brings	O
up	O
Youth	O
to	O
Thievery	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Swears	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
.	O
Ingram	O
.	O
The	O
Night	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
Committed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye	O
at	O
Holbourn-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
Burn	O
and	O
Jones	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
;	O
my	O
Mother	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
long	O
Persuasion	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
these	O
Fellows	O
,	O
not	O
I	O
.	O
To	O
Ingram	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
appear	O
'd	O
.	O
Ingram	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
Rogue	O
had	O
not	O
Swore	O
so	O
heartily	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
had	O
40	O
more	O
to	O
have	O
appear	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Burn	O
I	O
serv	O
'd	O
his	O
Majesty	O
;	O
but	O
have	O
fell	O
into	O
bad	O
Company	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
about	O
to	O
leave	O
off	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Jones	O
Swore	O
this	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
*	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
when	O
Jones	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Ingram	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
Weights	O
,	O
it	O
wanted	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
of	O
Dark	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
only	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
Alley	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
this	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
Dark	O
.	O
*	O
This	O
Declaration	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Questions	O
with	O
Regard	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Doors	O
being	O
fast	O
,	O
were	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Burglary	O
doubtful	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hardware	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
April	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Ann	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Tabby	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
check	O
'd	O
coloured	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
flaxen	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cattle	I-pers
.	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cattle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Night	O
these	O
Things	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hard	O
falling-too	O
of	O
my	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
'wak	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
Floor	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
hid	O
her	O
self	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Line	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Swan	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
my	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
screaming	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Servant	O
(	O
Cattle	O
)	O
at	O
her	O
Chamber	O
Door	O
in	O
her	O
Shift	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
Woman	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Candle	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
below	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
her	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	O
with	O
another	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
House	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
.	O
My	O
Companion	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
certain	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
screamed	O
out	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
terribly	O
frighted	O
:	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
is	O
welcome	O
to	O
say	O
what	O
she	O
pleases	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
drop	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
the	O
Witness	O
.	O
Line	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
mean	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
only	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Witness	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
frighted	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
her	O
self	O
:	O
-	O
pray	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
what	O
Cloaths	O
had	O
I	O
on	O
?	O
Cattle	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Fellow	O
Servants	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Hat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Manteel	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
another	O
Woman	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Line	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Cattle	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
very	O
Moon-light	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
Sky-light	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
very	O
plainly	O
.	O
Line	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
something	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
House	O
that	O
any	O
Gentleman	O
may	O
carry	O
a	O
Woman	O
into	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
12.	O
Susan	B-pers
Beachey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Emmet	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
March	O
29	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
13.	O
James	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
Feet	O
of	O
Leaden	O
Pipe	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
Freehold	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Lee	O
March	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mountague	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Callimanco	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
April	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15	O
,	O
16.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Vizard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morecock	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
half	O
hundred	O
Leaden	O
Weight	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Trout	I-pers
.	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
Vizard	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Morecock	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kerr	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Pint	O
Pots	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
;	O
three	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hampsted	I-pers
;	O
and	O
three	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
.	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
18.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Mecklin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
Cane	O
Hats	O
lin	O
'd	O
with	O
Blue	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
19.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
Pewter	O
Quart	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Holland	O
Mob	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
.	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
20.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
big	O
with	O
a	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Providence	O
of	O
God	O
the	O
said	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
did	O
privily	O
bring	O
forth	O
alive	O
,	O
March	O
22	O
.	O
And	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
both	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Flannel	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
did	O
wrap	O
and	O
hide	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
being	O
then	O
alive	O
)	O
by	O
Reason	O
of	O
which	O
wrapping	O
and	O
hiding	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
was	O
smother	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
which	O
smothering	O
it	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Mr.	O
-	O
Jodrell	O
.	O
This	O
unfortunate	O
Affair	O
happening	O
in	O
my	O
Family	O
,	O
Justice	O
Chamberlen	O
bound	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
my	O
Service	O
,	O
we	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
what	O
Enquiry	O
we	O
could	O
into	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
as	O
having	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
,	O
an	O
eminent	O
Druggist	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
five	O
Years	O
in	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
during	O
all	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
behav	O
'd	O
honestly	O
,	O
soberly	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
became	O
a	O
good	O
Servant	O
.	O
On	O
this	O
Character	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
continu	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
Family	O
13	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
answer	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
's	O
Character	O
in	O
every	O
Respect	O
.	O
I	O
entrusted	O
her	O
with	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
always	O
regularly	O
and	O
duly	O
accounted	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
soberly	O
and	O
virtuously	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
diligent	O
and	O
industrious	O
Servant	O
.	O
My	O
Health	O
calling	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
and	O
a	O
Man-a	O
Footman	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
during	O
that	O
Time	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
seduced	O
by	O
this	O
Servant	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
behav	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Manner	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
less	O
Reason	O
of	O
any	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
But	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
brought	O
me	O
Information	O
that	O
a	O
dead	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Cook-Maid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Mother	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
Regard	O
that	O
neither	O
I	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Servants	O
,	O
nor	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
had	O
any	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
who	O
behav	O
'd	O
so	O
well	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Fact	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Child	O
being	O
dead	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
incumbent	O
on	O
me	O
to	O
consult	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
preceeding	O
Day	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
About	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
following	O
Day	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
told	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
discover	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chamberlen	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
proper	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
Enquiry	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
the	O
Coroner	O
and	O
Justice	O
Chamberlen	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
Confession	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
will	O
be	O
given	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
always	O
related	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
constantly	O
declared	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
heard	O
it	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
and	O
the	O
Coroner	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
some	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
View	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
there	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
the	O
least	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
.	O
And	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
nam	O
'd	O
Justice	O
Chamberlen	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
declare	O
,	O
he	O
behav	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
Justice	O
as	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
Tenderness	O
and	O
Compassion	O
as	O
a	O
Christian	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
my	O
Judgment	O
on	O
Oath	O
may	O
avail	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
from	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Maid	O
while	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
the	O
Time	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Character	O
and	O
Behaviour	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
her	O
Child	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Jodrell	O
.	O
I	O
declare	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
on	O
any	O
Account	O
whatever	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Jodrell	O
As	O
Mr.	O
Jodrell	O
has	O
said	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
behav	O
'd	O
with	O
that	O
Manner	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
when	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
Rumour	O
I	O
heard	O
in	O
the	O
Family	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
her	O
Chamber	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
looking	O
into	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
a	O
Child	O
had	O
been	O
born	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Jodrell	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
Nurse	O
Carpenter	O
(	O
who	O
has	O
liv	O
'd	O
23	O
Years	O
in	O
our	O
Family	O
)	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
born	O
;	O
she	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
For	O
Christ	O
's	O
Sake	O
forgive	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
't	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
Box	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
Nurse	O
Carpenter	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Lap	O
:	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
it	O
carefully	O
over	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
,	O
in	O
no	O
Manner	O
of	O
Kind	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
marry	O
'd	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Under	O
Footman	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Jodrell	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chamberlen	O
and	O
the	O
Coroner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
proper	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
Provision	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Rags	O
done	O
up	O
together	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Opinion	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
useful	O
on	O
that	O
Occasion	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Work	O
perform	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
three	O
Months	O
before	O
her	O
Time	O
:	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
proper	O
Pieces	O
for	O
Shirts	O
and	O
Night-caps	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
mistaken	O
in	O
her	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
,	O
many	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
had	O
been	O
mistaken	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
apprehend	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
born	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Jodrell	O
By	O
her	O
own	O
Confession	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
at	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
in	O
so	O
modest	O
a	O
Manner	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
greatly	O
deceiv	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
so	O
great	O
an	O
Offence	O
as	O
killing	O
her	O
own	O
Child	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Jodrell	O
.	O
Farthest	O
from	O
it	O
of	O
any	O
one	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
on	O
Oath	O
I	O
think	O
so	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
juster	O
an	O
Account	O
than	O
what	O
my	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
have	O
done	O
:	O
I	O
question	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
dead	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
no	O
Assistance	O
.	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Mark	O
of	O
Violence	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
give	O
Suspicion	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
take	O
its	O
Life	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Child	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
Child	O
that	O
was	O
born	O
before	O
its	O
Time	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
proper	O
Judge	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Jodrell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Labour	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
came	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Months	O
before	O
her	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
is	O
alive	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
grown	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
only	O
Instance	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
mistaken	O
six	O
Weeks	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Reckoning	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Chamberlen	O
.	O
As	O
Mr.	O
Jodrell	O
has	O
been	O
telling	O
you	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
sat	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
is	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
will	O
give	O
a	O
better	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
her	O
Exation	O
;	O
she	O
wrote	O
her	O
Name	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
The	O
Examination	O
and	O
Confession	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
taken	O
this	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
1736.	O
``	O
This	O
Examinant	O
confesseth	O
and	O
saith	O
,	O
That	O
``	O
yesterday	O
she	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
``	O
Child	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
:	O
That	O
she	O
wrapped	O
``	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
``	O
deal	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
designed	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Friend	O
to	O
bury	O
``	O
it	O
privately	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
known	O
to	O
the	O
``	O
Family	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
,	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
``	O
her	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
saith	O
,	O
If	O
any	O
one	O
had	O
``	O
question	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
own	O
'd	O
``	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
no	O
Provision	O
,	O
nor	O
``	O
told	O
any	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
with	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
``	O
she	O
expected	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
three	O
Months	O
``	O
longer	O
before	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
deliver	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
my	O
Cook-Maid	O
five	O
Years	O
;	O
during	O
which	O
Time	O
she	O
behav	O
'd	O
soberly	O
,	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
virtuously	O
as	O
any	O
I	O
ever	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
very	O
unlikely	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
so	O
cruel	O
a	O
Thing	O
.	O
The	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Request	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jodrell	O
and	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
I	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
this	O
Child	O
;	O
't	O
was	O
as	O
fairly	O
born	O
as	O
any	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Coroner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
try	O
the	O
Experiment	O
on	O
the	O
Lungs	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
commonly	O
done	O
on	O
such	O
Occasions	O
'T	O
is	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
some	O
,	O
That	O
if	O
the	O
Lungs	O
float	O
in	O
Water	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Sign	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
breathed	O
;	O
if	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
float	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
.	O
On	O
trying	O
the	O
Experiment	O
upon	O
the	O
Lungs	O
of	O
this	O
Child	O
,	O
they	O
floated	O
on	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Certainty	O
of	O
this	O
Experiment	O
may	O
have	O
Objections	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
instance	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
Child	O
hath	O
stuck	O
in	O
the	O
Birth	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
comes	O
in	O
the	O
natural	O
Way	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
respire	O
and	O
breath	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
which	O
Respiration	O
may	O
make	O
the	O
Lungs	O
specifically	O
lighter	O
than	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
yet	O
the	O
Child	O
may	O
die	O
before	O
't	O
is	O
born	O
.	O
And	O
without	O
some	O
other	O
Circumstances	O
to	O
corroborate	O
this	O
Experiment	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
loth	O
to	O
determine	O
thereby	O
positively	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Experiment	O
(	O
where	O
a	O
Person	O
's	O
Life	O
is	O
at	O
Stake	O
)	O
too	O
slight	O
to	O
be	O
built	O
upon	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
was	O
perfectly	O
fair	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
smothering	O
a	O
Child	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
effected	O
without	O
some	O
external	O
Marks	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
any	O
Family	O
where	O
any	O
Woman	O
lay-in	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Knowledge	O
what	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
such	O
Cases	O
.	O
I	O
expected	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
deliver	O
'd	O
in	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Months	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
my	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Things	O
I	O
had	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
21.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
Yards	O
of	O
Stuff	O
,	O
26	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
and	O
Stuff	O
Poplin	O
,	O
3	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Tabby	O
Silk	O
,	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Sarsenet	O
,	O
1	O
Yard	O
of	O
Sattin	O
,	O
13	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
12	O
Yards	O
of	O
Burdet	O
,	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Damask	O
,	O
7	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Shagreen	O
,	O
3	O
Yards	O
of	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
25	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Persian	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spying-Glass	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Arabella	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Dwelling-House	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
Arabella	O
Evans	O
.	O
If	O
your	O
Lordship	O
pleases	O
to	O
swear	O
Justice	O
Frazier	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
seen	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
Witness	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
ca	O
n't	O
you	O
tell	O
what	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Really	O
they	O
are	O
so	O
many	O
-	O
There	O
's	O
Things	O
of	O
all	O
Sorts	O
,	O
Damasks	O
,	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
Poplin	O
,	O
Stuff	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
little	O
Mercer	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
my	O
Maid	O
;	O
her	O
Master	O
that	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
before	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
honest	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
soon	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
saucy	O
Tongue	O
.	O
Here	O
,	O
-	O
where	O
's	O
the	O
Constable	O
?	O
There	O
's	O
Justice	O
Frazier	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
Witness	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
she	O
cut	O
off	O
of	O
whole	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
whole	O
Pieces	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
Remnants	O
to	O
match	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
Italian	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
self	O
a	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
;	O
here	O
's	O
Sattins	O
,	O
Damasks	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
here	O
's	O
all	O
Sorts	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Spying	O
glass	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
Matter	O
of	O
two	O
Months	O
ago	O
.	O
She	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
got	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
by	O
Piece-meal	O
and	O
Piece-meal	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
a-bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
them	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Things	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
come	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
them	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
O	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Moore	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
by	O
Church-court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
all	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Part	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
Part	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
their	O
being	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
sent	O
off	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
she	O
begg	O
'd	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
;	O
-	O
but	O
why	O
Nelly	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
so	O
?	O
Why	O
the	O
Devil	O
pospossess	O
'd	O
me	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
Maid	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
advis	O
'd	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
cut	O
off	O
any	O
more	O
Bits	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
whole	O
Pieces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
found	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
in	O
Feather	O
's	O
alley	O
.	O
Here	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
speak	O
too	O
?	O
Why	O
this	O
Bundle	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Jane	O
Tyree	O
's	O
in	O
Feathers-alley	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
it	O
are	O
Part	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
there	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Why	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
upon	O
her	O
Oath	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
?	O
If	O
you	O
require	O
any	O
more	O
Questions	O
-	O
I	O
say	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
Goods	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
swore	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
wearing	O
Things	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
very	O
Pins	O
and	O
Aprons	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Box	O
.	O
Evans	O
.	O
O	O
,	O
the	O
Creature	O
!	O
She	O
took	O
all	O
my	O
Grandchild	O
's	O
Frocks	O
,	O
which	O
cost	O
me	O
14	O
s.	O
apiece	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
Gown	O
off	O
my	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Pretence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
match	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Shop	O
.	O
Evans	O
.	O
Pray	O
let	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Frazier	O
be	O
sworn	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
executed	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
Poplin	O
Gown	O
,	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Stuft	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
secured	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
several	O
Things	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
have	O
been	O
ever	O
since	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
.	O
The	O
best	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
was	O
present	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Burdet	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
that	O
to	O
an	O
Old	O
Cloaths-Man	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
her	O
Mistress	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Frazier	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
her	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
This	O
first	O
Search	O
was	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
Trifles	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
Tyree	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Feather's-alley	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
which	O
were	O
not	O
made	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
come	O
you	O
to	O
search	O
Tyree	O
's	O
House	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Tyree	O
came	O
to	O
Evans	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
probably	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
any	O
one	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
Maid	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
for	O
Victuals	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
,	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
cut	O
Bits	O
off	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
whole	O
Piece	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
this	O
Maid	O
lodg	O
'd	O
some	O
where	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
the	O
Hay	O
market	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
nor	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
only	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Welch	O
woman	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Tyree	I-pers
My	O
Husband	O
is	O
a	O
Taylor	O
:	O
We	O
live	O
in	O
Feathers-Alley	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
Stall	O
against	O
St.	O
Martin's-Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
Bundle	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
Morning	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Husband	O
in	O
his	O
Stall	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
that	O
Bundle	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
's	O
worth	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
our	O
Room	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Stall	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
Home	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
her	O
Bundle	O
,	O
come	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
show	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
bought	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
good	O
Things	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
pray	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
Yard	O
:	O
I	O
bought	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
had	O
measur	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Measure	O
was	O
rather	O
too	O
short	O
;	O
why	O
if	O
't	O
is	O
so	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
carry	O
them	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
No	O
-	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
Measure	O
was	O
short	O
,	O
-	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
cheap	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
keep	O
them	O
,	O
'till	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
following	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
and	O
enquired	O
in	O
the	O
Alley	O
for	O
one	O
Tyree	O
;	O
he	O
found	O
us	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
credible	O
Person	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
one	O
Eleanor	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
Sirname	O
:	O
She	O
knows	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desires	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
for	O
thievery	O
;	O
so	O
after	O
Dinner	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
desired	O
my	O
Husband	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
satisfy	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Trouble	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
for	O
an	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
we	O
found	O
out	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
May	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
and	O
another	O
Person	O
enquired	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
Warrant	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
this	O
Poplin	O
Gown	O
made-up	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
own	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
the	O
Box	O
into	O
my	O
Apartment	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
before	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
searching	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
for	O
being	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
at	O
my	O
Apartment	O
,	O
were	O
but	O
trifling	O
Things	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
blue	O
Burdet	O
to	O
be	O
Mrs.	O
Evans	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
likewise	O
some	O
Remnants	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Ewell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Lodging	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Burdet	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
(	O
if	O
her	O
Mistress	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
)	O
she	O
would	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
Justice	O
Frazier	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
equivocate	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
an	O
Old	O
Cloaths-Man	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Tyree	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Burdet	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Frazier	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
before-given	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
lay	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
William	B-pers
Rants	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Endfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Deal	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
February	O
2	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
Richard	B-pers
Debell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
barragon	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Uriel	I-pers
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
Richard	O
Uriel	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
swear	O
this	O
Coat	O
is	O
mine	O
:	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
scower	O
'd	O
at	O
Mary	O
Myers	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Window	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Uriel	O
brought	O
this	O
Coat	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
scower	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
stole	O
it	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Heatley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
Coat	O
to	O
sell	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
that	O
lives	O
there	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
8	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
dubious	O
about	O
his	O
Property	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
satisfy	O
me	O
about	O
his	O
Character	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
Bigs	O
's	O
against	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
spoke	O
with	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
me	O
to	O
another	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
liking	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
Some	O
little	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Myers	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Shops	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
such	O
a	O
Coat	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
committed	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Coat	O
.	O
Myers	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
Uriel	O
's	O
Coat	O
.	O
Uriel	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Coat	O
I	O
carried	O
Myers	O
to	O
clean	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
this	O
upon	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
too	O
little	O
for	O
me	O
indeed	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
came	O
cheap	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
full	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
Defence	O
;	O
can	O
you	O
call	O
your	O
Witnesses	O
and	O
prove	O
it	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
18	O
Robert	O
Thompson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Park	I-place
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
acquainted	O
before	O
;	O
Robin	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
what	O
makes	O
you	O
out	O
so	O
late	O
to	O
Night	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
come	O
away	O
from	O
your	O
Master	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Kensington	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
Home	O
with	O
it	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
Robin	O
,	O
Robin	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
one	O
Kiss	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
from	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
ran	O
back	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
challeng	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
Business	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
his	O
Wife	O
?	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Footmen	O
coming	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
Flambeau	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
down	O
to	O
Spring-Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
again	O
:	O
She	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
yet	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
at	O
this	O
House	O
knowing	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
likewise	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
say	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
only	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Marshal	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
your	O
Master	O
live	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
Women	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
call	O
'd	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Blackman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
Day	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
-	O
as	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
-	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
-	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
an	O
Hero-man	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
(	O
as	O
how	O
)	O
his	O
Boy	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
were	O
detained	O
.	O
I	O
requested	O
and	O
desired	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
by	O
the	O
Story	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
make	O
Restitution	O
:	O
For	O
all	O
I	O
requested	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
she	O
only	O
laugh	O
'd	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
kiss	O
her	O
A	O
-	O
se	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
besides	O
,	O
and	O
somewhat	O
else	O
,	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
repeat	O
to	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Court	O
.	O
So	O
next	O
Morning	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
worthy	O
honourable	O
Gentleman	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
handsome	O
Manner	O
indeed	O
;	O
he	O
examin	O
'd	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Page	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
Premisses	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
say	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
commit	O
her	O
to	O
Newgate	O
:	O
And-when	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Lad	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
stab	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Jaws	O
.	O
Where	O
's	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
?	O
He	O
's	O
somewhere	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
'm	O
sure	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
these	O
3	O
Hours	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sent	O
Thompson	O
to	O
fetch	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
Woman	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
Woman	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
.	O
Blackman	O
.	O
So	O
far	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Lad	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
just	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
wrong	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
sober	O
and	O
silly	O
too	O
.	O
What	O
Pocket	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
the	O
Watch	O
into	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
My	O
left	O
Coat	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
cross	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
shook	O
Hands	O
,	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25	O
,	O
26.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Harper-John	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sail-cloth	O
Markee	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Robers	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
April	O
3	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Oakes	I-pers
,	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Hoop	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
an	O
Ell	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
March	O
8	O
.	O
Ann	O
Oakes	O
.	O
The	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
stepp	O
'd	O
about	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
my	O
Window	O
to	O
cut	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sash	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
pin	O
'd	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Nail	O
)	O
was	O
thrust	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Hand	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hand	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Silk	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
Hoop	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Ell	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Holland	O
beside	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
pursu	O
'd	O
after	O
the	O
Thief	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
thought	O
of	O
hearing	O
more	O
about	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Evidence	O
informed	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Piper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
this	O
Robbery	O
:	O
Cook	O
shov	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Hoop	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Cap	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
't	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
Value	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
it	O
to	O
himself	O
.	O
How	O
he	O
unfasten	O
'd	O
the	O
Window	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
understands	O
those	O
Things	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Candle	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Mrs.	O
Oakes	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
twice	O
;	O
the	O
Moon	O
shone	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
shady	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
us	O
.	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
's	O
welcome	O
to	O
Swear	O
what	O
he	O
pleases	O
.	O
Piper	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Evidence	O
himself	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Felony	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
,	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
,	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
Ralph	O
Maddox	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Piper	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
Vinegar	O
Merchant	O
:	O
Cook	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
his	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Shop-window	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Pot	O
out	O
Cook	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
welcome	O
to	O
Swear	O
what	O
he	O
pleases	O
;	O
I	O
'm	O
cast	O
for	O
Transportation	O
already	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Instrument	O
made	O
of	O
Iron	O
and	O
Lead	O
,	O
used	O
for	O
grinding	O
Snuff	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
28	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
4th	O
Time	O
indicted	O
with	O
*	O
Peter	B-pers
Benyan	I-pers
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
5	O
Copper	O
Pattipans	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
Tarts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d	O
,	O
March	O
6	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
*	O
Peter	B-pers
Benyan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
Jan	O
.	O
Sessions	O
1735-6.	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Powers	I-pers
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Book	O
No	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
1735-6	O
;	O
p.	O
60.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Companions	O
in	O
Dec	O
.	O
Sessions	O
,	O
1736	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
I.	O
p.	O
19	O
.	O
&	O
20	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
and	O
maliciously	O
setting	O
Fire	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
Harry	B-pers
House	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
Time	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
an	O
Alarm	O
of	O
Fire	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rawlinson	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Straw	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Fire	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
some	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
loitering	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
Business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
only	O
sat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Rain	O
;	O
(	O
for	O
it	O
rain	O
'd	O
very	O
hard	O
)	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
at	O
the	O
Watchman	O
for	O
turning	O
him	O
away	O
.	O
At	O
Charing-Cross	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
again	O
upon	O
a	O
Bulk	O
;	O
we	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
away	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Night	O
Cellars	O
for	O
suspicious	O
Persons	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
Home	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
again	O
before	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
Watchman	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
for	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
took	O
his	O
Examination	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
Proof	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
charged	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
acknowledge	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
melancholy	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
this	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
be	O
Hang	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
behav	O
'd	O
Modestly	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
heavy	O
dull	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
order	O
thereto	O
,	O
he	O
committed	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
confes	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
my	O
Duty	O
to	O
Commit	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
appear	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
compos	O
Mentis	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
leaning	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
smother	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rawlinson	O
's	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Basket	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Straw	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lighted	O
Candle	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Candle	O
was	O
cover	O
'd	O
likewise	O
with	O
Straw	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Body	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
curse	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swear	O
the	O
House	O
should	O
be	O
down	O
before	O
Morning	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Wax-candle	O
into	O
the	O
Straw	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
doing	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
Tallow	O
one	O
for	O
this	O
Purpose	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Wetherhead	I-pers
.	O
About	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
on	O
Fire	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
easy	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Fire	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
to	O
satisfy	O
him	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
every	O
thing	O
safe	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
melancholly	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
.	O
One	O
Lord	O
's	O
Day	O
Morning	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
damned	O
to	O
all	O
Eternity	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
disorder	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Mind	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
another	O
Sabbath-Day	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
before	O
a	O
great	O
Society	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
damned	O
to	O
all	O
Eternity	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
melancholly	O
three	O
Months	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
a	O
Year	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
Lad	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
falling	O
in	O
strange	O
Phrenzies	O
and	O
Disorders	O
of	O
Mind	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
mean	O
'd	O
by	O
this	O
strange	O
Act	O
of	O
his	O
?	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Design	O
to	O
plunder	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
any	O
Resentment	O
against	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
View	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
ending	O
his	O
Days	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
him	O
distemper	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
melancholly	O
Disposition	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Twelve-month	O
;	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shoe-maker	O
by	O
Trade	O
:	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
addicted	O
to	O
Liquor	O
,	O
but	O
lives	O
in	O
all	O
Sobriety	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
some	O
People	O
say	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
or	O
drown	O
himself	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
30.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Heysham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
.	O
March	O
23	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
quart	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ellingham	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
32.	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cow	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Braint	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
John	B-pers
Irons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Alarum	O
Clock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Newman	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Boar-Inn	B-place
in	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
Clock	O
off	O
the	O
Stair-case	O
,	O
and	O
advertis	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
some	O
Thieves	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
turn	O
'd	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Clock	O
was	O
at	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Garton	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Steere	I-pers
.	O
I	O
gave	O
this	O
Clock	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Possession	O
and	O
hung	O
in	O
my	O
Chamber	O
at	O
Christ-Church	O
in	O
Oxford	O
,	O
2	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
from	O
an	O
hundred	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
Holes	O
in	O
the	O
Case	O
to	O
hang	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
Wainscot	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pendulum	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
bent	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
from	O
Oxford	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
's	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Garton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
a	O
single	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
lodged	O
in	O
Red-Lyon	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Reeves	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Reeves	O
brought	O
the	O
Clock	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
People	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
uttering	O
false	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
turned	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
about	O
this	O
Clock	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
by	O
one	O
Liberty	O
,	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
's	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Clock	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Garton	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
Liberty	O
brought	O
this	O
Clock	O
one	O
Night	O
into	O
my	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Reeves	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
at	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
.	O
Liberty	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Clock	O
go	O
till	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
owed	O
me	O
Money	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Garton	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Reeves	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
paid	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
C.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
Mrs.	O
Garton	O
a	O
Question	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
Way	O
of	O
your	O
Trade	O
(	O
and	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
one	O
)	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
enter	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
Persons	O
who	O
bring	O
you	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Money	O
you	O
pay	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
Books	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Garton	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
enter	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Thompson	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
none	O
but	O
himself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
James	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Orrel	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
April	O
15	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Orrel	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Essex	O
's	O
Ball	O
,	O
in	O
Old	O
Gravel	O
Lane	O
,	O
Wapping	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
thence	O
with	O
four	O
Women	O
(	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Fellow	O
to	O
light	O
us	O
)	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Wetherden	O
's	O
by	O
Bell-Dock	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
set	O
upon	O
near	O
Broad-Street	B-place
(	I-place
Wapping	I-place
)	I-place
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
clapp	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
:	O
This	O
he	O
repeated	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Lanthorn	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Candles	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
distinguish	O
his	O
Face	O
very	O
plain	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
Work	O
but	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
scraping	O
the	O
Ship	O
that	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
