TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
Country	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
John	O
Barnyard	O
,	O
Knight	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1738	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
War	O
wick-Lane	O
.	O
M.DC.XXXVIII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Three-Pence	O
.	O
)	O
N.B	O
.	O
The	O
Public	O
may	O
be	O
assured	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
during	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	O
BARNARD	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
)	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
Three-Pence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
shall	O
contain	O
the	O
usual	O
Quantity	O
sold	O
for	O
Six-Pence	O
for	O
many	O
Years	O
past	O
:	O
And	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
Sessions	O
shall	O
be	O
carefully	O
compriz	O
'd	O
in	O
One	O
such	O
Three-penny	O
Book	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
farther	O
Burthen	O
on	O
the	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
BARNARD	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
LEE	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
DENTON	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CARTER	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Worshipful	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Major	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Kemmis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Glinn	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Vansommer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
Naboth	B-pers
Tarrington	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bicknel	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Portal	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Horn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dickens	I-pers
,	O
Josiah	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hamlin	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Cowper	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Elkhorn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
John	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
large	O
leaden	O
Flower-Pots	O
,	O
value	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Foxall	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
2.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mandeville	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
linnen	O
Shift	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
James	B-pers
de	I-pers
Vignicourt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
34	O
Yards	O
of	O
linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
33	O
s	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
de	I-place
Quern	I-place
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4	O
Richard	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Staines	B-place
,	O
March	O
10	O
John	O
Wall	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
where	O
my	O
Horses	O
were	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
view	O
'd	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
sowing	O
some	O
Barley	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
harrowing	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Horses	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
Yard	O
;	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
Work	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
Horses	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
Stable	O
Door	O
fast	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Evening	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
safe	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
smoke	O
a	O
Pipe	O
with	O
my	O
Landlord	O
's	O
Man	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Stable	O
Door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Horse	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
Hands	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
Staines	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Bellman	O
,	O
who	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Sam	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
driving	O
the	O
Horse	O
before	O
him	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
;	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
Hallo	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
me	O
once	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
beating	O
the	O
Horse	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Hempen	O
Halter	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
his	O
Head	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Directions	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Ivall	O
,	O
at	O
South	O
Warnborough	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lives	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
claim	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
very	O
plainly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
5.	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
72	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Beef	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Faith	I-place
under	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abel	B-pers
Dobney	I-pers
,	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
,	O
value	O
3s	O
.	O
and	O
9	O
Hens	O
,	O
value	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Cockran	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Orkran	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Hens	O
,	O
value	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Annover	I-pers
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
8	O
,	O
9.	O
John	B-pers
Toon	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Blastock	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Seabrook	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
and	O
16s	O
.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Feb.	O
27	O
.	O
Edward	O
Seabrook	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Feb	O
I	O
was	O
riding	O
from	O
Muzzel-Hill	B-place
towards	O
Highgate	B-place
;	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
clapping	O
Pistols	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
they	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
about	O
16	O
or	O
18s	O
.	O
Toon	O
held	O
his	O
Hat	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Crown	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
stuck	O
upon	O
the	O
Brims	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
he	O
stoop	O
'd	O
down	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
dropp	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
only	O
the	O
Shilling	O
Toon	O
then	O
proposed	O
to	O
search	O
me	O
for	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
Blastock	O
seeing	O
the	O
String	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
Toon	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
Toon	O
demanded	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
delivered	O
it	O
,	O
Blastock	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
Horse	O
's	O
Bridle	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
whipp	O
'd	O
my	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Creature	O
immediately	O
fell	O
to	O
grazing	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
both	O
dismounted	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
Watch	O
,	O
they	O
mounted	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
gallop	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
catch	O
my	O
Horse	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
seeing	O
their	O
Horses	O
galloping	O
,	O
he	O
gallop	O
'd	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
perceiving	O
a	O
Horse	O
following	O
them	O
,	O
were	O
'frighted	O
(	O
I	O
suppose	O
)	O
and	O
imagined	O
I	O
was	O
pursuing	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
quitted	O
their	O
Horses	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
on	O
Foot	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Highgate	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
3	O
Horses	O
.	O
The	O
People	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
and	O
make	O
Oath	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
;	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Horses	O
to	O
be	O
Pounded	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
that	O
Evening	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
Horse	O
again	O
,	O
(	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
)	O
in	O
10	O
Minutes	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
nor	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
Highgate	O
Church	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
to	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
before	O
Blastock	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believ	O
'd	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
know	O
much	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
from	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
People	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
'd	O
his	O
Coat	O
again	O
perfectly	O
well	O
.	O
Toon	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
self	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
not	O
give	O
the	O
Court	O
any	O
Trouble	O
at	O
all	O
Blastock	O
Mr.	O
Seabrook	O
came	O
to	O
Newgate	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
down	O
;	O
six	O
of	O
us	O
came	O
down	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
one	O
Stevens	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Mr	O
Seabrook	O
.	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
Blastock	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
one	O
else	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
disguised	O
with	O
a	O
Napkin	O
round	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
yet	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
Mercy	O
.	O
Blastock	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
take	O
your	O
Money	O
and	O
Watch	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Seabrook	O
Toon	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Blastock	O
held	O
my	O
Horse	O
.	O
Blastock	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
comes	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
positive	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Seabrook	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Face	O
again	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
;	O
beside	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
his	O
Coat	O
had	O
been	O
torn	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
mended	O
in	O
this	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
brass	O
Buttons	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
begg	O
'd	O
Mercy	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
Power	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
any	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Grimston	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
Blastock	O
hir	O
'd	O
two	O
Horses	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Edmonton	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Jones	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
a	O
Hatter	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Temple-Lane	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
let	O
my	O
Horses	O
without	O
some	O
Satisfaction	O
;	O
therefore	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
after	O
this	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
told	O
me	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
let	O
Blastock	O
and	O
his	O
Companion	O
have	O
the	O
Horses	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
Men	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Horses	O
that	O
were	O
Pounded	O
at	O
Highgate	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
they	O
had	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
them	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
Blastock	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Toon	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
hire	O
the	O
two	O
Horses	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
them	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Manton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Constable	O
that	O
took	O
Toon	O
;	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Blastock	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
likewise	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Chamberlain	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Coat	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Seabrook	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Seabrook	O
knew	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
Moor	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
take	O
Blastock	O
,	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
him	O
hid	O
in	O
Guley	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
Tavern	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
for	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Handcuffs	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
confess	O
at	O
the	O
Tavern	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
bringing	O
him	O
down	O
Holborn	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
he	O
committed	O
this	O
Robbery	O
and	O
that	O
Toon	O
had	O
drawn	O
him	O
into	O
this	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Linton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
House	O
Gate	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Lodge	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Seabrook	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
shewn	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Persons	O
,	O
among	O
whom	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Coat	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
was	O
like	O
that	O
which	O
the	O
Man	O
wore	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Seabrook	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sorrier	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
than	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Nathan	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
subpaena	O
'd	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
the	O
Affair	O
.	O
Blastock	O
was	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
Barber	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
Years	O
ago	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Daniel-Hawkins	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Blastock	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
Years	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
(	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
)	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Seabrook	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
Toon	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Seabrook	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
say	O
so	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
particular	O
Time	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Seabrook	O
said	O
this	O
.	O
Blastock	O
has	O
had	O
dealings	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blastock	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Blastock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elleanor	B-pers
Wildair	I-pers
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Blastock	O
's	O
Character	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Toon	O
's	O
Wife	O
The	O
Day	O
after	O
my	O
Husband	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Seabrook	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
Mr.	O
Toon	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
Blastock	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
After	O
Blastock	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Seabrook	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
informed	O
he	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
from	O
among	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
yes	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
't	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
Descriptions	O
People	O
gave	O
me	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chamberlain	O
.	O
When	O
Toon	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
Blastock	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
's	O
Information	O
,	O
Blastock	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
a	O
Moment	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
himself	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
committed	O
but	O
this	O
one	O
Robbery	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Courage	O
enough	O
to	O
rob	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
yet	O
be	O
frighted	O
by	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
Rider	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
even	O
so	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
behind	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
quitted	O
their	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
to	O
London	O
on	O
Foot	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
one	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
Flint	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
no	O
Pan	O
Miss	O
Jacky	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
(	O
a	O
Convict	O
of	O
last	O
Sessions	O
)	O
I	O
come	O
here	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Blastock	O
's	O
Account	O
;	O
what	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Seabrook	O
say	O
,	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
how	O
,	O
-	O
when	O
we	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
below	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
walked	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
(	O
not	O
)	O
swear	O
to	O
no	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bugdon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
under	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
.	O
-	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
Charge	O
of	O
Perjury	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Blastock	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
no	O
one	O
but	O
Toon	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
10	O
,	O
11.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sparkes	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
value	O
15s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
April	O
6	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
John	B-pers
Petty	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
Sheets	O
;	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hayter	I-pers
,	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
John	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14	O
,	O
15	O
,	O
16.	O
Judith	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	I-pers
(	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Judith	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Tinman	I-pers
)	I-pers
)	O
William	B-pers
Tinman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
their	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
Persons	O
employed	O
at	O
the	O
Mint	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
(	O
not	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
)	O
for	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
nor	O
weighing	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
their	O
Allegiance	O
,	O
but	O
contriving	O
and	O
intending	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
People	O
,	O
feloniously	O
and	O
traiterously	O
to	O
deceive	O
and	O
defraud	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
22	O
Pieces	O
of	O
false	O
,	O
feigned	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Money	O
,	O
of	O
Pewter	O
,	O
Tin	O
,	O
Lead	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Metal	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Likeness	O
of	O
Shillings	O
,	O
falsely	O
,	O
deceitfully	O
and	O
traiterously	O
,	O
did	O
Forge	O
and	O
Coin	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
evil	O
Example	O
of	O
Others	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
against	O
their	O
Duty	O
and	O
Allegiance	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
not	O
being	O
Persons	O
employ	O
'd	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Mint	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
or	O
elsewhere	O
,	O
for	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
nor	O
being	O
lawfully	O
authorized	O
by	O
the	O
Lord	O
High	O
Treasurer	O
,	O
or	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
the	O
Treasury	O
for	O
the	O
Time	O
being	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
their	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
after	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
1697	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
with	O
Force	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Molds	O
made	O
of	O
Chalk	O
,	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
Molds	O
was	O
impress	O
'd	O
the	O
Figure	O
and	O
Resemblance	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Sides	O
of	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
lawfull	O
Authority	O
or	O
Excuse	O
,	O
knowingly	O
and	O
traiterously	O
had	O
in	O
their	O
Custody	O
and	O
Possession	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Saul	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
their	O
Allegiance	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
having	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Charge	O
,	O
the	O
following	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Donnavin	I-pers
I	O
was	O
born	O
at	O
Chester	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
bred	O
up	O
in	O
Ireland	O
:	O
Judith	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
was	O
born	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Ireland	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Murray	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
arrived	O
at	O
Park-Gate	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
Place	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
bad	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
off	O
for	O
her	O
Livelihood	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
keep	O
her	O
Counsel	O
?	O
I	O
promis	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
shewed	O
me	O
about	O
8l	O
.	O
in	O
these	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Half	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
Brother	O
Philip	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Way	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
and	O
call	O
for	O
something	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
Groat	O
or	O
Six-pence	O
:	O
Philip	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Half	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Change	O
in	O
good	O
Money	O
;	O
then	O
Judith	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
change	O
his	O
Half	O
Crown	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Half	O
Crown	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
these	O
Shillings	O
for	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
.	O
Thus	O
they	O
changed	O
the	O
bad	O
Money	O
for	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Way	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
Bread	O
.	O
I	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
Counsel	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Secret	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
me	O
how	O
she	O
made	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
accordingly	O
did	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
on	O
this	O
Side	O
of	O
Park-Gate	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
where	O
she	O
conceal	O
'd	O
her	O
making	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
suffered	O
only	O
to	O
pass	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Some	O
Time	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
Judith	O
Murray	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Time	O
precisely	O
)	O
and	O
we	O
left	O
Philip	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
in	O
England	O
,	O
while	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
our	O
bad	O
Money	O
.	O
In	O
France	O
we	O
got	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Tinman	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
landed	O
at	O
Dover	O
At	O
a	O
Place	O
call	O
'd	O
Hithe	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
detected	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
Judith	O
Murray	O
concealed	O
her	O
Molds	O
,	O
yet	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
discharged	O
by	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
of	O
Hithe	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Person	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
From	O
this	O
Place	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Cable-street	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
Months	O
ago	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lodge	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
in	O
Holywell-Lane	O
,	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
Donnavin	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
there	O
:	O
We	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
Money	O
made	O
there	O
,	O
'till	O
the	O
Day	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Morning	O
Judith	O
put	O
the	O
Chalk	O
,	O
(	O
or	O
something	O
White	O
)	O
into	O
the	O
Molds	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
made	O
an	O
Impression	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
a	O
Shilling	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
afterward	O
fix	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Molds	O
were	O
ready	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
two	O
pewter	O
Spoons	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
broke	O
them	O
to	O
Peices	O
,	O
she	O
fill	O
'd	O
a	O
Tobacco	O
Pipe	O
:	O
Phillip	O
Murray	O
held	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Fire	O
'till	O
the	O
Pipe	O
was	O
red-hot	O
;	O
then	O
Judith	O
pour	O
'd	O
the	O
Metal	O
into	O
the	O
Molds	O
,	O
and	O
Tinman	O
clipp	O
'd	O
the	O
edges	O
of	O
the	O
Shilling	O
thus	O
made	O
They	O
had	O
made	O
8	O
of	O
these	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
Morning	O
to	O
detect	O
them	O
.	O
Tinman	O
clipp	O
'd	O
the	O
edges	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Pieces	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Scissars	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
many	O
,	O
for	O
Judith	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
do	O
them	O
better	O
herself	O
.	O
Phillip	O
Murray	O
colour	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
4	O
Shillings	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
Morning	O
with	O
Quicksilver	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
pass	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
Judith	O
desired	O
Phillip	O
Murray	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
any	O
accident	O
happening	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
accept	O
of	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
detect	O
them	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
Mr.	O
North	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Constable	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
placed	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
stay	O
'till	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
still	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
always	O
hid	O
her	O
Molds	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Phillip	O
coming	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
whether	O
his	O
Sister	O
had	O
done	O
Coining	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
No	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
only	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Pot	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
fetch	O
the	O
Beer	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
now	O
go	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
Judith	O
when	O
the	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Flasks	O
(	O
or	O
Molds	O
)	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
thrown	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Window	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
about	O
18	O
s.	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
4	O
they	O
had	O
finish	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
This	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Phillip	O
Murray	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
Lodge	O
at	O
this	O
Place	O
;	O
Was	O
not	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
that	O
Morning	O
to	O
Bleed	O
my	O
Sister	O
?	O
Donnavin	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sent	O
for	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
he	O
did	O
Bleed	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
put	O
off	O
this	O
Money	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
Judith	O
Murray	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
?	O
Donnavin	O
.	O
We	O
generally	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
off	O
her	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
frequently	O
had	O
Battles	O
.	O
Phillip	O
Murray	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Haines	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
What	O
you	O
could	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
?	O
Donnavin	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
-	O
with	O
colouring	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
recollect	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
melted	O
the	O
Metal	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Surprize	O
.	O
Phillip	O
Murray	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
could	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
nothing	O
but	O
putting	O
off	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
Donnavin	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
I	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
Donnavin	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
some	O
Coiners	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Party	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
as	O
bad	O
as	O
They	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
Them	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
impeach	O
Her	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
Information	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
John	O
on	O
Horseback	O
,	O
in	O
Holywell	B-place
lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
placed	O
my	O
self	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
go	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
Mr.	O
Barlow	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Presently	O
Donnavin	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Purl	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
.	O
She	O
carry	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Purl	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
to	O
call	O
us	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
we	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
closely	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
3	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
whether	O
Judith	O
was	O
sitting	O
or	O
standing	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
keep	O
all	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Donnavin	O
,	O
who	O
she	O
charged	O
with	O
Coining	O
?	O
She	O
charg	O
'd	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Judith	O
lifted	O
up	O
her	O
Hands	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
-	O
What	O
!	O
have	O
you	O
serv	O
'd	O
me	O
so	O
!	O
And	O
immediately	O
she	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
Knees	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
for	O
Favour	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Surprize	O
,	O
and	O
lest	O
any	O
Mischief	O
should	O
happen	O
,	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
turn	O
out	O
their	O
Pockets	O
.	O
While	O
this	O
was	O
doing	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Barlow	O
found	O
the	O
Molds	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
hot	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
visible	O
Impression	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
King	O
William	O
's	O
Shilling	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
Impression	O
was	O
plain	O
,	O
but	O
Blank	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Barlow	O
found	O
18	O
Shillings	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
Cap	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
here	O
they	O
are	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
mark	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Wroth	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
them	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
Donnavin	O
brought	O
me	O
from	O
Ireland	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
her	O
hired	O
Servant	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
her	O
,	O
Whether	O
Phillip	O
Murray	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
Bleed	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Foot	O
?	O
Because	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
Fairer	O
,	O
than	O
Bleeding	O
in	O
the	O
Arm	O
would	O
.	O
Donnavin	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
spake	O
about	O
Bleeding	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
Money	O
upon	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
(	O
To	O
Rogers	O
.	O
Rogers	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
a	O
good	O
Shilling	O
upon	O
Judith	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barlow	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
Donnavin	O
told	O
us	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
Coiners	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Judith	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
Knees	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
was	O
searching	O
their	O
Pockets	O
for	O
Fear	O
of	O
Mischief	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Moulds	O
upon	O
a	O
Table	O
by	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
,	O
covered	O
with	O
a	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
hot	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
likewise	O
18	O
Shillings	O
in	O
the	O
Crown	O
of	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Cap	O
,	O
fifteen	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
mark	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
North	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Pipes	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
with	O
the	O
Moulds	O
.	O
Donnavin	O
charged	O
Judith	O
Murray	O
with	O
coining	O
them	O
,	O
Tinman	O
with	O
clipping	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Philip	O
Murray	O
with	O
silvering	O
them	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Wroth	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
she	O
charged	O
Phil	O
.	O
with	O
doing	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
John	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Donnavin	O
who	O
she	O
charged	O
?	O
all	O
three	O
for	O
coining	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
passing	O
off	O
bad	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
yet	O
she	O
should	O
save	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barlow	O
delivered	O
me	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
Pieces	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
North	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
very	O
speedily	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
the	O
Ashes	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Metal	O
.	O
Donnavin	O
charg	O
'd	O
Phil	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
with	O
silvering	O
the	O
Shillings	O
over	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Mr.	O
North	O
.	O
I	O
act	O
for	O
the	O
Solicitor	O
of	O
the	O
Mint	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hain	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
detain	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
search	O
their	O
Room	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Ashes	O
some	O
Bowls	O
of	O
Tobacco-pipes	O
,	O
discoloured	O
with	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
Metal	O
had	O
been	O
melted	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
imagined	O
the	O
Holes	O
in	O
the	O
Pipes	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
running	O
of	O
the	O
Metal	O
when	O
melted	O
into	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Metal	O
in	O
the	O
Ashes	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Quicksilver	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barlow	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
till	O
Mr.	O
North	O
came	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hain	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
North	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
and	O
search	O
the	O
Room	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
North	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
searched	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
again	O
and	O
saw	O
these	O
Moulds	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
perfect	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Impression	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Shilling	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
plain	O
upon	O
one	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Moulds	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
it	O
was	O
plain	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Pieces	O
that	O
were	O
shewn	O
to	O
me	O
exactly	O
tally	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Impression	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
Moulds	O
(	O
or	O
Flasks	O
)	O
which	O
were	O
then	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Chalk	O
is	O
now	O
fell	O
out	O
and	O
the	O
Impression	O
are	O
destroyed	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
Donnavin	O
swore	O
that	O
Judith	O
coin	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
Tinman	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
Knobs	O
and	O
finish	O
'd	O
the	O
Edges	O
,	O
and	O
Phil	O
.	O
Murray	O
silver	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
Quicksilver	O
.	O
Phil	O
.	O
Murray	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
bleed	O
my	O
Sister	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Conversation	O
with	O
Donnavin	O
,	O
but	O
work	O
'd	O
hard	O
for	O
my	O
Bread	O
.	O
Tinman	O
.	O
I	O
chanced	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
their	O
making	O
or	O
putting	O
off	O
bad	O
Money	O
.	O
Judith	O
Murray	O
.	O
No	O
one	O
ever	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
but	O
Donnavin	O
and	O
I	O
.	O
She	O
transported	O
her	O
own	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
whipped	O
at	O
Dublin	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
,	O
Archibald	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
-	O
Roach	O
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Banfield	I-pers
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
Tinman	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
-	O
Jackson	O
,	O
-	O
Craddock	O
,	O
-	O
Murray	O
,	O
-	O
Walker	O
,	O
-	O
Harrison	O
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Flawn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
-	O
Archpool	O
,	O
appeared	O
in	O
Philip	O
Murray	O
's	O
Behalf	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
industrious	O
Lad	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Guilty	O
;	O
Death	O
.	O
17.	O
James	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-six	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
March	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Woollen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Dunmore	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Henrietta-maria	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brocade	O
Lustring	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Ann	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Perrot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
two	O
Flannel	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
two	O
quilted	O
Coats	O
,	O
three	O
Aprons	O
,	O
six	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
March	O
15	O
,	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Thomas	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bolster	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Feather	O
Pillow	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
Blankets	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Daws	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Street	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Stephen	O
,	O
Coleman	O
Street	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
String	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d	O
a	O
Bathmetal	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Horn	O
Whistle	O
tipt	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
Tobacco-stopper	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
old	O
Coin	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
11	O
s	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Nov	O
6	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Woman	O
Home	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Spittlefields	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
returning	O
back	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
along	O
under	O
Bedlam	O
Wall	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
Men	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
String	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
into	O
my	O
Fob	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
being	O
robbed	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Bedlam	B-place
Gate	I-place
,	O
four	O
Men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
strike	O
up	O
my	O
Heels	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
off	O
with	O
my	O
Hands	O
;	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
Hand	O
before	O
this	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
was	O
put	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
in	O
this	O
Manner	O
they	O
held	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
String	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
a	O
Clasp	O
Penknife	O
,	O
a	O
Wire	O
Tobacco-stopper	O
,	O
a	O
Whistle	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Shape	O
of	O
a	O
Bugle	O
Horn	O
,	O
tipp	O
'd	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Flemish	O
Pocket-Piece	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
Dantzick	O
Skilling	O
on	O
the	O
one	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Flourish	O
round	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
their	O
Number	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
a	O
Lamp	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
rifled	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
Swift	O
(	O
the	O
Evidence	O
)	O
and	O
Golding	O
,	O
since	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
Swift	O
,	O
nor	O
can	O
I	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
Things	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
call	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
believed	O
Swift	O
,	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Burroughs	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
Swift	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
carried	O
out	O
of	O
Court	O
while	O
Burroughs	O
was	O
under	O
Examination	O
,	O
now	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
Golding	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Daws	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
met	O
at	O
Daws	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Barbican	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
rob	O
somebody	O
or	O
other	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
first	O
of	O
all	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Road	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
robbed	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
Seven-pence	O
Three	O
Farthings	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Bedlam	O
Wall	O
we	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Burroughs	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Hands	O
over	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
his	O
Pistol	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
Markham	O
stood	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Eleven	O
Shillings	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Daws	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Watch	O
we	O
carried	O
to	O
Rumford	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
;	O
Daws	O
kept	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
Share	O
,	O
we	O
three	O
divided	O
the	O
Guinea	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
7	O
s.	O
apiece	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Swift	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
seven	O
Aprons	O
of	O
Madam	O
Beavis	O
's	O
taken	O
from	O
Charter-House	O
Square	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Beavis	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
this	O
Fact	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
swear	O
any	O
Thing	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
Home	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
myself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
my	O
Companions	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
Information	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pawned	O
the	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Shirt	O
that	O
is	O
now	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Time	O
we	O
ever	O
went	O
out	O
altogether	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
Swift	O
,	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
Linnen	O
,	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
Information	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
included	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Why	O
your	O
only	O
Way	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
is	O
to	O
make	O
yourself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Farmer	O
's	O
at	O
No	O
.	O
14.	O
in	O
Princes-Square	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
only	O
his	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Story	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Information	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Warrener	O
(	O
the	O
Clerk	O
)	O
refused	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
without	O
we	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
voluntarily	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
Note	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
my	O
Word	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
the	O
Guinea	O
down	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
send	O
my	O
Watch	O
Home	O
to	O
my	O
Spouse	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Token	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Guinea	O
came	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Warrener	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Information	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sworn	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
Search	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
he	O
had	O
nam	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Information	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
this	O
very	O
Robbery	O
was	O
mentioned	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
express	O
'd	O
their	O
Resentment	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Warrener	O
's	O
Behaviour	O
;	O
and	O
declar	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Duty	O
of	O
all	O
,	O
who	O
serve	O
as	O
Clerks	O
under	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
always	O
ready	O
to	O
execute	O
their	O
office	O
without	O
Extortion	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Revington	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Evidence	O
Swift	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
some	O
Linnen	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
People	O
being	O
with	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Discovery	O
before	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
remanded	O
back	O
till	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Old-street	O
Square	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
frequently	O
seen	O
them	O
together	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
saw	O
Daws	O
,	O
Swift	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
together	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
often	O
together	O
,	O
both	O
by	O
Day	O
and	O
Night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pinkney	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
serv	O
'd	O
me	O
honestly	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
got	O
linked	O
with	O
this	O
Evidence	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
never	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ealing	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Painter	B-pers
Cade	I-pers
,	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
had	O
heard	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Loxley	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Soldier	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
Son	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
.	O
When	O
his	O
Apprenticeship	O
should	O
be	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
our	O
Troop	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
qualify	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Trooper	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
met	O
with	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
23.	O
of	B-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
Bar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6d	O
,	O
belonging	O
and	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
,	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24	O
,	O
25.	O
John	B-pers
Tisoal	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Irish	I-pers
John	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Susannah	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
1	O
s.	O
October	O
13	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26.	O
William	B-pers
Currants	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cambrick	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Haggarth	I-pers
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linnen	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
6	O
d	O
,	O
a	O
cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
lac	O
'd	O
Cap	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Jephs	I-pers
,	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
David	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
March	O
30	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Esther	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Nailor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
Coffee-Pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Liberty	B-place
of	I-place
Norton	I-place
Falgate	I-place
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30	O
Martha	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
Yards	O
of	O
Calamanco	O
,	O
value	O
34	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
March	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31.	O
William	B-pers
Sawbridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Basket	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
Loaves	O
of	O
Bread	O
,	O
value	O
2s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Travis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shipton	I-pers
,	O
M.D	O
.	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ellsmore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Manteel	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Surton	I-pers
,	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
John	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
bed	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1s	O
.	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
2	O
Blankets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
2s	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
Quilt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
,	O
March	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36.	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
procuring	O
John	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
David	B-pers
Birk	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Subject	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
to	O
enlist	O
and	O
enter	O
in	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
without	O
Leave	O
from	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
Sign	O
Manual	O
,	O
first	O
had	O
and	O
obtained	O
,	O
in	O
Contempt	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
his	O
Laws	O
&	O
c.	O
April	O
1st	O
And	O
afterwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
hiring	O
and	O
retaining	O
the	O
said	O
Davison	O
,	O
alias	O
Birk	O
,	O
a	O
Subject	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
cause	O
him	O
to	O
enlist	O
and	O
enter	O
himself	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
,	O
a	O
foreign	O
Prince	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
without	O
Leave	O
from	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
Sign	O
Manual	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
a	O
a	O
feloniously	O
procuring	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Subject	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
to	O
enlist	O
and	O
enter	O
in	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
-	O
as	O
above	O
,	O
April	O
1	O
.	O
And	O
afterwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
hiring	O
and	O
retaining	O
the	O
said	O
White	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
(	O
as	O
above	O
)	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Offence	O
;	O
then	O
proceeded	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
-	O
Snafe	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Shropshire	O
Man	O
.	O
About	O
Michaelmas	O
last	O
he	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
well	O
encourag	O
'd	O
and	O
rewarded	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
any	O
Men	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
6	O
Foot	O
high	O
or	O
upwards	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Forces	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
their	O
being	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
Prussia	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
End	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
me	O
Money	O
from	O
Time	O
to	O
Time	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
23	O
or	O
24	O
Shillings	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
Michaelmas	O
last	O
.	O
Twice	O
I	O
had	O
2	O
Half-Guineas	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
Half-a-Crown	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
23	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
Some	O
trifling	O
Pence	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
at	O
other	O
Times	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Davison	O
and	O
White	O
?	O
Snafe	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
here	O
they	O
are	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
their	O
being	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Snafe	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
(	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
that	O
I	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
)	O
in	O
Windsor-Court	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
likewise	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
remov	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
Vinegar	O
Yard	O
in	O
Guy's-Court	O
,	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
both	O
Houses	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
Windsor-Court	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
Clare-Market	O
,	O
between	O
Clare	O
Market	O
and	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
they	O
first	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
?	O
Snafe	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
he	O
Month	O
,	O
but	O
't	O
was	O
before	O
Christmas	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
been	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
several	O
Times	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
encourage	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
him	O
make	O
them	O
merry	O
with	O
Eatables	O
and	O
Drinking	O
.	O
I	O
may	O
express	O
the	O
Words	O
I	O
suppose	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
encourage	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Service	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
mentioned	O
of	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
continue	O
in	O
the	O
Prussian	O
Service	O
?	O
Snafe	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
must	O
continue	O
in	O
the	O
Service	O
3	O
Year	O
;	O
and	O
Davison	O
and	O
White	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
10	O
l.	O
each	O
[	O
Text	O
unreadable	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
at	O
Hamburgh	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Money	O
here	O
for	O
Fear	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
trust	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
there	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
give	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
any	O
Money	O
?	O
Snafe	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
White	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
White	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
Instant	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
Security	O
had	O
they	O
that	O
the	O
10	O
l.	O
should	O
be	O
paid	O
them	O
at	O
Hamburgh	O
?	O
Snafe	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
them	O
Notes	O
under	O
his	O
Hand	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Notes	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
Davison	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
deliver	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
read	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Purport	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
receive	O
10	O
l.	O
on	O
their	O
Arrival	O
at	O
Hamburgh	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Shilling	O
given	O
for	O
?	O
Snafe	O
.	O
To	O
enlist	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Both	O
Davison	O
and	O
White	O
read	O
their	O
Notes	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
give	O
White	O
his	O
Note	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
deliver	O
Davison	O
's	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
read	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Notes	O
again	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
?	O
Snafe	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Notes	O
:	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
read	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Defendant	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
read	O
?	O
Snafe	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Does	O
Davison	O
go	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
Name	O
?	O
Snafe	O
.	O
By	O
some	O
Title	O
of	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
call	O
'd	O
Birk	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Witnesses	O
's	O
Name	O
is	O
not	O
Snafe	O
,	O
but	O
Senett	O
.	O
Pray	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
me	O
seduce	O
Birk	O
or	O
White	O
,	O
to	O
enlist	O
into	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
's	O
Service	O
?	O
Snafe	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Service	O
,	O
was	O
named	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Defendant	O
's	O
delivering	O
colour	O
'd	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
Davison	O
and	O
White	O
?	O
Snafe	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
deliver	O
a	O
Snuff-colour	O
'd	O
Coat	O
to	O
White	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Coat	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
likewise	O
deliver	O
this	O
other	O
Coat	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
.	O
These	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
to	O
disguise	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
lest	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
discover	O
'd	O
in	O
their	O
Regimentals	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
board	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Evening	O
.	O
The	O
Notes	O
were	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
of	O
late	O
?	O
Snafe	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
angry	O
sometimes	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
neglected	O
what	O
he	O
encouraged	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
him	O
tall	O
Men	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
declar	O
'd	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Snafe	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	O
Davison	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Brik	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
We	O
met	O
him	O
at	O
Snafe	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Windsor-Court	B-place
,	O
where	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
my	O
Comerade	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Snafe	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Defendant	O
propose	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
your	O
going	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
?	O
Davison	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
several	O
Times	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
him	O
any	O
Men	O
,	O
6	O
Feet	O
high	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
to	O
Hamburgh	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
encourag	O
'd	O
and	O
rewarded	O
.	O
He	O
spoke	O
to	O
my	O
Comerade	O
,	O
White	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Mind	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
consented	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
propose	O
your	O
going	O
too	O
?	O
Davison	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
this	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
Pretence	O
;	O
for	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
White	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
3	O
Years	O
Service	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Guards	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Produce	O
the	O
Note	O
.	O
Davison	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Note	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wrote	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
my	O
Mark	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Williamson	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
this	O
Note	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
payable	O
to	O
David	B-pers
Birk	I-pers
?	O
Davison	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Brother	O
by	O
half	O
Blood	O
,	O
of	O
this	O
Name	O
,	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
most	O
People	O
that	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
call	O
me	O
by	O
his	O
Sur-name	O
.	O
His	O
Name	O
is	O
Toby	B-pers
Birk	I-pers
.	O
The	O
David	O
Birk	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
is	O
intended	O
for	O
my	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
means	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
always	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
John	O
Birk	O
,	O
except	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Barracks	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
Davison	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Note	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
David	O
Birk	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
farther	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
your	O
going	O
beyond	O
Sea	O
?	O
Davison	O
.	O
He	O
contriv	O
'd	O
so	O
far	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Comerade	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
with	O
the	O
Evening	O
Tide	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
colour	O
'd	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
in	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
us	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
learn	O
what	O
Time	O
the	O
Hamburgh	O
Ship	O
was	O
to	O
sail	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
us	O
Word	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Ship	O
would	O
sail	O
that	O
Tide	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
must	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastecoat	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
disguise	O
myself	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Soldier	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
Design	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
to	O
Serjeant	O
Philips	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Notes	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Williamson	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
with	O
some	O
Men	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
:	O
where	O
the	O
Colonel	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
-	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
either	O
Honour	O
or	O
Honesty	O
,	O
come	O
away	O
directly	O
;	O
because	O
we	O
had	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
Shilling	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
a	O
second	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
my	O
Comerade	O
White	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
Night	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
than	O
ordinary	O
upon	O
Guard	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
when	O
any	O
Conversation	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
White	O
,	O
in	O
Relation	O
to	O
his	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
.	O
Davison	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
White	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
a	O
Week	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
's	O
Guards	O
,	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
per	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
landed	O
at	O
Hamburgh	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
his	O
Promise	O
to	O
White	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
he	O
promised	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wrote	O
the	O
Promissory	O
Note	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
to	O
White	O
?	O
Davison	O
.	O
White	O
had	O
his	O
Note	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
White	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
Note	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
Hand-writing	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
and	O
deliver	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
The	O
Notes	O
were	O
read	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
March	O
30	O
,	O
1738	O
.	O
``	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
David	O
Birk	O
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
for	O
``	O
Value	O
received	O
,	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
Ten	O
Pounds	O
,	O
as	O
``	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
arrived	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
Hamburgh	O
;	O
``	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
own	O
Will	O
and	O
Proposal	O
,	O
for	O
three	O
``	O
Years	O
Service	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
's	O
Guards	O
.	O
By	O
Me	O
,	O
WILLIAM	O
LAWRENCE	O
.	O
LONDON	O
,	O
March	O
30	O
,	O
1738.	O
``	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
for	O
``	O
Value	O
received	O
,	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
Ten	O
Pounds	O
,	O
as	O
``	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
arrives	O
at	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
Hamburgh	O
;	O
``	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
Will	O
and	O
Proposal	O
,	O
``	O
to	O
enter	O
into	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
's	O
Service	O
for	O
``	O
three	O
Years	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
LAWRENCE	I-pers
.	O
Davison	O
.	O
Both	O
these	O
Notes	O
were	O
given	O
us	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-Head	O
,	O
in	O
Peter-Street	O
,	O
Clare-Market	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
since	O
Michaelmas	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
Time	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Business	O
of	O
entering	O
into	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
's	O
Guards	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
Account	O
he	O
daily	O
treated	O
me	O
with	O
Victuals	O
and	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
always	O
reflecting	O
upon	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
poor	O
sorry	O
Bread	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
rare	O
Things	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
Prussia	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
under	O
six	O
Foot	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
una	O
every	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
above	O
six	O
Foot	O
high	O
,	O
should	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
the	O
more	O
Pay	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
Meetings	O
had	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
Notes	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Several	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
Times	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
March	O
we	O
made	O
the	O
Agreement	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
our	O
Encouragement	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
Notes	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
for	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
payable	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Hamburgh	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
aboard	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
Provisions	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Things	O
proper	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
proceed	O
to	O
the	O
Vessel	O
.	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
disguise	O
me	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
colour	O
'd	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
kept	O
and	O
have	O
brought	O
hither	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
Davison	O
Cloaths	O
likewise	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
fit	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
aboard	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
gave	O
Information	O
to	O
my	O
Serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Williamson	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
a	O
Guard	O
from	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Colonel	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Who	O
writ	O
the	O
Notes	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Because	O
't	O
is	O
said	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
't	O
is	O
your	O
own	O
Will	O
and	O
Proposal	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
him	O
so	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
the	O
Scheme	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
his	O
Roguery	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
writ	O
the	O
Notes	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Presence	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Note	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
never	O
deluded	O
by	O
Birk	O
and	O
Sennett	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Germany	O
or	O
France	O
?	O
And	O
did	O
not	O
they	O
tell	O
you	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Foreign	O
Service	O
before	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Davison	O
and	O
I	O
intrigued	O
all	O
along	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
catch	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Birk	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
several	O
Times	O
on	O
that	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
I	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Mind	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
nor	O
should	O
I	O
go	O
.	O
We	O
shew	O
'd	O
a	O
Disposition	O
to	O
go	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
deceive	O
and	O
detect	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Sennet	O
(	O
Snafe	O
)	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Disposition	O
of	O
Spight	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
concerning	O
his	O
Wife	O
?	O
White	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
in	O
this	O
World	O
,	O
nor	O
Davison	O
neither	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
)	O
Davison	O
and	O
White	O
are	O
Soldiers	O
in	O
our	O
Regiment	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
White	O
came	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
Captain	O
Parker	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
his	O
Servant	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
White	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
Prussia	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Comrade	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Ten	O
Pound	O
Note	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Williamson	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Note	O
,	O
I	O
read	O
it	O
over	O
and	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
Colonel	O
Williamson	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
End	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
it	O
go	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Colonel	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
hold	O
a	O
Candle	O
to	O
his	O
Fingers	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
his	O
giving	O
those	O
Notes	O
?	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
resolve	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Men	O
obliged	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Colonel	O
Williamson	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
This	O
Serjeant	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Notes	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
Design	O
was	O
going	O
forwards	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
enlisted	O
two	O
Grenadiers	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
's	O
Service	O
.	O
The	O
Note	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
full	O
and	O
distinct	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
proper	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
this	O
Fellow	O
.	O
The	O
Serjeant	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Men	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
honest	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
this	O
Information	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
Men	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
not	O
only	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
Men	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
myself	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Serjeant	O
and	O
a	O
File	O
of	O
Musquetteers	O
,	O
and	O
planted	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
take	O
Water	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
waited	O
some	O
little	O
Time	O
,	O
Davison	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
be	O
there	O
presently	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Time	O
was	O
come	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
this	O
brown	O
Coat	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
produced	O
here	O
.	O
About	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
Guard	O
running	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
they	O
overtook	O
him	O
near	O
Thomas-street	O
by	O
Billingsgate	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
both	O
the	O
Notes	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
some	O
Questions	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
humm	O
'd	O
and	O
haw	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Rogues	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
Notes	O
(	O
and	O
shewing	O
him	O
one	O
)	O
is	O
this	O
your	O
Hand-Writing	O
?	O
Let	O
me	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Note	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
Writing	O
?	O
He	O
would	O
make	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
let	O
go	O
the	O
Note	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
it	O
go	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Candle	O
to	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
felt	O
the	O
Flame	O
he	O
quitted	O
his	O
Hold	O
.	O
On	O
this	O
full	O
Evidence	O
I	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Men	O
these	O
Notes	O
Serjeant	O
Philips	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
after	O
the	O
Colonel	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Note	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
While	O
we	O
waited	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
say	O
,	O
-	O
Now	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
either	O
Honour	O
or	O
Honesty	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
this	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
all	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Heels	O
and	O
run	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
Lane	O
towards	O
Thames-Street	O
,	O
the	O
Guard	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
running	O
against	O
him	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
again	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
Birk	O
and	O
Sennett	O
have	O
sent	O
Men	O
abroad	O
these	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
instigate	O
them	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
Thing	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
M'Cauly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Sennet	O
's	O
(	O
Snafe	O
's	O
)	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
Davison	O
and	O
White	O
with	O
Lawrence	O
eating	O
and	O
drinking	O
there	O
.	O
Snafe	O
kept	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
we	O
call	O
him	O
Sennett	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
encourage	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
Sennett	O
employ	O
'd	O
me	O
once	O
,	O
-	O
with	O
Submission	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
and	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Jury	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
employ	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
alter	O
an	O
old	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
against	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
paid	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
Sennett	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
employ	O
me	O
.	O
Sennett	O
helped	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
upon	O
Birk	O
's	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
White	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Room	O
up-stairs	O
to	O
dress	O
himself	O
in	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
seen	O
Lawrence	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Davison	O
and	O
White	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
eating	O
and	O
drinking	O
?	O
M'Cauly	O
Not	O
together	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Company	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
join	O
'd	O
Company	O
;	O
-	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
Seats	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
When	O
White	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Room	O
to	O
dress	O
himself	O
in	O
,	O
Snafe	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
Bl	O
-	O
d	O
and	O
W	O
-	O
ds	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
dress	O
yourself	O
there	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
(	O
can	O
not	O
)	O
mention	O
the	O
Day	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Recollect	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
M'Cauly	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
.	O
-	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
directly	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
sitted	O
on	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
?	O
M'Cauly	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
smelt	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
Snafe	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
get	O
5	O
Guineas	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
procure	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Snafe	O
measur	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
measur	O
'd	O
6	O
Feet	O
high	O
in	O
his	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Carpenter	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
bring	O
him	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
taller	O
than	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
Snafe	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
very	O
well	O
together	O
;	O
but	O
Carpenter	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Nathan	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Peruke-maker	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
frequently	O
in	O
Snafe	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
several	O
Quarrels	O
,	O
which	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
understood	O
,	O
were	O
from	O
Jealousy	O
of	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Once	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
Wife	O
had	O
abus	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
Snafe	O
often	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
even	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
Night	O
or	O
by	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
one	O
upon	O
his	O
Taw	O
,	O
swearing	O
bloody	O
Oaths	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
warn	O
Davison	O
from	O
keeping	O
Snafe	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
Snafe	O
)	O
was	O
a	O
spunging	O
,	O
lurking	O
Companion	O
It	O
was	O
entirely	O
out	O
of	O
jealousy	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
Uneasiness	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Snafe	O
and	O
Davison	O
deserted	O
out	O
of	O
France	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
and	O
Snafe	O
's	O
Wife	O
are	O
Brother	O
and	O
Sister	O
's	O
Children	O
.	O
Snafe	O
has	O
often	O
complained	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
kept	O
his	O
Wife	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
even	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
have	O
had	O
Words	O
together	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
Occasion	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
Snafe	O
)	O
has	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
sold	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Devil	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Birmingham	O
?	O
Riley	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
several	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
But	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
Birmingham	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
?	O
Riley	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Turner	O
,	O
a	O
noted	O
Man	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
he	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
?	O
Riley	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Birmingham	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
This	O
Day	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
April	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
.	O
He	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
so	O
went	O
to	O
Snafe	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
settle	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
light	O
Candles	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
wonder	O
at	O
his	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
at	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
?	O
Riley	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
a	O
Porter	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
Come	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
,	O
-	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
too	O
late	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
want	O
any	O
Body	O
to	O
come	O
;	O
if	O
they	O
do	O
n't	O
come	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
stay	O
.	O
The	O
Porter	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
.	O
Lawrence	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Drink	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
down	O
Russel-Court	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
Birk	O
,	O
(	O
or	O
Davison	O
:	O
)	O
I	O
enter	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Windsor	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Land-man	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sick	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
St.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newtoner	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
Birk	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Nights	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
3	O
Years	O
ago	O
last	O
Winter	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
soul	O
Disease	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
France	O
for	O
a	O
Cure	O
;	O
telling	O
me	O
that	O
Soldiers	O
were	O
punish	O
'd	O
here	O
for	O
the	O
least	O
Fault	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
they	O
are	O
punish	O
'd	O
for	O
nothing	O
but	O
stealing	O
.	O
Birk	O
,	O
alias	O
Davison	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Man	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Connor	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Riley	O
's	O
the	O
(	O
Shoemaker	O
's	O
)	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Snafe	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
dogg	O
'd	O
his	O
Wife	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
Night	O
or	O
by	O
Day	O
;	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
sleep	O
'till	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
Irons	O
.	O
Snafe	O
is	O
my	O
Relation	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
these	O
Men	O
,	O
Davison	O
and	O
White	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
oblige	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
his	O
Note	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
Water	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Englishman	O
,	O
not	O
an	O
Irishman	O
,	O
the	O
2	O
Men	O
would	O
trust	O
him	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
all	O
thro	O
'	O
Jealousy	O
this	O
is	O
done	O
.	O
Snafe	O
told	O
me	O
farther	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Men	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
Snafe	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sennett	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Snafe	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
that	O
Man	O
's	O
(	O
Snafe	O
's	O
)	O
Wife	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
one	O
Day	O
last	O
Week	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
-	O
thro	O
'	O
Vinegar	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
meeting	O
Davison	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Thistle	O
and	O
Crown	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
vile	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
as	O
this	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
He	O
was	O
heartily	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
raise	O
Snafe	O
and	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
both	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
;	O
for	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
loth	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Hand	O
in	O
the	O
Blood	O
of	O
the	O
Innocent	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
I	O
been	O
persuaded	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Davison	O
have	O
often	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Davison	O
,	O
and	O
White	O
,	O
have	O
often	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Sennett	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
never	O
but	O
once	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
Ale	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Two-penn	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
White	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Bowl	O
of	O
Punch	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
.	O
Another	O
Time	O
,	O
White	O
and	O
Davison	O
,	O
and	O
Sennett	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
Lawrence	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
then	O
)	O
and	O
White	O
complained	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
affronted	O
in	O
the	O
Barracks	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Corporal	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
live	O
such	O
a	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
Irish	O
Villain	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
any	O
where	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
rather	O
serve	O
the	O
Turk	O
than	O
K.	O
G	O
-	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
preparing	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
?	O
Sennett	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
being	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Patrick	O
Riley	O
and	O
he	O
drank	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Porter	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
haste	O
to	O
be	O
gone	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
thing	O
more	O
about	O
Birk	O
.	O
-	O
About	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
knew	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
foreign	O
Countries	O
you	O
would	O
go	O
too	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
pretend	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Protestant	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
turn	O
Roman	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
Purse	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Patrick	O
M'Cauly	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
55	O
l.	O
by	O
this	O
Means	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
Rome	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Gibbon	I-pers
.	O
About	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Sennett	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
disputing	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
flung	O
up	O
his	O
Pay	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
Men	O
for	O
the	O
K.	O
of	O
Prussia	O
.	O
Glynn	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
Day	O
at	O
Sennett	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
falling	O
out	O
,	O
Sennett	O
cry	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
provide	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
are	O
got	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
provide	O
a	O
better	O
Master	O
for	O
you	O
than	O
ever	O
you	O
had	O
in	O
your	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
me	O
like	O
a	O
Cow	O
or	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
avoided	O
the	O
Fellow	O
's	O
Company	O
.	O
Patrick	O
M'Cauly	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
French	O
Service	O
myself	O
,	O
Sennett	O
was	O
a	O
Trooper	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Birk	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
but	O
-	O
I	O
'm	O
upon	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
speak	O
Truth	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'enight	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Man	O
Sennett	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Lawrence	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
reveng	O
'd	O
on	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
vile	O
thing	O
in	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
such	O
Exceptions	O
,	O
and	O
swear	O
so	O
.	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
not	O
wish	O
for	O
a	O
Million	O
of	O
Money	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Action	O
,	O
for	O
bringing	O
this	O
upon	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
Sennett	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
known	O
him	O
long	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
Thing	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Luttuych	I-pers
.	O
If	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
dye	O
this	O
Moment	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
my	O
Opinion	O
,	O
this	O
Contrivance	O
is	O
owing	O
to	O
Sennett	O
's	O
Jealousy	O
.	O
Sometime	O
ago	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
demanded	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
Lawrence	O
's	O
having	O
us	O
'd	O
him	O
ill	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
Bitch	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
Sennett	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
Affair	O
proceeds	O
from	O
pure	O
Jealousy	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
But	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
Birk	O
,	O
(	O
Davison	O
)	O
and	O
White	O
,	O
who	O
have	O
no	O
Wives	O
to	O
be	O
jealous	O
of	O
,	O
would	O
work	O
themselves	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
perjure	O
themselves	O
,	O
because	O
Sennett	O
is	O
jealous	O
?	O
Luttwyel	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
that	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
.	O
Birk	O
must	O
degenerate	O
very	O
much	O
from	O
that	O
noble	O
Family	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
is	O
related	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
so	O
Col.	O
Williamson	O
.	O
That	O
very	O
Man	O
,	O
under	O
his	O
own	O
Hand	O
,	O
recommended	O
Birk	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
-	O
to	O
Mary	O
Sennett	O
.	O
Look	O
upon	O
that	O
Coat	O
and	O
Wastcoat	O
.	O
Sennett	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
myself	O
of	O
M'Cauly	O
The	O
other	O
Coat	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
Sennett	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
White	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
bid	O
White	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
your	O
Husband	O
had	O
Money	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
Account	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Sennett	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
2	O
Half-Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Money	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Husband	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
for	O
.	O
-	O
'T	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Debt	O
of	O
5	O
Guineas	O
which	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
;	O
my	O
Husband	O
dusted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
Men	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
3	O
went	O
away	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
-	O
Come	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
too	O
late	O
?	O
Sennett	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
only	O
-	O
Come	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hanning	I-pers
.	O
Never	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
Affairs	O
of	O
this	O
Kind	O
before	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Carr	O
.	O
Gave	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Behaviour	O
of	O
Davison	O
and	O
White	O
as	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
Men	O
.	O
Snafe	O
,	O
alias	O
Sennett	O
.	O
What	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
have	O
sworn	O
,	O
with	O
Relation	O
to	O
my	O
saying	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Innocent	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
my	O
being	O
sorry	O
for	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
is	O
all	O
false	O
upon	O
my	O
Oath	O
.	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
even	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Comerade	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
because	O
he	O
often	O
abus	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
not	O
getting	O
him	O
Men	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
Word	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
about	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
He	O
himself	O
left	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
Davison	O
and	O
White	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
them	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
forswear	O
my	O
self	O
for	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
37.	O
John	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Side	O
of	O
Pork	O
,	O
weighing	O
66	O
lb	O
.	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
and	I-pers
John	I-pers
Carlow	I-pers
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
38	O
,	O
39.	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Raby	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Hannah	B-pers
Gamball	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catherine	I-place
Coleman	I-place
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
scarlet	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
Oct.	O
17	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
40	O
,	O
41.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Woodrrow	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s	O
and	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
Pumps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
And	O
William	B-pers
Macclean	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Woodrow	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
Macclean	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Woodrrow	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Macclean	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
42.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
silk	O
Night	O
Gowns	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
linnen	O
Gown	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
silver	O
Tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
Thimble	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Mahogony	O
Tea-chest	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ketcherman	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43	O
James	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Darley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
Wastecoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Crossly	I-pers
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
44.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
Yards	O
of	O
printed	O
Cotton	O
,	O
value	O
34	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gibbon	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4s	O
.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45.	O
James	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
red	O
Frieze	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
46.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Mackenny	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
half-hundred	O
Weight	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
47.	O
Aspasia	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
Stock	O
Buckle	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turnham	I-pers
.	O
Mar	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
Turnham	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Woman	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
at	O
Fleet-Ditch	O
;	O
she	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
her	O
Company	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
laid	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
caught	O
her	O
attempting	O
to	O
steal	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
challeng	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
slipp	O
'd	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
for	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
Then	O
she	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
pull	O
my	O
Breeches	O
off	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
Stock	O
Buckle	O
,	O
laying	O
all	O
my	O
Things	O
on	O
a	O
Stool	O
by	O
the	O
Bed-side	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lain	O
down	O
again	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
but	O
Madam	O
was	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
needs	O
go	O
get	O
some	O
small	O
Beer	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
little	O
confounded	O
too	O
-	O
She	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
small	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Madam	O
for	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Hours	O
:	O
My	O
Watch	O
and	O
Stock	O
Buckle	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Neighbours	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	B-place
.	O
This	O
Man	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Rents	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
2	O
s.	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
all	O
Night	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
Couzen	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
to	O
be	O
sav	O
'd	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
48.	O
Jane	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Rowley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
Rehearsal	O
at	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
Crowd	O
,	O
by	O
going	O
through	O
Cannon	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Pater-noster-Row	I-place
.	O
In	O
the	O
Alley	O
I	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
2	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
push	O
'd	O
me	O
close	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
my	O
Hoop	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
This	O
Gentleman	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Addy	O
)	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
Madam	O
,	O
your	O
Pocket	O
is	O
pick	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
brought	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Half-Crown	O
and	O
a	O
Six-pence	O
left	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Addy	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
step	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
accordingly	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
search	O
'd	O
;	O
for	O
my	O
Lord	O
imagin	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
Receivers	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
-	O
What	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
picking	O
Pockets	O
here	O
!	O
Mr.	O
Addy	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Window	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Crowd	O
at	O
the	O
Rehearsal	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
her	O
2	O
Fellows	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
pick	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Pockets	O
that	O
Morning	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
Lady	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
under	O
my	O
very	O
Window	O
.	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
2	O
Men	O
to	O
shove	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
clap	O
something	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
positive	O
she	O
took	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
Prosecute	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
Half	O
,	O
or	O
2	O
Hours	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Alley	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Pockets	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Then	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
call	O
out	O
before	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Addy	O
.	O
Because	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
hurrying	O
and	O
picking	O
Pockets	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
under	O
my	O
Window	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Rowley	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Fellows	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
emptied	O
my	O
Pockets	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
close	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Addy	O
call	O
out	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Rowley	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Shop	O
when	O
that	O
Man	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
accused	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
