TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
OF	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
13th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Region	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Micajah	O
Perry	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Peter-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
MDCCXXXIX	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
MICAJAH	B-pers
PERRY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
THOMSON	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Gibbon	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bolton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Biddle	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Brathwaite	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	B-pers
Higgonson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Buckstone	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Cooling	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichol	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bristol	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
429.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
French	O
Books	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Salkeld	I-pers
,	O
July	O
11	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
430.	O
William	B-pers
Cardel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Phillis	B-pers
Grindall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
publick	O
Street	O
and	O
common	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Butolph	O
,	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
four	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
three	O
Callico	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
five	O
linen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Chaplin	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Grindall	O
,	O
Aug.	O
15	O
.	O
Phillis	O
Grindall	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
with	O
this	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dogged	O
me	O
;	O
sometimes	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
sometimes	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
Heels	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
10	O
Doors	O
past	O
the	O
Corner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
he	O
snatched	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Bundle	O
;	O
I	O
screamed	O
out	O
-	O
Murder	O
!	O
-	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
ruined	O
!	O
I	O
held	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pulled	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Struggle	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
violence	O
of	O
the	O
Fall	O
stopped	O
my	O
Breath	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
my	O
Elbow	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
use	O
my	O
Arm	O
for	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
got	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
still	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Merchant	O
Taylors	O
Alms-Houses	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
some	O
People	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
(	O
they	O
said	O
)	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
four	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
three	O
Callico	O
Shirts	O
,	O
five	O
Linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Petticoat	O
in	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	O
Chaplin	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
from	O
me	O
just	O
by	O
a	O
Lamp	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
imagining	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
ill	O
design	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
my	O
Bundle	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Nott	I-pers
,	O
junior	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
Nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
heard	O
this	O
young	O
Woman	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
!	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
tugging	O
the	O
Bundle	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
be	O
quarrelling	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Heels	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
about	O
thirty	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
flung	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
struck	O
me	O
upon	O
my	O
Thigh	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
left	O
Left	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
my	O
Right	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Bundle	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
dropped	O
.	O
Grindall	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Bundle	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
just	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
Things	O
which	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
Mr.	O
Nott	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
stir	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
.	O
Nott	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
Right	O
Hand	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
seized	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
Resistance	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
an	O
Oaken	O
Stick	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Nott	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
resist	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
Grindall	O
whether	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
persuaded	O
to	O
prosecute	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Nott	O
;	O
and	O
whether	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
is	O
not	O
carry	O
'd	O
on	O
it	O
his	O
Expence	O
?	O
Grindall	O
.	O
No	O
body	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
prosecute	O
;	O
But	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
obliged	O
to	O
prosecute	O
:	O
We	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bound	O
us	O
all	O
over	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nott	O
,	O
senior	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
that	O
Night	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
talking	O
with	O
my	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
Hearing	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Murder	O
!	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
I	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
Way	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
right	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
dropped	O
the	O
Bundle	O
and	O
was	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
dragg	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Son	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Linnen	O
was	O
my	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Mary	O
Chaplin	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
Aldermanbury	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
Grindall	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
their	O
being	O
wash	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
carrying	O
them	O
home	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
:	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Lad	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
He	O
makes	O
Backs	O
for	O
Distillers	O
and	O
Brewers	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Time	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Years	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
has	O
any	O
Business	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
work	O
;	O
but	O
since	O
the	O
Commencement	O
of	O
the	O
Gin	B-pers
Act	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Trade	O
has	O
been	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
Distillers	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
vastly	O
fuddled	O
,	O
between	O
Five	O
and	O
Six	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Another	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rosemary	O
Branch	O
,	O
pretty	O
near	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
quarreling	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
beating	O
him	O
.	O
Several	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
;	O
who	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
declared	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
Business	O
he	O
had	O
followed	O
this	O
last	O
half	O
Year	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
imagined	O
his	O
Father	O
maintained	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
Constable	O
likewise	O
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
Mr.	O
Nott	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Another	O
Constable	O
mentioned	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
Fray	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
wrong	O
'd	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
run	O
against	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
not	O
a	O
Man	O
on	O
Earth	O
,	O
can	O
lay	O
any	O
Dishonesty	O
to	O
my	O
Charge	O
,	O
before	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Clemency	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
431.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
lbs	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Colin	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
and	O
David	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
July	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
432.	O
John	B-pers
Albin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ann	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
them	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Ann	O
his	O
Wife	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
Ring	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
an	O
Halfpenny	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Hannah	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
May	O
21	O
.	O
Ann	O
Price	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Prior	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Kilburn	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
between	O
Three	O
and	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
us	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Fields	O
from	O
Mary-bone	B-place
:	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
one	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Minute	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Dread	O
upon	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
rob	O
us	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
with	O
a	O
sauntering	O
Pace	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Prior	O
,	O
-	O
we	O
shall	O
certainly	O
be	O
robb	O
'd	O
!	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
not	O
,	O
-	O
pray	O
take	O
Courage	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
Tom	O
Prior	O
,	O
Tom	O
Prior	O
(	O
which	O
is	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Prior	O
's	O
Husband	O
's	O
Name	O
)	O
-	O
you	O
sha'n't	O
go	O
abroad	O
with	O
us	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
must	O
stay	O
behind	O
to	O
look	O
Birds-nests	O
.	O
Mr	O
Prior	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
imagine	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
this	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
Yards	O
beyond	O
us	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
overtook	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
Aye	O
,	O
God	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
something	O
besides	O
Birds-nests	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
left	O
Side-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Pistol	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
uncommon	O
Size	O
,	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
left	O
Breast	O
,	O
crying	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
and	O
Rings	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
but	O
my	O
Wedding	O
ring	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
my	O
Wedding-ring	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
still	O
kept	O
his	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
stamping	O
with	O
his	O
Foot	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
d-mn	O
you	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
about	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
,	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cork-screw	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
at	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
stamp	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Prior	O
,	O
-	O
And	O
D-mn	O
you	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
your	O
Money	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
demanding	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Prior	O
's	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
Now	O
,	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
'll	O
meet	O
two	O
more	O
presently	O
;	O
this	O
struck	O
such	O
a	O
Terror	O
into	O
us	O
,	O
than	O
we	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Path	O
way	O
,	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
over	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Ditches	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Farm-house	O
,	O
kept	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Francis	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
ready	O
to	O
die	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
immediately	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
Wig	O
on	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
;	O
his	O
Hat	O
was	O
flapp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Bough	O
which	O
he	O
play	O
'd	O
about	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
abus	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
several	O
Bitches	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
of	O
Pancras	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
brought	O
me	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
,	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
breaking	O
open	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Books	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Hay-loft	O
,	O
at	O
Tottenham-Court	O
,	O
pretty	O
near	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
hid	O
behind	O
the	O
Hay	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
then	O
,	O
nor	O
have	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
Discourse	O
with	O
him	O
concerning	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
no	O
Confession	O
of	O
any	O
Kind	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
under	O
a	O
great	O
Surprize	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
but	O
little	O
Resistance	O
.	O
This	O
Witness	O
inform	O
'd	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
Hannah	O
Prior	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
an	O
Apoplectick	O
Fit	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
this	O
Trial	O
came	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
but	O
just	O
alive	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
and	O
't	O
is	O
hard	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
Life	O
for	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
as	O
God	O
's	O
my	O
Saviour	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
my	O
Judge	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
433.	O
John	B-pers
Albin	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
with	O
Fortunatus	B-pers
Albin	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
printed	O
Book	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Craftsman	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Critique	O
on	O
the	O
Times	O
.	O
Vol	O
.	O
II	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
Book	O
called	O
the	O
Craftsman	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Vol	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
Book	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Craftsman	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Vol	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Books	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Aug.	O
2	O
.	O
John	O
Albin	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Fortunatus	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
434.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silk	O
Skirts	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
and	O
other	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
435.	O
Edward	B-pers
Goynes	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Joynes	I-pers
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
GOD	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Mary	B-pers
his	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
her	O
upon	O
the	O
Throat	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
maliciously	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
squeeze	O
and	O
press	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
squeezing	O
and	O
pressing	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
15th	O
to	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
she	O
languished	O
,	O
and	O
languishing	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
charged	O
,	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
his	O
said	O
Wife	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Cadmore	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lived	O
at	O
Poplar	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
his	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Chimney	O
Corner	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Ground-Room	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
sold	O
Greens	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
holding	O
one	O
Arm	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
O	O
that	O
wicked	O
Villain	O
!	O
that	O
wicked	O
Villain	O
has	O
wrung	O
my	O
Arm	O
to	O
Pieces	O
!	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
Did	O
I	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
old	O
Toad	O
?	O
I	O
only	O
flung	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
at	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
indeed	O
a	O
Slop	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
Doors	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
Time	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
Outcry	O
again	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Face	O
all	O
over	O
gore	O
Blood	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
drove	O
her	O
in	O
that	O
Condition	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
O	O
that	O
Villain	O
,	O
-	O
now	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
my	O
Business	O
!	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
no	O
more	O
from	O
the	O
15th	O
to	O
Friday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
call	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Arm	O
under	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
to	O
raise	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
Gammer	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Word	O
)	O
have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
alledge	O
against	O
me	O
?	O
She	O
shook	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
spoke	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
urg	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Convulsion	O
Fit	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
laid	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
herself	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
lay	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
?	O
Upon	O
this	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
forgave	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
World	O
would	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
Word	O
he	O
wanted	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cadmore	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
she	O
fall	O
down	O
and	O
hurt	O
herself	O
?	O
And	O
when	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
lay	O
to	O
my	O
Charge	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
she	O
say	O
,	O
-	O
No	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Cadmore	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
Weeks	O
or	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
)	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
broke	O
her	O
Arm	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
Time	O
exactly	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Spalding	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
my	O
Mother	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
marry	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
or	O
14	O
Months	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
her	O
very	O
barbarously	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
strike	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
heave	O
Stones	O
,	O
Brick-bats	O
,	O
Pans	O
,	O
Pipkins	O
,	O
and	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bruise	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
gross	O
Manner	O
.	O
Once	O
he	O
hit	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
-	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
of	O
her	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
frequently	O
had	O
black	O
Bruises	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
up	O
on	O
these	O
Occasions	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
Bread	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
her	O
Business	O
.	O
About	O
Ten	O
or	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Morning	O
,	O
my	O
Mother	O
was	O
a-dry	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
her	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Ale-house	O
right	O
against	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Beer	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
flew	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
heave	O
the	O
Pot	O
and	O
the	O
Beer	O
at	O
her	O
:	O
She	O
had	O
the	O
Beer	O
in	O
her	O
Right	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
beat	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Left	O
Arm	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
twisted	O
it	O
;	O
with	O
his	O
other	O
Hand	O
he	O
grasped	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
Her	O
Arm	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
much	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
Misery	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
Throat	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
That	O
Rogue	O
had	O
broke	O
her	O
Arm	O
again	O
,	O
-	O
all	O
to	O
Pieces	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
Hours	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
buffeted	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
with	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
till	O
her	O
Eyes	O
ran	O
down	O
with	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
old	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
and	O
shew	O
her	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
again	O
Tomorrow	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
O	O
fie	O
upon	O
you	O
Mary	O
!	O
Spalding	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
cut	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Head	O
before	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
was	O
ago	O
)	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
ill	O
Usage	O
was	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
she	O
took	O
to	O
her	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
came	O
down	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
down	O
;	O
she	O
died	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
Mary	O
,	O
she	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
.	O
Spalding	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
We	O
spoke	O
to	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
about	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
that	O
she	O
died	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
Looks	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
any	O
Marks	O
upon	O
her	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Them	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
complain	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
her	O
Throat	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
hold	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
yet	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
she	O
died	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swallow	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
She	O
complain	O
'd	O
likewise	O
of	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
for	O
something	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
Month	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Kick	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Violence	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
slipped	O
down	O
three	O
Stairs	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
Back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	O
,	O
did	O
I	O
kick	O
her	O
down	O
Stairs	O
?	O
Spalding	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
beat	O
the	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
-	O
there	O
she	O
stands	O
,	O
and	O
knows	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
buffeted	O
her	O
with	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
Eyes	O
bleed	O
;	O
-	O
she	O
always	O
had	O
sore	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Spalding	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
buffeted	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Edge	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Blood	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Inside	O
;	O
for	O
her	O
Eyes	O
were	O
afterwards	O
wash	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Corners	O
were	O
sore	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
washed	O
away	O
the	O
Blood	O
,	O
it	O
ouzed	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Minute	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
-	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
fast	O
.	O
Catherina	B-pers
Lutolph	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
I	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
;	O
I	O
rather	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Bed	O
,	O
sick	O
,	O
than	O
(	O
have	O
)	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
Sight	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
very	O
great	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
nobody	O
but	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
tell	O
her	O
Secrets	O
to	O
;	O
so	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
this	O
Damage	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
dangerous	O
Condition	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
;	O
her	O
Neck	O
was	O
very	O
sore	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
complained	O
very	O
much	O
of	O
her	O
Back	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
catched	O
Cold	O
,	O
-	O
no	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
said	O
)	O
my	O
Husband	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
drunken	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
pinch	O
'd	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
my	O
Head	O
against	O
the	O
Brick-wall	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
Death	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
like	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
Shoring	O
(	O
picking	O
up	O
what	O
she	O
could	O
find	O
upon	O
the	O
Shores	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Tide	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
Firing	O
)	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
this	O
Hurt	O
was	O
done	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Shore	O
,	O
and	O
hurt	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
with	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
now	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
nothing	O
but	O
her	O
Back	O
and	O
her	O
Throat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mind	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Dutchwoman	O
.	O
Lutolph	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
shew	O
'd	O
all	O
Love	O
and	O
Kindness	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
Husband	O
should	O
speak	O
to	O
a	O
Wife	O
.	O
She	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
Work	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
much	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sit	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
away	O
:	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
what	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
O	O
fie	O
upon	O
you	O
!	O
Lutolph	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Day	O
she	O
died	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Gammer	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Fox	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Poor	O
want	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
you	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
bear	O
no	O
Malice	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
-	O
People	O
say	O
I	O
killed	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
hanged	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
now	O
tell	O
before	O
Mrs.	O
Fox	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Poor	O
if	O
I	O
killed	O
you	O
:	O
He	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
to	O
raise	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
in	O
a	O
Convulsion	O
Fit	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
herself	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
Forgiveness	O
;	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
(	O
said	O
she	O
)	O
ask	O
Forgiveness	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
will	O
forgive	O
you	O
if	O
the	O
World	O
will	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
O	O
mind	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
.	O
Lutolph	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
-	O
After	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
himself	O
round	O
on	O
his	O
Foot	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
a	O
T-rd	O
for	O
you	O
all	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
wanted	O
.	O
Before	O
she	O
died	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
and	O
another	O
to	O
lay	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
should	O
see	O
(	O
she	O
said	O
)	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
gone	O
through	O
;	O
She	O
died	O
that	O
Day	O
;	O
we	O
laid	O
her	O
out	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
observ	O
'd	O
that	O
her	O
Neck	O
was	O
swelled	O
;	O
but	O
next	O
Morning	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
black	O
a	O
Hand	O
's	O
Breadth	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
far	O
(	O
we	O
imagin	O
'd	O
)	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
grasp	O
'd	O
.	O
While	O
she	O
was	O
alive	O
,	O
her	O
Throat	O
was	O
so	O
swell	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swallow	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Tea-spoonful	O
,	O
nor	O
could	O
she	O
pin	O
her	O
Cap	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
ever	O
take	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Throat	O
?	O
Indeed	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
about	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
:	O
She	O
would	O
have	O
eaten	O
a	O
little	O
Milk	O
Porrage	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Throat	O
was	O
so	O
swell	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
Tea-spoonful	O
down	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pinch	O
'd	O
her	O
Throat	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Lutolph	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
several	O
black	O
and	O
blue	O
Marks	O
upon	O
her	O
Legs	O
and	O
her	O
Back	O
;	O
her	O
Throat	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
swell	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
black	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
I	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
Dame	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
Gaffer	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
bad	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
her	O
several	O
Times	O
to	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
World	O
would	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
disturbed	O
at	O
the	O
Sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
her	O
Death	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
terribly	O
bruised	O
all	O
over	O
her	O
Body	O
,	O
from	O
Head	O
to	O
Foot	O
,	O
her	O
Sides	O
and	O
her	O
Back	O
in	O
particular	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Tumor	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Side	O
of	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
,	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
pinching	O
or	O
strangling	O
.	O
The	O
Coats	O
of	O
the	O
Gullet	O
were	O
putrify	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
into	O
the	O
Stomach	O
there	O
was	O
extravasated	O
Blood	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
turn	O
'd	O
into	O
Pus	O
or	O
Matter	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
occasioned	O
the	O
Soreness	O
which	O
prevented	O
her	O
swallowing	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Opinion	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
between	O
her	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
were	O
some	O
black	O
Places	O
,	O
as	O
broad	O
as	O
the	O
Palm	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
imagin	O
'd	O
were	O
made	O
by	O
beating	O
or	O
kicking	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
left	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
under	O
her	O
Breast	O
were	O
great	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
Arm	O
fractur	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Disorder	O
in	O
her	O
Throat	O
might	O
occasion	O
her	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
ill	O
Usage	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
might	O
hasten	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
only	O
heav	O
'd	O
the	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
down	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
fetch	O
it	O
where	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
Daughter	O
;	O
please	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
Consideration	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
to	O
her	O
now	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
436.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lacock	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
Blankets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
Feather	O
Pillows	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Smoothing-iron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
let	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Hussey	O
,	O
Sept.3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
437.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harrard	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Isleworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
being	O
big	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Male	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Male	O
Child	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
secretly	O
,	O
bring	O
forth	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
Male	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Bastard	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
not	O
having	O
GOD	O
before	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
said	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
with	O
Force	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
Male	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
,	O
so	O
alive	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
both	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
certain	O
River	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Powder-Mills	O
River	O
,	O
did	O
cast	O
and	O
throw	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
which	O
casting	O
and	O
throwing	O
into	O
the	O
said	O
River	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
was	O
suffocated	O
and	O
drowned	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Suffocating	O
and	O
Drowning	O
it	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
July	O
10	O
.	O
She	O
shas	O
likewise	O
charged	O
,	O
by	O
vertue	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thackery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Beadle	O
of	O
Isleworth	B-place
:	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ions	O
,	O
a	O
Farmer	O
there	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
young	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Powder-mills	O
River	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
a	O
Meadow	O
,	O
covered	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
Grass	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
swelled	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
Water	O
in	O
its	O
Body	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
it	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Blow	O
;	O
the	O
Blood	O
was	O
congealed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Place	O
was	O
so	O
soft	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
thrust	O
my	O
Finger	O
into	O
the	O
Scull	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Stock-house	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
Overseers	O
of	O
the	O
Poor	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr	O
Wright	O
,	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
for	O
Letters	O
to	O
bury	O
it	O
.	O
While	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
gathered	O
Fruit	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Overseers	O
of	O
Teddington	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
Churchwardens	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
fit	O
Condition	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
Coroner	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
bring	O
it	O
near	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
(	O
said	O
she	O
)	O
't	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
Child	O
,	O
-	O
born	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Body	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
tell	O
That	O
,	O
unless	O
she	O
saw	O
it	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
would	O
she	O
suffer	O
me	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Coffin	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
first	O
brought	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
told	O
her	O
under	O
what	O
Circumstances	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
John	O
Gadd	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Drayton	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
last	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Field	O
of	O
Wheat	O
to	O
reap	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
last	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
met	O
him	O
again	O
had	O
she	O
not	O
been	O
taken	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nell	I-pers
,	O
Midwife	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
examine	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
a	O
Style	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Men	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Child	O
behind	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
Story	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
feasible	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
reply	O
'd	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
by	O
its	O
Head	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
bruised	O
and	O
swelled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blood	O
was	O
congeal	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
apprehend	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
born	O
dead	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Midwife	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
Truth	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
-	O
then	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Midwife	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
Truth	O
:	O
-	O
The	O
Child	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
Pain	O
by	O
the	O
River-side	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
it	O
rolled	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lap	O
into	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
she	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
lived	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
tore	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
her	O
Apron	O
to	O
wrap	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
or	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
she	O
threw	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
any	O
Preparation	O
for	O
its	O
being	O
born	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
Caps	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Cage	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
plainly	O
saw	O
its	O
Death	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
for	O
no	O
Water	O
appeared	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
fresh	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thackery	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Bell	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
poor	O
Creature	O
that	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
said	O
)	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
drown	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
John	B-pers
Gadd	I-pers
was	O
the	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
odd	O
Manner	O
,	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
miscarr'yd	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
once	O
before	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
poor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
delivered	O
of	O
this	O
Child	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
a	O
Style	O
:	O
That	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
it	O
cry	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
wrap	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
Bit	O
of	O
her	O
old	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
herself	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
John	O
Gadd	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
wicked	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
just	O
before	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
herself	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
done	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
not	O
impossible	O
that	O
Bruise	O
might	O
be	O
given	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Water	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Richmond	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
in	O
Travel	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
for	O
two	O
Hours	O
to	O
ease	O
my	O
Pains	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
of	O
Richmond	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Help	O
of	O
some	O
good	O
Women	O
.	O
He	O
threatened	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
cross	O
the	O
Water	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
shift	O
for	O
myself	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Twickenham	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
likewise	O
I	O
was	O
refused	O
Relief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Beadle	O
of	O
that	O
Place	O
,	O
led	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
bad	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
my	O
Baby	O
was	O
dead	O
or	O
alive	O
.	O
The	O
Midwife	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
say	O
something	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Beadle	O
of	O
Richmond	O
refusing	O
her	O
Help	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Day	O
the	O
Coroner	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
Person	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
John	O
Gadd	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
seen	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
under	O
my	O
Haycocks	O
.	O
She	O
likewise	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
,	O
John	O
Gadd	O
took	O
her	O
Apron	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
tore	O
a	O
Piece	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
wrapped	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
438.	O
John	B-pers
Maw	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chiswick	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
seven	O
Linnen	O
Shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
35	O
s.	O
two	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
ten	O
Linnen	O
Caps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
Cambrick	O
Aprons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
Cambrick	O
ditto	O
,	O
laced	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Sattin	O
Mantelet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
Fans	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
ditto	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Dimitty	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Flannel	O
ditto	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
Stock	O
Sleeves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
41	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Atwater	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Styles	I-pers
,	O
July	O
5	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Atwater	I-pers
.	O
All	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Reading	O
Waggon	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
.	O
We	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
sold	O
a	O
yellow	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
the	O
very	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Atwater	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
carry	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Waggon	O
;	O
his	O
Name	O
is	O
Richard	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
.	O
And	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
is	O
the	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Waggon	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Atwater	O
's	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Waggon	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
Turnham	B-place
Green	I-place
.	O
We	O
came	O
from	O
Reading	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Waggon	O
was	O
robbed	O
the	O
5th	O
about	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
Horseback	O
.	O
Three	O
Men	O
on	O
Foot	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
d-mn	O
you	O
,	O
stop	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
Fire-Arms	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Guard	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
-	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
an	O
old	O
Man	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
stood	O
Guard	O
over	O
me	O
while	O
the	O
others	O
robbed	O
the	O
Waggon	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
visited	O
me	O
one	O
Night	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
,	O
about	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
the	O
Waggon	O
then	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Man	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
.	O
The	O
Moon	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
shone	O
pretty	O
bright	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
discern	O
something	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
had	O
then	O
a	O
pretty	O
deal	O
of	O
Talk	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Size	O
,	O
his	O
Voice	O
,	O
and	O
Manner	O
of	O
Speaking	O
,	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
now	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
last	O
Time	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
discerned	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
remembered	O
his	O
Size	O
and	O
Voice	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
Hopes	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
let	O
me	O
gone	O
on	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
so	O
lately	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
mistaken	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
presenting	O
their	O
Pistols	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
stop	O
the	O
Waggon	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
them	O
stop	O
it	O
themselves	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
I	O
apprehend	O
)	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
got	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
could	O
find	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
near	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
out	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
,	O
a	O
Trunk	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Shirt	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pockets	O
,	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
put	O
on	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
my	O
telling	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
guarded	O
me	O
bid	O
him	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
took	O
their	O
Goods	O
upon	O
their	O
Backs	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
near	O
Turnham-Green	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
Russel	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
driving	O
the	O
Waggon	O
)	O
whether	O
any	O
Body	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Fire-arms	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
tall	O
,	O
brisk	O
,	O
active	O
Man	O
(	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Size	O
and	O
Voice	O
)	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
two	O
Companions	O
,	O
-	O
d-mn	O
you	O
,	O
get	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Waggon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
they	O
threw	O
out	O
a	O
large	O
Scale-beam	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Horse	O
's	O
Harness	O
;	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Portmanteau	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
wedged	O
in	O
between	O
some	O
Barrels	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Tail	O
of	O
the	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
they	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
my	O
Coat	O
which	O
lay	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Shirt	O
in	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Russel	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
lame	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
(	O
whom	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
five	O
Minutes	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
long	O
in	O
doing	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
Nine	O
and	O
Twelve	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
Mantelet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Hood	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
This	O
Gown	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother-in-Law	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
these	O
three	O
Things	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
25s	O
.	O
These	O
Goods	O
in	O
this	O
Bundle	O
(	O
producing	O
another	O
Parcel	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
likewise	O
from	O
his	O
Mother-in-Law	O
;	O
her	O
Name	O
is	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
Discourse	O
with	O
him	O
concerning	O
the	O
Things	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
(	O
in	O
his	O
Presence	O
)	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Things	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
since	O
died	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Grubb	I-pers
,	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
an	O
Apron	O
and	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother-in-Law	O
,	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
Money	O
on	O
them	O
:	O
Soon	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Notice	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
given	O
her	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
were	O
produced	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Atwater	O
.	O
This	O
Cap	O
and	O
Apron	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
particular	O
Apron	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
Hands	O
.	O
Grubb	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
Friend	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Hickman	O
Young	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
's	O
when	O
he	O
granted	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
us	O
what	O
our	O
Business	O
was	O
?	O
We	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
hand-cuffed	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
his	O
Mother	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Cap	O
produced	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
had	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Turner	O
Turner	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Cap	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
selling	O
off	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
any	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
very	O
reasonable	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Cap	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
brought	O
her	O
Mother	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
my	O
Room	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
Mother	O
7s	O
.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
deliver	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hands	O
at	O
the	O
Foot	O
of	O
my	O
Bed	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Atwater	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Cap	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
)	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sleeves	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Grubb	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
afterwards	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
Sleeves	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Atwater	O
own	O
'd	O
;	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sick	O
when	O
this	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Pray	O
did	O
I	O
say	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
Mother	O
those	O
Things	O
?	O
Becket	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
These	O
Things	O
(	O
the	O
Sleeves	O
)	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Mother	O
's	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
had	O
the	O
Mother	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
herself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
her	O
Son	O
made	O
her	O
a	O
Present	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nicholene	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
House	O
in	O
King	O
street	O
,	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
seven	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
catch	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
him	O
He	O
lay	O
abroad	O
two	O
Nights	O
in	O
the	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
sick	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Wound	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
caus	O
'd	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Nurse	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
.	O
I	O
once	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
his	O
Face	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
quarrelling	O
and	O
fighting	O
.	O
-	O
Bold	O
.	O
I	O
nursed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Illness	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
seven	O
Weeks	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
four	O
Nights	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
with	O
him	O
every	O
Night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
These	O
Things	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Nicholene	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
.	O
Bold	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Mother	O
bring	O
some	O
Things	O
into	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
439.	O
Jane	B-pers
Gainsley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Copper	O
Lid	O
of	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
July	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
440.	O
John	B-pers
George	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Clasp	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dubois	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
Plate	O
of	O
Gold	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Deveer	I-pers
,	O
July	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
441.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Lomas	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
442.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Munns	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Cochineal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
Aug.	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
443.	O
Ann	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
flower	O
'd	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Twig-Basket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ezekiel	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
444.	O
Robert	B-pers
Butteriffe	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
Table-cloths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
Quart	O
Bottles	O
filled	O
with	O
Shrub	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Sept.3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
445.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Colebourn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Brass	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
Two	O
Pound	O
Brass	O
Weight	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spateman	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
446.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bitby	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
lac	O
'd	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
July	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
447.	O
William	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
wooden	O
Cask	O
filled	O
with	O
Small	O
Beer	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
448	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
John	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
in-disposed	O
Person	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
1734	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Dionis	O
Backchurch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
offensive	O
Weapon	O
called	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Iron	O
and	O
Steal	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Miles	B-pers
Rigg	I-pers
,	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Rigg	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
*	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
In	O
April	O
1737	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
setting	O
Fire	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rawlinson	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquitted	O
on	O
the	O
Representation	O
of	O
his	O
Friends	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
disorder	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions-Book	O
for	O
that	O
Year	O
,	O
No	O
IV	O
.	O
p.	O
94	O
.	O
In	O
July	O
Sessions	O
1738	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
,	O
and	O
convicted	O
,	O
for	O
writing	O
an	O
Incendiary	O
Letter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dolly	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
afterwards	O
pardoned	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
;	O
his	O
Friends	O
having	O
given	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rigg	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fenchurch-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
West	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Lime	O
street	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Crape	O
over	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
a	O
Cobler	O
's	O
Knife	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
deliver	O
my	O
Money	O
:	O
I	O
stood	O
a	O
little	O
surprised	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
again	O
,	O
-	O
Deliver	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Blow	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
reel	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
Lime-street	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
(	O
about	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
)	O
with	O
the	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Crape	O
upon	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Watchman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
West	O
confirmed	O
the	O
former	O
Evidence	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
charge	O
given	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mr.	O
Rigg	O
This	O
Knife	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Crape	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Handkerchiefs	O
of	O
different	O
Sorts	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
449.	O
Mary	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Linnen	O
Shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
six	O
Linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
Dimmitty	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2s	O
.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rustat	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
April	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
450.	O
John	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Illidge	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
451.	O
Richard	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Pair	O
of	O
Glass	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
452.	O
Priscilia	B-pers
Trillcourt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Selwin	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
19	O
.	O
Selwin	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
Seal	O
,	O
worth	O
3	O
l.	O
with	O
a	O
King	O
's	O
Road	O
Ticket	O
(	O
which	O
hung	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
)	O
o	O
he	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Fob	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
in	O
Oxendon-street	B-place
,	O
about	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
House	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
there	O
about	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
't	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
indeed	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
my	O
Watch	O
till	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
How	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
this	O
private	O
House	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
o'Night	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Watch	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
:	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
her	O
along	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Road	O
Ticket	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
she	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Pray	O
did	O
not	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
-	O
sit	O
upon	O
your	O
Knee	O
?	O
Selwin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
both	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Amount	O
of	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
l.	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
that	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
House	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
was	O
jealous	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
took	O
more	O
Notice	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
than	O
he	O
did	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
upon	O
his	O
Knee	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
Years	O
.	O
Her	O
Character	O
!	O
-	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
talk	O
about	O
that	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Man	O
did	O
come	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
serv	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
Liquor	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
five	O
Half-pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
last	O
Half-pint	O
was	O
serv	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
my	O
Maid	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Watch	O
in	O
Pawn	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
?	O
Money	O
was	O
short	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
that	O
serv	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
Liquor	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
-	O
who	O
sat	O
upon	O
his	O
Knee	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
five	O
Half-pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
gave	O
me	O
-	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
Money	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
Mistress	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
Guinea	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
My	O
Mistress	O
would	O
not	O
lend	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
with	O
him	O
-	O
not	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Indeed	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
Night	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
-	O
looking	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
Oxendon-street	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
really	O
;	O
come	O
,	O
come	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
is	O
signifies	O
nothing	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
You	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
a	O
Robbery	O
against	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lost	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
People	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
he	O
treated	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beet	O
,	O
asked	O
my	O
Pardon	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Man	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Butchers	O
Arms	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Lombard-Court	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
a	O
Constable	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
told	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
discharge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
her	O
:	O
The	O
Constable	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
without	O
carrying	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
no	O
Justice	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Constable	O
would	O
have	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Landlord	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
of	O
-	O
such	O
Honour	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Constable	O
took	O
her	O
Word	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
accordingly	O
came	O
.	O
Ellen	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Mantua-maker	O
;	O
she	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Mistress	O
two	O
Years	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
hard-working	O
Woman	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
She	O
worked	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
s	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Years	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
Wife	O
these	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
true	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
Ellen	B-pers
Dillon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
four	O
Year	O
Her	O
Husband	O
and	O
Mine	O
are	O
now	O
at	O
Sea	O
together	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
453.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boddice	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Stomacher	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirkalder	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
454.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7s	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Aug.6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
455	O
,	O
456.	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
smoothing	O
Irons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lavars	I-pers
,	O
in	O
their	O
Lodging	O
,	O
April	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
Mary	O
[	O
being	O
his	O
Wife	O
]	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
457.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fowke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
her	O
late	O
Majesty	O
Queen	O
Anne	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Alhallows	O
in	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
married	O
Sarah	B-pers
Parsley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
her	O
had	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
:	O
And	O
afterwards	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Wardrobe	I-place
,	O
feloniously	O
married	O
Ann	B-pers
Fowke	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
;	O
Sarah	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
full	O
Life	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
having	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Charge	O
and	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Offence	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Clerk	O
of	O
Alhallows	O
London	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Register	O
Book	O
of	O
that	O
Parish	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
See	O
if	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
Entry	O
of	O
Fowke	O
's	O
Marriage	O
in	O
1712	O
.	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Clerk	O
reads	O
.	O
''	O
Marriages	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Title	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
)	O
Thomas	O
``	O
Fowke	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Parsley	I-pers
,	O
Aug	O
the	O
31st	O
,	O
1712	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
Clerk	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
Years	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
Person	O
living	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Minister	O
in	O
1712	O
.	O
Fisher	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
Minister	O
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
Sexton	O
,	O
are	O
all	O
dead	O
:	O
But	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Book	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Entries	O
were	O
then	O
made	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
the	O
Register	O
Book	O
of	O
our	O
Parish	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
my	O
Predecessor	O
:	O
His	O
Name	O
was	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wallington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Clerk	O
twenty-seven	O
Years	O
.	O
The	O
Minister	O
keeps	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Possession	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fetched	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
Yesterday	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
He	O
's	O
my	O
Son	O
in-Law	O
,	O
by	O
marrying	O
my	O
Daughter-in-Law	O
;	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
Sarah	B-pers
Parsley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
twenty-seven	O
Years	O
the	O
1st	O
Day	O
of	O
last	O
August	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Wedding	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
Home	O
to	O
dress	O
the	O
Wedding	O
Dinner	O
:	O
But	O
a	O
Kinswoman	O
of	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Wedding	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
John	B-pers
North	I-pers
gave	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Night	O
I	O
bedded	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
it	O
all	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Why	O
they	O
lived	O
together	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
House	O
for	O
themselves	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
two	O
Children	O
by	O
her	O
:	O
They	O
are	O
both	O
now	O
alive	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
eldest	O
is	O
in	O
her	O
26th	O
Year	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
Daughter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Son	O
is	O
,	O
-	O
(	O
stay	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
a	O
Lye	O
)	O
the	O
Son	O
is	O
in	O
his	O
25th	O
Year	O
.	O
They	O
lived	O
together	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
Parish	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Is	O
Sarah	B-pers
Parsley	I-pers
living	O
or	O
dead	O
.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
She	O
died	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
after	O
he	O
marry	O
'd	O
this	O
second	O
Wife	O
.	O
The	O
Books	O
are	O
here	O
to	O
shew	O
it	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
die	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
dead	O
about	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
Year	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
a	O
Lie	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
House	O
for	O
themselves	O
,	O
how	O
long	O
did	O
they	O
live	O
together	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
Years	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
acknowledged	O
her	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
remember	O
their	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
twenty-seven	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
very	O
well	O
remember	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
Father	O
five	O
Years	O
before	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Church	O
,	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Richardson	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
they	O
lived	O
together	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Years	O
afterward	O
.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
they	O
lived	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Tom	O
.	O
Fowke	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Parish	O
where	O
he	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
Relief	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
two	O
Children	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
died	O
with	O
Grief	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
Time	O
you	O
saw	O
her	O
alive	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
two	O
Years	O
before	O
she	O
died	O
,	O
less	O
than	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
her	O
within	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
now	O
about	O
5	O
Years	O
since	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
-	O
within	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
old	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
particular	O
Days	O
.	O
He	O
cohabited	O
with	O
her	O
sometime	O
after	O
the	O
Marriage	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
lived	O
together	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Years	O
I	O
dressed	O
the	O
Wedding	O
Dinner	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Wedding	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
not	O
young	O
Folks	O
,	O
nor	O
so	O
flashy	O
as	O
to	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Weddings	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Years	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
And	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Strole	O
,	O
and	O
lov	O
'd	O
to	O
gad	O
about	O
,	O
as	O
Men	O
do	O
too	O
much	O
that	O
have	O
the	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
put	O
herself	O
and	O
Children	O
on	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
lived	O
where	O
he	O
pleased	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
Men	O
like	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Parsley	I-pers
,	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
marry	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
marry	O
'd	O
,	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
alive	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1736	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Raddish	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
Hackney	O
Town	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
lived	O
there	O
about	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
was	O
alive	O
then	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Ale	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
died	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Wedding	O
?	O
Crane	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
remember	O
their	O
living	O
together	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
marry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
worked	O
together	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
John	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
is	O
my	O
First-Cousen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
Sarah	O
Parsley	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
vast	O
Distance	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
her	O
Application	O
to	O
this	O
Raddish	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Clerk	O
to	O
a	O
Brewer	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
1736	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
at	O
Joiners	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
15c.wt	O
.	O
and	O
one	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Lead	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
hasten	O
the	O
Carman	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
appears	O
by	O
my	O
Books	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Clerk	O
of	O
Butalph	O
Bishopsgate	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Register-book	O
of	O
that	O
Parish	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
See	O
for	O
the	O
Burials	O
in	O
September	O
1736	O
.	O
Stanley	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
Entry	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fowke	I-pers
's	O
Burial	O
.	O
Clerk	O
reads	O
.	O
''	O
Burials	O
;	O
September	O
1736	O
,	O
Sarah	O
``	O
Fowke	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
Aged	O
47	O
.	O
'	O
Ann	B-pers
Fowke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
my	O
Sorrow	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
1735	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
married	O
at	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Wardrobe	I-place
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
the	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
Years	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
for	O
any	O
Harm	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Widdow	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Name	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
related	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
longer	O
than	O
three	O
Years	O
?	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Years	O
before	O
Marriage	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Fowke	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
justly	O
say	O
:	O
He	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
belive	O
not	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Years	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
Marriage	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Fowke	O
.	O
Not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
any	O
Dishonesty	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
my	O
Housekeeper	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
three	O
Years	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Fowke	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
keep	O
a	O
Table	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Register-Clerk	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
Wardrobe	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Register-Book	O
of	O
Marriages	O
.	O
Clerk	O
reads	O
.	O
''	O
Married	O
in	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Ward-robe	O
``	O
and	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Black	O
Fryars	O
,	O
Anno	O
Domini	O
``	O
1735	O
,	O
October	O
10th	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Fowke	O
,	O
``	O
Widower	O
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
Westminster	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
Ann	O
Fowke	O
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
``	O
Place	O
:	O
By	O
William	B-pers
Grainger	I-pers
.	O
''	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
this	O
Marriage	O
,	O
but	O
't	O
is	O
impossible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
remember	O
Faces	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
seen	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
called	O
upon	O
other	O
Trials	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
were	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
against	O
Thomas	O
Fowke	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Point	O
of	O
Law	O
,	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
long	O
Separation	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
.	O
That	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
presumed	O
,	O
after	O
so	O
long	O
an	O
Absence	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
know	O
she	O
was	O
living	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Proviso	O
in	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
which	O
restrained	O
it	O
from	O
extending	O
to	O
any	O
Person	O
whose	O
Husband	O
or	O
Wife	O
should	O
continually	O
remain	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
Seven	O
Years	O
beyond	O
the	O
Seas	O
;	O
or	O
whose	O
Husband	O
or	O
Wife	O
should	O
absent	O
himself	O
or	O
herself	O
for	O
Seven	O
Years	O
,	O
within	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Dominions	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Party	O
so	O
left	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
be	O
alive	O
:	O
And	O
as	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
no	O
Proof	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
Defendant	O
's	O
knowing	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
was	O
alive	O
,	O
they	O
hoped	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
the	O
Statute	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
her	O
Separation	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
Raddish	O
to	O
call	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
Christian	O
Name	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
's	O
the	O
Person	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
.	O
Raddish	O
appeared	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
him	O
sworn	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Raddish	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Sarah	O
Parsley	O
:	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
sixteen	O
or	O
seventeen	O
Years	O
,	O
or	O
upwards	O
.	O
She	O
died	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
1736	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
buried	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Raddish	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
seen	O
her	O
often	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
within	O
nine	O
or	O
10	O
Years	O
last	O
past	O
?	O
Raddish	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
who	O
they	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
Husband	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
spake	O
three	O
Words	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
,	O
People	O
have	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
That	O
Man	O
was	O
Sarah	O
Parsley	O
's	O
Husband	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
often	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Witness	O
being	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Sight	O
weak	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Now	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Raddish	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
I	O
reckon	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
tell	O
how	O
long	O
before	O
her	O
Death	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
Time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
People	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
Sarah	O
Parsley	O
's	O
Husband	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
then	O
see	O
Sarah	O
Parsley	O
?	O
Raddish	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
or	O
alive	O
then	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Just	O
now	O
you	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
Raddish	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
well	O
tell	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
Man	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
did	O
she	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Raddish	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
She	O
commonly	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
come	O
but	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Raddish	O
.	O
As	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
its	O
being	O
fine	O
Weather	O
-	O
a	O
fine	O
Season	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
him	O
Half	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
who	O
that	O
Man	O
was	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
Sarah	O
Fowkes	O
's	O
Husband	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
alive	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
And	O
how	O
long	O
is	O
this	O
ago	O
?	O
Raddish	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Crane	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Raddish	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
He	O
reported	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
Raddish	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
his	O
Whore	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Years	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
often	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Whore	O
and	O
a	O
Bitch	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
with	O
old	O
Raddish	O
,	O
and	O
tuck	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
he	O
often	O
said	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
within	O
nine	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
within	O
that	O
Time	O
I	O
have	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
When	O
he	O
saw	O
his	O
Wife	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
has	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
D-mn	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
,	O
-	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
We	O
often	O
talked	O
about	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
some	O
Conversation	O
with	O
him	O
since	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
not	O
mentioned	O
,	O
except	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
Months	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Tipstaff	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
base	O
,	O
to	O
marry	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
was	O
alive	O
?	O
D-mn	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
said	O
he	O
)	O
what	O
's	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
Conversation	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Life-Time	O
?	O
Crane	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
nine	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
or	O
thereabout	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
within	O
ten	O
Years	O
,	O
or	O
eleven	O
Years	O
?	O
Crane	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Council	O
to	O
Raddish	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
she	O
die	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Raddish	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Merriman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Sarah	O
Fowke	O
:	O
She	O
lived	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
died	O
in	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
buried	O
her	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
1736	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
458.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bowmaster	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
August	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
459	O
,	O
460.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
29	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
461.	O
William	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Upper	O
Leather	O
for	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Last	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Leopold	B-pers
Schutte	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
11	O
.	O
And	O
462.	O
John	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Leather	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
Aug.	O
11	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
463.	O
William	B-pers
Glossop	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Randall	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
,	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
464.	O
Mary	B-pers
Candy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Copper	O
Lamp	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
465.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Wine-quart	O
Pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Abram	B-pers
Franshaw	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
466.	O
Jarib	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
Schoolmaster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Judith	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Redman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
by	O
striking	O
,	O
beating	O
,	O
casting	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
her	O
Jaw-Bone	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
Bruise	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
her	O
Jaw	O
Bone	O
,	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
Aug.	O
20	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Coach	B-place
and	I-place
Horses	I-place
in	I-place
Conduit-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
Bed	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
behind	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Accident	O
happened	O
.	O
About	O
Six	O
,	O
some	O
Carpenters	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
I	O
'wak	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Word	O
-	O
Bitch	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
little	O
Room	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
Drinking-Room	O
on	O
the	O
Ground-Floor	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
by	O
a	O
Single-deal	O
Partition	O
,	O
pannell	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
imagin	O
'd	O
somebody	O
was	O
abusing	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
this	O
little	O
Room	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
Left	O
Arm	O
round	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
somewhere	O
on	O
her	O
Breast	O
.	O
Lord	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
's	O
the	O
Matter	O
!	O
His	O
Answer	O
was	O
,	O
-	O
The	O
Gentlewoman	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
!	O
In	O
a	O
Fit	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
!	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
't	O
is	O
something	O
worse	O
;	O
how	O
came	O
her	O
Mouth	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
bloody	O
?	O
For	O
the	O
Blood	O
ran	O
from	O
her	O
Mouth	O
down	O
her	O
Stays	O
and	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
Head	O
lolling	O
back	O
over	O
his	O
Arm	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
three	O
times	O
for	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fourth	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
:	O
I	O
sprinkled	O
some	O
in	O
her	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
some	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
escaped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
some	O
new	O
Linnen	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
Child	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
.	O
Some	O
small	O
Time	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
another	O
Child	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
Sir	O
!	O
I	O
hear	O
my	O
Mother	O
is	O
killed	O
,	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
Mother	O
was	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
Mother	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
Linnen	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
-	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Carnaby	O
Market	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Child	O
and	O
the	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
knew	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Evening	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
then	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
Watts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
meet	O
his	O
Mother	O
at	O
one	O
Carter	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Red	O
Cross	O
in	O
May-Fair	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
Carter	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Days	O
;	O
he	O
believed	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
him	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
Usher	O
in	O
a	O
School	O
.	O
At	O
Kensington	O
we	O
enquired	O
after	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
one	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
having	O
some	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
Carter	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
Coachman	O
to	O
Madam	O
Jacob	O
at	O
Kensington	O
)	O
he	O
put	O
us	O
upon	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Stables	O
where	O
the	O
Coachman	O
lay	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
?	O
and	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
shamm	O
'd	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Carter	O
's	O
Son	O
spoke	O
to	O
us	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
us	O
what	O
we	O
wanted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
We	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
[	O
Carter	O
]	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
:	O
Then	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
Hay-loft	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
some	O
Straw	O
to	O
stand	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
aside	O
with	O
my	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
behind	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
but	O
his	O
Penknife	O
.	O
His	O
Ruffles	O
and	O
his	O
Right	O
Hand	O
were	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Shirt	O
on	O
when	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
was	O
asleep	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
unlock	O
'd	O
?	O
Pemberton	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Lock	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
not	O
lock	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
Window	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
where	O
the	O
Carpenters	O
were	O
at	O
Work	O
?	O
Pemberton	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Glass	O
Door	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Curtain	O
before	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
Common	O
Drinking	O
Room	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
call	O
for	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
desire	O
Assistance	O
?	O
Pemberton	O
.	O
Not	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
remember	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
in	O
Liquor	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Pemberton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
then	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Lochlan	B-pers
Maclaughlan	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
about	O
Six	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
Woman	O
was	O
dying	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
siting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Pemberton	O
was	O
washing	O
the	O
Blood	O
from	O
her	O
Mouth	O
.	O
Her	O
Pulse	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
being	O
warm	O
,	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
a	O
Vein	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bled	O
about	O
a	O
Spoonful	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Mark	O
of	O
a	O
Blow	O
,	O
or	O
Fall	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
Left	O
Jaw	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
bleed	O
much	O
at	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
gave	O
an	O
Account	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
that	O
Evening	O
at	O
Pemberton	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
direct	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Despagnol	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
towards	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
That	O
immediately	O
afterward	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
Woman	O
was	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
,	O
bleeding	O
at	O
the	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Head	O
lolling	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
wipe	O
the	O
blood	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
her	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Despagnol	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
at	O
this	O
House	O
,	O
