TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
12th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Micajah	O
Perry	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
MICAJAH	B-pers
PERRY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
LEE	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bampshire	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hoggard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Nemes	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chamberlen	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Pinkney	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Whipham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
,	O
Pennington	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Moran	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Coppendale	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Threadgold	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Tesh	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Blagrave	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lydall	I-pers
.	O
234.	O
William	B-pers
Kirkwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
the	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	O
wa	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
James	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Hunt	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
Head	O
,	O
Face	O
,	O
Stomach	O
,	O
Sides	O
and	O
Back	O
,	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
beat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
did	O
cast	O
and	O
throw	O
,	O
giving	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Hunt	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
by	O
striking	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
by	O
casting	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
several	O
mortal	O
Wounds	O
and	O
Bruises	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
from	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
to	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
above-mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
he	O
languished	O
,	O
and	O
languishingly	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
dy	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ladyman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
House	O
with	O
his	O
Fellow-Servant	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
his	O
Companion	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Penny	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
he	O
sha'n't	O
lend	O
you	O
a	O
Penny	O
.	O
Why	O
would	O
you	O
impose	O
upon	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
impose	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
he	O
shall	O
not	O
lend	O
you	O
a	O
Penny	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
asked	O
the	O
Deceased	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
his	O
own	O
Company	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
the	O
Deceased	O
damn	O
'd	O
his	O
Body	O
and	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
lick	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
says	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
damn	O
you	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
make	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
wait	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
wait	O
all	O
Night	O
I	O
'll	O
do	O
your	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
accordingly	O
paid	O
Two-pence	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Presently	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
fighting	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Battle	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Battle	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
damn	O
his	O
Eyes	O
and	O
Body	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
him	O
again	O
on	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
Affront	O
?	O
Ladyman	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
and	O
easy	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
behave	O
any	O
otherwise	O
than	O
quietly	O
and	O
civilly	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
how	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
began	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
afterwards	O
fighting	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
first	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Cut	O
on	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Blood	O
upon	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
fighting	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
several	O
Falls	O
,	O
and	O
Blows	O
pass	O
'd	O
on	O
both	O
Sides	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
had	O
a	O
Cut	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
a	O
Fall	O
on	O
the	O
Stones	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wimpers	I-pers
gave	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Geary	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
came	O
Home	O
that	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
Liquor	O
;	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
complained	O
of	O
his	O
Hip	O
,	O
and	O
Side	O
.	O
His	O
Eyes	O
and	O
Face	O
were	O
black	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
fighting	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Fool	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
off	O
by	O
the	O
worst	O
?	O
Well	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
better	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
for	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
fought	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
the	O
next	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
Workhouse	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Man	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
Fever	O
,	O
(	O
in	O
a	O
deplorable	O
Condition	O
)	O
on	O
Friday	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
my	O
Brother	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
his	O
Illness	O
came	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
by	O
Fighting	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Bed-cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
Side	O
and	O
Elbow	O
sadly	O
bruised	O
and	O
morrify	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
fought	O
with	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
with	O
an	O
Irishman	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
helping	O
to	O
unload	O
four	O
Loads	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
Work	O
was	O
done	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
but	O
2	O
d.	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Fighting	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Westbrook	O
,	O
(	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Deceased	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Work-house	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
a	O
Fever	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
senseless	O
and	O
delirious	O
.	O
After	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
the	O
Body	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
bruised	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bruises	O
might	O
hasten	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
ill	O
State	O
,	O
his	O
Bowels	O
were	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Body	O
was	O
very	O
morbid	O
.	O
In	O
all	O
Probability	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
liv	O
'd	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
longer	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Topliff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
that	O
Evening	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Penny	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
changing	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Black-guard	O
Dog	O
,	O
for	O
spunging	O
upon	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
deserv	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Brains	O
knock	O
'd	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
knock	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
declared	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
me	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
lay	O
some	O
Minutes	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Thing	O
I	O
saw	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
recover	O
'd	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Deceased	O
naked	O
,	O
fighting	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
so	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
who	O
struck	O
the	O
first	O
Blow	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hanford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
began	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
what	O
Words	O
pass	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
coming	O
out	O
.	O
Topliff	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
)	O
went	O
out	O
next	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
struck	O
him	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
.	O
People	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
left	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
would	O
fight	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
fought	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
a	O
Fall	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
fight	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Evan	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
-	O
He	O
would	O
fight	O
the	O
best	O
[	O
Man	O
]	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
He	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
fight	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
stripp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
fight	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Witness	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
[	O
the	O
Witness	O
]	O
went	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
Hunt	O
dy	O
'd	O
a	O
natural	O
Death	O
.	O
235.	O
Anne	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Box	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Eleanor	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
Mar	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
236.	O
John	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Brodu	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Mar	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
237.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
238.	O
Margery	B-pers
Akers	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
Apr	O
2.	O
William	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
Spring	O
Gardens	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Barnes	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
not	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Spring	O
Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Cross	B-place
Keys	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
Barnes	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Watch	O
:	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
presently	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
Lap	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
other	O
Woman	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
upon	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
after	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
this	O
Evidence	O
[	O
Watkins	O
]	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Akers	O
lives	O
in	O
Lumley	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
a	O
Friend	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Akers	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
(	O
Akers	O
)	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
George	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
this	O
Watch	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
Groves	O
happen	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
;	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
three	O
Guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
would	O
lend	O
but	O
two	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
Two	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
He	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
coming	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
informed	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
that	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
Money	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Hutchinson	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Watch	O
I	O
lost	O
:	O
Watkins	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hutchinson	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
going	O
sometimes	O
to	O
Akers	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
shewed	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
talking	O
to	O
me	O
several	O
Times	O
before	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Concern	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
no	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hutchinson	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Akers	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pull	O
out	O
the	O
Watch	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
pay	O
me	O
a	O
Shilling	O
for	O
the	O
Wine	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Shilling	O
for	O
lying	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
all	O
Night	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
She	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
Fear	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
should	O
refuse	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
herself	O
asked	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
the	O
Money	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fraser	O
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
(	O
Akers	O
)	O
keeps	O
a	O
most	O
notorious	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
a	O
Harbour	O
for	O
Thieves	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
no	O
Manner	O
of	O
Defence	O
.	O
Hutchinson	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
received	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Akers	O
's	O
House	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
[	O
Watkins	O
]	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Trifle	O
of	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
Matter	O
upon	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
her	O
the	O
Rent	O
which	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
which	O
she	O
rented	O
at	O
next	O
Door	O
.	O
She	O
refused	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
Money	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
to	O
lend	O
,	O
)	O
but	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
till	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
Fellow	O
has	O
pawned	O
the	O
Watch	O
for	O
two	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
3	O
Minutes	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
before	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
Akers	O
keeps	O
a	O
private	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
drank	O
Punch	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
drank	O
something	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
drink	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Akers	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
received	O
at	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
George	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Footman	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
Watkins	O
.	O
Watkins	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
Man	O
(	O
Chapman	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
nor	O
have	O
I	O
ever	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
239.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Daniel	B-pers
King	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
Daniel	O
King	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
Talbot	O
Inn	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Basket	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
towards	O
Kensington	B-place
;	O
and	O
between	O
Knights-Bridge	O
and	O
The	O
Half-way	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
Yards	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Moon	O
shone	O
bright	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
passed	O
by	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
Foot	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
came	O
on	O
my	O
Left	O
Hand	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
my	O
Right	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
But	O
End	O
of	O
this	O
Pistol	O
on	O
the	O
Stomach	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
laid	O
his	O
Pistol	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
Feet	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
kneelled	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
Shoes	O
;	O
the	O
Buckles	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
take	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
-	O
they	O
are	O
good	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
them	O
inside	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
demanded	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
damned	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Pockets	O
were	O
sewed	O
up	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Money	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
searched	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
thence	O
three	O
Shillings	O
,	O
two	O
Six-pences	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
Five-pence	O
Half-penny	O
,	O
or	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
in	O
Copper	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
searched	O
my	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
the	O
Straw	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
some	O
People	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
My	O
Face	O
was	O
then	O
towards	O
Kensington	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
to	O
follow	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Breeches	O
being	O
about	O
my	O
Heels	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
run	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
Moon	O
shone	O
very	O
bright	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
them	O
run	O
,	O
'till	O
they	O
were	O
fifty	O
Yards	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
Striped-Waistcoat	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
:	O
His	O
Hat	O
was	O
cocked	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Cap	O
was	O
pulled	O
a	O
little	O
over	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
his	O
Face	O
very	O
plain	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
!	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
!	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
Money	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
coming	O
by	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
run	O
down	O
a	O
narrow	O
Passage	O
,	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
saved	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Way	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
borrow	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
at	O
the	O
Half	O
Way	O
House	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
within	O
a	O
hundred	O
Yards	O
of	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Gilpin	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
made	O
me	O
go	O
so	O
uneasy	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
Men	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
directly	O
Homewards	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
how	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Colcot	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
,	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Kensington	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
April	O
12	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
the	O
Half-Way	O
House	O
and	O
Kensington	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Men	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
King	O
!	O
What	O
the	O
Devil	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
without	O
your	O
Shoes	O
!	O
Why	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
Shoes	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Striped-Waistcoat	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Fright	O
for	O
Fear	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
robbed	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
pushed	O
on	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Knights-Bridge	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Bottom	O
,	O
there	O
stood	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Men	O
on	O
each	O
Side	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
we	O
were	O
beset	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
little	O
Stand	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
called	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Person	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
that	O
young	O
Fellow	O
in	O
the	O
Striped-Waistcoat	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
;	O
nobody	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Cloth-fair	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Kensington-Gore	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Sweetheart	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Green	O
's	O
Daughter	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
improper	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
courting	O
without	O
a	O
Coat	O
;	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp-lighter	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
wore	O
a	O
Coat	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
committed	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
answer	O
King	O
's	O
Description	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
holding	O
up	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
Lanthorn	O
to	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
he	O
coloured	O
prodigiously	O
.	O
God	O
forbid	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
accuse	O
an	O
innocent	O
Man	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
are	O
like	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
King	O
described	O
.	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
offer	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Beadle	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
very	O
light	O
Night	O
?	O
Colcot	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Moonlight	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
very	O
bright	O
:	O
Not	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Face	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
Beadle	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
my	O
Rounds	O
,	O
three	O
Quarters	O
after	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Nag's-Head	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
ask	O
a	O
Man	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
any	O
Body	O
run	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
has	O
been	O
robbed	O
a	O
little	O
higher	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
one	O
had	O
run	O
the	O
Way	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
enquired	O
which	O
Way	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
gone	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
towards	O
Kensington	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
very	O
readily	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
a	O
pretty	O
Wav	O
after	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Causeway	O
,	O
by	O
Hyde-Park	O
Wall	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
searched	O
several	O
Courts	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
searching	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
his	O
Name	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
twas	O
Abraham	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp-lighter	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Cloth	O
Fair	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
courted	O
a	O
Girl	O
at	O
Kensington-Gore	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
going	O
thither	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
an	O
hundred	O
Yards	O
from	O
King	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
upon	O
his	O
[	O
King	O
's	O
]	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
Thieves	O
,	O
with	O
King	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Men	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Bear	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
King	O
not	O
caring	O
to	O
go	O
any	O
farther	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
over	O
the	O
Pursuit	O
likewise	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
saying	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
surprizing	O
Thing	O
the	O
Thieves	O
should	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
so	O
near	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
move	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
got	O
about	O
10	O
Yards	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Colcot	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
us	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
us	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Telling	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
answered	O
the	O
Description	O
that	O
King	O
had	O
given	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
asked	O
him	O
several	O
Questions	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
King	O
,	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
directly	O
,	O
-	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
held	O
his	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
These	O
Shoes	O
we	O
found	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
King	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
my	O
Rounds	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Coat	O
upon	O
the	O
Threshold	O
of	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
at	O
Knights-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Pistol	O
under	O
the	O
Coat	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
a	O
Crack	O
on	O
each	O
Side	O
the	O
Trigger	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
loaded	O
very	O
high	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
drew	O
the	O
Charge	O
this	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Ball	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
The	O
Pistol	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
drew	O
it	O
this	O
Morning	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
so	O
high	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
some	O
Accident	O
might	O
happen	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
Three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
(	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
Agreement	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
robbing	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
Crown	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Chick	O
Lane	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Wall	O
between	O
,	O
Knights-Bridge	O
and	O
Kensington	O
.	O
We	O
stood	O
Two	O
Hours	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
)	O
by	O
the	O
Half-Way	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
several	O
People	O
pass	O
,	O
who	O
we	O
thought	O
were	O
not	O
worth	O
our	O
Trouble	O
to	O
rob	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
we	O
should	O
go	O
Home	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Holidays	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
from	O
somebody	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
resolved	O
to	O
attack	O
the	O
first	O
Man	O
we	O
met	O
,	O
which	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
this	O
Mr.	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
a-head	O
of	O
[	O
before	O
]	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
demanded	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
clapped	O
his	O
Pistol	O
to	O
his	O
Breast	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
stopping	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
Pistol	O
in	O
that	O
Posture	O
,	O
I	O
kneeled	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Pair	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
-	O
as	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
the	O
Buckles	O
were	O
Silver	O
?	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
no	O
,	O
they	O
cost	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
Groat	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
passed	O
them	O
we	O
ran	O
faster	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
keep	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Causeway	O
down	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
all	O
along	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
observing	O
a	O
Woman	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
kept	O
strait	O
along	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
Turning	O
by	O
the	O
White-Bear	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
that	O
Turning	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
Wall	O
into	O
Hyde-Park	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
into	O
Grosvenor	O
Square	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
'till	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
two	O
Striped-Waistcoats	O
on	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Cotton-Cap	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
plush	O
Cape	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cutter	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Coat	O
which	O
the	O
Watchman	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
on	O
but	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Coat	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
when	O
the	O
Watchman	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
finding	O
the	O
Evidence	O
strong	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
;	O
And	O
said	O
he	O
lent	O
it	O
the	O
Evidence	O
that	O
Night	O
to	O
rob	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
were	O
both	O
before	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
Catherine	O
Sommerly	O
.	O
Once	O
or	O
twice	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Evidence	O
in	O
a	O
ragged	O
Coat	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Plush-Cape	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Once	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Master	O
,	O
to	O
treat	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
lighting	O
his	O
Lamps	O
.	O
Another	O
Time	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
half	O
a	O
Day	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Short's-Gardens	O
,	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
desirous	O
of	O
being	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
not	O
sworn	O
positively	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
consented	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
accus	O
'd	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
being	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
granted	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
[	O
the	O
Evidence	O
]	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
swear	O
only	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
Confession	O
in	O
Writing	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Confession	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
produced	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
till	O
after	O
King	O
had	O
sworn	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
240.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Etherington	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold-Rings	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
Bristol	O
Stones	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
and	O
Locket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
three	O
Pounds	O
eighteen	O
Shillings	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
241	O
,	O
242.	O
Robert	B-pers
Davy	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
60	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
April	O
18	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
243.	O
Henry	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
Eighteen	O
Ells	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
,	O
March	O
20	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
244	O
,	O
Brian	B-pers
Murtogh	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
245	O
,	O
246	O
,	O
247.	O
Jane	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Corker	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
and	O
Gold	O
Seat	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Spragg	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
And	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Edward	O
Spragg	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Charing	B-place
Cross	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
Entrance	O
of	O
some	O
Court	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
their	O
Faces	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
answer	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
how	O
far	O
I	O
was	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
to	O
listen	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
either	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
pick	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
,	O
on	O
their	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
seized	O
Jane	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
my	O
Pocket	O
:	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
held	O
her	O
fast	O
'till	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Whitehall	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
demanded	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
some	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
in	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
Church	O
Yard	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
or	O
Constable	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Mary	O
Corker	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
being	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
likewise	O
.	O
Next	O
Morning	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
(	O
George	O
Swindell	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
Watch	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
get	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Soldier	O
upon	O
Duty	O
on	O
the	O
Parade	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Officer	O
delivered	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
knowing	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
us	O
that	O
Trouble	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
it	O
directly	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
Jane	O
Smith	O
owned	O
she	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Jane	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
my	O
Tryal	O
when	O
my	O
Husband	O
is	O
cleared	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
abed	O
and	O
asleep	O
when	O
the	O
Thing	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
pick	O
us	O
both	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
us	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
?	O
And	O
did	O
we	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
where	O
we	O
could	O
pick	O
up	O
a	O
Sweetheart	O
?	O
Upon	O
which	O
you	O
told	O
us	O
you	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
in	O
a	O
convenient	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
us	O
a	O
Present	O
.	O
Spragg	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
met	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
but	O
't	O
is	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
any	O
Questions	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
George	O
Swindell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
and	O
shaved	O
and	O
powdered	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
that	O
Morning	O
about	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
this	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
Spragg	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Watch	O
.	O
Swindell	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Watch	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
)	O
shewed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
under	O
Arms	O
on	O
the	O
Parade	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
learned	O
at	O
the	O
Round-house	O
that	O
a	O
Gentl	O
man	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hilsley	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spragg	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hilsley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
April	O
2	O
,	O
between	O
Two	O
and	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
brought	O
Jane	O
Smith	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
in	O
St.	O
Margarets	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
somewhere	O
about	O
Chairing-Cross	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
by	O
Jane	O
Smith	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
Northumberland	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
several	O
other	O
Women	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
somebody	O
else	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
only	O
she	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
purged	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
that	O
other	O
Woman	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
't	O
was	O
Mary	O
Corker	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
her	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
secured	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
Corker	O
;	O
and	O
hearing	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
that	O
She	O
and	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
Soldier	O
,	O
were	O
just	O
gone	O
down	O
an	O
Alley	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
stepped	O
after	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
[	O
Corker	O
]	O
but	O
the	O
Soldier	O
ran	O
away	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
However	O
we	O
locked	O
Her	O
and	O
Jane	O
Smith	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
'till	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
Swindell	O
(	O
the	O
Barber	O
)	O
came	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
Watch	O
in	O
Thomas	O
Smith's-Possession	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
off	O
the	O
Parade	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Justice	O
Manley	O
's	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
us	O
the	O
Trouble	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
we	O
sent	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
(	O
where	O
we	O
waited	O
'till	O
the	O
Justice	O
could	O
hear	O
us	O
)	O
Jane	O
Smith	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
-	O
yes	O
,	O
damn	O
her	O
Soul	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
she	O
had	O
kept	O
a	O
House	O
before	O
now	O
,	O
at	O
Antigua	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
;	O
and	O
(	O
snapping	O
her	O
Fingers	O
)	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
value	O
being	O
sent	O
there	O
,	O
nor	O
going	O
abroad	O
,	O
provided	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
sent	O
to	O
Virginia	O
or	O
Maryland	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
that	O
while	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
fond	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
convey	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Corker	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Swindell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
after	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
going	O
to	O
Tothil-street	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Mob	O
about	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
up	O
like	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Foolish	O
Women	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Jenny	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
Molly	O
Corker	O
was	O
asleep	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
Jenny	O
wake	O
Molly	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
for	O
?	O
Jenny	O
Smith	O
took	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
String	O
and	O
a	O
Seal	O
and	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Stocking	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
Is	O
not	O
this	O
a	O
noble	O
Watch	O
?	O
And	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
My	O
dear	O
Tom	O
Smith	O
be	O
true	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Watch	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
D-mn	O
my	O
Soul	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Jane	O
Smith	O
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
Molley	O
Corker	O
for	O
her	O
Cloak	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
two	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
send	O
us	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
searched	O
,	O
we	O
might	O
keep	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
make	O
the	O
most	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
some	O
foul	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Husband	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
pick	O
'd	O
us	O
up	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
smaller	O
Money	O
than	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
trust	O
to	O
his	O
Honour	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
dishonourable	O
as	O
to	O
cheat	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Mrs.	O
Swindell	O
that	O
Morning	O
in	O
Green's-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
dirty	O
Cap	O
and	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
:	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Pledges	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Barber	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Parade	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Swindell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
my	O
Oath	O
,	O
Smith	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
Husband	O
through	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Jane	O
Smith	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Corker	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Thomas	O
Smith	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
248.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Linton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
Mar	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
single	O
Felony	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Owen	I-pers
Tudor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Leghorn	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
Mar	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
249	O
,	O
250.	O
John	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
and	O
Little	B-pers
George	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
,	O
about	O
Eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
1	O
Peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Agar	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
1	O
Peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
1	O
Peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
13	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
251.	O
Richard	B-pers
Sedgewick	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mare	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
Colour	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
,	I-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Burlington	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
brown	O
bay	O
Colour	O
,	O
val	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
grey	O
Colour	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gladman	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ivory	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
16	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
4th	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
Chesnut	O
Colour	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
And	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
5th	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gelding	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
brown	O
bay	O
Colour	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Burlington	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
black	O
Mare	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
Pastures	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
.	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
Enquiry	O
I	O
could	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
3d	O
or	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
's	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
If	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Burlington	O
's	O
Mare	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Horses	O
:	O
Upon	O
this	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Mare	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
one-eyed	O
Farmer	O
at	O
Rochester	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
at	O
Maidstone	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
enter	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Toll-book	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Maidstone	O
to	O
be	O
satisfied	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
enter	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Seller	O
's	O
Name	O
in	O
the	O
Toll-book	O
was	O
not	O
Sedgewick	O
,	O
but	O
Seddock	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Meadows	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
:	O
I	O
always	O
behaved	O
handsomely	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
under	O
Mr.	O
Goring	O
for	O
my	O
Lord	O
Burlington	O
.	O
Goring	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Bailiff	O
under	O
his	O
Lordship	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
his	O
Farms	O
.	O
In	O
September	O
last	O
I	O
discharged	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
Fault	O
in	O
his	O
Work	O
,	O
not	O
for	O
any	O
Dishonesty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Horse	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
advertised	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
towards	O
Turnham	O
Green	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Chesnut	O
Gelding	O
going	O
by	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Clog	O
on	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Gelding	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
cast	O
my	O
Eye	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
a	O
Bridle	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
great	O
Coat	O
,	O
or	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Horse	O
:	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
Name	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Sedgewick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
hard	O
by	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
upon	O
the	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Gelding	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
satisfy	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
Pains	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
a	O
low-pric	O
'd	O
Horse	O
fit	O
for	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
disposed	O
of	O
:	O
Why	O
,	O
(	O
says	O
he	O
)	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
Horse	O
that	O
will	O
do	O
your	O
Business	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
's	O
Horse	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
seen	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
Bridle	O
upon	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Round-house	O
at	O
Chiswick	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
an	O
open	O
Declaration	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
;	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
my	O
Horse	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
call	O
'd	O
Plumb-street	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Mile	O
beyond	O
Woolwich	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
whose	O
Name	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
(	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
)	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Kent-street	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
enquiring	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
I	O
learn	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
Battersea	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
kept	O
an	O
Ale-house	O
in	O
Plumb-street	O
.	O
My	O
Horse	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Brown-bay	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Dark-brown	O
,	O
almost	O
a	O
Black	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Plumb-Street	O
,	O
in	O
Battersea	O
's	O
Close	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
my	O
Horse	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
home	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
again	O
stole	O
away	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ivory	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
my	O
Horse	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
him	O
again	O
:	O
But	O
I	O
lost	O
him	O
on	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
Grounds	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
had	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Comerades	O
took	O
the	O
Horse	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
Fields	O
at	O
Chiswick	O
.	O
Ours	O
was	O
a	O
grey	O
Gelding	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
call	O
'd	O
Manor-house-Field	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
Horses	O
in	O
that	O
Field	O
,	O
his	O
Companions	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
our	O
Horse	O
to	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
Linnen-draper	O
's	O
Shop	O
at	O
Rochester	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
Horse	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
rather	O
than	O
have	O
any	O
Trouble	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Hooper	O
telling	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
Common	O
with	O
my	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
put	O
a	O
Bridle	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
Horse	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
off	O
Turnham	B-place
Green	I-place
.	O
Mine	O
was	O
a	O
Chesnut	O
Gelding	O
:	O
And	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
his	O
stealing	O
the	O
Horses	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
People	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
examin	O
'd	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Horse	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
mine	O
:	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Horse	O
was	O
a	O
Brown-bay	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Hill	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
called	O
Offspring	O
,	O
near	O
Feversham	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Direction	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
unborn	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
led	O
into	O
this	O
Thing	O
very	O
innocently	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Goring	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
weak	O
,	O
simple	O
Fellow	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Life	O
spar	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
transported	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
on	O
all	O
the	O
Indictments	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Hooper	O
's	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
252.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hofman	I-pers
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
,	O
4	O
s	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
's	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
let	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Wilson	O
,	O
Feb.	O
26	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
253.	O
Richard	B-pers
Tobin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Michael	B-pers
Crosby	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
and	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
s	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
Michael	O
Crosby	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
last	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
from	O
Black	O
Mary	O
's	O
Hole	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
young	O
Woman	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
overtook	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Field	O
we	O
pass	O
'd	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
upon	O
me	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Jolt	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
he	O
wanted	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
What	O
I	O
wanted	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
nothing	O
but	O
Civility	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
this	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
deliver	O
your	O
Money	O
this	O
Moment	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
will	O
kill	O
you	O
:	O
The	O
young	O
Woman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
longer	O
in	O
delivering	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
thrusting	O
my	O
Watch	O
into	O
my	O
Breeches	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
him	O
all	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
then	O
he	O
snatch	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Wig	O
falling	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stooping	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
Mercy	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
any	O
Ale-house	O
nigh	O
Town	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
unty	O
'd	O
his	O
Garter	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
entreated	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Black	O
Mary	O
's	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
not	O
only	O
my	O
own	O
Money	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Houses	O
about	O
Black	O
Mary	O
's	O
Hole	O
were	O
very	O
bad	O
ones	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
stripp	O
'd	O
of	O
all	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
resolv	O
'd	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
about	O
forty	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
bound	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
some	O
People	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
demand	O
your	O
Money	O
?	O
Crosby	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Quarrel	O
he	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
both	O
my	O
Thumbs	O
at	O
once	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
disengage	O
myself	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
bit	O
his	O
Nose	O
;	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
untangle	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
tear	O
the	O
Flesh	O
off	O
my	O
Thumb	O
in	O
getting	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pinkney	I-pers
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Crosby	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Islington	B-place
to	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
perceived	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Waistcoat	O
coming	O
towards	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
jostled	O
against	O
Crosby	O
,	O
and	O
Crosby	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
ask	O
Crosby	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
Crosby	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
-	O
nothing	O
but	O
Civility	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
my	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
toward	O
the	O
Houses	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
People	O
at	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
in	O
blue	O
grey	O
was	O
in	O
Danger	O
from	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
striped	O
Flannel	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Apple-tree	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Warner	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
Woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
come	O
out	O
!	O
-	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
is	O
set	O
upon	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
a	O
striped	O
Flannel	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
any	O
Body	O
will	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
her	O
Friend	O
's	O
Name	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
't	O
was	O
Michael	O
:	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
Stile	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
-	O
Michael	O
,	O
as	O
loud	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
answer	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
Woman	O
[	O
Pinkney	O
]	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
'frighted	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
persuaded	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
any	O
farther	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Link-boy	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
Link	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
100	O
Yards	O
into	O
the	O
second	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
met	O
Michael	O
Crosby	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Nape	O
of	O
the	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hardly	O
Strength	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
puff	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
only	O
say	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
met	O
Crosby	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
private	O
Way	O
,	O
which	O
leads	O
from	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Warner-street	O
to	O
Black	O
Mary	O
's	O
Hole	O
;	O
not	O
many	O
People	O
pass	O
that	O
Way	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
common	O
Foot-path	O
in	O
a	O
Field	O
that	O
joins	O
to	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
Crosby	O
.	O
The	O
high	O
Road	O
runs	O
by	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
cross	O
Path	O
through	O
the	O
Field	O
to	O
Black	O
Mary	O
's	O
Hole	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
these	O
Men	O
,	O
Crosby	O
and	O
Jones	O
,	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Fields	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Warner-street	O
,	O
(	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
)	O
.	O
Crosby	O
said	O
,	O
-	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
this	O
Man	O
has	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
me	O
ill	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
stab	O
Crosby	O
directly	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
Knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
Lad	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
hard	O
for	O
my	O
Bread	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Walk	O
last	O
Sunday	O
Afternoon	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
quarelling	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
use	O
me	O
civilly	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
take	O
off	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Garters	O
,	O
and	O
bind	O
me	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
civilly	O
?	O
Crosby	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
bound	O
you	O
;	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
this	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
beat	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
search	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Crosby	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
Money	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Were	O
not	O
my	O
Hands	O
ty	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
Crosby	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Hold	O
of	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
?	O
My	O
Hands	O
were	O
ty	O
'd	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
,	O
taking	O
a	O
Knife	O
off	O
the	O
Pavement	O
,	O
-	O
swore	O
I	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Jones	O
.	O
His	O
Wrists	O
were	O
ty	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
close	O
together	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
my	O
Finger	O
between	O
his	O
two	O
Hands	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Leadbeater	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Vicks	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alderman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susan	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
appeared	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Behalf	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
254.	O
James	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Barley	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
255.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Helot	I-pers
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
Silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Helot	O
;	O
one	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Vuljohn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5l	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
a	O
Person	O
unknown	O
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
256.	O
Laetitia	B-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Alicia	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Elisha	I-pers
Pike	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
April	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
257.	O
Peter	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
300	O
and	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Printed	O
Paper	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
into	O
Books	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hinson	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
March	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
258.	O
Ann	B-pers
Morson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen-Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Mob	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
March	O
26	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
259.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
William	I-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Bottles	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
seven	O
Pint-Bottles	O
of	O
Palm	O
Sack	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
and	I-pers
James	I-pers
Chalie	I-pers
,	O
April	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
260.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kidd	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Donalson	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
April	O
9	O
.	O
Donalson	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
one	O
Bird	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Coal-Yard	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Holborn	I-place
;	O
(	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
here	O
presently	O
)	O
We	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
together	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
This	O
Bird	O
keeps	O
a	O
bad	O
House	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
-	O
About	O
Ten	O
or	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
Liquor	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
(	O
the	O
next	O
Witness	O
)	O
brought	O
up	O
a	O
hot	O
Pint	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
for	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
Brian	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
Liquor	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
not	O
Guilty	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Evidence	O
[	O
Brian	O
]	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
convey	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Ann	O
Brian	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
the	O
hot	O
Pint	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
-	O
together	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
her	O
take	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
pull	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
give	O
it	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
to	O
take	O
of	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
herself	O
.	O
Sometime	O
afterwards	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
his	O
Money	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
her	O
move	O
out	O
at	O
her	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
1/2	O
under	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
under	O
some	O
Bricks	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
When	O
Brian	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
Donalson	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
search	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
under	O
two	O
Bricks	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Grate	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
Brian	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
,	O
and	O
Brian	O
swore	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
Brian	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
going	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
admitted	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
Watch	O
would	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
that	O
Notice	O
at	O
Bird	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
Hours	O
Time	O
Bird	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
reprimanded	O
Donalson	O
for	O
his	O
Conduct	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
Acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
261.	O
John	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Graidon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sparrow	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
262.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
double	O
deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Staple	I-pers
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
263.	O
William	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
with	O
an	O
Out-side	O
and	O
Inside	O
Case	O
made	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
39	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
base	O
Metal	O
Seal	O
plaited	O
over	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
264.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
Mesluage	O
,	O
or	O
Tenement	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
,	I-pers
Lord	I-pers
Onslow	I-pers
,	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gibbins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Lease	O
of	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Onslow	O
's	O
Houses	O
in	O
Tyburn	B-place
Road	I-place
;	O
we	O
were	O
repairing	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Lead	O
was	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
rolled	O
up	O
,	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Ponsir	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
in	O
Tyburn-Road	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
my	O
Rounds	O
the	O
10th	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
at	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
empty	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
Brother	O
Watchman	O
to	O
stand	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lead	O
and	O
some	O
Casements	O
were	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
collered	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
Business	O
I	O
had	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
pushed	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
up	O
another	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
be	O
intended	O
to	O
do	O
all	O
the	O
Mischief	O
he	O
could	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Lead	O
and	O
four	O
Casements	O
were	O
rolled	O
up	O
,	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
assist	O
my	O
Brother	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
slipped	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Joists	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
seeing	O
my	O
Lanthorn	O
he	O
run	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
Closer	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
that	O
Night	O
with	O
the	O
Overseers	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
allow	O
him	O
any	O
Thing	O
for	O
his	O
Subsistance	O
,	O
so	O
his	O
Design	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
all	O
the	O
Mischief	O
he	O
could	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
two	O
Nights	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
knows	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Fire	O
there	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knew	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
:	O
)	O
so	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
away	O
for	O
the	O
Sake	O
of	O
Twenty	O
Shillings	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Parish	O
allows	O
,	O
for	O
every	O
Person	O
they	O
can	O
convict	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
attempted	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
scuffled	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
I	O
tumbled	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Ponsir	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
Leave	O
to	O
lye	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
Parishioner	O
in	O
that	O
very	O
Parish	O
for	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
served	O
Offices	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
.	O
He	O
kept	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
in	O
this	O
very	O
House	O
a	O
great	O
While	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
lame	O
and	O
reduced	O
so	O
low	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
Jury-Men	O
at	O
a	O
Club-Feast	O
made	O
a	O
Collection	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
from	O
Starving	O
.	O
The	O
Parish	O
ought	O
to	O
do	O
something	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
censured	O
the	O
Parish	O
's	O
ill	O
Usage	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
265.	O
Mary	B-pers
Timself	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Pepper	O
Box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Olivers	I-pers
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
266.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
Chickens	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
April	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
267.	O
Francis	B-pers
Knaston	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Barrels	O
of	O
Pitch	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
April	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
268.	O
John	B-pers
Trotter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
Ells	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
value	O
30s	O
.	O
22	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Buckram	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
15	O
Gross	O
of	O
Braid	O
for	O
Stays	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l	O
,	O
15	O
Gross	O
of	O
Galloons	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
3	O
Pieces	O
of	O
white	O
Buckram	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
15	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Canvas	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
3	O
Pieces	O
of	O
brown	O
Buckram	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Ticken	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Doughty	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hitchins	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Vine	O
street	O
,	O
near	O
Round	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Presence	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Doughty	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
more	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Goods	O
we	O
seized	O
,	O
some	O
were	O
produced	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fraser	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Cart	O
near	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
sealed	O
the	O
Bags	O
up	O
into	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
them	O
are	O
what	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Possession	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Alteration	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Doughty	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
stole	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
my	O
Buckram	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
my	O
Stamp	O
at	O
each	O
Corner	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
this	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
another	O
Piece	O
of	O
Buckram	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Silesia	O
Holland	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
:	O
He	O
and	O
his	O
Clerk	O
are	O
here	O
to	O
vouch	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
fall	O
on	O
my	O
Leg	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
Accident	O
I	O
was	O
confin	O
'd	O
for	O
seven	O
Weeks	O
to	O
my	O
Chamber	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
the	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
Time	O
to	O
examine	O
my	O
Shop	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
recover	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
several	O
of	O
my	O
Customers	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
buy	O
Goods	O
cheaper	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
than	O
they	O
could	O
of	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
was	O
strange	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
cast	O
up	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
by	O
my	O
Bills	O
of	O
Parcels	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
150	O
l.	O
Worth	O
of	O
Goods	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Goods	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
at	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
?	O
Doughty	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
several	O
Parcels	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
these	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Buckram	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silesia	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
White	O
;	O
here	O
's	O
my	O
Stamp	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
more	O
Buckrams	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
produced	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
Pieces	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
?	O
Doughty	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
Pieces	O
,	O
-	O
all	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
Mark	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
seven	O
Pieces	O
of	O
White	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
stamp	O
'd	O
at	O
each	O
Corner	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
made	O
this	O
Stamp	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
?	O
Doughty	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
or	O
better	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
arrested	O
for	O
Wages	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Doughty	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
Time	O
to	O
examine	O
my	O
Books	O
:	O
I	O
remember	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Officer	O
,	O
-	O
There	O
's	O
something	O
extraordinary	O
in	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
like	O
a	O
Nobleman	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
arrested	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
these	O
Goods	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
sold	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
Directions	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Number	O
of	O
50	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Goods	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
you	O
miss	O
'd	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
in	O
your	O
Shop	O
?	O
Doughty	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
certainly	O
;	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
those	O
Goods	O
be	O
sold	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
the	O
Mark	O
on	O
them	O
?	O
Doughty	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
trusted	O
to	O
sell	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
sell	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
Mark	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
sell	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
keep	O
my	O
Books	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
settle	O
Accounts	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
up	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
parted	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Doughty	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Doughty	I-pers
,	O
junior	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
Father	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
where	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
conversant	O
with	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Shop	O
and	O
Business	O
ever	O
since	O
last	O
March	O
was	O
Twelvemonth	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
these	O
Goods	O
are	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Months	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
while	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
illness	O
lasted	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
near	O
seven	O
Weeks	O
)	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
about	O
two	O
Days	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
did	O
Business	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
while	O
my	O
Father	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
but	O
myself	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
any	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Buckrams	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
before	O
your	O
Father	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
?	O
Doughty	O
junior	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
But	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sensible	O
(	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
Shop	O
)	O
that	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Pieces	O
were	O
wanting	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
not	O
sold	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
?	O
Doughty	O
junior	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
If	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
never	O
enter	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
we	O
ever	O
receive	O
a	O
Farthing	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
lye	O
before	O
you	O
?	O
Doughty	O
junior	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
the	O
Buckrams	O
that	O
we	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
is	O
about	O
5	O
l.	O
James	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
stiffen	O
'd	O
these	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Buckram	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Doughty	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
these	O
have	O
been	O
stiffen	O
'd	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
are	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
done	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
for	O
we	O
always	O
stamp	O
every	O
Persons	O
Goods	O
with	O
their	O
own	O
Mark	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
a	O
Penny	O
a	O
Yard	O
for	O
Stiffening	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
about	O
a	O
Dozen	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
this	O
Piece	O
may	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
stiffen	O
'd	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
ago	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
some	O
Buckrams	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
two	O
Pieces	O
,	O
at	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
cheaper	O
than	O
the	O
Market	O
Price	O
by	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
usual	O
Price	O
is	O
8	O
d.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
two	O
Pieces	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Doughty	O
's	O
Direction	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
Buckram	O
was	O
never	O
bought	O
unstiffen	O
'd	O
under	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Yard	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
these	O
Buckrams	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Doughty	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
Abroad	O
,	O
with	O
many	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
the	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
was	O
received	O
and	O
book	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
when	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
delivered	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Person	O
not	O
going	O
the	O
Voyage	O
that	O
he	O
expected	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Goods	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
Use	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
again	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fraser	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
so	O
large	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Goods	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
Mr.	O
Doughty	O
's	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
paid	O
Mr.	O
Doughty	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
now	O
gone	O
Abroad	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Doughty	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
the	O
Voyage	O
he	O
expected	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
off	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
18	O
Guineas	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Galloons	O
,	O
I	O
buy	O
my	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Makers	O
and	O
Hawkers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
must	O
sell	O
to	O
more	O
People	O
than	O
Mr.	O
Doughty	O
.	O
The	O
Day	O
after	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
my	O
Wages	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
civilly	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
me	O
then	O
;	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Days	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
a	O
Writ	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Doughty	O
,	O
senior	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
.	O
In	O
November	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
Buckrams	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Master	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
Days	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
:	O
They	O
came	O
either	O
by	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
after	O
wards	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
Pieces	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
Sort	O
of	O
Goods	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
himself	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
them	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lately	O
:	O
I	O
sold	O
him	O
11	O
Pieces	O
of	O
white	O
Linnen	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
or	O
18th	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
these	O
Goods	O
that	O
are	O
now	O
produced	O
are	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
which	O
I	O
sold	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
bought	O
no	O
other	O
Goods	O
of	O
me	O
but	O
what	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
this	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
Years	O
;	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
given	O
to	O
pilfering	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
knew	O
him	O
suspected	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hyde	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
him	O
brown	O
Irish	O
Linnen	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
are	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
among	O
the	O
Goods	O
now	O
produced	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
two	O
small	O
Parcels	O
of	O
Irish	O
Buckrams	O
,	O
at	O
10	O
1/2	O
d.	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
)	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
Stay-makers	O
:	O
These	O
that	O
are	O
produced	O
are	O
of	O
another	O
Sort	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
for	O
Taylors	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
Scotch	O
Buckrams	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
not	O
what	O
I	O
sold	O
him	O
.	O
Col.	O
Sinclair	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
Recommendation	O
from	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
the	O
Lady	O
Beard	O
,	O
wherein	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
into	O
some	O
Shop-keeper	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
therein	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
honest	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
keep	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
take	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
Favour	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
him	O
recommended	O
as	O
a	O
Book-keeper	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
accordingly	O
spoke	O
to	O
some	O
People	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
into	O
Business	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
an	O
Uncle	O
at	O
Edinburgh	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Shop-keeper	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
addicted	O
to	O
Pilfering	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lindsay	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
know	O
serv	O
'd	O
his	O
Apprenticeship	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Stewart	O
,	O
at	O
Edinburgh	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
His	O
Uncle	O
is	O
a	O
considerable	O
Dealer	O
at	O
Edinburgh	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
here	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Doughty	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Doughty	O
say	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
such	O
Satisfaction	O
to	O
his	O
Customers	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
chose	O
to	O
be	O
serv	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
none	O
but	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
addicted	O
to	O
Pilfering	O
before	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
eight	O
Weeks	O
and	O
two	O
Days	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
soberly	O
,	O
liv	O
'd	O
moderately	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
swear	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
People	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
Warren	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
Year	O
last	O
November	O
;	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
universal	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Hair-cutter	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Hair	O
done	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
once	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Doughty	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
another	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fryer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
eight	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Clemency	O
.	O
269.	O
John	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Ounces	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lanning	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
270.	O
Tabitha	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
John	O
Talbot	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Tabitha	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
271.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Whitehouse	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Chain	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Governor	B-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
New	I-pers
River	I-pers
Water	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
from	O
Anwell	O
and	O
Chadwell	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
272	O
,	O
273	O
.	O
*	O
Abraham	B-pers
>	I-pers
Wells	I-pers
``	I-pers
/	I-pers
>	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Endfield	B-place
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Mare	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
23.	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
*	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
were	O
Evidences	O
on	O
Bonner	O
's	O
Trial	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
They	O
swore	O
that	O
Bonner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Grey	O
hound	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Perjury	O
being	O
detected	O
,	O
they	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
viz	O
,	O
Lyon	O
and	O
Story	O
,	O
were	O
committed	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
See	O
Session-Book	O
1736	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
7.	O
p.	O
176	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Sessions	O
Wells	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
were	O
convicted	O
of	O
Perjury	O
on	O
the	O
above-mention	O
'd	O
Trial	O
.	O
Story	O
dy	O
'd	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
See	O
Sessions-Book	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
8.	O
p.	O
206.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Sympson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
brown	O
Mare	O
from	O
Endfield	B-place
Chace	I-place
three	O
Years	O
ago	O
this	O
May	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
since	O
,	O
nor	O
can	O
I	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Stranger	O
)	O
when	O
they	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Sympson	O
's	O
Mare	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
from	O
Old	O
Pond	O
Course	O
on	O
Endfield	O
Chace	O
.	O
Sympson	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
her	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
1736	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
caught	O
her	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sold	O
my	O
Sheep	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
my	O
Pains	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Mare	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
gave	O
me	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
The	O
Reason	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
this	O
sooner	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
loth	O
to	O
blow	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
swear	O
for	O
Bonner	O
the	O
Highwayman	O
,	O
I	O
foreswore	O
their	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
deserted	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Another	O
Reason	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
discover	O
them	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
is	O
my	O
Brother-in-Law	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
have	O
been	O
easy	O
in	O
my	O
Conscience	O
since	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
sick	O
and	O
like	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
resolved	O
to	O
ease	O
my	O
Mind	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
World	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
live	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Wells	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
charge	O
me	O
before	O
?	O
This	O
Man	O
indicted	O
me	O
at	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Commons	O
about	O
eight	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
D.	O
Wells	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
,	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
live	O
near	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
arrested	O
his	O
Brother-in-Law	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
Wells	O
into	O
Newgate	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
having	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Garland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Abraham	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Years	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
-	O
really	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
-	O
only	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
no	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
-	O
nor	O
have	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
any	O
Good	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Waltham	O
Abbey	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Parnel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Abraham	O
Wells	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Years	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Rogue	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
a	O
Brother-in-Law	O
of	O
mine	O
:	O
He	O
took	O
all	O
my	O
Goods	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
confin	O
'd	O
in	O
Goal	O
.	O
Parnel	O
.	O
But	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
my	O
Money	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Daniel	O
Wells	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
Night	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
Lewis	O
's	O
impeaching	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
Character	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Woodham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Abraham	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Years	O
:	O
His	O
general	O
Character	O
is	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
farther	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Wells	O
.	O
Why	O
I	O
have	O
dwelt	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
-	O
and	O
paid	O
you	O
honestly	O
.	O
Woodham	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
so	O
you	O
have	O
John	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Abraham	O
five	O
Years	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
Character	O
.	O
He	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
ruin	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Daniel	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wibert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Abraham	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Years	O
:	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
bears	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Daniel	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
Years	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
slender	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
say	O
more	O
,	O
if	O
your	O
Lordship	O
would	O
hear	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
's	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
in	O
respect	O
to	O
Stealing	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
gets	O
his	O
Bread	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Wells	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
pay	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
dealt	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Long	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
have	O
eat	O
me	O
out	O
again	O
very	O
handsomely	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Abraham	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
have	O
a	O
worse	O
Character	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
except	O
a	O
Murtherer	O
:	O
The	O
first	O
Time	O
I	O
saw	O
Daniel	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
Epping	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Slighter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Abraham	O
ten	O
Years	O
.	O
His	O
Character	O
is	O
bad	O
:	O
-	O
no	O
one	O
's	O
worse	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
great	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
Daniel	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Abraham	O
Seven	O
or	O
Eight	O
Years	O
.	O
His	O
General	O
Character	O
is	O
base	O
,	O
-	O
none	O
's	O
worse	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
very	O
dishonest	O
Man	O
,	O
using	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
much	O
to	O
his	O
Dispraise	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Elson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Abraham	O
Twelve	O
Years	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Daniel	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
much	O
of	O
him	O
-	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
another	O
Country	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
from	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
.	O
A	O
.	O
Wells	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
dealt	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
pay	O
you	O
honestly	O
?	O
Elson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
dealt	O
with	O
you	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
Who	O
is	O
it	O
that	O
gives	O
me	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
?	O
Elson	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Butchers	O
that	O
come	O
from	O
Epping	O
,	O
say	O
you	O
are	O
as	O
bad	O
as	O
Abraham	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
Difference	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Yarrow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Abraham	O
Seven	O
or	O
Eight	O
Years	O
.	O
His	O
general	O
Character	O
is	O
very	O
bad	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Daniel	O
.	O
Daniel	O
Wells	O
.	O
They	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Abraham	O
Wells	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
swore	O
the	O
Peace	O
against	O
Lewis	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
give	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
(	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
Oath	O
)	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
something	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
There	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
any	O
Quarrels	O
between	O
us	O
lately	O
:	O
My	O
Wife	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
may	O
have	O
differed	O
:	O
That	O
's	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
274.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Top	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
green	O
Baise-Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Pymer	I-pers
,	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
275.	O
John	B-pers
England	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
