TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
TUESDAY	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
14th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Humphry	O
Parsons	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1741	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
1	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
MDCCXLI	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHRY	O
PARSONS	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
CHAPELL	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CARTER	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRANGE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Peers	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cripps	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Horrabin	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Oak	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Milward	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
David	I-pers
Kemp	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bonell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bastnet	I-pers
,	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
on	O
Saturday	O
instead	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bastnett	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Storey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Ignatius	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cullis	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
John	B-pers
Cawdell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Magdalen	I-place
,	I-place
Milk-Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
Yards	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Mantua	O
Silk	O
,	O
25	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silver	O
Ducape	O
,	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cloth	O
colour	O
'd	O
Ducape	O
,	O
28	O
Yards	O
of	O
Black	O
Callimancoe	O
,	O
42	O
Yards	O
of	O
fine	O
Brown	O
Stuff	O
,	O
28	O
Yards	O
of	O
flower	O
'd	O
Worsted	O
Damask	O
,	O
25	O
Yards	O
of	O
Green	O
half	O
Ell	O
Mantua	O
,	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
washed	O
Garlix	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Ravenhill	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
3	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Goods	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hook	O
's	O
a	O
Mercer	O
in	O
St.	O
Martins	O
le-Grand	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
Elliot	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
Neighbour	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Baptist's-Head	O
in	O
Milk-street	O
,	O
where	O
Elliot	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
serv	O
'd	O
us	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
for	O
the	O
20	O
Yards	O
of	O
Garlix	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ravenhill	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
Pieces	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
Callimancoe	O
,	O
a	O
brown	O
Stuff	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
wash	O
'd	O
Garlix	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hook	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
Garlix	O
might	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hook	I-pers
.	O
Elliot	O
brought	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
blue	O
Mantua	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
afterwards	O
brought	O
some	O
Silver	O
Ducape	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Yard	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Trade	O
gave	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
makes	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Means	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
:	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
Elliot	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
better	O
fix	O
the	O
Thing	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
more	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
them	O
this	O
Callimancoe	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
brown	O
Stuff	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
When	O
Elliot	O
was	O
asked	O
about	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Ware-house	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hook	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
that	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Condition	O
as	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
like	O
what	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elliot	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Market	O
Price	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
otherwise	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
Business	O
he	O
follows	O
,	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
for	O
Linnen	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sawbridge	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Baptist's-Head	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
,	O
Hook	O
and	O
Elliot	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
these	O
Goods	O
to	O
Elliot	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
Master	O
ever	O
since	O
1739	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
John	B-pers
Runsburgh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
;	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
November	O
19	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
Eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
Kingston	O
Market	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
between	O
Brentford	B-place
and	O
Turnham-Green	B-place
,	O
by	O
three	O
Footpads	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
me	O
off	O
my	O
Horse	O
into	O
a-Field	O
,	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
Groat	O
into	O
my	O
Bag	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
which	O
in	O
particular	O
took	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
to	O
Richard	O
Hall	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
Assistance	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
fir	O
'd	O
at	O
me	O
directly	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
cock	O
'd	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
yield	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
turning	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
Rogues	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
cock	O
'd	O
the	O
Pistol	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
Richard	O
Hall	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Guns	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Man	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Field	O
where	O
this	O
Robbery	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
immediately	O
wounded	O
in	O
the	O
Neck	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
getting	O
over	O
a	O
Hedge	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
cock	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
his	O
Coat	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wig	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Hats	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
desir	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
another	O
Man	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
one	O
Way	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
and	O
Collier	O
and	O
Hall	O
another	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
got	O
past	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fired	O
at	O
Collier	O
and	O
wounded	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Fire	O
fly	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
heard	O
a	O
crackling	O
in	O
the	O
Hedge	O
;	O
I	O
jump	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
leven	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
Head	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Hall	O
and	O
Collier	O
came	O
through	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
was	O
fir	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
Hedge	O
crack	O
;	O
we	O
immediately	O
got	O
through	O
the	O
Hedge	O
,	O
and	O
Wood	O
presented	O
his	O
Gun	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
surrender	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
his	O
Brains	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
yielded	O
to	O
us	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
this	O
Pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Intention	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Thistleworth	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
weary	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
enter	O
'd	O
this	O
Field	O
to	O
rest	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
at	O
that	O
Moment	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Affair	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Pistol	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
3.	O
Peter	B-pers
Pairpait	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1734	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Pistol	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
Intent	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Weston	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
November	O
19	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
4.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Huddle	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cain	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
two	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barfoot	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Knee-Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Stock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
Stock	O
Clasp	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
16	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Cain	O
,	O
October	O
18.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cain	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
two	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Tea	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
of	O
Stepney	O
;	O
we	O
refused	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
by	O
him	O
without	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
a	O
Field	O
,	O
he	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
tripp	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
Heels	O
,	O
fell	O
on	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
Knife	O
to	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
16	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Shoe	O
Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
Metal	O
Knee	O
Buckles	O
,	O
my	O
Stock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Clasp	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Tea	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
Arm	O
when	O
I	O
fell	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Force	O
of	O
the	O
Fall	O
it	O
flew	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
signify	O
denying	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barfoot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
signify	O
'd	O
nothing	O
denying	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Randal	O
Edwards	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
5.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
White	I-place
Chapple	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Hair	O
Brooms	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
18	O
Birch	O
Brooms	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
12	O
Mops	O
,	O
val	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
Pound	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
October	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
Shoe-maker	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
GOD	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
on	O
Hannah	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Pistol	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
charged	O
with	O
Powder	O
,	O
and	O
small	O
leaden	O
Shot	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
,	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Hannah	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
shoot	O
off	O
and	O
discharge	O
,	O
he	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
loaden	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Force	O
of	O
the	O
Powder	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
left	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
penetrate	O
;	O
giving	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
Breadth	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
charged	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
into	O
my	O
Coach	O
at	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
them	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
End	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
green	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
flash	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
screamed	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
doing	O
of	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
was	O
enquiring	O
for	O
a	O
Gunsmith	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Pistol	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
dead	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
the	O
Pistols	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Feet	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hand	O
bloody	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
poor	O
dear	O
Sister	O
,	O
the	O
youngest	O
of	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Pistols	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
draw	O
one	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
Gunsmith	O
's	O
Door	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Report	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
Pistol	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
present	O
the	O
first	O
Pistol	O
at	O
the	O
Woman	O
?	O
Moore	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
to	O
her	O
than	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
a-breast	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
was	O
by	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
rain	O
'd	O
very	O
hard	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
married	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1738	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
used	O
her	O
very	O
ill.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
her	O
Lip	O
;	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
black	O
Eye	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
would	O
murder	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
twice	O
with	O
using	O
her	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Macdonnal	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
her	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
.	O
One	O
Time	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
beat	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Hanger	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
(	O
she	O
said	O
)	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
kill	O
her	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lee	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
he	O
then	O
struck	O
her	O
across	O
the	O
Nose	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
bleed	O
sadly	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Friday	O
Night	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
grosly	O
abused	O
by	O
her	O
Husband	O
a	O
long	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
had	O
two	O
black	O
Eyes	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
inspected	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
Wounds	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
Forehead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
upper	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Mortal	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cause	O
of	O
her	O
Death	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
penetrated	O
through	O
the	O
Vertebre	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Ribs	O
.	O
These	O
Shot	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
left	O
behind	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Pistol	O
must	O
be	O
held	O
quite	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
Wound	O
as	O
this	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
Reasons	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
is	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Pistol	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
some	O
Distance	O
from	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
the	O
Shot	O
would	O
have	O
seperated	O
,	O
whereas	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
one	O
Orifice	O
:	O
My	O
other	O
Reason	O
is	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Lips	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
were	O
actually	O
burnt	O
with	O
the	O
Powder	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Pistol	O
must	O
likewise	O
be	O
held	O
upwards	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Wound	O
penetrated	O
obliquely	O
downwards	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
but	O
even	O
with	O
this	O
Posture	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Colebroke	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
above	O
Deposition	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Pistol	O
which	O
flash	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Pan	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
ten	O
Inches	O
in	O
the	O
Barrel	O
,	O
and	O
loaded	O
8	O
Inches	O
deep	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Levett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
by	O
two	O
Coachmen	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
his	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
might	O
hang	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
do	O
what	O
we	O
would	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
poor	O
Girl	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lee	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
kill	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
Home	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Morning	O
before	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
thinking	O
to	O
receive	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
disappointed	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
Pistols	O
out	O
to	O
Sell	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
in	O
Clarges-Street	O
to	O
Dinner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
din	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Pistols	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Piccadilly	O
in	O
our	O
Way	O
Home	O
,	O
it	O
Rained	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
dry	O
'd	O
ourselves	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
wanted	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
she	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
Pistols	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
directed	O
the	O
Coachman	O
where	O
to	O
stop	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
pulling	O
one	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
it	O
snapp	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
stupid	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
any	O
Thing	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
h	O
ave	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
Infancy	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
Thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
handsome	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
dined	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
loving	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
bruised	O
or	O
beat	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
heard	O
her	O
complain	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dolley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Deceased	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
above	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Times	O
since	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
her	O
complain	O
.	O
Hester	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
.	O
They	O
lived	O
very	O
lovingly	O
for	O
any	O
Thing	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
observ	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
bruised	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
once	O
see	O
a	O
little	O
yellow	O
Speck	O
about	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
asked	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dump	I-pers
.	O
They	O
lived	O
by	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
them	O
these	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
bruised	O
at	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lockyer	I-pers
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
on	O
either	O
Side	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
has	O
often	O
desired	O
a	O
'Prentice	O
of	O
mine	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
how	O
to	O
load	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
seen	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
loaded	O
these	O
herself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
7.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Newlove	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Coffee	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Rows	O
of	O
Gold	O
Beads	O
,	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9	O
,	O
10	O
,	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
,	O
13.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
,	I-place
Black-Fryars	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Dixey	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
1	O
large	O
Pottagepot	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
1	O
Copper	O
Pottage-pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea-kettle	O
,	O
30	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
12	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Warming-pot	O
,	O
a	O
Funnel	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Box-iron	O
and	O
Heater	O
,	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
6	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Dixey	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
11	O
.	O
And	O
Atty	B-pers
alias	I-pers
Hester	I-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Laxton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Dixey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Plank	O
which	O
goes	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Doors	O
where	O
I	O
let	O
down	O
my	O
Beer	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Door	O
which	O
comes	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
were	O
safe	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Goods	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lilliston	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
about	O
the	O
10th	O
Day	O
of	O
last	O
Month	O
,	O
Coates	O
,	O
Nash	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
Black-Fryars	B-place
,	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dixey	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
)	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
King	O
in	O
White-Fryars	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Pewter	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Shelf	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
Home	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Laxton	I-pers
's	O
in	O
George-Alley	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Ditch-side	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Tinder-Box	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
Laxton	O
,	O
Matthews	O
,	O
and	O
Walker	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
contriving	O
how	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
about	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
Plank	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
Coates	O
and	O
Nash	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Plank	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
Cellar	O
with	O
my	O
Tinder-Box	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
I	O
burnt	O
all	O
the	O
Tinder	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
Stairs	O
in	O
a	O
Hurry	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
stay	O
by	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
;	O
when	O
Coates	O
found	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Knock	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Light	O
of	O
a	O
Watchman	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
Nash	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
which	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
wrenched	O
a	O
Door	O
open	O
with	O
Coates	O
's	O
Chissel	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Nash	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pull	O
the	O
Lock	O
Spring	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
Coates	O
opened	O
it	O
himself	O
;	O
when	O
Nash	O
came	O
in	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
a	O
Locker	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
took	O
down	O
all	O
the	O
Pewter	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Brass	O
Pottage	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Warming	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Gallon	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Box	O
Iron	O
and	O
Heater	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
wrap	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
Pewter	O
in	O
my	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
Nash	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
least	O
Pottage	O
Pot	O
we	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
to	O
Laxton	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
Laxton	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Landlord	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
;	O
so	O
Bess	O
Matthews	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
Laxton	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Laxton	O
asleep	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
;	O
Walker	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Coates	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
there	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
desir	O
'd	O
Matthews	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Goods	O
up	O
safe	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Keys	O
out	O
of	O
Laxton	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Pewter	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
the	O
Dishes	O
we	O
put	O
between	O
the	O
Sacking	O
and	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
while	O
Laxton	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
we	O
put	O
under	O
the	O
Drawers	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
Nash	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
Women	O
Prisoners	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
mov	O
'd	O
them	O
by	O
Degrees	O
into	O
Fleet-Lane	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Wilson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Coates	O
was	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
4	O
s.	O
earnest	O
for	O
the	O
Pewter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
and	O
the	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
up	O
higher	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
stopp	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
largest	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Warming	O
Pot	O
,	O
Laxton	O
and	O
Walker	O
sold	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
how	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
us	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
large	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Warming	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
Coates	O
brought	O
us	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
we	O
three	O
equally	O
divided	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Coates	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
how	O
much	O
was	O
divided	O
?	O
Lilliston	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
Prisoner	O
Walker	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
we	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
Lilliston	O
.	O
They	O
sold	O
the	O
Pot	O
as	O
I	O
understand	O
,	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
and	O
the	O
Warming	O
Pot	O
for	O
1	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
us	O
but	O
6	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Boomer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
that	O
a	O
*	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Laxton	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
suspected	O
Persons	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Goods	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Plates	O
,	O
Knives	O
and	O
Forks	O
;	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Coates	O
,	O
Laxton	O
,	O
and	O
Matthews	O
were	O
then	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Coates	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
a-bed	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dixey	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
to	O
me	O
exactly	O
agrees	O
with	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
said	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Pottage	O
Pot	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Directions	O
,	O
in	O
Water	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Walker	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Funnel	O
,	O
the	O
Box	O
Iron	O
and	O
Heater	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
When	O
Coates	O
found	O
that	O
Lilliston	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
the	O
most	O
Discoveries	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
do	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
This	O
Chissel	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Laxton	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
Coates	O
to	O
the	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Chissel	O
with	O
which	O
Coates	O
broke	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
the	O
following	O
Trial	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Paget	I-pers
.	O
Laxton	O
and	O
Matthews	O
brought	O
a	O
large	O
Pot	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
seven	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cluff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Wilson	O
's	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	O
,	O
some	O
Pewter	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
behind	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Coates	O
had	O
4	O
s.	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
.	O
Boomer	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
put	O
Nash	O
into	O
his	O
Information	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
People	O
being	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Coates	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
vile	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
first	O
one	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
.	O
Nash	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Affair	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
above	O
twice	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Laxton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
fast	O
asleep	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
sold	O
nothing	O
for	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Matthews	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
three	O
Times	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Coates	O
and	O
Nash	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Laxton	O
,	O
Matthews	O
and	O
Walker	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
,	O
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Dozen	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
8	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
4	O
Dozen	O
and	O
7	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
,	O
2	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Necklaces	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
14	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
14.	O
Hester	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Laxton	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mickey	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Coates	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
rest	O
Guilty	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Coates	O
,	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Newbury	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
59	O
Yards	O
of	O
checqu	O
'd	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Aaron	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
October	O
2	O
,	O
both	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Laxton	O
,	O
Matthews	O
,	O
Walker	O
,	O
Mickey	O
,	O
Newbury	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sign	O
Iron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Beaty	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
William	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
3	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Mary	B-pers
Peachum	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
Quilts	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
November	O
29	O
,	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Richard	B-pers
Quail	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
.	O
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Stock	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Fusan	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
,	O
October	O
18	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
Leicester-Fields	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
Bundles	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
hanging	O
on	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
carry	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
from	O
me	O
A	O
Coachman	O
happening	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
,	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Colour-Shop	O
by	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Ring	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
had	O
conceal	O
'd	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Ring	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
several	O
Times	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
together	O
.	O
-	O
Proctor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
Goodman's-Fields	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
by	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Boy	O
scream	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
this	O
Bundle	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
Sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
where	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
Ring	O
on	O
his	O
Finger	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
very	O
Person	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
Ring	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
under	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Ring	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp	O
not	O
3	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Glass	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Bundle	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fusan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Shirt	O
,	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
Stock	O
belong	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
Boy	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brogdon	O
.	O
The	O
little	O
Boy	O
has	O
told	O
the	O
same	O
Story	O
exactly	O
now	O
,	O
as	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
varied	O
one	O
Word	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Crowd	O
running	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Croud	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
Innocent	O
indeed	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
20.	O
Michael	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Pattins	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bushnell	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Turville	B-pers
Lash	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
81	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Pot	O
Ashes	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Shipner	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
November	O
15	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
22.	O
John	B-pers
Legg	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
36	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
,	O
Oct	O
23	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
*	O
23	O
Robert	B-pers
Legrose	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
White-chapple	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Yorke	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clack	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
31	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
23	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
13	O
Cloth	O
Jackets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
13	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
Shirts	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
Shifts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clack	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
17	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
*	O
For	O
this	O
Fact	O
Edward	B-pers
Mudder	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Tho	B-pers
Clack	I-pers
,	O
were	O
tryed	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
24.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Frame	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
10	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
3	O
Cloth	O
Jackets	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Parcel	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clack	I-pers
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Sept	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
my	O
Doors	O
were	O
fast	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
wak	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
'em	O
broke	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
manner	O
.	O
The	O
Lock	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Padlock	O
taken	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
so	O
many	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
hire	O
a	O
Cart	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
here	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Valentine	O
Harman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Legrose	O
,	O
one	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Men	O
that	O
were	O
try	O
'd	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
brought	O
some	O
Cloaths	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
Rabbits	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Brew-house	O
for	O
Grains	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
with	O
each	O
his	O
Arm	O
full	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
of	O
Sept.	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
They	O
laid	O
their	O
Bundles	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
one	O
to	O
another	O
:	O
Come	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
back	O
for	O
some	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Studder	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
with	O
each	O
another	O
Arm	O
full	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
threw	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
for	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
Clack	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
some	O
Victuals	O
and	O
Drink	O
first	O
.	O
Aye	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Shillings	O
worth	O
of	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
.	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
these	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
fetch	O
some	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
let	O
Studder	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Closet	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
Madder	O
,	O
Clack	O
,	O
and	O
Wood	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
as	O
many	O
more	O
Cloaths	O
at	O
Carlow	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Frame	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Key	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
through	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Legrose	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
were	O
let	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Cloaths	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
soon	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
secur	O
'd	O
those	O
three	O
Men	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Studder	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
above	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Clack	O
,	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
that	O
Gentlewoman	O
who	O
stands	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
lives	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
demanded	O
Entrance	O
;	O
she	O
kept	O
us	O
some	O
time	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
before	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
did	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
the	O
Cellar-stairs	O
.	O
Harman	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Carlow	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
gone	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Frame	O
,	O
was	O
left	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Frame	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
may	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Cloaths	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
?	O
Clack	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
.	O
Harman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Frame	O
that	O
kept	O
us	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Key-Hole	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Yard-Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
going	O
out	O
.	O
Frame	O
.	O
I	O
waited	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
with	O
his	O
Witnesses	O
all	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
my	O
Name	O
was	O
never	O
mentioned	O
;	O
I	O
drank	O
Part	O
of	O
two	O
full	O
Pots	O
of	O
Beer	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Clack	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
mention	O
her	O
Name	O
here	O
several	O
Times	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
drinking	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
drink	O
a	O
drop	O
of	O
Gin	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
Legrose	O
's	O
Commitment	O
from	O
Justice	O
Fowke	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Way	O
thither	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
have	O
gone	O
abroad	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
too	O
late	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
old	O
Rogue	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
in	O
my	O
Place	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
speak	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
with	O
his	O
Accomplice	O
Madder	O
.	O
Legrose	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
is	O
alledged	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Frame	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
for	O
looking	O
after	O
this	O
Woman	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
Man	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Prison	O
.	O
The	O
Revd	O
Mr.	O
Guthrie	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Frame	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Yeomans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
herself	O
well	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cray	I-pers
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
her	O
Bail	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
receive	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Legrose	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Frame	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25	O
,	O
26	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ozell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
with	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Laurence	B-pers
Price	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
their	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
Hugh	B-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
feloniously	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stark	I-pers
with	O
a	O
certain	O
drawn	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
Iron	O
and	O
Steel	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
short	O
Ribs	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Montgomery	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
stab	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
five	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Ozell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Laurence	B-pers
Price	I-pers
were	O
present	O
,	O
assisting	O
,	O
comforting	O
,	O
and	O
maintaining	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Stark	O
,	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
commit	O
and	O
do	O
,	O
Dec.	O
10	O
.	O
Stark	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
feloniously	O
slaying	O
the	O
said	O
Montgomery	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Carrel	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
Orders	O
about	O
last	O
June	O
,	O
to	O
raise	O
200	O
Men	O
for	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
Government	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
recruiting	O
very	O
fast	O
,	O
the	O
Savoy	O
was	O
full	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
Tilbury-Fort	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Deceased	O
took	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Bond-Street	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
Men	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
confin	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
thought	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
active	O
,	O
careful	O
Man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Dec.	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
this	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Recruits	O
are	O
kept	O
,	O
in	O
Ducking-Pond	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	O
in	O
Bond-Street	B-place
.	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
Soldier	O
s	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
Ozell	O
for	O
one	O
Sturges	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
but	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
forced	O
in	O
.	O
They	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
full	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Sturges	O
down	O
;	O
Stark	O
immediately	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
my	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
stuck	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Door	O
Post	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
called	O
Mrs.	O
Crosley	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
38	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
let	O
out	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
them	O
good	O
;	O
but	O
Stark	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Sturges	O
was	O
a	O
Deserter	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
Deserter	O
any	O
where	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Woman	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
Officer	O
,	O
they	O
staid	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
they	O
wanted	O
Sturges	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
drew	O
his	O
Hanger	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
?	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
Hanger	O
up	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sight	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
went	O
away	O
except	O
Ozell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
kept	O
striking	O
them	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
down	O
the	O
Steps	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
turning	O
about	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
Stark	O
drew	O
his	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
immediately	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
killed	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
in	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
about	O
10	O
Hours	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Stark	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
200	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
Ozell	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
do	O
or	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
first	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
standing	O
with	O
their	O
Backs	O
to	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
them	O
go	O
along	O
,	O
they	O
mutter	O
'd	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
can	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Stark	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
last	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Champion	O
,	O
Ozell	O
,	O
and	O
Price	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
assist	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Deserter	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
Ale-House	O
;	O
Sturges	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
they	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Deserter	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
very	O
easy	O
till	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
drew	O
his	O
Hanger	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
several	O
Times	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
my	O
Bayonet	O
when	O
his	O
Blows	O
came	O
so	O
fast	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
cleave	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Stark	O
Guilty	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
Ozell	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27	O
.	O
28.	O
James	B-pers
Maccartney	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
valu	O
e	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
November	O
1st	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
November	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
;	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
Handkerchiefs	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
Stockings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Maccartney	O
.	O
Pray	O
Madam	O
do	O
n't	O
laugh	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
proper	O
when	O
People	O
take	O
an	O
Oath	O
to	O
laugh	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stokes	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
shewing	O
them	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Woman	O
stoop	O
down	O
twice	O
below	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
some	O
thing	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
counted	O
over	O
my	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
me	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
which	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
another	O
Pair	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
I	O
took	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
the	O
Linnen	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Woman	O
drop	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
me	O
three	O
Shillings	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
touch	O
,	O
or	O
look	O
at	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Maccartney	O
.	O
Let	O
her	O
tell	O
the	O
Truth	O
before	O
the	O
whole	O
Congregation	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
11	O
s	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
October	O
29	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Pounds	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
sewing	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parting	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Oct.	O
20	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31	O
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linnen	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	B-pers
Chief	I-pers
Justice	I-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
17	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
32.	O
Richard	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Shalloon	O
,	O
4	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
Cambrick	O
Stocks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Futcher	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Grice	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Stock	O
Buckle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
September	O
22d	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
Brussels	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Apron	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Stewarta	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Thread-Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Francis	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
3d	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
William	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
160	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Pepper	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
.	O
Oct.	O
15	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
320	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Pepper	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
Sept.	O
30	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
having	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
.	O
In	O
September	O
last	O
was	O
Twelve-months	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
were	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Thomas	B-place
and	I-place
Mary	I-place
Hoy	I-place
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Master	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
River	O
to	O
an	O
Indiaman	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
our	O
Loading	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Botolph	B-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
the	O
next	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Greenwood	O
,	O
were	O
put	O
on	O
Board	O
us	O
,	O
as	O
Watchmen	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Bags	O
of	O
Pepper	O
in	O
the	O
Hold	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
an	O
Agreement	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Hold	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
Greenwood	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
about	O
200	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Bags	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
keeping	O
a	O
Look-out	O
on	O
Deck	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
we	O
were	O
about	O
.	O
We	O
put	O
the	O
Pepper	O
into	O
two	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Cabbin	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Clowes	O
haul	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
on	O
Deck	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Night	O
we	O
took	O
130	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
two	O
Bags	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Ridout	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
on	O
Deck	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Clowes	O
handed	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Ridout	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
Bag	O
started	O
into	O
his	O
Cellar	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
in	O
at	O
his	O
Back-Door	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
us	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
by	O
Land	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
paying	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
his	O
share	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
the	O
Cabbin	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
They	O
hung	O
up	O
always	O
on	O
Deck	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
Goods	O
which	O
are	O
taken	O
in	O
should	O
be	O
lost	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
to	O
stand	O
to	O
the	O
Damage	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
Master	O
I	O
suppose	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clowes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
39	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
boarded	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Oliver	O
's	O
Hoy	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
Burges	O
opened	O
the	O
Hold	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
fill	O
'd	O
2	O
Bags	O
of	O
Pepper	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
haul	O
'd	O
them	O
on	O
Deck	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
by	O
Land	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Ridout	O
's	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
weighed	O
the	O
Pepper	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
casting	O
up	O
what	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
32	O
l	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
5	O
l.	O
for	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Partners	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Burges	O
take	O
theirs	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
to	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
some	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Pepper	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Hold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Keys	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Company	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
these	O
were	O
private	O
Keys	O
with	O
which	O
Burges	O
opened	O
the	O
Doors	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Ship	O
Scarborough	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
Moorings	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
reported	O
at	O
the	O
Custom-House	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
the	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
came	O
up	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
loaden	O
with	O
Pepper	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
exactly	O
how	O
many	O
Bags	O
there	O
were	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
What	O
Method	O
is	O
taken	O
in	O
locking	O
up	O
these	O
Goods	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Hoy	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Commander	O
locks	O
up	O
the	O
Hatches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Keys	O
are	O
sealed	O
up	O
and	O
given	O
generally	O
to	O
the	O
Husband	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
done	O
to	O
prevent	O
any	O
one	O
from	O
getting	O
at	O
the	O
Cargo	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Captain	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
sends	O
up	O
an	O
Impression	O
of	O
the	O
Seal	O
which	O
he	O
intends	O
to	O
use	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Have	O
the	O
Company	O
ever	O
suffer	O
'd	O
by	O
losing	O
their	O
Goods	O
before	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
great	O
Sufferers	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Arrival	O
of	O
the	O
Ships	O
,	O
they	O
lighten	O
at	O
Long-Reach	O
or	O
Erith	O
;	O
the	O
Captain	O
reports	O
at	O
the	O
Custom	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Entry	O
is	O
made	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Cargo	O
may	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
once	O
.	O
It	O
appears	O
by	O
the	O
Register	O
,	O
that	O
Greenwood	O
and	O
Clowes	O
were	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
,	O
but	O
Greenwood	O
has	O
absconded	O
from	O
his	O
Duty	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
Security	O
for	O
the	O
Performance	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Councel	O
to	O
Burges	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
Bags	O
were	O
open	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
this	O
Pepper	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
16	O
or	O
18	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
ty	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Corners	O
with	O
Twine	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cheney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Owner	O
of	O
the	O
Hoy	O
of	O
which	O
Oliver	O
is	O
Master	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
several	O
Doors	O
,	O
all	O
lock	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Locks	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
have	O
a	O
particular	O
Key	O
to	O
each	O
:	O
but	O
my	O
People	O
have	O
no	O
Right	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Hold	O
;	O
they	O
only	O
unlock	O
the	O
Hatches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Porters	O
sling	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
to	O
support	O
the	O
2d	O
Indictment	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
Effect	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
that	O
likewise	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36	O
,	O
37.	O
Charles	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Kilby	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Pepper	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
united	B-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
Merchants	I-pers
trading	I-pers
to	I-pers
the	I-pers
East-Indies	I-pers
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
July	O
13	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
Indictment	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
2d	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ridout	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
Grocer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
at	O
a	O
Sessions	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
before	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Parsons	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
William	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
was	O
by	O
due	O
Course	O
of	O
Law	O
convicted	O
for	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
320	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
Pepper	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
united	B-pers
Company	I-pers
of	I-pers
Merchants	I-pers
trading	I-pers
to	I-pers
the	I-pers
East	I-pers
Indies	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Ridout	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Pepper	O
did	O
receive	O
and	O
have	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
160	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Pepper	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
Councel	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Crime	O
with	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
charg	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
heinous	O
Nature	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
owing	O
to	O
such	O
Persons	O
that	O
so	O
many	O
Enormities	O
are	O
daily	O
committed	O
;	O
and	O
unless	O
there	O
were	O
People	O
to	O
receive	O
Goods	O
from	O
Offenders	O
,	O
there	O
would	O
consequently	O
be	O
fewer	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Record	O
of	O
Oliver	O
's	O
Conviction	O
being	O
read	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Hoy	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
Mate	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Loading	O
of	O
Pepper	O
from	O
an	O
East-India	O
Man	O
,	O
in	O
Sept.	O
last	O
was	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
where	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
passed	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
you	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
Botolph	B-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
and	O
beckon	O
'd	O
me	O
on	O
Shore	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
Craft	O
we	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
Pepper	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
Trade	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
what	O
Officers	O
would	O
be	O
put	O
on	O
Board	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Hold	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
Keys	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Bags	O
to	O
put	O
any	O
Thing	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
Home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
Bags	O
;	O
I	O
accordingly	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
Bags	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
filled	O
with	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Pepper	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
filled	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Back	O
Door	O
,	O
at	O
Wapping	O
New-Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
us	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Pepper	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
quite	O
dark	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
Quantity	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
Each	O
Bag	O
contained	O
112	O
lb	O
.	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
struck	O
off	O
some	O
for	O
Dirt	O
and	O
Tare	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
the	O
Pepper	O
from	O
you	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ridout	O
himself	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
us	O
10	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
weigh	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Pepper	O
into	O
a	O
Tub	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bags	O
again	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
we	O
got	O
130	O
lb	O
.	O
Wt	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
this	O
10	O
l.	O
paid	O
to	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
Clowes	O
took	O
his	O
own	O
and	O
his	O
Partner	O
Greenwood	O
's	O
Shares	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
Oliver	O
his	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
50	O
s.	O
piece	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Bill	O
of	O
Parcels	O
made	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
Ridout	O
pay	O
you	O
the	O
Money	O
himself	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
when	O
we	O
divided	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
the	O
Hold	O
;	O
where	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
ashore	O
on	O
the	O
Key	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
us	O
two	O
present	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Pepper	O
directly	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
put	O
the	O
Pepper	O
into	O
the	O
Bags	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
Greenwood	O
and	O
I	O
;	O
the	O
Master	O
of	O
the	O
Vessel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Officer	O
haul	O
'd	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Cabbin	O
.	O
Councel	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
allowed	O
for	O
Dirt	O
and	O
Tare	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
Twelve	O
Pounds	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
Pepper	O
weigh	O
'd	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
weigh	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
great	O
Scales	O
hang	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Servants	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
weighing	O
it	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Family	O
present	O
but	O
himself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
You	O
speak	O
of	O
a	O
Back-Door	O
;	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
a	O
common	O
passage	O
to	O
carry	O
in	O
all	O
Goods	O
that	O
come	O
by	O
Water	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
do	O
carry	O
in	O
Goods	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
a	O
Back-Door	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
a	O
common	O
place	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
carry	O
'd	O
Goods	O
in	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
Door	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
your	O
Oath	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
never	O
declare	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
this	O
Pepper	O
was	O
run	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
so	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Service	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
then	O
?	O
Burges	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
our	O
Loading	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Ships	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Pepper	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
Hold	O
at	O
Botolph	O
Wharf	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
lay	O
sometimes	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
before	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
to	O
touch	O
our	O
Goods	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clowes	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
latter	O
End	O
of	O
Sept.	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
39	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
boarded	O
on	O
the	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
,	O
which	O
was	O
loaden	O
with	O
Bags	O
of	O
Pepper	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Burges	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Hold	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
fill	O
'd	O
2	O
Bags	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
Ridout	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
fill	O
the	O
Bags	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
him	O
and	O
Greenwood	O
below	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Oliver	O
walked	O
down	O
by	O
Land	O
to	O
Ridout	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pay	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Pepper	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
was	O
equally	O
divided	O
amongst	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
proud	O
of	O
such	O
another	O
Freight	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Clowes	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Burges	O
,	O
Oliver	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
Discourse	O
about	O
the	O
Price	O
?	O
Clowes	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
the	O
Pepper	O
had	O
been	O
weigh	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
away	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pay	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Division	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Apprentices	O
or	O
Servants	O
present	O
?	O
Clowes	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
,	O
-	O
in	O
my	O
Opinion	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
private	O
Transaction	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Receipt	O
given	O
for	O
this	O
Money	O
?	O
Clowes	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
drink	O
any	O
Thing	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
?	O
Clowes	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
Punch	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
ourselves	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
pretend	O
that	O
this	O
Pepper	O
was	O
a	O
Perquisite	O
?	O
Clowes	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
that	O
Burges	O
put	O
the	O
Pepper	O
into	O
the	O
Boat	O
;	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Clowes	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
Burges	O
and	O
Robinson	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
Punch	O
?	O
Clowes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ridout	O
sells	O
Liquors	O
;	O
we	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Punch	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
among	O
our	O
selves	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
Bags	O
were	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
this	O
Pepper	O
?	O
Clowes	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
on	O
Deck	O
with	O
Oliver	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Burges	O
.	O
About	O
18	O
or	O
20	O
were	O
opened	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
lb	O
.	O
out	O
of	O
each	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
sew	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Boat	O
with	O
the	O
Pepper	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
it	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
at	O
Wapping-new	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
exactly	O
tell	O
the	O
Hour	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Pepper	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Burges	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Back-door	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
Burges	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
you	O
whether	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
People	O
at	O
Work	O
on	O
the	O
Keys	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
Pepper	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Porters	O
had	O
done	O
Work	O
on	O
the	O
Keys	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
paid	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
Boat	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
Boat	O
;	O
-	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Hoy	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
We	O
shall	O
now	O
shew	O
,	O
that	O
Greenwood	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
although	O
the	O
Strictest	O
Enquiry	O
has	O
been	O
made	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Inspectors	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Business	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
the	O
Tidesmen	O
do	O
their	O
Duty	O
.	O
I	O
find	O
by	O
the	O
Register	O
,	O
that	O
these	O
2	O
Men	O
Clowes	O
and	O
Greenwood	O
were	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
boarded	O
as	O
Watchmen	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thomas	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
what	O
Enquiry	O
has	O
been	O
made	O
after	O
Greenwood	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Foster	O
.	O
Since	O
the	O
Discovery	O
of	O
the	O
Hoy	O
's	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
strictest	O
Search	O
has	O
been	O
made	O
after	O
Greenwood	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
absconded	O
from	O
his	O
Duty	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
Security	O
for	O
the	O
Performance	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
Warrant	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
is	O
against	O
him	O
-	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Billers	I-pers
The	O
Warrant	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gambier	O
Sworn	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
Pepper	O
in	O
Sept.	O
Sale	O
,	O
1739	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gambier	O
.	O
In	O
that	O
Sale	O
,	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Pepper	O
sold	O
from	O
10	O
d	O
78ths	O
,	O
to	O
11	O
d.	O
farthing	O
the	O
Average	O
was	O
above	O
11	O
.	O
They	O
allow	O
the	O
Buyer	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
Discount	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
the	O
home	O
Consumption	O
Duty	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
4	O
d.	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
so	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
Bag	O
it	O
might	O
come	O
to	O
a	O
Groat	O
less	O
than	O
12	O
d.	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
worth	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
every	O
Duty	O
paid	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Gambier	O
.	O
The	O
nearest	O
Computation	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
made	O
,	O
is	O
14	O
d.	O
farthing	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
so	O
much	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
Duty	O
paid	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Suppose	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
you	O
Pepper	O
at	O
12	O
d.	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
what	O
should	O
you	O
have	O
thought	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Gambier	O
.	O
If	O
Pepper	O
had	O
been	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
at	O
13	O
d.	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
thought	O
it	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
a	O
large	O
profit	O
on	O
this	O
Pepper	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Gambier	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Wholesale	O
Way	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
half-penny	O
per	O
lb	O
I	O
believe	O
all	O
the	O
Year	O
round	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
is	O
generally	O
allowed	O
for	O
the	O
Tare	O
of	O
each	O
Bag	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Gambier	O
.	O
The	O
Company	O
allow	O
15	O
lb	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Tare	O
of	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
112	O
lb	O
.	O
for	O
a	O
Bag	O
of	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
Tare	O
is	O
too	O
much	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Suppose	O
the	O
Pepper	O
had	O
been	O
damaged	O
,	O
or	O
put	O
into	O
foul	O
Bags	O
,	O
what	O
then	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Gambier	O
.	O
Damaged	O
Pepper	O
will	O
not	O
bear	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
good	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
;	O
but	O
putting	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
Bag	O
into	O
another	O
will	O
not	O
hurt	O
it	O
,	O
provided	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
any	O
Wet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pepper	O
be	O
found	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Waste	O
and	O
Dirt	O
in	O
this	O
Pepper	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Gambier	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
last	O
Sale	O
,	O
5400	O
Bags	O
of	O
Pepper	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
those	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
116	O
Bags	O
of	O
Dust	O
;	O
but	O
these	O
Bags	O
of	O
Dust	O
do	O
not	O
weigh	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
Bags	O
of	O
Pepper	O
,	O
although	O
they	O
are	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Size	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Scarborough	O
Pepper	O
in	O
39	O
,	O
after	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
sitted	O
sold	O
for	O
about	O
11	O
d.	O
Farthing	O
to	O
3	O
8ths	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
amount	O
to	O
about	O
14	O
d	O
,	O
Farthing	O
Duty	O
paid	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Torin	O
sold	O
Pepper	O
after	O
the	O
Company	O
's	O
Sale	O
in	O
Sept.	O
was	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
for	O
11	O
d.	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
Buyer	O
paid	O
the	O
Duty	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
never	O
buy	O
any	O
but	O
for	O
Exportation	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
here	O
urg	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Defendant	O
,	O
that	O
Oliver	O
in	O
Point	O
of	O
Law	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
deem	O
'd	O
a	O
Principal	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
Defendant	O
to	O
Trial	O
,	O
Burges	O
and	O
Robinson	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
principally	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
stealing	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
should	O
first	O
have	O
been	O
convicted	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
Defence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
Burges	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
believ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
China	O
Bowls	O
and	O
Handkerchiefs	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
Pepper	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
run	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
should	O
have	O
given	O
1	O
s.	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
Servants	O
will	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
full	O
of	O
Dust	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
fore	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
clean	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
again	O
for	O
13	O
d.	O
Half-penny	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Pepper	O
brought	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
it	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
publick	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
clean	O
'd	O
;	O
-	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
vast	O
many	O
Stones	O
and	O
Dirt	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
private	O
Transaction	O
?	O
The	O
Witness	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
Bag	O
weigh	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
emptied	O
into	O
some	O
Casks	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
;	O
-	O
the	O
Shop	O
was	O
not	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
neither	O
fore	O
Door	O
,	O
nor	O
back	O
Door	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
this	O
Door	O
a	O
common	O
Passage	O
for	O
Goods	O
?	O
The	O
Witness	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
we	O
ship	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
receive	O
by	O
Water	O
come	O
to	O
this	O
Door	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Burges	O
bring	O
these	O
Bags	O
?	O
The	O
Witness	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
who	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Does	O
your	O
Brother	O
use	O
to	O
receive	O
Goods	O
in	O
at	O
this	O
Door	O
,	O
at	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
?	O
The	O
Witness	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Tide	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
Bags	O
those	O
were	O
which	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
-	O
are	O
they	O
your	O
Brother	O
's	O
?	O
The	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Mark	O
on	O
them	O
?	O
Alice	B-pers
Obermore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
this	O
Pepper	O
was	O
brought	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
what	O
Time	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
Door	O
,	O
-	O
as	O
publickly	O
as	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
it	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
and	O
clean	O
'd	O
for	O
Sale	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
weigh	O
'd	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
Weight	O
of	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
much	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
weigh	O
'd	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
large	O
Goods	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
Punch	O
carry	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
joining	O
to	O
the	O
publick	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
paid	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
Money	O
was	O
there	O
paid	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
how	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
paid	O
down	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
done	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
Manner	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
publick	O
as	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
Dealings	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Burges	O
and	O
Oliver	O
there	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
Clowes	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Who	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
much	O
Notice	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
Persons	O
partook	O
of	O
the	O
Punch	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
remember	O
only	O
Burges	O
and	O
Oliver	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
your	O
Master	O
's	O
giving	O
a	O
Dram	O
to	O
any	O
Body	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
The	O
Lad	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
Master	O
did	O
ask	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
Oliver	O
sent	O
him	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
your	O
Master	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
for	O
the	O
Pepper	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
A	O
Shilling	O
a	O
Pound	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
whether	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
fore	O
Shop	O
,	O
a	O
back	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Room	O
between	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Door	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Air	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
wide	O
open	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
the	O
Casks	O
stand	O
which	O
this	O
Pepper	O
was	O
emptied	O
into	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
Shop	O
or	O
the	O
back	O
Shop	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
fore	O
Shop	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
weigh	O
'd	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
back	O
Shop	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
great	O
Scales	O
beside	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
Shop	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
that	O
will	O
weigh	O
100	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
Goods	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
Master	O
's	O
Servants	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
weighing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
?	O
Obermore	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
nor	O
Journeyman	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
serve	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
serve	O
when	O
my	O
Brother	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
this	O
Pepper	O
for	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
d.	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Ounce	O
for	O
five	O
Farthings	O
,	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
clean	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marlow	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
Pepper	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
in	O
September	O
was	O
Twelve-months	O
,	O
from	O
10	O
d	O
78ths	O
,	O
to	O
11	O
d.	O
1	O
8th	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
6	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
per	O
Cent	O
.	O
Discount	O
;	O
which	O
reduces	O
the	O
price	O
to	O
10	O
d.	O
Farthing	O
;	O
the	O
Duty	O
is	O
near	O
a	O
Groat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
,	O
Suppose	O
you	O
should	O
buy	O
Pepper	O
unclean	O
'd	O
,	O
would	O
you	O
give	O
1	O
s.	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Marlow	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
buy	O
any	O
unclean	O
'd	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
What	O
would	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
a	O
Person	O
brought	O
you	O
Pepper	O
for	O
12	O
d	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marlow	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
worth	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
I	O
speak	O
Sir	O
,	O
of	O
that	O
Pepper	O
in	O
Sept.	O
Sale	O
,	O
39	O
,	O
what	O
should	O
you	O
think	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
offer	O
'd	O
you	O
for	O
1	O
s	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marlow	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
run	O
,	O
or	O
-	O
Councel	O
.	O
Or	O
what	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Marlow	O
.	O
Or	O
otherwise	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
This	O
Pepper	O
was	O
weigh	O
'd	O
;	O
could	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
be	O
a	O
Judge	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
15	O
d.	O
or	O
12	O
d.	O
per	O
lb	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marlow	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
Dealer	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
Goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shippey	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Years	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
fair	O
Dealer	O
.	O
Mr.	O
SHERIFF	O
Marshall	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
his	O
Character	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
Question	O
.	O
Mr	O
Roberts	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Camden	O
,	O
Mr.	O
White	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Neaves	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Burnet	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pool	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Ridout	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Earle	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Windsor	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Priestly	O
,	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
The	O
Jury	O
withdrew	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
short	O
Stay	O
,	O
return	O
'd	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
acquitted	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
Indictment	O
.	O
39.	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
Nov.	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40	O
Ann	B-pers
Caffey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Damask	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Scarlet	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
,	O
October	O
2	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
41.	O
James	B-pers
Roice	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Nov.	O
in	O
the	O
twelth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
William	B-pers
III	I-pers
.	O
at	O
South	O
Mims	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
Marry	O
Ann	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
,	O
to	O
Wife	O
took	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
full	O
Life	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Jorddan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
above	O
80	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
remember	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
away	O
Ann	O
Mason	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
at	O
South	O
Mims	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Parson	O
on	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
whole	O
Ceremony	O
was	O
said	O
over	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mason	O
afterwards	O
lived	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
have	O
lived	O
very	O
well	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
a	O
Rascal	O
.	O
They	O
lived	O
together	O
10	O
Years	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
alive	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
just	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
whom	O
I	O
gave	O
away	O
40	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
South	O
Mims	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Wroth	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
kis	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
his	O
Wife	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
41.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Waitcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boots	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
20	O
,	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
42	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Learner	O
Saddles	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Saddle	O
Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Sasiogales	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Leather	O
Bridle	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Leather	O
Saddle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Srrups	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Vandrey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
November	O
19	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
43.	O
Ann	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
Pillowbiers	O
,	O
4	O
Bed-Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
Brass-pot	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Headly	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
October	O
21	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
44.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Apron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Muslin	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Harry	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Nov.	O
2	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
45.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Blankets	O
'	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Crape	O
Gown	O
,	O
5	O
Linnen	O
Shifts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Crisley	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
19	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
46.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Flexman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Coffee-pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
2	O
pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
26	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
47	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
2	O
linnen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
11	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
48.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
2	O
silver	O
Watches	O
,	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Blind	I-pers
,	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Novem	O
.	O
20	O
,	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
49.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dicky	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Agar	I-pers
,	O
from	O
her	O
Person	O
,	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
50.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Book	O
,	O
called	O
Histories	O
and	O
Novels	O
by	O
the	O
late	O
Ingenious	O
Mrs.	O
Behn	O
,	O
1	O
other	O
Book	O
called	O
,	O
Letters	O
from	O
a	O
Persian	O
at	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Friend	O
at	O
Ispahan	O
,	O
1	O
other	O
Book	O
called	O
,	O
A	O
Journey	O
from	O
Aleppo	O
to	O
Damascus	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Description	O
of	O
those	O
two	O
Capital	O
Cities	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
neighbouring	O
Parts	O
of	O
Syria	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roland	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
51.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dunstan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
,	O
Oct	O
17	O
.	O
Mr	O
Knowles	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
up	O
Stairs	O
by	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
Chick	O
Lane	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
half	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confessed	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
52	O
,	O
53.	O
Avery	B-pers
Joice	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
Geese	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Thomlinson	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
30	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
54	O
,	O
55.	O
Francis	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
,	O
16	O
Linnen	O
Caps	O
,	O
3	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
1	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
1	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Breeches	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hannam	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
20	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Simmonds	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fuller	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
56.	O
John	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Mary	B-pers
Ludford	I-pers
,	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
being	O
living	O
,	O
Aug.26	O
.	O
Bridget	O
Parker	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Register	O
at	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
in	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
Woman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Wedding	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
this	O
Certificate	O
from	O
the	O
Fleet	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
read.	O
``	O
John	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
married	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Poole	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
``	O
two	B-place
Fighting	I-place
Cocks	I-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
middle	I-place
of	I-place
Fleet-Lane	I-place
,	O
``	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Ceremonies	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
``	O
England	O
;	O
as	O
appears	O
by	O
the	O
Register	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
``	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Picket	I-pers
.	O
``	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Minister	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
legal	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
57	O
,	O
58.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
Piece	O
,	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Challoner	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
Oct.	O
22	O
.	O
Challoner	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
these	O
two	O
Women	O
near	O
Catherine-Street	O
End	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
Tavern	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
among	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Eagle-Court	B-place
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Liquor	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
drink	O
any	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
dirty	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
but	O
just	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
Wood	O
very	O
busy	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Money	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
but	O
Wood	O
swore	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
Credit	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
for	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
my	O
Purse	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
were	O
brought	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
of	O
Riley	O
's	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
they	O
confessed	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
never	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
