TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
14th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1741	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XLI	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
DANIEL	B-pers
LAMBERT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
LEE	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holder	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eyles	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Tuckwell	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gooding	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Tomlin	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Blakesley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Woolley	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lightonhouse	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Filmore	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hayman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hammerton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Shimell	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
George	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew-Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
(	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fernley	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
Thirty-six	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rash	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Rash	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fernley	I-pers
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Chambers	O
in	O
Furnival's-Inn	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
into	O
a	O
Closet	O
with	O
Glass	O
Doors	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Dining-Room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
Chest	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
Servant	O
Simon	B-pers
Kidder	I-pers
said	O
there	O
was	O
Money	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
Fernley	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
threatned	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
persisted	O
in	O
his	O
Intention	O
.	O
Fernley	O
not	O
regarding	O
that	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Bureau	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
2	O
Keys	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Glass	O
Doors	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Wire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
went	O
half	O
down	O
the	O
Stain	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
hoping	O
by	O
that	O
Mean	O
to	O
frighten	O
Feruley	O
and	O
make	O
him	O
desist	O
from	O
his	O
Design	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Glass	O
Doors	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Feruley	O
take	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
a	O
Nail	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
Handle	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
looking	O
about	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Chest	O
in	O
a	O
China	O
Bason	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
bent	O
the	O
Pipe	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
'till	O
he	O
had	O
straiten	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
opened	O
the	O
Chest	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
threatning	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
saw	O
that	O
Feruley	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chest	O
a	O
Canvass-bag	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
telling	O
the	O
Money	O
over	O
on	O
a	O
green	O
Table	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
desist	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
partake	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
him	O
hard	O
on	O
his	O
Refusal	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
through	O
many	O
Persuasions	O
he	O
was	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
to	O
take	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Thirty-six	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
,	O
one	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
desired	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Money	O
into	O
the	O
Bag	O
again	O
,	O
fearing	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
discovered	O
by	O
a	O
Medal	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
as	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Share	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
designed	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Bag	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Hurry	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
Brass	O
Porte-Bells	O
Pocket-piece	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
Minutes	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
perceiving	O
his	O
Mistake	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
Pocket-piece	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
Medal	O
into	O
the	O
Bag	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
likewise	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Money	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
lodged	O
with	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
whose	O
Hands	O
I	O
found	O
2	O
Hangers	O
,	O
3	O
Thirty-six	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
remained	O
unspent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Servant	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Mr	O
.	O
Rash	O
.	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Hackney-writer	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Service	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Rash	O
informing	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
lavish	O
in	O
spending	O
their	O
Money	O
at	O
Furnival's-Inn-Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
giving	O
us	O
sufficient	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
make	O
this	O
Confession	O
of	O
which	O
Mr	O
.	O
Rash	O
has	O
given	O
an	O
Account	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
.	O
Some	O
Time	O
in	O
last	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Fernley	O
left	O
about	O
20	O
l.	O
in	O
my	O
Hands	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
this	O
Money	O
they	O
bought	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
Watches	O
and	O
Hangers	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
every	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
3	O
Thirty-six	O
Shilling	O
Pieces	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
which	O
they	O
left	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
last	O
Time	O
they	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
down	O
his	O
Watch	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
Fernley	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sharew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Lad	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
now	O
about	O
14	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
wronged	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
fuddled	O
or	O
concerned	O
in	O
Liquor	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Harbin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
8	O
Years	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
Lad	O
both	O
to	O
himself	O
and	O
his	O
Parents	O
.	O
His	O
Father	O
was	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
as	O
ever	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peele	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
no	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mayes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
Fellow-Clerk	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
exceeding	O
well	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
2.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Brass	O
Cups	O
and	O
2	O
Brass	O
Nozzels	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
Branch	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Church-Wardens	B-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Parish	I-pers
of	I-pers
St.	I-pers
Martin	I-pers
in	I-pers
the	I-pers
Fields	I-pers
,	O
April	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
3.	O
Mary	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
Linen-Frock	O
,	O
3	O
Linen	O
Napkins	O
,	O
4	O
Linen	O
Caps	O
,	O
2	O
Silk	O
Hoods	O
,	O
1	O
Linen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Quartern	O
Loaf	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Silk	O
Ribbons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
March	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Jane	B-pers
(	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
)	I-pers
Danvers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
4	O
Diaper	O
Table-Cloths	O
,	O
5	O
Diaper	O
Napkins	O
,	O
2	O
Linen-Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Damask-Clouts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Mary	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen-Shirt	O
,	O
2	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
a	O
Linen-Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Saxey	I-pers
;	O
a	O
Linen-Apron	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Goble	I-pers
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
William	B-pers
Ostrow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
old	O
Iron	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
John	B-pers
Car	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Finchley	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Peace	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
Fear	O
and	O
Danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
put	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ingram	O
.	O
The	O
Person	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
met	O
me	O
on	O
Finchley-Common	B-place
;	O
he	O
presented	O
a	O
Pistol	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
stand	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Villain	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
shoot	O
me	O
!	O
And	O
that	O
Moment	O
he	O
fired	O
his	O
Pistol	O
and	O
shot	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
gave	O
him	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
demanded	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
Rascal	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
carry	O
any	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Ingram	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
be	O
thick	O
of	O
hearing	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
stand	O
!	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Mind	O
to	O
be	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
together	O
we	O
almost	O
shouldered	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
saying	O
,	O
You	O
Villain	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
shoot	O
me	O
!	O
He	O
shot	O
my	O
Eye	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
for	O
3	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
lost	O
one	O
Eye	O
intirely	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
On	O
your	O
Oath	O
am	O
I	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Ingram	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Person	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Part	O
of	O
Finchley-Common	O
was	O
this	O
done	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Ingram	O
.	O
Between	O
the	O
five	O
Mile	O
Tree	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Ballast	O
,	O
which	O
lies	O
just	O
by	O
a	O
Path	O
that	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
Hog-Market	O
.	O
-	O
Bigg	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
;	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turn	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Ingram	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ingram	O
's	O
Face	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
made	O
him	O
shoot	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
?	O
His	O
Reply	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
served	O
you	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
-	O
Bigg	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
about	O
Sun-set	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ingram	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Sun	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
set	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
All	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
-	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Work	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drinking	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
3	O
Horseshoes	O
on	O
Finchley-Common	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
that	O
Man	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
,	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Car	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
shot	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Hill	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
went	O
off	O
bidding	O
the	O
Man	O
good	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
hurt	O
a	O
Brother	O
Trade	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
down	O
a	O
Bottom	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Horse	O
running	O
against	O
a	O
Post	O
at	O
Brown's-Well	O
he	O
dropped	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Heels	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
Horse	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Lewsome	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
only	O
hearing	O
a	O
Hue	O
and	O
Cry	O
of	O
a	O
Highwayman	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
quitted	O
his	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Norvey	I-pers
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
Time	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
him	O
on	O
Bush	O
Causeway	O
:	O
We	O
let	O
him	O
pass	O
by	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Evers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
twice	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Coachman	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shuter	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
,	O
of	O
Tottenham	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
6	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
that	O
Time	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Chair-Carrier	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
shoed	O
Horses	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
thought	O
him	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
8.	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Door	O
Glass	O
of	O
a	O
Chariot	O
Value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
.	O
March	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
9.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
after	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
1731	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Leaden	O
Pipe	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
did	O
steal	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lesborough	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
tanned	O
Calves	O
Skins	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wiltshire	I-pers
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tate	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Linen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wigans	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Lodging	O
let	O
by	O
Contract	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Tate	O
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hambler	I-pers
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Linen	O
Shifts	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
1	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
Headclothes	O
laced	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
2	O
Linen	O
Caps	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Linen	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Towels	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
d.	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Aprons	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
1	O
half	O
Guinea	O
and	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hambler	O
,	O
March	O
11	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hambler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Officer	O
of	O
the	O
Marshal	O
's	O
Court	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
arrest	O
a	O
Person	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
Harry	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
dismissed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
at	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
Time	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
Window	O
wide	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
taken	O
out	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
any	O
Person	O
in	O
your	O
House	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Hambler	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
this	O
Condition	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
Wife	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
Hanger	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
a	O
Box	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
about	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
disorderly	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
a	O
tall	O
thin	O
Man	O
ran	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
and	O
dropp	O
'd	O
a	O
Cap	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Shirts	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bed	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Elephant	O
and	O
Castle	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
another	O
Alehouse	O
and	O
delivered	O
me	O
some	O
more	O
of	O
my	O
Things	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
and	O
imagining	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
Stockings	O
on	O
his	O
Legs	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
they	O
were	O
darred	O
in	O
the	O
Toe	O
with	O
light	O
grey	O
Worsted	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
their	O
being	O
pulled	O
off	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hambler	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
parted	O
from	O
us	O
in	O
Redlion-street	O
,	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
10	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
Sheer-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
the	O
Ground-Floor	O
wide	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
washing	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
wet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
this	O
Window	O
fastened	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Hambler	I-pers
.	O
There	O
is	O
an	O
Iron	O
Masp	O
to	O
fasten	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Window	O
Shutters	O
were	O
not	O
put	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
was	O
just	O
against	O
the	O
Hasp	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Window	O
shut	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Hambler	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
it	O
was	O
wide	O
open	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Quarters	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Elephant	O
and	O
Castle	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
he	O
ran	O
backwards	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
Hambler	O
's	O
Shirts	O
on	O
his	O
Bed	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
this	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bear	O
and	O
Ragged	O
staff	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
delivered	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
These	O
Stockings	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Legs	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
Hambler	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Apron	O
for	O
me	O
!	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
these	O
Things	O
from	O
a	O
Woman	O
man	O
that	O
kept	O
him	O
Company	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Camp	O
,	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
her	O
detaining	O
some	O
white	O
Stockings	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
wash	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
between	O
Ludgate-Hill	O
and	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Apron	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
wet	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hambler	O
.	O
I	O
washed	O
this	O
very	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
wet	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
-	O
Cooper	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
parted	O
with	O
Hambler	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Red-Lion	O
Street	O
,	O
Goodmans	O
Fields	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
stay	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
Hambler	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
staid	O
'till	O
near	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
Night	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
Diversion	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
arrest	O
some	O
Body	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
my	O
Foot	O
struck	O
against	O
this	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
Home	O
.	O
Susan	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
that	O
Rhodes	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
Rhodes	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Clothes	O
and	O
Money	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hinton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
2	O
Years	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Haines	O
a	O
Printer	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Haines	O
asked	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Presence	O
what	O
he	O
designed	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
Hambler	O
replied	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
Tyburn-ticket	O
which	O
is	O
worth	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Reward	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
Equivalent	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
our	O
Regiment	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
was	O
3	O
Weeks	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
my	O
Officer	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
5	O
l.	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Bill	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
hurt	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Hambler	O
's	O
Brother	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
take	O
Hambler	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
himself	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
these	O
2	O
Years	O
and	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
dishonest	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
his	O
Mis-conduct	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
13.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
Stable	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Master	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wardens	I-pers
and	I-pers
Commonalty	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Mystery	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Grocery	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
the	I-pers
House	I-pers
of	I-pers
Langley-Hill	I-pers
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Charles	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Phebe	B-pers
Bredey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Bredey	I-pers
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Demee	I-pers
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
16.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Macmanus	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Christopher	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Rule	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Compasses	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
February	O
7	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Peacock	O
from	O
Newington	B-place
to	O
Shore-ditch	B-place
,	O
and	O
about	O
150	O
Yards	O
on	O
this	O
Side	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
passed	O
us	O
both	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
some	O
By-Word	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
a	O
Pistol	O
against	O
my	O
Face	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
turned	O
myself	O
about	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
snapped	O
his	O
Pistol	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
damn	O
'd	O
it	O
because	O
it	O
missed	O
Fire	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
he	O
was	O
welcome	O
to	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
a	O
Rule	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Compasses	O
,	O
a	O
Socket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pencil	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
searching	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Fellow	O
that	O
cut	O
Mr.	O
Peacock	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
holding	O
up	O
my	O
Cane	O
to	O
defend	O
myself	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
it	O
almost	O
asunder	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Instrument	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
wounded	O
Peacock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
Ditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
hazy	O
Night	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
Moon-light	O
enough	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
them	O
50	O
Yards	O
after	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Peacock	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
dead	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Birt	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Glanville	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
in	O
Wheeler	O
Street	O
,	O
Spittle-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kennely	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
drinking	O
there	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
?	O
Birt	O
.	O
Because	O
they	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
Fore-Room	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
7	O
by	O
Glanville	O
's	O
Dial	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
at	O
least	O
3	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
to	O
Wheeler	O
Street	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kennely	I-pers
whom	O
I	O
kept	O
Company	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Glanville	O
's	O
in	O
Wheeler	O
Street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
at	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
not	O
a	O
married	O
Woman	O
?	O
Burn	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Husband	O
is	O
gone	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
kept	O
with	O
Kennely	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
till	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
every	O
Time	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
for	O
your	O
Living	O
?	O
Burn	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
every	O
Thing	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
get	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
an	O
honest	O
Livelihood	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Burn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wheeler-Street	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
Room-Keeper	O
there	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
taking	O
an	O
Oath	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
?	O
Burn	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
2	O
Oaths	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
swear	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Kennely	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
him	O
?	O
Burn	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
so	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Kennely	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
Justice	O
you	O
had	O
given	O
in	O
a	O
wrong	O
Name	O
?	O
Burn	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
Woman	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
Burn	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
kept	O
with	O
Kennely	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
one	O
Child	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
Weston	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
Countrywoman	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Weston	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
within	O
the	O
Sound	O
of	O
Bow-Bell	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
4	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
honest	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
trusted	O
him	O
by	O
himself	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
Lead	O
and	O
Bags	O
of	O
Nails	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
employed	O
him	O
these	O
8	O
Months	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
He	O
worked	O
at	O
Thread-making	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
attended	O
at	O
Stock's-Market	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
him	O
in	O
bringing	O
Goods	O
Home	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Markets	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
Thing	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
Charge	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
civil	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
employed	O
him	O
for	O
these	O
6	O
Months	O
?	O
Conyers	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chipperfield	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Frances	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
swore	O
that	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
7	O
till	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Landlord	O
Glanville	O
swore	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
,	O
Burn	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Husband	O
is	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
Kennely	O
my	O
Husband	O
because	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
with	O
Child	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Peacock	O
just	O
before	O
this	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
with	O
them	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
8	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
brought	O
Peacock	O
Home	O
wounded	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
Zacchens	O
Bourne	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Beadle	O
of	O
Aldgate	O
Parish	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
was	O
a	O
Housekeeper	O
with	O
us	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
fair	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
17.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cock	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
Hens	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
March	O
29th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18	O
.	O
19.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mackenny	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Leveret	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
300	O
Wt	O
.	O
of	O
Rope	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bramston	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
George	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1000	O
Wt	O
.	O
of	O
Ropes	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Eyres	I-pers
,	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
21.	O
Peter	B-pers
Beardsley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
George	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1000	O
Wt	O
.	O
of	O
Ropes	O
Value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Eyres	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Beardsley	O
afterwards	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
did	O
receive	O
and	O
have	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
*	O
Timothy	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Teddy	I-pers
Brian	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
David	B-pers
Patten	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cane	O
with	O
a	O
Gold	O
Head	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
David	B-pers
Patten	I-pers
,	O
November	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
Sessions	O
of	O
stealing	O
Goods	O
Value	O
15	O
s.	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Transportation	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Patten	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
1739	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
into	O
Bow-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
under	O
the	O
Arch	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
Earl	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
of	O
my	O
Head	O
which	O
sunk	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
Knee	O
:	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
rise	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
throw	O
up	O
my	O
Hands	O
to	O
defend	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
rose	O
I	O
received	O
several	O
other	O
Blows	O
which	O
sunk	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
received	O
a	O
Blow	O
with	O
something	O
very	O
heavy	O
,	O
which	O
cut	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Scull	O
:	O
Upon	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Sweep	O
with	O
my	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
it	O
was	O
snatched	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
draw	O
my	O
Sword	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Right-hand	O
was	O
so	O
disabled	O
by	O
warding	O
off	O
the	O
Blows	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
draw	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
Men	O
run	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
Bow-Street	O
and	O
told	O
some	O
Chairmen	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
;	O
they	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
me	O
back	O
my	O
Hat	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
carried	O
off	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
1739	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Teddy	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
,	O
*	O
John	O
Lincham	O
who	O
is	O
executed	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
hump	O
backed	O
little	O
Boy	O
who	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	O
of	O
Gaunt	O
went	O
out	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Lambert	O
's	O
in	O
Parcer	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
round	O
Covent-Garden	O
'till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Earl	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Patten	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bludgeon	O
which	O
he	O
concealed	O
under	O
the	O
Lining	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
made	O
a	O
Defence	O
with	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
he	O
fell	O
by	O
a	O
Blow	O
or	O
a	O
Slip	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatched	O
the	O
Cane	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
attempting	O
to	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
who	O
were	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
Lambert	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
her	O
telling	O
us	O
the	O
Cane	O
was	O
not	O
Gold	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
washed	O
over	O
,	O
we	O
sold	O
it	O
her	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
Money	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
Sessions	O
Block	O
N	B-pers
.	I-pers
2	O
,	O
1740	O
,	O
pag	O
.	O
76	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
Night	O
,	O
besides	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
Mr.	O
Patten	O
is	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Patten	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Moon	O
was	O
under	O
a	O
Cloud	O
;	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Archand	O
I	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Shade	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
attacked	O
me	O
.	O
Thompson	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Lamp	O
which	O
strikes	O
directly	O
into	O
the	O
Arch	O
,	O
besides	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
except	O
John	O
of	O
Gaunt	O
lodged	O
at	O
Lambert	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Bed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
tell	O
what	O
particular	O
Marks	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Thompson	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
this	O
Thing	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Sore	O
on	O
his	O
Lip	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
scrape	O
Lint	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Transports	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
picked	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
James	B-pers
Macdonnel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
5	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
his	O
Uncle	O
Patrick	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
in	O
May-Street	O
,	O
Ireland	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Irishman	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
above	O
5	O
Months	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
'till	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
Consinement	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
within	O
these	O
twelve	O
Months	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Ireland	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
come	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Ireland	O
at	O
his	O
Step-Father	O
's	O
Burial	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
Ireland	O
last	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
November	O
before	O
that	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
rightly	O
tell	O
the	O
Month	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
quite	O
5	O
Months	O
in	O
this	O
Town	O
yet	O
.	O
C.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
you	O
left	O
Ireland	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
a	O
Week	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
every	O
Day	O
.	O
C.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
you	O
came	O
away	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
there	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
Ireland	O
these	O
6	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
settled	O
Time	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
Step-Father	O
's	O
Burial	O
November	O
was	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
C.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
him	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Teddy	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
that	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
Timothy	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
working	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Ireland	O
every	O
Week	O
of	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
there	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
Reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
Ireland	O
?	O
Macdonnel	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
5	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
rightly	O
tell	O
when	O
I	O
last	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Twisten	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Castle-Street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
May-Street	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
Months	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
Patrick	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
's	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Uncle	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
away	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
Witness	O
,	O
Macdonnel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
both	O
came	O
over	O
from	O
Ireland	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
there	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
lived	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
every	O
Day	O
,	O
especially	O
every	O
Sunday	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
called	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
Name	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Ivory	I-pers
.	O
I	O
worked	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
Years	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
Name	O
than	O
Burn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
6	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
Night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
Shoes	O
were	O
full	O
of	O
Country	O
Dirt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stir	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
tired	O
:	O
-	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
here	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Night	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
England	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
We	O
desire	O
Thompson	O
may	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Cane	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
himself	O
brought	O
it	O
into	O
Lambert	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
she	O
persuaded	O
us	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Gold	O
,	O
and	O
Lincham	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
Smith	O
,	O
Lincham	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
Eighteen	O
Pence	O
a	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
of	O
Gaunt	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
withdrew	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
their	O
Verdict	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
returned	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
Guilty	O
.	O
23.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Macmanus	I-pers
,	O
was	O
again	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Maccleaver	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
George	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Hanger	O
made	O
of	O
Iron	O
and	O
Steel	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
which	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
fore	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Peacock	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
cut	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
seven	O
Inches	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Month	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Peacock	O
languished	O
and	O
languishing	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Leonard-Shoreditch	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Andrew	B-pers
Macmanus	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Maccleaver	I-pers
were	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
,	O
comforting	O
and	O
maintaining	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Robinson	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
to	O
commit	O
and	O
do	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
in	O
his	O
former	O
Trial	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
Defect	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
24.	O
George	B-pers
Hough	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
42	O
Pair	O
of	O
Boy	O
's	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
25	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
February	O
16	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
rather	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Breach	O
of	O
Trust	O
than	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gold-Bead	O
Necklace	O
,	O
Value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Gold-Locket	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
March	O
6	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26	O
,	O
27.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Esther	B-pers
(	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
)	I-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
grey	O
Bob	O
Peruke	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Linen-Pockets	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
7	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Snuffers	O
and	O
a	O
Stand	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Dredging	O
Box	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Legborn	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
April	O
3	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
William	B-pers
Boot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
wicked	O
disposed	O
Person	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
1734	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
March	O
17	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
offensive	O
Weapon	O
,	O
or	O
Wooden	O
Truncheon	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
on	O
George	B-pers
Long	I-pers
unlawfully	O
,	O
maliciously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
with	O
Intent	O
the	O
Monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Long	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
last	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Newgate	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Gateway	O
which	O
comes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hospital	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rushed	O
out	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
this	O
Stick	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
:	O
On	O
my	O
receiving	O
this	O
Blow	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
backwards	O
against	O
some	O
Shutters	O
of	O
a	O
Corner	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seized	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
Hip	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
recovered	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
round	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Collar	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
?	O
He	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
Answer	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
cursing	O
me	O
in	O
an	O
inward	O
Manner	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
struggled	O
and	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
crying	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
as	O
loud	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
Ivy-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Doors	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
after	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Collar	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
Waist	O
;	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
touch	O
him	O
?	O
Long	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
with	O
both	O
Hands	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
ask	O
for	O
any	O
Money	O
?	O
Long	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
no	O
Provocation	O
to	O
strike	O
you	O
?	O
Long	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
struck	O
him	O
'till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Satterthat	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Ivy-Lane	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
Body	O
cry	O
stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
Staff	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
stepped	O
into	O
this	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
ran	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
my	O
Head	O
in	O
a	O
desperate	O
Manner	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Watchman	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cruiksbank	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
8	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Character	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
served	O
the	O
latter	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Time	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
an	O
exceeding	O
good	O
Servant	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
his	O
Honesty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
constantly	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
ill	O
of	O
his	O
Character	O
before	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Frewen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Misbehaviour	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Liquor	O
when	O
he	O
attacked	O
you	O
.	O
Long	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29	O
,	O
30	O
,	O
31.	O
Jane	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
And	O
Elisha	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Flora	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
All	O
acquitted	O
.	O
30.	O
Ann	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Linen	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
China	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
,	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31	O
Tobias	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Aaron	B-pers
Hinds	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
32.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Loosedale	I-pers
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
James	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
with	O
another	O
Person	O
unknown	O
)	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
French	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
French	O
to	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Indictment	O
farther	O
charged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Castle	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
aforesaid	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
with	O
Intent	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
French	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
having	O
opened	O
the	O
Indictment	O
and	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wiat	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mr.	O
French	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Plumb-tree	B-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
latched	O
the	O
Door	O
fast	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
What	O
fastening	O
is	O
there	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
?	O
Wiat	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
an	O
Iron	O
Latch	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
shut	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
and	O
pushed	O
against	O
it	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
French	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Plumb-tree	O
Court	O
,	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Maid	O
were	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
she	O
sat	O
next	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
next	O
the	O
Chimney	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
sat	O
thus	O
,	O
somebody	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Door	O
with	O
their	O
Knuckles	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Briton	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
burst	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
violently	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
old	O
Dog	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
your	O
Business	O
for	O
you	O
:	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
more	O
ado	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
put	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
about	O
my	O
Throat	O
,	O
to	O
throttle	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
struggled	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
Murder	O
!	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Body	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
throttled	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
across	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Grate	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Head	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
himself	O
on	O
me	O
and	O
clapped	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
on	O
my	O
Mouth	O
to	O
stop	O
my	O
Breath	O
.	O
I	O
kicked	O
with	O
my	O
Feet	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
his	O
Hold	O
from	O
my	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
cried	O
Murder	O
twice	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
put	O
his	O
Hands	O
on	O
my	O
Mouth	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
suffocated	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
swearing	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
least	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
certainly	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
across	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
Condition	O
I	O
continued	O
'till	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
being	O
alarmed	O
at	O
the	O
Noise	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
with	O
him	O
some	O
Time	O
ago	O
;	O
and	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
threaten	O
to	O
serve	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Copy	O
of	O
a	O
Writ	O
for	O
Money	O
which	O
I	O
owed	O
him	O
?	O
French	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
about	O
7	O
Weeks	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
owed	O
me	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
glad	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
propose	O
to	O
pay	O
you	O
some	O
Money	O
that	O
Night	O
?	O
French	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
mentioned	O
a	O
Word	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
not	O
have	O
seen	O
my	O
Face	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
Light	O
?	O
French	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
dark	O
the	O
best	O
Part	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
May	O
not	O
a	O
Person	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
of	O
your	O
outward	O
Door	O
,	O
without	O
your	O
hearing	O
it	O
?	O
French	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
easily	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Table	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
somebody	O
rap	O
at	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
2	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
Passage	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Briton	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Foot	O
stopped	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Moment	O
a	O
Fellow	O
pushed	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
he	O
throttled	O
me	O
and	O
squeezed	O
my	O
Throat	O
all	O
Manner	O
of	O
Ways	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
dead	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
flew	O
on	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
across	O
the	O
Grate	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Fellow	O
used	O
me	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Manner	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
farther	O
Observations	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
?	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
distinguished	O
one	O
Person	O
's	O
Face	O
from	O
another	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
Master	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
?	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Word	O
spoke	O
about	O
Money	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
asked	O
for	O
Briton	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
standing	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
Israel	O
Mitchel	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Work	O
in	O
our	O
Shop	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
rattling	O
in	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Throat	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
the	O
same	O
Noise	O
about	O
a	O
Minute	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
Stick	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
stand	O
with	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Maid	O
standing	O
in	O
a	O
frightful	O
Posture	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
across	O
the	O
Grate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
him	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
on	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Throat	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
Master	O
then	O
?	O
Mitchel	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
lying	O
a	O
cross	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
upon	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Hands	O
on	O
my	O
Masster	O
's	O
Throat	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
still	O
to	O
observe	O
what	O
Motions	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
observe	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
there	O
is	O
in	O
this	O
Stick	O
Upon	O
that	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
beating	O
him	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
my	O
Hands	O
would	O
meet	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
out	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
some	O
Steps	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
recovered	O
himself	O
and	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
Heels	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
possible	O
for	O
People	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
House	O
without	O
your	O
hearing	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Mitchel	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
owed	O
this	O
Man	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threatned	O
to	O
serve	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Copy	O
of	O
a	O
Writ	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Night	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Time	O
.	O
This	O
Maid	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
flew	O
into	O
a	O
violent	O
Passion	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
me	O
grossly	O
before	O
I	O
touched	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
honestly	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
spiteful	O
or	O
malicious	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Public-House	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
3	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
a	O
malicious	O
Temper	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
believe	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
35.	O
John	B-pers
Storer	I-pers
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
4	O
Feather	O
Beds	O
,	O
4	O
Bolsters	O
,	O
4	O
Pillows	O
,	O
10	O
Blankets	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Linen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
Box	O
,	O
2	O
Glass	O
Sconces	O
,	O
2	O
Stove-Grates	O
,	O
4	O
Saucepans	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Harrateen	O
Window	O
Curtains	O
,	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
a	O
Pistol	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
Dimity	O
Pockets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
October	O
1	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
September	O
was	O
twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Town	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
Word	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
robbed	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
recovered	O
my	O
Surprise	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
Coach	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
Scullery	O
Window	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Frame	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
I	O
found	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
Locks	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
the	O
Locks	O
were	O
whole	O
,	O
the	O
Doors	O
were	O
split	O
in	O
'peces	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
what	O
Goods	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
missed	O
4	O
Feather	O
Beds	O
,	O
Bolsters	O
and	O
Pillows	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Blankets	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Astley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Broker	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Harp-Alley	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
me	O
2	O
Stove-Grates	O
for	O
Sale	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
suspecting	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
stopped	O
the	O
Grates	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
some	O
People	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
'till	O
now	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Boat	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Fulham	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Glass	O
in	O
a	O
Chest	O
of	O
Drawers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Sconce-Glass	O
under	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
himself	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Davis	O
.	O
This	O
Glass	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
-	O
Lacey	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
Constable	O
of	O
Fulham	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
Accordingly	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Thing	O
I	O
found	O
was	O
one	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
under	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
this	O
Glass	O
,	O
a	O
Window	O
Curtain	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
or	O
15	O
Blankets	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
in	O
one	O
Place	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
another	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
searched	O
about	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
we	O
perceived	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
demanding	O
an	O
Entrance	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
Corn	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Poker	O
,	O
threw	O
the	O
Door	O
off	O
the	O
Hooks	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
Bolsters	O
,	O
10	O
Blankets	O
,	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
China	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Feather	O
Beds	O
under	O
the	O
Corn	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Poker	O
to	O
force	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
locked	O
or	O
bolted	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
The	O
Door	O
opens	O
into	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
secured	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
hardly	O
get	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Davis	O
at	O
Fulham	O
.	O
My	O
Daughter	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
some	O
Damage	O
was	O
done	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Davis	O
's	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Garden	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
stepped	O
in	O
and	O
cried	O
Holla	O
!	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
!	O
But	O
no	O
Body	O
answering	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Doors	O
open	O
;	O
a	O
Window	O
Case	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Brick	O
Work	O
and	O
thrown	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Casement	O
lying	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
called	O
my	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
House	O
had	O
been	O
ranshackled	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Jack-smith	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
Man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
me	O
any	O
Harm	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
What	O
Character	O
does	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bear	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
Some	O
Neighbours	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
.	O
Being	O
well	O
informed	O
how	O
this	O
Matter	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
absconded	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
those	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
an	O
Arrest	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Davis	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
his	O
House	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
loose	O
,	O
idle	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
spend	O
whole	O
Days	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Warren	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
his	O
Goods	O
would	O
be	O
seized	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Key	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Car	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
above	O
30	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
made	O
his	O
Accompts	O
good	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Strut	I-pers
.	O
All	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
who	O
is	O
sick	O
about	O
12	O
a	O
Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Warren	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wager	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
30	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
and	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Does	O
he	O
hear	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
Character	O
now	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
30	O
Years	O
ago	O
?	O
Wager	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
away	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
Talk	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
Neighbours	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
and	O
some	O
the	O
reverse	O
.	O
Another	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
rented	O
a	O
Shop	O
of	O
me	O
about	O
3	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
known	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Salkin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Brother-in-law	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hat	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
30	O
Years	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
these	O
3	O
Months	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
Dealings	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
Shoes	O
for	O
my	O
Horses	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
he	O
would	O
drink	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Beer	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Drinking	O
of	O
a	O
Mug	O
of	O
Beer	O
is	O
no	O
criminal	O
Offence	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
no	O
Ill	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36.	O
John	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Woollen-Cloth	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hamman	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Pumps	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Whip	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
,	O
March	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37.	O
George	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Quart	O
Pot	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Plate	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hoggins	I-pers
,	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
38.	O
William	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rance	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Holland	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mumford	I-pers
,	O
February	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
William	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
48	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
Building	O
belonging	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Gold	O
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
42.	O
Mary	B-pers
Provost	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
small	O
Trunk	O
covered	O
with	O
red	O
Leather	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Scoles	I-pers
,	O
April	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43.	O
Penelope	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear-Rings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
and	O
a	O
Calico	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Garshier	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Garshier	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
44.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Chain	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Shoe	O
Buckles	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Stock	O
Buckle	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cross	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Mackenny	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
March	O
11	O
.	O
Mackenny	O
.	O
What	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
is	O
this	O
:	O
It	O
happened	O
some	O
Time	O
in	O
March	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
disguised	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
making	O
Home	O
,	O
this	O
here	O
Prisoner	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
a	O
Linkman	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Sarah	O
Adams	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
capable	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Bed	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
afterwards	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
Goods	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
tell	O
all	O
this	O
?	O
Mackenny	O
.	O
Adams	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
:	O
They	O
waked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Articles	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
House	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Deponent	O
hearing	O
a	O
Watch	O
click	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
satisfied	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
not	O
robbed	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
and	O
Chain	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Brass	O
pair	O
of	O
Scales	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
45.	O
Ann	B-pers
(	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
)	I-pers
Spelman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
5	O
small	O
Leather	O
Bags	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
2	O
Bags	O
made	O
of	O
Linen	O
and	O
Cotton	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
7	O
pound	O
of	O
human	O
Hair	O
,	O
Val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bois	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bois	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Long-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Bags	O
with	O
me	O
full	O
of	O
Hair	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Black	O
Swan-Court	O
,	O
in	O
Golden-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
my	O
Bags	O
were	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
in	O
them	O
brown	O
Hairs	O
,	O
pale	O
Hairs	O
,	O
ash-coloured	O
Hairs	O
,	O
grey	O
brown	O
Hairs	O
and	O
grizzled	O
Hairs	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
about	O
8	O
l.	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
's	O
Time	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Bags	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
give	O
a	O
true	O
Account	O
who	O
put	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
shot	O
down	O
or	O
pushed	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
fall	O
myself	O
.	O
The	O
Hairs	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
fell	O
down	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Boucher	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
your	O
Bags	O
fall	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Bois	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
somebody	O
snatch	O
my	O
Bags	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
as	O
I	O
felt	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Guess	O
,	O
-	O
a	O
rough	O
Guess	O
how	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
the	O
Bags	O
fall	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Bois	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Thought	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
not	O
fuddled	O
?	O
Bois	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Senses	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
swore	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Bags	O
off	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
Bois	O
.	O
What	O
I	O
do	O
I	O
will	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
World	O
whether	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
could	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
was	O
near	O
me	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Murrin	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Business	O
is	O
to	O
buy	O
Hair	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
or	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Long-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
called	O
me	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
into	O
a	O
House	O
and	O
shewed	O
us	O
some	O
Hairs	O
:	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Cobb	O
,	O
a	O
Bird-Cage	O
Maker	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Lane	O
.	O
She	O
offered	O
us	O
3	O
Pieces	O
of	O
dark	O
brown	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
light	O
pale	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
help	O
us	O
to	O
a	O
larger	O
Quantity	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
promised	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
to	O
Stevenson	O
's	O
House	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
Hairs	O
from	O
a	O
Bird-Cage	O
Maker	O
's	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Murrin	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
about	O
to	O
buy	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
us	O
in	O
.	O
She	O
carried	O
us	O
into	O
an	O
upper	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
Bird-Cage	O
Maker	O
's	O
House	O
and	O
shewed	O
us	O
3	O
Pieces	O
of	O
dark	O
Hair	O
and	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
pale	O
Hair	O
,	O
which	O
Bois	O
bought	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
agreeing	O
for	O
the	O
Price	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
some	O
other	O
Hair	O
.	O
She	O
not	O
coming	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
promise	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Hannah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
,	O
I	O
watched	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seeing	O
me	O
promised	O
again	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
more	O
Hair	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
her	O
not	O
coming	O
I	O
searched	O
Cobb	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
fou	O
nd	O
87	O
pieces	O
of	O
Hair	O
and	O
these	O
Bags	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Box	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Room	O
where	O
she	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
3	O
Locks	O
of	O
Hair	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Person	O
here	O
that	O
found	O
these	O
Hairs	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
Hair	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
and	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
.	O
Soon	O
afterwards	O
I	O
read	O
the	O
News-paper	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
advertised	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
my	O
Business	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
brought	O
Stevenson	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Hair	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
3	O
Years	O
in	O
Newgate	O
for	O
Perjury	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
nor	O
when	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Bags	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
Spanish	O
Goods	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
for	O
forfeited	O
Recognizances	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
3	O
pieces	O
of	O
Hair	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cobb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Hair	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
lay	O
by	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
her	O
general	O
Character	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Grigg	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
searched	O
his	O
House	O
for	O
these	O
Hairs	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tipper	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Hair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
46.	O
Arabella	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Copper	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
47.	O
Robert	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
72	O
lb	O
.	O
Wt	O
.	O
of	O
Hog	O
's	O
Fat	O
,	O
Value	O
19	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Lefebuer	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
;	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
48.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tumbleton	I-pers
;	O
March	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
when	O
called	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
49.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Pollard	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Beaty	I-pers
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Prow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Thread	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
51.	O
Ann	B-pers
Shute	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
52	O
.	O
53.	O
Esther	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Breams	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
Burroughs	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Cooper	O
in	O
Chick	O
Lane	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Alley	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
that	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
put	O
it	O
beside	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
54.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Thirty-six	O
Shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
1	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
when	O
called	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
55	O
.	O
56.	O
William	B-pers
Tilly	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Shock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Perryman	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Main	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
several	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
Silver	O
Tobacco-Box	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
a	O
Tobacco	O
Stopper	O
tipped	O
with	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
15	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
June	O
29	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Love's-Court	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
George-Alley	I-place
,	O
by	O
the	O
Ditch	O
Side	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
above	O
2	O
Steps	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
before	O
2	O
Women	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
rifling	O
my	O
pockets	O
;	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
standing	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
Back	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
to	O
guard	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Perryman	O
said	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
I	O
wonder	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
ashamed	O
to	O
pick	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
so	O
:	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Shillings	O
of	O
my	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
Tilly	O
took	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
3	O
Women	O
came	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pulled	O
me	O
in	O
by	O
Force	O
and	O
Violence	O
:	O
then	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
my	O
right	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
my	O
left	O
,	O
while	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
searched	O
my	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Breeches-pockets	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
Tobacco	O
Box	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
3	O
Women	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
staid	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mary	O
White	O
came	O
out	O
by	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
Hat	O
off	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
sooner	O
die	O
,	O
than	O
accept	O
her	O
Invitation	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
took	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
off	O
her	O
Neck	O
and	O
twisted	O
it	O
with	O
both	O
her	O
Hands	O
;	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
begin	O
to	O
fret	O
,	O
imagining	O
they	O
designed	O
to	O
throttle	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
desired	O
William	B-pers
Perryman	I-pers
to	O
get	O
me	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
going	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
57.	O
John	B-pers
Lopton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Morel	I-pers
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
Trunk	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
grey	O
Shagreen	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
green	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
2	O
Linen	O
Shifts	O
,	O
2	O
Linen	O
Aprons	O
,	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
Pocket	O
Book	O
,	O
11	O
Guineas	O
,	O
3	O
Thirty-six	O
Shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
a	O
three	O
pound	O
twelve	O
Shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
Ruth	B-pers
Ragg	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
March	O
11	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Morel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
when	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Ragg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
lost	O
were	O
mine	O
.	O
Jervis	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
2	O
other	O
Men	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
great	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Things	O
,	O
a	O
Drawer	O
of	O
a	O
Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Leather	O
pocket	O
book	O
.	O
They	O
burnt	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
Nut	O
crackers	O
to	O
my	O
Daughter	O
.	O
Ragg	O
.	O
These	O
Nut-crakers	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
Trunk	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Morel	O
's	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lopton	I-pers
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Alexander	B-pers
O	I-pers
Flack	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Lowden	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dearmore	I-pers
,	O
about	O
8	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
short	O
Cloak	O
,	O
a	O
Camlet	O
Bed	O
Curtain	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dearmore	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Lutestring	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Ukely	I-pers
,	O
March	O
2	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ukely	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dearmore	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Maid	O
shut	O
the	O
parlour	O
Windows	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Window	O
pushed	O
up	O
,	O
my	O
Trunk	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
when	O
you	O
missed	O
your	O
Goods	O
?	O
Ukely	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
Time	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Trunk	O
to	O
take	O
something	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
Things	O
were	O
safe	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
parlour	O
Window	O
?	O
Ukely	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
pushed	O
up	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
it	O
would	O
go	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
is	O
this	O
parlour	O
to	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
you	O
was	O
sitting	O
?	O
Ukely	O
.	O
About	O
2	O
Yards	O
or	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brocas	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Night	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Dearmore	O
's	O
House	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
outside	O
Shutters	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
how	O
light	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Brocas	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
one	O
Man	O
's	O
Face	O
from	O
another	O
?	O
Brocas	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
fasten	O
the	O
Windows	O
?	O
Brocas	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
them	O
as	O
close	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
without	O
bolting	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
the	O
Shutters	O
were	O
opened	O
and	O
the	O
Sash	O
pushed	O
up	O
as	O
high	O
it	O
would	O
go	O
.	O
Jervis	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	B-pers
Lowdon	I-pers
and	O
Aleck	O
O-Flack	O
brought	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Things	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
coarse	O
Apron	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
what	O
Things	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
left	O
this	O
Curtain	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dearmore	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Curtain	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
Curtain	O
in	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Dearmore	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
same	O
Evening	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
it	O
?	O
Dearmore	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
one	O
Person	O
's	O
Face	O
from	O
another	O
?	O
Dearmore	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Stair-Case	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
singing	O
Ballads	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Man	O
or	O
Woman	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
do	O
an	O
ill	O
Thing	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Runnington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Misdemeanour	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
58.	O
John	B-pers
Theobalds	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Barretry	O
.	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
charged	O
with	O
Barretry	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Matter	O
of	O
Concern	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
honourable	O
prosession	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
demean	O
himself	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
stir	O
up	O
Suits	O
among	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Subjects	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
Money	O
to	O
himself	O
and	O
distress	O
his	O
Fellow	O
Creatures	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
15	O
separate	O
Articles	O
of	O
Barretry	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
proof	O
of	O
three	O
only	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
be	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
him	O
of	O
this	O
Offence	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
4th	O
Article	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
the	O
Substance	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Theobalds	O
,	O
on	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
13th	O
Day	O
of	O
July	O
1739	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Castledine	I-pers
,	O
did	O
incite	O
and	O
persuade	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Castledine	O
,	O
to	O
join	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Drinkwater	I-pers
for	O
Barretry	O
;	O
which	O
Bill	O
of	O
Indictment	O
by	O
the	O
procurement	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Theobald	O
,	O
was	O
preferred	O
to	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
them	O
found	O
a	O
true	O
Bill	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Lee	O
's	O
Warrant	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Drinkwater	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Woodstreet	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
detained	O
till	O
he	O
gave	O
Bail	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Drinkwater	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Offence	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Here	O
the	O
Record	O
of	O
the	O
Drinkwater	O
's	O
Acquittal	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
]	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Castledine	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
Meeting	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Salutation-Tavern	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
it	O
was	O
agreed	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
an	O
Indictment	O
should	O
be	O
preferred	O
against	O
Drinkwater	O
for	O
Barretry	O
:	O
Theobalds	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
Means	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
Terms	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Bill	O
was	O
preferred	O
to	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
himself	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
true	O
Bill	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Mention	O
made	O
of	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Barretry	O
that	O
Drinkwater	O
had	O
done	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Indictments	O
between	O
Drinkwater	O
and	O
Castledine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
would	O
bring	O
Drinkwater	O
to	O
Terms	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Theobalds	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
Drinkwater	O
was	O
cast	O
for	O
Barretry	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
hard	O
Thing	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
what	O
few	O
people	O
understood	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
The	O
first	O
Time	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
Theobalds	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
out	O
a	O
new	O
Way	O
to	O
punish	O
Drinkwater	O
:	O
Then	O
Griffits	O
,	O
Castledine	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
to	O
consult	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Bill	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
all	O
this	O
Discourse	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
At	O
Castledine	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Johnson's-Court	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Constable	O
of	O
St.	O
Bride	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
Drinkwater	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
Castledine	O
.	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Theobalds	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
for	O
my	O
Trouble	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Hick's-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Theobalds	O
,	O
Griffits	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Maul	I-pers
go	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
returned	O
presently	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Bill	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Griffits	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
Bill	O
against	O
Drinkwater	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Name	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
of	O
the	O
Bill	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
who	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
framing	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
prosecute	O
Drinkwater	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
me	O
an	O
Injury	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
this	O
Thing	O
set	O
on	O
Foot	O
without	O
your	O
Knowledge	O
?	O
Griffits	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
was	O
intended	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
joined	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
Cause	O
depending	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
against	O
Castledine	O
,	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
Bawdy-House	O
?	O
Griffits	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
Reason	O
why	O
I	O
designed	O
to	O
prosecute	O
Drinkwater	O
was	O
this	O
:	O
He	O
met	O
me	O
and	O
abused	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
3	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
he	O
served	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Copy	O
of	O
a	O
Writ	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
Easter	O
Term	O
,	O
so	O
Castledine	O
employed	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
got	O
Judgment	O
against	O
me	O
by	O
Default	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
countermanded	O
Trial	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
on	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Willes	O
I	O
nonsuited	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Term	O
at	O
Guild-Hall	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Notice	O
of	O
Trial	O
;	O
when	O
that	O
very	O
Morning	O
he	O
delivered	O
a	O
Brief	O
into	O
his	O
Council	O
's	O
Hand	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Drinkwater	O
's	O
general	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
was	O
looked	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
litigious	O
Man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cummins	O
.	O
About	O
2	O
Years	O
and	O
half	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
