TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
Country	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
14th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Humphry	O
Parsons	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1741	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
in	O
Warwick-Lane	O
.	O
MDCCXLI	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Public	O
may	O
be	O
assured	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
during	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
HUMPHRY	O
PARSONS	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
present	O
Year	O
)	O
the	O
Sessions-Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
SIX-PENCE	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
double	O
Books	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
HUMPHRY	O
PARSONS	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
PAGE	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
PARKER	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
ABNEY	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRANGE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Scullard	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Littlebury	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Crisp	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Dimmock	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hoole	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hebert	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Pincke	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wintle	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tassel	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bignel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Elcock	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Holden	B-pers
Bonker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Deakins	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jumard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Horne	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wellbeloved	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Aust	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Betty	I-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
9th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
at	O
Bedminster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Somerset	O
,	O
took	O
to	O
Husband	O
Richard	B-pers
Aust	I-pers
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
July	O
5th	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
Ludgate	I-place
,	O
married	O
Allen	B-pers
Pincock	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
Husband	O
being	O
living	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Philip	B-pers
Lipscomb	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newsome	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
with	O
Intent	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Newsome	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Jan	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newsome	I-pers
.	O
O	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
nt	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
ing	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
On	O
searching	O
my	O
Cellar	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newsome	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
and	O
I	O
fastened	O
all	O
the	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
called	O
up	O
about	O
4	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Custody	O
of	O
there	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
very	O
bloody	O
.	O
This	O
Hat	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
Newsome	O
's	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
Halloo	O
!	O
he	O
said	O
Halloo	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
Yards	O
from	O
Newsome	O
's	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
all	O
round	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
open	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
go	O
down	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
up	O
John	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
was	O
fast	O
;	O
he	O
(	O
Blake	O
)	O
smiled	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
mistaken	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
turned	O
my	O
Back	O
to	O
call	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Newsome	O
,	O
but	O
Blake	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
Stair	O
he	O
gave	O
Blake	O
a	O
Knock	O
with	O
something	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
him	O
reel	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Lathing	O
Hammer	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
.	O
About	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
Ford	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
Man	O
go	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Newsome	O
's	O
Cellar	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
assist	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
fast	O
,	O
I	O
niled	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
mistaken	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
certa	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
to	O
call	O
Mr.	O
Newsome	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
Cut	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
something	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
I	O
cut	O
my	O
Legs	O
and	O
bruised	O
my	O
Face	O
ry	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
for	O
the	O
Cut	O
on	O
that	O
Man	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
3.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Maccartney	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Bridget	B-pers
(	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
)	I-pers
Beale	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Chimney	O
Grasses	O
,	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
John	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Bar	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
stove	O
Grate	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
leaden	O
Pipe	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
leaden	O
Sink	O
value	O
10	O
d	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
Building	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Tailor	O
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6	O
,	O
7.	O
John	B-pers
Castody	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Person	O
unknown	O
)	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
Richard	B-pers
Briton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
put	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watch	O
with	O
the	O
outside	O
and	O
inside	O
Cases	O
made	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l	O
a	O
Brass	O
Watch	O
Key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Shoe	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Knee	O
Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Briton	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Briton	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Richard	B-pers
Briton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
had	O
some	O
Business	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Fastnege	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Liquor	O
.	O
They	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Box	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
o'Clock	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
past	O
2	O
.	O
They	O
staid	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Two-penny	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Princes-street	O
,	O
into	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
and	O
turned	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Side	O
with	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcostle	O
's	O
House	O
:	O
I	O
immediately	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
at	O
my	O
Heels	O
,	O
like	O
the	O
running	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Hunt	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Coat	O
on	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
hide	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
suspicious	O
of	O
some	O
Mischief	O
,	O
walked	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Cassody	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
a	O
Pistol	O
into	O
my	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Dead	O
Man	O
!	O
he	O
advanced	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lamps	O
shone	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
Immediately	O
Hunt	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
a	O
Pistol	O
to	O
my	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
Bl	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
likewise	O
my	O
Shoe	O
and	O
Knee	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
least	O
Resistance	O
they	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
set	O
at	O
every	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
Person	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Watchman	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Story	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
cou	O
'd	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
I	O
advertised	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
5	O
Guineas	O
for	O
any	O
Person	O
to	O
impeach	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
makes	O
it	O
his	O
Business	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
People	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
10	O
or	O
20	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Sort	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
sat	O
long	O
before	O
Hunt	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Cassody	O
presently	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Men	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
o'Clock	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Briton	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
Minutes	O
past	O
2	O
.	O
They	O
staid	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Two-penny	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
parted	O
with	O
me	O
presently	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
Princes-street	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
exactly	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
now	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
in	O
Search	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
that	O
harbours	O
these	O
People	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
staid	O
long	O
,	O
before	O
Hunt	O
and	O
Cassody	O
went	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Persons	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
Hunt	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
o'Clock	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
and	O
Briton	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
Minutes	O
past	O
2	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
satisfied	O
them	O
what	O
o'Clock	O
it	O
was	O
they	O
left	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Briton	O
and	O
his	O
Friends	O
soon	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
Hunt	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Skirmish	O
he	O
cut	O
my	O
Hand	O
almost	O
off	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Fastnege	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Two-penny	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Briton	O
and	O
his	O
Friends	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
Hunt	O
asked	O
what	O
o'Clock	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
and	O
Briton	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
paid	O
his	O
Reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
paid	O
for	O
their	O
Liquor	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
parted	O
with	O
his	O
Company	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Hunt	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
may	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Briton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Hunt	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
quite	O
light	O
or	O
quite	O
dark	O
?	O
Briton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
clear	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
Pin	O
,	O
besides	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
's	O
House	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
Lamps	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Hunt	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
he	O
may	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
what	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
and	O
what	O
Colour	O
the	O
Night	O
was	O
.	O
Briton	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
before	O
,	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
clear	O
Night	O
.	O
Hunt	O
.	O
What	O
Sort	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
had	O
I	O
on	O
?	O
Briton	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Coat	O
on	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
.	O
Hunt	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
but	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
too	O
soon	O
.	O
Briton	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
their	O
Coats	O
were	O
button	O
'd	O
under	O
their	O
Chins	O
.	O
Hunt	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
you	O
a	O
Question	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
,	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Night	O
was	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
Briton	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
clear	O
Morning	O
.	O
Hunt	O
.	O
This	O
Fellow	O
will	O
swear	O
Black	O
is	O
White	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
scruple	O
his	O
Conscience	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
Shape	O
in	O
Life	O
.	O
Cassody	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
-	O
Rhodes	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Cassody	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
resist	O
As	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
midling	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
8.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Timms	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Penknife	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1d	O
.	O
an	O
Iron	O
Key	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1d	O
.	O
and	O
3s	O
.	O
11d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Rhodes	O
,	O
Feb.	O
12	O
.	O
To	O
this	O
Indictment	O
Robert	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
take	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
for	O
a	O
Street	O
Robbery	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Drum-Alley	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
Fellows	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
some	O
with	O
Mopsticks	O
,	O
some	O
Broomsticks	O
,	O
naked	O
Hangers	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	B-pers
,	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	O
n	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
Murder	O
him	O
,	O
Kill	O
him	O
.	O
Immediately	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Club	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
the	O
wrong	O
side	O
outwards	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
:	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Holford's-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
being	O
broke	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
through	O
and	O
saw	O
Hunt	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
on	O
the	O
Vertue	O
of	O
your	O
Oath	O
that	O
I	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
Rhodes	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Company	O
and	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Atley	I-pers
I	O
was	O
Assistant	O
to	O
Rhodes	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
Robinson	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
Heap	O
of	O
Irishmen	O
rescued	O
him	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Hunt	O
push	O
'd	O
Rhodes	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
with	O
Broomsticks	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
Hunt	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Mr.	O
South	O
's	O
in	O
Holford	O
s-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
Hunt	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
drink	O
Boys	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
merry	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Money	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
broke	O
,	O
through	O
which	O
we	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
afraid	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
Charles	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
rather	O
die	O
than	O
impeach	O
his	O
Companions	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
White-cross	O
street	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Rescue	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
where	O
Robinson	O
was	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Hunt	O
,	O
when	O
Rhodes	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Night	O
that	O
Robinson	O
was	O
rescued	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Rhodes	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Holford	O
's	O
Alley	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
a	O
broken	O
pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Hunt	O
by	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
,	O
and	O
Hunt	O
said	O
B	O
-	O
d	O
and	O
W	O
-	O
ds	O
Timms	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
some	O
more	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
merry	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Vertue	O
of	O
your	O
Oath	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
rob	O
Mr.	O
Rhodes	O
?	O
Lewis	B-pers
No	I-pers
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
Rhodes	O
say	O
,	O
take	O
my	O
Money	O
and	O
spare	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Quaits	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Hunt	O
in	O
Drum-Alley	O
,	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Rhodes	O
,	O
cry	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
With	O
Submission	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
beg	O
leave	O
that	O
the	O
Justice	O
may	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
as	O
touching	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
his	O
general	O
Character	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
the	O
least	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
maintained	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
ever	O
liv	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
a	O
Robber	O
or	O
a	O
Rioter	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
this	O
Fellow	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chillingworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
3	O
Months	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
Thing	O
of	O
him	O
'till	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
King's-Arms	O
Alehouse	O
opposite	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
keeps	O
a	O
common	O
Two-Penny	O
Hop	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
Club	O
of	O
Irish	O
meet	O
and	O
Dance	O
some	O
cloath	O
'd	O
and	O
some	O
naked	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Ireland	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Waiter	O
at	O
a	O
Tavern	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
Action	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
6	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Eagle	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Dublin	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
honestly	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Journey	O
Forty	O
Miles	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
2	O
Guineas	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Poland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
I	O
frequented	O
Mr.	O
Chillingworth	O
's	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
Harm	O
by	O
him	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
private	O
House	O
of	O
14	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
in	O
Angel	O
Court	O
,	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
Lodgings	O
.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
keeps	O
a	O
common	O
Baudy-House	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
Night-Cellar	O
before	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
House	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Mizzet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
with	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
Credit	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Valentine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
2	O
Months	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
him	O
than	O
his	O
drinking	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
9	O
,	O
10.	O
John	B-pers
Hurt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bed	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
Boisters	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pillow	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Blanket	O
,	O
Value	O
9	O
d.	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Counterpane	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Stuff	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
d.	O
2	O
Holland	O
Shifts	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
2	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Counterpane	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
Dec	O
3	O
.	O
Hurt	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
Watson	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
John	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Pair	O
of	O
Glass	O
Ink	O
Bottles	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
eight	O
Penny	O
Weight	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pickard	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
2	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
Building	O
belonging	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Tottel	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Robert	B-pers
Parsonson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	O
Albemarle	O
,	O
Feb	O
8	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Helper	O
in	O
the	O
Lord	O
Albermarle	O
's	O
Stables	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
Day	O
of	O
Feb.	O
having	O
Occasion	O
for	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Hings	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
strain	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
Nails	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Iron	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
Stead	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Waggs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
robbing	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Back	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
find	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
left	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
3	O
new	O
Shirts	O
,	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Stock	O
Buckle	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
his	O
Landlady	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
had	O
given	O
his	O
Brother	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
Account	O
of	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
the	O
Nails	O
,	O
strained	O
the	O
Hinges	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
8	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
2	O
Bs	O
of	O
Iron	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
The	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
before	O
Sir	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
these	O
Things	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
these	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Iron	O
into	O
the	O
Purse	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
14	O
,	O
15	O
,	O
16.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Courtney	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Weyland	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Iron	O
Rigtree	O
Chains	O
,	O
three	O
Iron	O
Braces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Iron	O
Sharpins	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Lowton	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
All	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17	O
Thomas	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Lamp	O
Oil	O
,	O
Value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Tin	O
Pot	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
January	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
18.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bosman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Dowlas	O
Shirt	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Curr	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Edward	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Percival	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21	O
,	O
22.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Quartern	O
Loaves	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Horne	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
9	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sacking	O
Bag	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
Four	O
Lambs	O
,	O
Value	O
40	O
s.	O
a	O
Mare	O
of	O
a	O
Brown	B-pers
Colour	I-pers
,	O
Value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Leather	O
Bridle	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
d	O
and	O
a	O
Pannel	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
February	O
6	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
Side	O
Cobham-Deep	B-place
,	O
by	O
2	O
Men	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
Meadow	O
and	O
unhors	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
my	O
great	O
Coat	O
off	O
and	O
ty	O
'd	O
my	O
Hands	O
and	O
Legs	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
4	O
Lambs	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
Horse	O
I	O
rode	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sent	O
Brown	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
Lambs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dobey	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
kill	O
4	O
Lambs	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charlton	I-pers
.	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
4	O
Lambs	O
,	O
his	O
great	O
Coat	O
and	O
Bags	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
determined	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
ask	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Lambs	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
Dobey	O
's	O
Son	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
eager	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
conduct	O
(	O
deduct	O
)	O
it	O
when	O
the	O
Lambs	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
bury	O
the	O
Skins	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Lambs	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
some	O
more	O
Sheep	O
and	O
would	O
employ	O
me	O
to	O
kill	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Dobey	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
returned	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
attempted	O
twice	O
to	O
escape	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
me	O
no	O
Good	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Life	O
away	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dobey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
kill	O
4	O
Lambs	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
promised	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
done	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
Beard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
Son	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Beard	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
Beard	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Hue	O
and	O
Cry	O
in	O
the	O
Market	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
Lambs	O
and	O
Bags	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
four	O
Lambs	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
a	O
Person	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
fetch	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charlton	I-pers
.	O
All	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
,	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Lambs	O
from	O
Austin	O
's	O
to	O
Beard	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Direction	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dobey	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
24.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
56	O
lb	O
.	O
Bar	O
Iron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
cast	O
ditto	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Rudsby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Abel	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
13	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26	O
,	O
27.	O
John	B-pers
Copperfield	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
Vessel	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
Fire-Engine	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
26	O
s	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Denew	I-pers
,	O
Dec	O
14	O
.	O
And	O
William	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Dec	O
,	O
20	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
28.	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Deakins	I-pers
.	O
Dec	O
11	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Peter	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
and	O
open	O
Place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Fowling	O
Piece	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
'	O
.	O
November	O
28.	O
John	B-pers
Jay	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
was	O
employed	O
to	O
watch	O
some	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
beat	O
and	O
wounded	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Grounds	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Skins	O
of	O
2	O
Sheep	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Zachary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Jay	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
watching	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
4	O
Men	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
.	O
They	O
presently	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
Home	O
to	O
alarm	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
D	O
-	O
my	O
B	O
-	O
d	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
Body	O
is	O
under	O
this	O
Hedge	O
;	O
so	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
escape	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
cock	O
'd	O
my	O
Gun	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
miss	O
'd	O
Fire	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
came	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
shoot	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
they	O
laid	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
tied	O
my	O
Hands	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
water	O
Furrow	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
11	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
Noise	O
they	O
would	O
knock	O
my	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
greatest	O
Difficulty	O
that	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
Head	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
;	O
I	O
bled	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
like	O
a	O
Pig	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
Gun	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
Cap	O
on	O
my	O
Head	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
Dead	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
not	O
Dark	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
Attack	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Manner	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
when	O
they	O
Men	O
came	O
first	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Moon	O
rose	O
before	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
light	O
as	O
Day	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
he	O
kneeled	O
down	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
a	O
Fool	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
shoot	O
us	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
I	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
your	O
Cap	O
.	O
Butler	O
.	O
You	O
swore	O
bitterly	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
another	O
Word	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
knock	O
my	O
Brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
turned	O
my	O
Pockets	O
the	O
inside	O
outward	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
nothing4	O
but	O
a	O
Halfpennyworth	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
Fellow	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Barracks	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jay	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
Information	O
of	O
some	O
Soldiers	O
at	O
the	O
Tower	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
Butler	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
likewise	O
an	O
Information	O
of	O
some	O
Men	O
at	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
and	O
Butler	O
pitch	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
stood	O
Centry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
for	O
2	O
Hours	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Gun	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Butler	O
was	O
so	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
directly	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
inform	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
we	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
the	O
Guard	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
Child	O
that	O
is	O
unborn	O
James	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
,	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Coldstream	O
Regiment	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
did	O
his	O
Duty	O
as	O
a	O
Soldier	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
We	O
desire	O
Butler	O
may	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
sure	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
Gun	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Gun	O
from	O
me	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
tied	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
30.	O
John	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cocks	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s	O
and	O
5	O
Hens	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Passingham	I-pers
,	O
December	O
24	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31.	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Stamped	O
Silk	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
30	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
32	O
,	O
33.	O
Francis	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
lb	O
of	O
Tallow	O
Candles	O
,	O
19	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tallow	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
.	O
Feburary	O
5	O
.	O
Chapman	O
the	O
Elder	O
,	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
6.	O
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
William	B-pers
Falconer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Coals	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
August	O
28	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
35.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
,	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Roman	B-pers
Sequin	I-pers
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Gerrard	O
Brooks	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
Feburary	O
26	O
.	O
Gerrard	O
Brooks	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
Night	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Play	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Misfortune	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
James-Street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
prevail	O
'd	O
on	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Rummer	O
Tavern	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
staid	O
the	O
Drinking	O
of	O
4	O
Pints	O
of	O
Wine	O
:	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
grew	O
warm	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desirous	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
Bed	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
gingling	O
of	O
a	O
Purse	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
19	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Roman	B-pers
Sequin	I-pers
in	O
my	O
Purse	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
Immediately	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
light	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Purse	O
4	O
Guineas	O
and	O
the	O
Sequin	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
worth	O
about	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Purse	O
with	O
only	O
15	O
Guineas	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Sheets	O
and	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Beadle	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
more	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
Present	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
Oath	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
his	O
Purse	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
?	O
Brooks	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
Guinea	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
slept	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
,	O
Beadle	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
Custody	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
complain	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
4	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Sequin	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
this	O
Deponent	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Decency	O
would	O
permit	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Corner	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
cried	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
Prosecute	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
Material	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
36.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Carman	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Street	O
call	O
'd	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Michael	O
Le	O
Querce	O
,	O
on	O
George	B-pers
Orchard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
then	O
driving	O
a	O
certain	O
Horse	O
,	O
then	O
drawing	O
a	O
certain	O
Cart	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Orchard	O
to	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Ground	O
did	O
cast	O
and	O
throw	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
him	O
so	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
near	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Cart	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
did	O
give	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
three	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
Breadth	O
of	O
2	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
by	O
Virtue	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
riding	O
in	O
his	O
Cart	O
with	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
attempting	O
to	O
cross	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
near	O
Wheel	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
going	O
over	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
Spot	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Manslaughter	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36	O
.	O
37	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Red	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Applebey	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
16	O
,	O
Crawford	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Mosely	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Brass	O
Tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Park	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
.	O
Jan.	O
18	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
39.	O
William	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pincers	O
,	O
4	O
Knives	O
,	O
2	O
Hammers	O
,	O
8	O
Als	O
,	O
a	O
Tub	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
wooden	O
Form	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brabant	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
wicked	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Mind	O
,	O
greedy	O
of	O
Lucre	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
unlawfully	O
devising	O
and	O
intending	O
to	O
cheat	O
and	O
defraud	O
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Surman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
Sum	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
viz	O
52	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
of	O
good	O
and	O
lawful	O
Money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
to	O
get	O
and	O
acquire	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
himself	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Furman	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
being	O
then	O
concerned	O
as	O
a	O
Company	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Banking	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
keeping	O
Cash	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
then	O
keeping	O
a	O
Public	O
Shop	O
:	O
After	O
the	O
24th	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1734	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
January	O
1	O
,	O
1740	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Woolnoth	I-place
,	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Brabant	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
wicked	O
Mind	O
,	O
Intention	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
made	O
and	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
and	O
forged	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
Paper	O
Writing	O
,	O
purporting	O
a	O
Note	O
.	O
Order	O
,	O
Power	O
,	O
or	O
Authority	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Tipper	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
bearing	O
Date	O
,	O
January	O
1st	O
,	O
1740	O
41	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
,	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
authorizing	O
them	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Tho	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
of	O
52	O
l.	O
10	O
s	O
and	O
place	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Accompt	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Tipper	I-pers
:	O
The	O
Tenor	O
of	O
which	O
false	O
and	O
forged	O
Order	O
,	O
is	O
contain	O
'd	O
in	O
these	O
English	O
Words	O
,	O
Abbreviations	O
of	O
English	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
Figures	O
following	O
.	O
Jan.	O
1st	O
,	O
1740	O
41.	O
``	O
Pay	O
to	O
Tho	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
Fifty-two	O
Pounds	O
,	O
Ten	O
``	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
place	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Acct	O
of	O
l.	O
s.	O
d.	O
James	B-pers
Tipper	I-pers
.	O
''	O
52	O
10	O
0	O
``	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
and	O
Con	O
.	O
Thereby	O
meaning	O
and	O
intending	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
should	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Brabant	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
of	O
52	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
Whereas	O
in	O
Truth	O
and	O
Fact	O
the	O
said	O
Paper	O
or	O
Writing	O
was	O
never	O
subscribed	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Tipper	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Contempt	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
his	O
Laws	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
The	O
Jurors	O
further	O
present	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Brabant	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
wicked	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Mind	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
afterwards	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
Jan.	O
1	O
,	O
secretly	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
same	O
did	O
utter	O
and	O
publish	O
,	O
he	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
(	O
as	O
above	O
)	O
for	O
making	O
,	O
and	O
causing	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Order	O
for	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
defraud	O
James	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
and	O
Comp	O
.	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sum	O
.	O
The	O
Tenor	O
of	O
which	O
forged	O
Order	O
,	O
is	O
contain	O
'd	O
in	O
these	O
English	O
Words	O
and	O
Figures	O
following	O
.	O
Dec.	O
31	O
,	O
1740.	O
``	O
Pay	O
to	O
the	O
Bearer	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
Ten	O
Pounds	O
``	O
Ten	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
place	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Acct.	O
``	O
of	O
l.	O
s.	O
d.	O
James	B-pers
Tipper	I-pers
.	O
10	O
10	O
0	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
and	O
Com	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
farther	O
charged	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Brabant	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
forged	O
Order	O
did	O
publish	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
and	O
Comp	O
.	O
Bankers	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Tipper	I-pers
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
keeps	O
Cash	O
at	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Book-keeper	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
coming	O
to	O
your	O
Master	O
's	O
Shop	O
with	O
Draughts	O
for	O
Money	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
Note	O
for	O
ten	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Look	O
on	O
the	O
Name	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
:	O
whose	O
Name	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Tipper	O
's	O
Handwriting	O
,	O
otherwise	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
paid	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
bring	O
any	O
other	O
besides	O
this	O
ten	O
Guinea	O
Note	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
afterwards	O
(	O
New-Year's-Day	O
)	O
he	O
brought	O
another	O
for	O
50	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
You	O
keep	O
New-Year's-Day	O
as	O
a	O
Holiday	O
;	O
did	O
he	O
make	O
no	O
Excuse	O
for	O
coming	O
then	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
paid	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Tipper	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
writing	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Look	O
on	O
those	O
two	O
Notes	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
those	O
Notes	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Tipper	O
's	O
Hand-writing	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Ellis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
neither	O
the	O
Signing	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Notes	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
conversant	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
above	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
a	O
hundred	O
times	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goodeve	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Tipper	O
upwards	O
of	O
sixteen	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
often	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
those	O
Notes	O
were	O
wrote	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Tipper	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Goodeve	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
Opinion	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
Reason	O
;	O
this	O
seems	O
to	O
be	O
wrote	O
after	O
some	O
Copy	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
stiff	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ellis	O
.	O
I	O
observe	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Sriffness	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
the	O
Person	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
an	O
unusual	O
Course	O
:	O
It	O
wants	O
the	O
Freedom	O
of	O
an	O
Original	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
pretty	O
well	O
done	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Heaviness	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
all	O
Copies	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Orr	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Tipper	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Essex	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
New-Year's-Day	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Note	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
to	O
our	O
Shop	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Tipper	O
4	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
frequently	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Water	O
Side	O
when	O
Tobacco	O
's	O
are	O
weigh	O
'd	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
those	O
Notes	O
are	O
his	O
Hand-writing	O
?	O
Witness	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
by	O
my	O
Master	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Tipper	O
)	O
to	O
write	O
and	O
improve	O
me	O
in	O
Accompts	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Hand	O
at	O
imitating	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
any	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Hand	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
but	O
once	O
,	O
to	O
such	O
an	O
Exactness	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
distinguished	O
from	O
the	O
Original	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
counterfeit	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Hand	O
from	O
a	O
Frank	O
so	O
nicely	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
discern	O
the	O
Difference	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Tipper	O
at	O
Baddow	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
New-Year's-Day	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Rumford	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
Notes	O
to	O
our	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
write	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
telling	O
him	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
We	O
shall	O
now	O
call	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
to	O
prove	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Tipper	O
had	O
no	O
Dealings	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Dealings	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
desire	O
Mr.	O
Tipper	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
Character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tipper	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Tobacco-Broker	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Person	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
a	O
good	O
Hand	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
I	O
had	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Care	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
:	O
I	O
returned	O
on	O
New-Year's-Day	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
taken	O
the	O
Keys	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
set	O
a	O
Ladder	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
Boy	O
in	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
any	O
Letter	O
which	O
you	O
had	O
wrote	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Custody	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tipper	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
Letter	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
insert	O
some	O
Particulars	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Look	O
on	O
those	O
Notes	O
;	O
are	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
your	O
Writing	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Tipper	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
neither	O
the	O
Signing	O
nor	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Notes	O
;	O
neither	O
had	O
I	O
ever	O
any	O
Dealings	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
on	O
both	O
Indictments	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
41.	O
John	B-pers
Freshwater	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
Quart	O
Glass	O
Bottles	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
Wine	O
,	O
Value	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
King	O
Gould	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Sept.	O
19	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
42	O
,	O
43	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
Weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
Value	O
6s	O
.	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
10	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
44.	O
Matth.ias	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Ewe	O
Sneep	O
,	O
Value	O
14s	O
.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
45	O
,	O
46.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reveley	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
ten	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
,	O
an	O
Iron	O
Poker	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Bellows	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
a	O
Heater	O
,	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pattins	O
,	O
a	O
Table	O
Cloth	O
,	O
4	O
Pewter	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pan	O
,	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Coffee	O
Pot	O
,	O
a	O
Stew	O
Pan	O
,	O
a	O
Pot-Lid	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reveley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
and	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Cap	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
Macneal	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
18	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reveley	I-pers
.	O
About	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
my	O
Doors	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Some	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Robinson	O
brought	O
me	O
two	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Heater	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
15	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
speak	O
any	O
Thing	O
but	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
my	O
Soul	O
will	O
be	O
damned	O
to	O
all	O
Eternity	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
old	O
Man	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
with	O
us	O
a	O
Co	O
in	O
a	O
Tea	O
Pot	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
Light	O
.	O
Middleton	O
broke	O
a	O
Board	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
unbolted	O
two	O
Bolts	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
They	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
cou	O
'd	O
get	O
through	O
a	O
smaller	O
Place	O
than	O
they	O
:	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
we	O
filled	O
a	O
Bag	O
with	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Robinson	B-pers
Home	I-pers
with	O
it	O
.	O
Than	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
and	O
I	O
went	O
backward	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
;	O
out	O
the	O
Window	O
which	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
being	O
shut	O
,	O
she	O
forced	O
it	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
from	O
thence	O
ten	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Robinson	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
Home	O
as	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
.	O
When	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
were	O
carried	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
Middleton	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
old	O
M	O
Lodger	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
kill	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
knew	O
they	O
had	O
Money	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
Cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
certainly	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
Robinson	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
pulled	O
her	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Middleton	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
ever	O
propose	O
killing	O
Mr.	O
Reveley	O
?	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
Indeed	O
you	O
did	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
nothing	O
out	O
the	O
Truth	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Macneal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Reveley	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
my	O
Cap	O
was	O
found	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
Line	O
in	O
this	O
Middleton	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Hat	O
was	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Heads	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Middleton	O
lodged	O
at	O
Reveley	O
's	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
unfortunately	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
bad	O
Company	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Truby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
Robinson	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Girl	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
wronging	O
any	O
Body	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
47.	O
George	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Blasdell	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
24	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
48.	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
Day	O
of	O
Jan	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
,	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
on	O
Alexander	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
feloniously	O
,	O
willfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
drawn	O
Sword	O
made	O
of	O
Iron	O
and	O
Steel	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
which	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
V	O
-	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
left	O
Thing	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Watson	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
stab	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
6	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
28th	O
of	O
Jan	O
to	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
he	O
languish	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
languishing	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2	O
d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Statute	O
of	O
Stabbing	O
;	O
And	O
a	O
3d	O
Time	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
laying	O
the	O
said	O
Alexander	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Stainbank	I-pers
.	O
I	O
made	O
out	O
a	O
Process	O
from	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Palace	O
Court	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Suit	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
for	O
150	O
l.	O
It	O
was	O
read.	O
``	O
George	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Grace	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
``	O
To	O
the	O
Bearer	O
of	O
the	O
Bargess	O
of	O
our	O
Household	O
,	O
``	O
Officers	O
,	O
and	O
Masters	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
We	O
command	O
``	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
ever	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Bodies	O
of	O
``	O
V	O
-	O
A	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
bring	O
``	O
them	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Stainbank	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
this	O
Writ	O
into	O
the	O
Plaintiff	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
's	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
Watson	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bearers	O
of	O
the	O
Verges	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
Debt	O
which	O
was	O
contracted	O
in	O
the	O
Years	O
1731	O
and	O
32	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Year	O
32	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Joint	O
Note	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Dec.	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Joint	O
Bond	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
waited	O
six	O
Months	O
after	O
it	O
became	O
due	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
added	O
the	O
Interest	O
and	O
the	O
Principal	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Joint	O
Bond	O
in	O
Dec.	O
33	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Easter	O
Term	O
36	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
obtained	O
a	O
Judgement	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common-Pleas	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Year	O
38	O
,	O
I	O
(	O
being	O
Administrator	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
)	O
employ	O
'd	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Whitehall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Verge	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Piazza	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Marshal	O
's	O
Court	O
Writ	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
to	O
Execute	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
use	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
handsomely	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
expose	O
him	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Who	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
Information	O
where	O
you	O
might	O
take	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
Person	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Piazza	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
Watson	O
the	O
Writ	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
News	O
I	O
heard	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
Alexander	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
was	O
my	O
Father	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
gave	O
my	O
Father	O
this	O
Writ	O
in	O
the	O
Piazza	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
with	O
Orders	O
to	O
execute	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
use	O
him	O
well	O
.	O
We	O
waited	O
from	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
till	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Fry	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
four	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
parted	O
with	O
his	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
James	O
street	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
my	O
Father	O
bid	O
me	O
and	O
his	O
Assistants	O
keep	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
you	O
:	O
Immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropp	O
'd	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
stabb	O
'd	O
my	O
Father	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
left	O
Thigh	O
After	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
!	O
he	O
has	O
murder	O
'd	O
me	O
!	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fry	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Linney	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
Hilt	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Blade	O
of	O
the	O
Sword	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Blade	O
la	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
Father	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
at	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
discern	O
all	O
this	O
?	O
Watson	B-pers
It	I-pers
was	O
neither	O
light	O
nor	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
fine	O
Morning	O
,	O
besides	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp	O
about	O
3	O
Doors	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
with	O
your	O
Father	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Thomas	B-pers
Linney	I-pers
,	O
Evan	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
(	O
whom	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
had	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
Where	O
did	O
your	O
Father	O
stand	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Piazza	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
Jenkins	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Father	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
alone	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
you	O
apprehend	O
it	O
was	O
difficult	O
to	O
get	O
at	O
me	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
Turner	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
Trouble	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Noise	O
or	O
Disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
still	O
and	O
quiet	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
a	O
Voice	O
might	O
easily	O
be	O
heard	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Linney	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Jan	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-Posts	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
to	O
arrest	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Verge	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Piazza	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
with	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
more	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Fry	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
parted	O
with	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
James	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
Chairman	O
(	O
Evan	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
)	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
handsome	O
manner	O
;	O
accordingly	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
.	O
your	O
humble	O
Servant	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
you	O
.	O
Immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dropp	O
'd	O
his	O
Cane	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
Sword	O
,	O
and	O
stuck	O
him	O
directly	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
Provocation	O
given	O
?	O
Linney	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
bid	O
us	O
keep	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
stabb	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
killed	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
stabb	O
'd	O
!	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fry	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Heels	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
thrown	O
down	O
before	O
,	O
or	O
after	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
?	O
Linney	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
with	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
Weapon	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
given	O
?	O
Linney	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
three	O
edg	O
'd	O
Sword	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
Blood	O
Councel	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
Light	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
all	O
this	O
?	O
Linney	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
2	O
Yards	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
Councel	O
Did	O
the	O
Deceased	O
assault	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
?	O
Linney	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
touched	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
very	O
civilly	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
Deceased	O
live	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Linney	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
might	O
live	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Noise	O
or	O
Tumult	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
?	O
Linney	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Soul	O
stirring	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positive	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Provocation	O
given	O
?	O
Linney	O
.	O
No	O
other	O
than	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
telling	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
fell	O
off	O
.	O
Evan	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Effect	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Perkins	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
attend	O
the	O
Deceased	O
in	O
his	O
Life	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
present	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
Body	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
a	O
Wound	O
on	O
his	O
Thigh	O
,	O
which	O
penetrated	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Inches	O
downwards	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
passed	O
the	O
Crural	O
Artery	O
.	O
There	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
counter	O
opening	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
who	O
attended	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Discharge	O
of	O
Matter	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
Side	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mortification	O
begun	O
.	O
I	O
th	O
en	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Abdomen	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
examining	O
the	O
Intestines	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Pus	O
or	O
Matter	O
,	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Kidneys	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
in	O
the	O
Lobes	O
of	O
the	O
Lungs	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
inspecting	O
the	O
Stomach	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Corruption	O
ting	O
'd	O
with	O
Blood	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
this	O
Wound	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Perkins	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
immediate	O
Cause	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
your	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Man	O
would	O
have	O
died	O
by	O
any	O
Disorder	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
received	O
this	O
Wound	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Perkins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
3	O
Inches	O
below	O
the	O
Groin	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Thigh	O
,	O
and	O
[	O
Pages	O
missing	O
in	O
original	O
.	O
]	O
was	O
almost	O
closed	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
dilated	O
it	O
to	O
promote	O
a	O
Discharge	O
of	O
Matter	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
the	O
Wound	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Aspect	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
feverish	O
,	O
and	O
troubled	O
with	O
a	O
Looseness	O
;	O
and	O
continued	O
to	O
till	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
a	O
Hardness	O
about	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
The	O
Fever	O
and	O
Looseness	O
(	O
notwithstanding	O
our	O
Applications	O
)	O
increased	O
daily	O
more	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
last	O
Time	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Kilpatrick	O
dress	O
the	O
Wound	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
State	O
of	O
healing	O
as	O
possibly	O
could	O
be	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
that	O
Time	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
In	O
your	O
Judgment	O
did	O
the	O
receiving	O
this	O
Wound	O
contribute	O
to	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
whole	O
Course	O
of	O
this	O
Wound	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
any	O
Symptoms	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
fairly	O
say	O
were	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
Looseness	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
remov	O
'd	O
all	O
those	O
Symptoms	O
from	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
We	O
apprehend	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
bad	O
Constitution	O
,	O
therefore	O
do	O
you	O
not	O
imagine	O
,	O
that	O
so	O
great	O
an	O
Effusion	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
might	O
occasion	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
Blood	O
makes	O
a	O
great	O
Shew	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
,	O
no	O
large	O
Vessel	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
Application	O
we	O
made	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Lint	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
bigness	O
of	O
a	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
Plaister	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
not	O
imagine	O
that	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
Blood	O
occasioned	O
the	O
Loosness	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
prolong	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
the	O
Loosness	O
the	O
first	O
Thing	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
done	O
to	O
relieve	O
him	O
,	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
Blood	O
from	O
him	O
William	O
Kirk	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Deceased	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
his	O
Death	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
on	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
received	O
this	O
Wound	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
hearty	O
and	O
strong	O
as	O
any	O
Man	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
made	O
any	O
Complaints	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
had	O
an	O
exceeding	O
good	O
Appetite	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
wounded	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
bled	O
a	O
Hat	O
full	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
2	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
his	O
Decease	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
strong	O
and	O
hearty	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
Complaints	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
Surgeons	O
gave	O
my	O
Father	O
his	O
Physic	O
,	O
it	O
brought	O
a	O
Loosness	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
one	O
before	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
this	O
Wound	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
hearty	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
Day	O
's	O
Illness	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Itorno	I-pers
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Deceased	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
every	O
Day	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
this	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
he	O
appear	O
'd	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
strong	O
and	O
hearty	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
Complaints	O
,	O
but	O
eat	O
and	O
drank	O
well	O
.	O
Mary	O
Thomas	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
one	O
here	O
,	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
Illness	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bed	O
but	O
once	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Vomit	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
bad	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
again	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Mr	O
Van	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
rushed	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
Robbers	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Mount	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Engraver	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
Gaming	O
at	O
the	O
Lady	O
Castile	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Great	O
Piazza	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Fry	O
's	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
come	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
I	O
heard	O
Watson	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
is	O
!	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
parted	O
with	O
his	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
towards	O
James-street	O
;	O
Watson	O
hid	O
himself	O
by	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
rushed	O
on	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
in	O
the	O
hottest	O
Manner	O
.	O
They	O
presently	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
you	O
!	O
And	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
I	O
heard	O
Watson	O
complain	O
he	O
was	O
stabb	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
still	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
Person	O
had	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
Writ	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
Body	O
cry	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stabb	O
'd	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
Warrant	O
?	O
Mount	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
nothing	O
about	O
a	O
Warrant	O
till	O
Watson	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
being	O
stabb	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
Thieves	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
(	O
said	O
he	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Night	O
so	O
still	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
and	O
see	O
every	O
Thing	O
that	O
passed	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
without	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
?	O
Mount	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
without	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
all	O
rush	O
'd	O
on	O
him	O
at	O
once	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Sword	O
drawn	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
Watson	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stabbed	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
this	O
Discovery	O
?	O
Mount	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fry	O
's	O
,	O
Two	O
or	O
Three	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kingston	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Scotland	O
Yard	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
apprehended	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
there	O
for	O
Shelter	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
always	O
went	O
abroad	O
as	O
other	O
Gentlemen	O
go	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
his	O
Temper	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
a	O
Fact	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
-	O
Hardy	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
George	O
's	O
Coffee-House	O
,	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ten	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
least	O
4	O
times	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
conspicuous	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Coffee-Room	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
spend	O
the	O
Evening	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Van	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Reason	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
Bailiffs	O
were	O
in	O
any	O
Danger	O
of	O
losing	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
least	O
Speed	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
walks	O
fast	O
may	O
easily	O
get	O
Ground	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
his	O
Temper	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
quarrelsome	O
or	O
rash	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
the	O
reverse	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
:	O
He	O
dined	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
Day	O
this	O
Accident	O
happened	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
his	O
Character	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
,	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
would	O
pay	O
every	O
Body	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
being	O
Security	O
for	O
his	O
Mother	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
some	O
Trouble	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
any	O
Extravagance	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Van	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
supped	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fry	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
Night	O
this	O
Accident	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
any	O
Fear	O
of	O
an	O
Arrest	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
several	O
Coffee-Houses	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
seemed	O
shy	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
,	O
but	O
always	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
Room	O
frequently	O
two	O
Hours	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
natur	O
'd	O
,	O
humane	O
,	O
generous	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
draw	O
his	O
Sword	O
on	O
a	O
Man	O
without	O
some	O
Surprize	O
.	O
Mr	O
Trion	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
from	O
his	O
Childhood	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
appear	O
'd	O
publickly	O
without	O
any	O
Interruption	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Whitehall	O
for	O
Shelter	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
sweet	O
Tempered	O
Man	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Rushworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
by	O
applying	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Debt	O
due	O
to	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
his	O
Circumstances	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
press	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
that	O
Time	O
he	O
never	O
secreted	O
himself	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bathurst	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
appear	O
'd	O
publickly	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
as	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Fear	O
of	O
his	O
Creditors	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Knight	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Blake	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
's	O
being	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
till	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
lit	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
staid	O
talking	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Friends	O
turned	O
towards	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
James	O
street	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
under	O
any	O
Apprehension	O
of	O
an	O
Arrest	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
frequently	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
Stranger	O
had	O
asked	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
called	O
him	O
down	O
or	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
known	O
it	O
Mr.	O
Rayswell	O
.	O
I	O
supp	O
'd	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Blakes	O
with	O
the	O
soner	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
'till	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
together	O
where	O
he	O
staid	O
some	O
Time	O
pressing	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
used	O
to	O
secret	O
himself	O
.	O
Col.	O
Stevens	B-pers
I	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
last	O
Summer	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
thought	O
him	O
subject	O
to	O
quarrelling	O
.	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
.	O
Mr.	O
V	O
-	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
his	O
Housekeeper	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
before	O
me	O
for	O
Felony	O
:	O
The	O
Son	O
(	O
Tho	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
)	O
hath	O
been	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
recollect	O
the	O
Particulars	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Nevet	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upwards	O
of	O
10	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
frequently	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
in	O
Arundel	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
commonly	O
came	O
on	O
Foot	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
mild	O
Disposition	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Revis	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
4	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
thought	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Edward	B-pers
Mount	I-pers
a	O
Dozen	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
say	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Truth	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
withdrew	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
returned	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
49.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
Hilt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Thread	O
Stockings	O
,	O
a	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Scarlet	O
Cloaks	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Whitworth	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
51.	O
John	B-pers
Burdus	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Knee-buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Besser	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Chain	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
Coral	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richer	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
52.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
brass	O
Nobs	O
,	O
a	O
Coach	O
Seat	O
,	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
Hinge	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Serjeant	O
at	O
Law	O
;	O
and	O
4	O
brass	O
Knobs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Coach	O
Seat	O
Cloth	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Stable	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tea	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
53.	O
James	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Calf	O
,	O
val	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
54.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sturt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Men	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coe	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
55.	O
Charles	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hempen	O
Sack	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
4	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Malt	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
17	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
56	O
,	O
57.	O
William	B-pers
Canterbury	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
(	O
with	O
William	O
Warner	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
1	O
C	O
lb	O
.	O
Lead	O
,	O
2	O
brass	O
Cocks	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
Bushels	O
of	O
Barley	O
Malt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rich	B-pers
Thornhill	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
10	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
58.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
34	O
lb	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Broad	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
Feb	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
59.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
60.	O
Mary	B-pers
Magdalen	I-pers
Spalding	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Mahogany	O
Tea	O
Chest	O
,	O
3	O
Tin	O
Canisters	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tea	O
Tongs	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Foss	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
26	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
61.	O
John	B-pers
Jubs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea	O
Kettle	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
Feb	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
62.	O
David	B-pers
Stochbury	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Touchbury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
Malice	O
afore	O
thought	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Poinard	O
or	O
Dagger	O
made	O
of	O
Iron	O
and	O
Steel	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d	O
which	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
Hand	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Breast	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
Pap	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
6th	O
and	O
7th	O
Rib	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Porter	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
stab	O
,	O
giving	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
one	O
Mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
Depth	O
of	O
5	O
Inches	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
charged	O
,	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Wilful	O
Murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Porter	O
John	B-pers
Galcoigne	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
3	O
more	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
and	O
saw	O
2	O
Men	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Simkin	I-pers
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Crown	O
's	O
Door	O
;	O
immediately	O
Simkin	O
rushed	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Voice	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
Alehouse	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
strike	O
the	O
Deceased	O
?	O
Galcoigne	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
fighting	O
with	O
Simkin	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Galcoigne	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Tuck	O
was	O
shewn	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
Father	O
to	O
one	O
Lloyd	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Bromley	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hollaly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Headborough	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mile	O
End	O
Old	O
Town	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
'till	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
parted	O
from	O
the	O
Company	O
about	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
2	O
Men	O
scuffling	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
to	O
the	O
Anchor	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
2	O
other	O
Men	O
fighting	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Porter	O
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fireside	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
Part	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
Blood	O
on	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
stripping	O
his	O
Coat	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Blood	O
flow	O
'd	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
Fighting	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
the	O
Deceased	O
fell	O
from	O
his	O
Chair	O
that	O
this	O
pass	O
'd	O
.	O
Hollaly	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
Child	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
Fighting	O
and	O
done	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
Weapon	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
Lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
found	O
this	O
naked	O
Tuck	O
,	O
all	O
dirty	O
and	O
bloody	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
deaf	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
whether	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
Answer	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ricards	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
lent	O
that	O
Weapon	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
of	O
Bromley	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
into	O
his	O
Hands	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
within	O
the	O
Step	O
of	O
the	O
Three	O
Crown	O
Door	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
Men	O
fighting	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
Man	O
,	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
stepp	O
'd	O
up	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulders	O
into	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Wife	O
scream	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
)	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ricards	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
lent	O
the	O
Weapon	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
of	O
Bromley	O
,	O
that	O
Lloyd	O
gave	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
6	O
d.	O
a-piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
Tuck	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
back	O
himself	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
the	O
Deceased	O
push	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
off	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Peace	O
?	O
Campion	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
Interposing	O
.	O
Francis	O
Green	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hollaly	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Neighbours	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
my	O
House	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
expiring	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
Weapon	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
this	O
Tuck	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
very	O
dirty	O
and	O
bloody	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Simkin	O
into	O
the	O
Cage	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
this	O
;	O
Simkin	O
,	O
replied	O
,	O
You	O
Rogue	O
,	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
the	O
Dagger	O
Green	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Time	O
it	O
was	O
shewn	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
Lloyd	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Widow	O
My	O
Husband	O
had	O
parted	O
with	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
Home	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
He	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
hardly	O
turn	O
'd	O
myself	O
round	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
like	O
2	O
Men	O
striving	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
my	O
Husband	O
holding	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
he	O
that	O
has	O
kill	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pointed	O
with	O
his	O
Finger	O
to	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
fix	O
'd	O
his	O
Eyes	O
on	O
the	O
Ceiling	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
spoke	O
Words	O
more	O
.	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
Husband	O
speak	O
loud	O
enough	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
hear	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
Porter	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Friends	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Supper	O
:	O
About	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
,	O
News	O
was	O
brought	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
murdered	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
Weapon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
this	O
Tuck	O
all	O
dirty	O
and	O
bloody	O
,	O
within	O
six	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Simkin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Oh	O
!	O
Mrs.	O
Marsh	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
!	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
?	O
Marsh	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mile	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Croud	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
there	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
Councel	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
serv	O
'd	O
his	O
Father	O
with	O
