TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
14th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1741	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
J.	O
ROBERTS	O
in	O
Warwick	O
Lane	O
.	O
M.DCC.XLI	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honourable	O
DANIEL	B-pers
LAMBERT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
JUSTICE	O
CHAPPLE	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
REYNOLDS	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Masseter	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cleaver	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
,	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Springhall	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Pomeroy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pershouse	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Okell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Kriton	I-pers
,	O
Robert	O
Green	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
*	O
Allen	O
Evans	O
,	O
*	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
on	O
Friday	O
and	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Labatt	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Carlton	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Veer	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jerquel	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Line	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
large	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
4	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Tongs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Linen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5.	O
s.	O
a	O
Cotton	O
Counterpane	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Garnet	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
and	O
4	O
small	O
Diamond	O
Sparks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Mather	I-pers
;	O
2	O
Linen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Linen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
val	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Mather	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Mather	I-pers
,	O
May	O
2	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Mather	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
and	O
having	O
lost	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
that	O
she	O
conveyed	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
taking	O
as	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
recollect	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Messenger	O
's	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
in	O
Excuse	O
of	O
herself	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Mather	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
Reason	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
Uncle	O
of	O
whom	O
she	O
expected	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
looking	O
over	O
my	O
Linen	O
I	O
missed	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Mather	O
gave	O
me	O
Charge	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
these	O
Things	O
.	O
C	O
Did	O
she	O
attempt	O
to	O
excuse	O
herself	O
?	O
Mears	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
straiten	O
'd	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
coming	O
into	O
Trouble	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Debt	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
9	O
Gallon	O
Cask	O
filled	O
with	O
small	O
Beer	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Humphries	I-pers
,	O
April	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Dard	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Wall	I-pers
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Stick	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Yard	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
called	O
Bell-Yard	B-place
,	O
being	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
;	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
forcible	O
and	O
violent	O
Manner	O
demanding	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
with	O
Intent	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
steal	O
&	O
c.	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
John	O
Wall	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
Business	O
which	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
City	O
to	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
staid	O
'till	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
past	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Salisbury-Court	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
3	O
Persons	O
who	O
seemed	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
a	O
Conference	O
together	O
:	O
I	O
passed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Fetter-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
by	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
even	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
Bell-Yard	O
as	O
my	O
nearest	O
way	O
Home	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
'till	O
we	O
came	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Coat	O
with	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
pulled	O
a	O
short	O
Stick	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
Imprecations	O
demanded	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Immediately	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
and	O
repeated	O
his	O
Blows	O
so	O
fast	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
held	O
me	O
up	O
by	O
my	O
Coat	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
fallen	O
to	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
cryed	O
out	O
Watch	O
!	O
but	O
none	O
being	O
near	O
,	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
myself	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
a	O
Sodomite	O
,	O
but	O
some	O
People	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
secured	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Prison	O
together	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tenant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
in	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
Watch	O
called	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
great	O
Sheer	O
Lane	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
much	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lying	O
over	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
a	O
short	O
Stick	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
said	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
Sodomite	O
,	O
and	O
still	O
kept	O
beating	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
the	O
Stick	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
a	O
Watch-man	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Roll	O
's	O
Liberty	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
Stand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
?	O
Tenant	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
be	O
stopped	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
a	O
Robbery	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
up	O
Bell	O
Yard	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
:	O
this	O
Man	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
jostled	O
together	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Stick	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
Satisfaction	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
committed	O
to	O
Prison	O
together	O
.	O
He	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
put	O
upon	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
for	O
the	O
Sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
Reward	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
Cases	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
Tenant	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
Wig	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
unhandsom	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
His	O
Father	O
is	O
a	O
Picture	O
Frame	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
follow	O
'd	O
that	O
Business	O
'till	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Drawwater	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Latham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Rogers	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
Doors	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Honesty	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
intrusted	O
him	O
to	O
deal	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
brought	O
me	O
my	O
Money	O
honestly	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
4.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
(	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Arthur	I-pers
)	I-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Cassandra	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Stuff-petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Cassandra	O
,	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
Cassandra	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
of	O
so	O
tender	O
an	O
Age	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
thought	O
proper	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
sworn	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
three	O
Weeks	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
running	O
up	O
the	O
Road	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
mended	O
her	O
pace	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
half	O
way	O
up	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
green	O
Meadow	O
which	O
is	O
paled	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
throw	O
something	O
over	O
the	O
pals	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
continued	O
the	O
pursuit	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
she	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
which	O
leads	O
to	O
Pimlico	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Yard	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Child	O
came	O
in	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
Road	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
thing	O
which	O
she	O
flung	O
into	O
the	O
Meadow	O
was	O
green	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
throw	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
Child	O
wear	O
that	O
Coat	O
?	O
Edmonds	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
without	O
it	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Thing	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
Edmonds	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Meadow	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
's	O
Uncle	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
petticoat	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
.	O
Richard	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
petticoat	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Girl	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
certain	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
on	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Mob	O
rose	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Vincent	B-pers
Sunmonds	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Yards	O
of	O
Callimanco	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
20	O
pieces	O
of	O
Leather	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
April	O
24	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dean	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
together	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
some	O
Goods	O
to	O
a	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Flutter	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
stand	O
upright	O
;	O
however	O
I	O
pulled	O
him	O
upright	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
this	O
Callimanco	O
drop	O
'd	O
from	O
his	O
Clothes	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
Villain	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
robbed	O
me	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
a	O
Word	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
gave	O
himself	O
up	O
to	O
such	O
practices	O
?	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Callimanco	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
that	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
to	O
somebody	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
who	O
that	O
somebody	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
perhaps	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
used	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
proper	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
declared	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
there	O
of	O
mine	O
:	O
We	O
were	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Word	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
searched	O
his	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
pieces	O
of	O
Leather	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
these	O
were	O
not	O
mine	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
all	O
belong	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
a	O
Leather-cutter	O
in	O
Maiden-lan	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
Leather-cutter	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
some	O
Time	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
none	O
of	O
those	O
peices	O
were	O
ever	O
his	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
sent	O
me	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stick	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
Callimanco	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
roll	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Leather	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
Customers	O
before	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
least	O
Indiscretion	O
or	O
Injustice	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Morcan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
in	O
Life	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mascal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
Infancy	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
'till	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Affair	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
six	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
honest	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Catesby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
Bed-fellow	O
these	O
twelve	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
.	O
He	O
served	O
his	O
Time	O
with	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
Fact	O
of	O
this	O
Nature	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
William	B-pers
Sykes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Drab-Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
German	O
Serge	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Heart	I-pers
,	O
April	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
being	O
big	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
female	O
Child	O
,	O
afterwards	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Providence	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
alone	O
and	O
secretly	O
she	O
did	O
bring	O
forth	O
alive	O
;	O
which	O
said	O
female	O
Child	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Laws	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
Bastard	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
born	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
female	O
Child	O
,	O
so	O
alive	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
said	O
female	O
Child	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
her	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
into	O
a	O
certain	O
privy	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
cast	O
and	O
throw	O
;	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
which	O
casting	O
and	O
throwing	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Child	O
was	O
choaked	O
and	O
suffocated	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
choaking	O
and	O
suffocating	O
,	O
it	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
charged	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
Colick	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
.	O
She	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
seemingly	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
backwards	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
complaining	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Room	O
and	O
a	O
Bed	O
to	O
spare	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
Husband	O
to	O
ask	O
our	O
Lodger	O
to	O
resign	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
walked	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
backwards	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
staying	O
longer	O
than	O
I	O
expected	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
that	O
the	O
Necessary-house	O
had	O
been	O
washed	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Nose	O
had	O
bled	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
single	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
good	O
Woman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Distance	O
of	O
Time	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Little-house	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
Minutes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
any	O
pain	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
.	O
My	O
Fright	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
C.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
any	O
provision	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
wrote	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
for	O
some	O
things	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
lodges	O
in	O
our	O
House	O
would	O
resign	O
her	O
Room	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
Return	O
,	O
my	O
Wife	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
Betty	O
is	O
not	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
washing	O
her	O
Hands	O
at	O
the	O
Water-tub	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
her	O
Apron	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
.	O
I	O
informed	O
my	O
Wife	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
hoped	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
looked	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
something	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
at	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
Mrs.	O
Watlin	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
it	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Leg	O
appeared	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
escaping	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
C.	O
Can	O
you	O
form	O
any	O
Judgment	O
by	O
the	O
Growth	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
To	O
my	O
Thoughts	O
,	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Growth	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
had	O
Hair	O
and	O
Nails	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
observed	O
no	O
Marks	O
on	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
's	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
than	O
ordinary	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
opening	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
Room	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
mighty	O
bad	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
``	O
I	O
fear	O
,	O
Betty	O
,	O
thou	O
hast	O
``	O
been	O
delivered	O
of	O
a	O
Child	O
.	O
''	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
;	O
so	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
and	O
see	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
looking	O
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
I	O
perceived	O
a	O
new-born	O
Infant	O
.	O
I	O
informed	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Child	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
another	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
get	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
Growth	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
Nails	O
on	O
its	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
Hair	O
on	O
its	O
Head	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
was	O
not	O
covered	O
over	O
with	O
the	O
Soil	O
;	O
it	O
lay	O
on	O
its	O
Face	O
,	O
leaning	O
rather	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Face	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Soil	O
.	O
C.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
Nothing	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
naked	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
possible	O
for	O
a	O
Child	O
to	O
be	O
born	O
casually	O
from	O
a	O
Woman	O
under	O
these	O
Circumstances	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
it	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Watlin	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
Candle	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
directly	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
paper	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
and	O
rapped	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
founded	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
turning	O
it	O
about	O
,	O
a	O
Leg	O
or	O
an	O
Arm	O
appeared	O
.	O
He	O
strove	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
?	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Child	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
Marks	O
of	O
Violence	O
at	O
all	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
possible	O
for	O
Nature	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
?	O
Watlin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
competent	O
Judge	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
God	O
is	O
sufficient	O
at	O
all	O
times	O
to	O
help	O
poor	O
Creatures	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
ever	O
had	O
any	O
Trial	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Conversation	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
making	O
provision	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
?	O
Watlin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
that	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Cousin	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
who	O
lodges	O
at	O
Lucas	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
with	O
a	O
Child	O
in	O
her	O
Arms	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
delivered	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
a	O
Pail	O
,	O
covered	O
with	O
an	O
Apron	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
any	O
provision	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
for	O
some	O
things	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
none	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Colick	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
came	O
from	O
me	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
near	O
my	O
Time	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Tailor	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Gate	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
:	O
she	O
sent	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
keeper	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
opening	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
proper	O
for	O
a	O
young	O
Infant	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
poor	O
Women	O
have	O
not	O
so	O
many	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Winnington	O
's	O
House-keeper	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Box	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
delivered	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
necessary	O
Uses	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
for	O
some	O
Child	O
bed	O
linen	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
possible	O
for	O
a	O
Child	O
to	O
be	O
born	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
Mother	O
's	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
perceive	O
it	O
?	O
Chambers	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
an	O
Instance	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Child	O
bed-linen	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
;	O
-	O
she	O
sat	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
dull	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
but	O
little	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
of	O
telling	O
it	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
any	O
preparation	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
be	O
found	O
when	O
that	O
was	O
opened	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
8.	O
Edward	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
pounds	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Rowland	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
May	O
11	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Porter	O
at	O
Bear-key	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
the	O
common	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
been	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
little	O
Sugar	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Bag	O
full	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
pockets	O
full	O
besides	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
them	O
cry	O
,	O
Who	O
will	O
work	O
?	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
wanted	O
no	O
body	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
this	O
Sugar	O
off	O
the	O
Boards	O
,	O
lying	O
loose	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
Canvas	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
Bays	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Upsdale	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kelloway	I-pers
,	O
May	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10.	O
Ross	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Bond	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
an	O
East-India	O
Bond	O
,	O
No	O
12000	O
,	O
bearing	O
Date	O
,	O
November	O
1	O
,	O
1736	O
,	O
sealed	O
with	O
the	O
common	O
Seal	O
of	O
the	O
united	O
Company	O
of	O
Merchants	O
trading	O
to	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
Bond	O
the	O
said	O
Company	O
acknowledged	O
to	O
have	O
received	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Company	O
promised	O
to	O
repay	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Executors	O
,	O
Administrators	O
or	O
Assigns	O
,	O
by	O
Indorsement	O
thereon	O
,	O
with	O
Interest	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
then	O
next	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Rate	O
of	O
3	O
per	O
Cent	O
.	O
per	O
Annum	O
,	O
on	O
6	O
Months	O
Notice	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Company	O
in	O
the	O
London	O
Gazette	O
,	O
or	O
6	O
Months	O
Notice	O
to	O
be	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Webb	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Company	O
's	O
Accomptant	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
true	O
Payment	O
whereof	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Company	O
and	O
their	O
Successors	O
did	O
bind	O
themselves	O
for	O
the	O
Payment	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
said	O
Bond	O
was	O
indorsed	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
under	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Bond	O
at	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
this	O
Felony	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
and	O
others	O
;	O
the	O
said	O
sum	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
being	O
then	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfy	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Lupton	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Alexander	B-pers
Flack	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
handled	O
Cup	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Zachary	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-house	O
;	O
Feb	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
Sessions	O
on	O
2	O
Indictments	O
for	O
Burglaries	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
.	O
About	O
10	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Alexander	B-pers
Flack	I-pers
went	O
out	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
go	O
a-thieving	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Zachary	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Fisher	B-place
's	I-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
Red-Lion	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Beauset	O
in	O
his	O
parlour	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
and	O
a	O
Spoon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Jervis	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Fleet-Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
purchase	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
help	O
us	O
to	O
one	O
that	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Tom	B-pers
Cummins	I-pers
at	O
Fleet-Ditch	O
for	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
Trueman	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
for	O
his	O
Trouble	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
3	O
looked	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Zachary	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
Chance	O
was	O
haddy	O
and	O
only	O
2	O
Children	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
staid	O
without	O
to	O
tip	O
me	O
Peter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Trueman	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
and	O
desired	O
you	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
?	O
Lowther	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
come	O
against	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
here	O
before	O
?	O
Lowther	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
taken	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Zachary	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
for	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
my	O
Child	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Cup	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Alexander	O
Flack	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
two	O
handled	O
Cup	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Pepper-box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Punch-ladle	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Wheeler	O
;	O
March	O
29	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Easter	O
Sunday	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
at	O
8	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
to	O
Supper	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
Supper	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
Daughter	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
the	O
Parlour	O
to	O
set	O
some	O
Tea	O
Things	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
sooner	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
but	O
they	O
both	O
made	O
an	O
Outcry	O
:	O
I	O
started	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Chair	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Daughter	O
met	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
outside	O
Window	O
Shutters	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
Sash	O
lifted	O
quite	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blind	O
laid	O
on	O
a	O
Bureau	O
which	O
stands	O
near	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
Beauset	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
Winchester	O
Quart	O
two	O
handled	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
Winchester	O
pint	O
Mug	O
,	O
a	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
Spoon	O
and	O
a	O
Punch	O
Laddle	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
were	O
safe	O
at	O
4	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
at	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Evening	O
the	O
Window	O
Shutters	O
were	O
pulled	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
fastened	O
and	O
the	O
Blinds	O
were	O
bolted	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
they	O
were	O
wide	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
after	O
this	O
happened	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Reward	O
of	O
four	O
Guineas	O
for	O
any	O
Person	O
who	O
should	O
inform	O
me	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
Letter	O
from	O
Newgate	O
,	O
the	O
Contents	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
Way	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
Goods	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Friend	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
the	O
Author	O
of	O
that	O
Letter	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
he	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
whining	O
Cry	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
declare	O
the	O
whole	O
:	O
whereof	O
I	O
took	O
Pen	O
,	O
Ink	O
and	O
paper	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
to	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
out	O
since	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
Flack	O
and	O
Lowther	O
,	O
were	O
concerned	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
Flack	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
Lowther	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
stood	O
Peter	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
meant	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
to	O
watch	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
lighted	O
the	O
Candle	O
at	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Dark	O
Lanthorn	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Brown	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
my	O
making	O
Enquiry	O
no	O
such	O
Person	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
his	O
Companions	O
had	O
sunk	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
heard	O
it	O
rattle	O
in	O
their	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
asking	O
them	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Tobacco-box	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
before	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
Lowther	O
and	O
Flack	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
Easter	O
Sunday	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
Plate	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
only	O
saw	O
a	O
2	O
handled	O
Cup	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
else	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
sunk	O
the	O
rest	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
Flack	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
on	O
Easter-Sunday	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
and	O
pulled	O
open	O
the	O
Window	O
Shutters	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wheeler	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
-	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
Denmark	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
:	O
Flack	O
pushed	O
up	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Blind	O
which	O
was	O
bolted	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
undo	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
Flack	O
got	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Top	O
of	O
a	O
Bureau	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
shut	O
the	O
Window	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
Candle	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Light	O
,	O
Flack	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
Woman	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chandler	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
we	O
put	O
the	O
Shutters	O
to	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
Flack	O
took	O
a	O
silver	O
2	O
handled	O
Cup	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
Mug	O
,	O
a	O
Spoon	O
,	O
a	O
pepper-box	O
and	O
a	O
Punch	O
Ladle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
not	O
minding	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Chandler	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
Flack	O
flew	O
into	O
a	O
Passion	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
blow	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Candle	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
other	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
let	O
a	O
Spoon	O
fall	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
that	O
alarm	O
'd	O
the	O
People	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Strand	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
and	O
directly	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bower	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Bower	O
's	O
we	O
enquired	O
for	O
Betty	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
out	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
or	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
and	O
Flack	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
Room	O
:	O
Flack	O
presently	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
Bargain	O
for	O
four	O
Pounds	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
sunk	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
Death	O
.	O
12.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Neck	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Riding	O
Hood	O
,	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Linen	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wooding	I-pers
,	O
May	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ruby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
with	O
Intent	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Tucker	O
to	O
steal	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
April	O
28	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Angel	O
Inn	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
my	O
Servant	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Watchman	O
had	O
found	O
Thieves	O
breaking	O
into	O
my	O
Cellar	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
secure	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
concealed	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
body	O
.	O
My	O
Man	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
!	O
Thieves	O
!	O
and	O
ran	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
alarm	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
afterwards	O
hearing	O
a	O
second	O
Noise	O
,	O
of	O
some	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
my	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
a-cross	O
the	O
Yard	O
:	O
immediately	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
run	O
along	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
limped	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
Leg	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
some	O
Time	O
before	O
this	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
My	O
Ostler	O
hearing	O
the	O
Noise	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
hearing	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
Kitchen	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
Shoes	O
,	O
case	O
Knife	O
and	O
penknife	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Iron	O
Fly	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
gaming	O
Table	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Day	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
here	O
Tom	O
?	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Reply	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
Master	O
you	O
will	O
forgive	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
ask	O
ten	O
thousand	O
Pardons	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
excuse	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
Hand	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Public	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
a	O
Headborough	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
Victuals	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
Hat	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
to	O
wear	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Digner	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
Watchman	O
was	O
crying	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
,	O
he	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
Thieves	O
were	O
breaking	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cellar	O
Window	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
li't	O
a	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Cellar	O
to	O
fasten	O
the	O
Windows	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
wrenched	O
open	O
wide	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
Dog	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
they	O
were	O
fast	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
shut	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
2	O
Watchmen	O
coming	O
by	O
assisted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Key	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
again	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
afterwards	O
,	O
hearing	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
rustling	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
which	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
stand	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
Thie	O
ves	O
!	O
Murder	O
!	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
alarmed	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Iron	O
Fly	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
see	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
?	O
Digner	O
.	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Claring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
and	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Tucker	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
break	O
Mr.	O
Tucker	O
's	O
Cellar	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
disturbed	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Stone	O
Cutter	O
's	O
Yard	O
,	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
and	O
broke	O
in	O
backwards	O
at	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
Window	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
delivered	O
some	O
Implements	O
for	O
Gaming	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
De	O
Viel	O
,	O
the	O
Iron	O
Fly	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
were	O
produced	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
Tucker	O
's	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
starved	O
with	O
Hunger	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tucker	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
getting	O
some	O
Victuals	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
bolder	O
there	O
than	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
14.	O
Constantia	B-pers
Murrel	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Constantia	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Guineas	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
:	O
April	O
26	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
full	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
who	O
the	O
House	O
belongs	O
to	O
neither	O
can	O
I	O
tell	O
who	O
the	O
Person	O
was	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
a	O
Bed	O
together	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
above	O
20	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
Watkins	O
when	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
a-bed	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
People	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
3	O
Beds	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
people	O
in	O
each	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Watkins	O
were	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
House	O
belongs	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
15.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
of	O
Twickenham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
Timothy	O
Hall	O
,	O
the	O
elder	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
assaulting	O
James	B-pers
Hedger	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
outside	O
and	O
inside	O
Cales	O
made	O
of	O
Silver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Watch	O
Chain	O
made	O
of	O
base	O
Metal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hedger	O
,	O
April	O
21	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hedger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
Sale	O
where	O
the	O
next	O
Witness	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
Goods	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
overtook	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
another	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
it	O
all	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Sale	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
owed	O
some	O
Money	O
followed	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
,	O
seeing	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
afterwards	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
C.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
your	O
Watch	O
again	O
?	O
Hedger	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Gardner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
planting	O
some	O
Lettices	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Doors	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
were	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Watch	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
Table	O
under	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
his	O
Daughter	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
Watch	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
?	O
Hedger	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Red-Lion	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
?	O
Hedger	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Hitt	O
or	O
Miss	O
on	O
Twickenham	O
Common	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
Sale	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
some	O
things	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Hours	O
afterwards	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
were	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
Custody	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
my	O
Dishonesty	O
?	O
Wiseman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
search	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
?	O
Wiseman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
having	O
a	O
Watch	O
about	O
him	O
when	O
you	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Wiseman	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
Man	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
Hedger	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
to	O
leave	O
his	O
Watch	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Lion	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Hedger	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
paid	O
Money	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Receipt	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Wiseman	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Red-Lion	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
after	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
one	O
Ned	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
go	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
to	O
the	O
Red-Lion	O
?	O
Hedger	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
my	O
Desire	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
these	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
any	O
Misdemeanour	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Mary	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
for	O
his	O
Honesty	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
any	O
Trouble	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
17.	O
Francis	B-pers
Piggot	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Henry	B-pers
Corner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
Shoe-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Corner	O
,	O
April	O
24	O
.	O
Henry	O
Corner	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Piggot	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
play-house	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
again	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Johnson	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
Tankards	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
expected	O
them	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
part	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
treat	O
then	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
something	O
that	O
was	O
good	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
not	O
having	O
my	O
Hat	O
en	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
go	O
so	O
far	O
without	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Piggot	O
clapped	O
his	O
on	O
my	O
Head	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
they	O
knocked	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
people	O
being	O
a-bed	O
,	O
they	O
led	O
me	O
about	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
that	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bedford	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
Square	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
my	O
nearest	O
Way	O
home	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
Word	O
they	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
was	O
to	O
borrow	O
Money	O
;	O
immediately	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
stopped	O
my	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
Piggot	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
Watch	O
by	O
main	O
Force	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
my	O
Buckle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shoe	O
,	O
Strap	O
and	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
both	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Piggot	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
never	O
leave	O
his	O
Watch	O
in	O
my	O
Custody	O
?	O
Corner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Watch	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
C.	O
Whereabouts	O
did	O
they	O
rob	O
you	O
?	O
Corner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
above	O
Southampton-Row	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
cried	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Watchman	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
me	O
a	O
Constable	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
:	O
He	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
at	O
a	O
Milk-cellar	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Lane	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
cry	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
12	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
Murder	O
cried	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Field-Gate	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
see	O
no	O
body	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
afterwards	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
very	O
bloody	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
were	O
concerned	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
bring	O
him	O
a	O
Constable	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
laid	O
wait	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
two	O
Places	O
.	O
Corner	O
and	O
I	O
waited	O
for	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
staid	O
'till	O
we	O
had	O
Information	O
that	O
the	O
Constable	O
had	O
apprehended	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Milk-cellar	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Corner	O
direct	O
you	O
where	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
?	O
Perkins	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
most	O
likely	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
last	O
Witness	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
.	O
We	O
set	O
out	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
Information	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Milkwoman	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Lane	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Piggot	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
Milk-cellars	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
enquiring	O
for	O
Piggot	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
just	O
gone	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
be	O
within	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
Word	O
sent	O
me	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
Fellow-servant	O
of	O
Piggot	O
's	O
at	O
a	O
Bagnio	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
quickly	O
expected	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
Watchman	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
into	O
Bow-street	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Headborough	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
Milk-cellar	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
long	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
poker	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
what	O
my	O
Business	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
lock	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
they	O
surrendered	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
who	O
examined	O
them	O
separate	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
;	O
Johnson	O
in	O
particular	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
Corner	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
while	O
Piggot	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
both	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Horton	O
owned	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
with	O
great	O
Boldness	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
snapping	O
his	O
Fingers	O
,	O
singing	O
,	O
At	O
the	O
Tree	O
I	O
shall	O
suffer	O
with	O
Pleasure	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
short	O
Life	O
and	O
a	O
merry	O
one	O
.	O
C.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Information	O
where	O
the	O
Watch	O
and	O
Buckle	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
Johnson	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Corner	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Piggot	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
may	O
be	O
asked	O
whether	O
we	O
had	O
any	O
Arms	O
about	O
us	O
?	O
Corner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Piggot	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
we	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
Fear	O
then	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
This	O
very	O
Watch	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Piggot	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
lent	O
him	O
two	O
Guineas	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Harvey	O
.	O
Johnson	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
waiting	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Rugier	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Piggot	O
,	O
brought	O
this	O
Buckle	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
was	O
waiting	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
sent	O
a	O
Watchman	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
Corner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Buckle	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Waiter	O
at	O
the	O
Turk	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Bow	O
Street	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Piggot	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
Buckle	O
,	O
while	O
Johnson	O
held	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
a	O
Watchman	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Lane	O
;	O
we	O
sat	O
at	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Piggot	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Milk-woman	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Johnson	O
in	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
seeing	O
us	O
,	O
she	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
jumped	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
farther	O
Assistance	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Piggot	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
turned	O
Gentleman	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Douglas	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
at	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Evening	O
as	O
the	O
Prince	O
and	O
Princess	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Play	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Fancy	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Play	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Footman	O
's	O
Gallery	O
;	O
I	O
having	O
no	O
Livery	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
upper	O
Gallery	O
with	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
out	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
step	O
home	O
and	O
make	O
his	O
Appearance	O
and	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
James	O
Street	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sat	O
'till	O
the	O
Watchman	O
came	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
Eleven	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
Beer	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
not	O
chusing	O
to	O
drink	O
any	O
more	O
Beer	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
towards	O
Tottenham	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
something	O
that	O
was	O
good	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
we	O
crossed	O
over	O
towards	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
behind	O
a	O
little	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
Johnson	O
cry	O
our	O
Hort	O
!	O
Hort	O
!	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
indecent	O
Posture	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
expose	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
his	O
Watch	O
and	O
both	O
his	O
Buckles	O
;	O
but	O
recollecting	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
when	O
I	O
go	O
home	O
having	O
lost	O
both	O
my	O
Buckles	O
,	O
``	O
the	O
people	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
will	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
pawned	O
``	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
we	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Buckles	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
Farrel	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Piggot	O
served	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
Months	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bagnio	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cormond	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
keeps	O
a	O
Bagnio	O
in	O
Suffolk	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Piggot	O
two	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
three	O
Months	O
and	O
during	O
that	O
Time	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Piggot	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Piggot	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
well	O
known	O
,	O
that	O
never	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
alledged	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Johnson	O
from	O
his	O
Infancy	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
or	O
saw	O
any	O
Harm	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Veer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
Infancy	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Sawyer	O
by	O
Trade	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Body	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
misbehaving	O
Word	O
till	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
nor	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
Years	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Body	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
ill	O
Word	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Piggot	O
lived	O
a	O
Servant	O
with	O
my	O
Husband	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
very	O
reputable	O
public	O
House	O
in	O
Clare-Market	O
and	O
have	O
entrusted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Piggot	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Johnson	O
is	O
a	O
Sawyer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
'till	O
now	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Liston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Johnson	O
these	O
five	O
Years	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
'till	O
now	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Scafe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
foul	O
Thing	O
of	O
Johnson	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Johnson	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
12	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
thought	O
him	O
a	O
sober	O
Fellow	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
received	O
and	O
paid	O
Money	O
for	O
me	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
defrauded	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
indifferent	O
Character	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
belongs	O
to	O
a	O
Gaming	O
Table	O
in	O
the	O
Piazza	O
,	O
Convent	O
Garden	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
five	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
Lord	O
Mordington	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
Cook	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
Porter	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
Gaming	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
he	O
can	O
play	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
Game	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
18	O
Ann	B-pers
(	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Stanbourn	I-pers
)	I-pers
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
flaxen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Linsey	O
Wolsey	O
Bed	O
Curtains	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Melvin	I-pers
.	O
in	O
a	O
Lodging	O
let	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Melvin	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Stanbourn	O
,	O
Feb.	O
15th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
19.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper-pot	O
and	O
Cover	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
;	O
April	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
20.	O
George	B-pers
Chiverton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
same	O
Rabbits	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Pierce	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
April	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Charles	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
Wt	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
Freehold	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hamlington	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
April	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Richard	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Robert	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Pen-knife	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
an	O
Iron	O
Key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
11	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
;	O
Feb.	O
12	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Request	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Headborough	O
last	O
Year	O
for	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Parish	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12	O
of	O
February	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
William	O
Alley	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Drum-Alley	B-place
in	I-place
Drury-Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
People	O
came	O
with	O
Clubs	O
,	O
Sticks	O
and	O
Hangers	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
bail	O
him	O
.	O
Immediately	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
into	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
Hunt	O
,	O
Cassody	O
,	O
and	O
Timms	O
who	O
are	O
executed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
who	O
are	O
fled	O
to	O
Ireland	O
,	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
did	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stamped	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
turned	O
my	O
Left-hand	O
Breeches-Pocket	O
the	O
wrong	O
Side	O
outwards	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
into	O
Holsford	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
South	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Hunt	O
and	O
Timms	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
towards	O
Clare-market	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
From	O
that	O
Time	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
Cary	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
among	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
used	O
you	O
in	O
this	O
Manner	O
?	O
Rhodes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
stamped	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
.	O
Rhodes	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
I	O
drest	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Rhodes	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
Clothes	O
on	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
his	O
Wig	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
Light	O
did	O
he	O
see	O
me	O
?	O
Rhodes	O
.	O
The	O
People	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
play	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Link-men	O
about	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Alley	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
some	O
people	O
had	O
not	O
come	O
with	O
Lights	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
killed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
this	O
Alley	O
from	O
the	O
Play-House	O
?	O
Rhodes	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
just	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Playhouse-passage	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Swinney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
Mr.	O
South	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Holsford	O
's	O
Alley	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Club	O
of	O
Irishmen	O
,	O
which	O
used	O
to	O
meet	O
there	O
and	O
spend	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
every	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
.	O
One	O
Evening	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
in	O
Drum-Alley	O
,	O
to	O
inform	O
the	O
Club	O
,	O
that	O
Robinson	O
was	O
taken	O
:	O
Immediately	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Mopsticks	O
and	O
Broomsticks	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
rescue	O
Robinson	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Timms	O
,	O
Cassody	O
,	O
Hunt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
long	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
brought	O
Robinson	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
Gin	O
and	O
Twopenny	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
themselves	O
merry	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
this	O
House	O
of	O
South	O
's	O
a	O
common	O
Receptacle	O
for	O
lewd	O
Women	O
?	O
Swinney	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
every	O
body	O
is	O
welcome	O
to	O
come	O
for	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
I	O
dreft	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Swinney	O
.	O
As	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
brown	O
Coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
a	O
Wig	O
as	O
he	O
wears	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
dark	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
light	O
Coat	O
?	O
Swinney	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
darker	O
than	O
that	O
which	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
she	O
get	O
her	O
living	O
?	O
Swinney	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
Service	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
at	O
South	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
ever	O
saw	O
me	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
before	O
or	O
since	O
?	O
Swinney	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Club	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Times	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Has	O
not	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
since	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Consinement	O
,	O
frequently	O
promised	O
you	O
your	O
Liberty	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
me	O
?	O
Swinney	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Atley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
Robinson	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Rhodes	O
went	O
into	O
Drum-Alley	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Maccleaver	I-pers
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
into	O
Holsford	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
whole	O
Posse	O
of	O
Irishmen	O
came	O
with	O
Broomsticks	O
and	O
other	O
Weapons	O
,	O
and	O
rescued	O
Robinson	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
Rhodes	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
about	O
6	O
Yards	O
into	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
Hunt	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
Timms	O
stood	O
over	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
who	O
stamped	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
kill	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
Money	O
he	O
lost	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Atley	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
South	O
's	O
in	O
Holsford	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
broke	O
,	O
through	O
which	O
we	O
saw	O
Timms	O
,	O
Hunt	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Hunt	O
said	O
,	O
B	O
-	O
d	O
and	O
W	O
-	O
s	O
Boys	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
drink	O
and	O
be	O
merry	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
I	O
drest	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Atley	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
darker	O
colour	O
'd	O
Coat	O
on	O
then	O
than	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
strait-bodied	O
Coat	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
great	O
Coat	O
?	O
Atley	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
strait-bodied	O
Coat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
declare	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
last	O
Week	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
unless	O
Rhodes	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
of	O
Hand	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
Atley	O
.	O
There	O
never	O
was	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
he	O
get	O
his	O
living	O
?	O
Atley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
my	O
Trade	O
now	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jasper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
help	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
'till	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
from	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
?	O
Jasper	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
little	O
Way	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
lower	O
than	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
several	O
Times	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
a-bed	O
.	O
He	O
afterwards	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ill.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
Time	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
after	O
you	O
was	O
a-bed	O
?	O
Jasper	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
Time	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
was	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
Time	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ginn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Birtworth	O
,	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Coach-maker	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
commonly	O
rise	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Work	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
5	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
have	O
found	O
my	O
Doors	O
locked	O
and	O
bolted	O
:	O
Besides	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
Vermin	O
(	O
a	O
Dog	O
)	O
that	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
any	O
Body	O
come	O
in	O
or	O
go	O
out	O
without	O
alarming	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
Doors	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
to	O
a	O
Taylor	O
to	O
alter	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
an	O
old	O
Coat	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
My	O
People	O
are	O
always	O
a-bed	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
9	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bolt	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
fasten	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
C.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Ginn	O
.	O
About	O
3	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
was	O
a	O
civil	O
Man	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
C.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
other	O
Lodgers	O
besides	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Ginn	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
2	O
young	O
Men	O
,	O
Oliver	O
and	O
Jasper	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
sick	O
from	O
the	O
7th	O
to	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
his	O
Clothes	O
from	O
the	O
Taylor	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
from	O
the	O
7th	O
to	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Key	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
Vermin	O
that	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
or	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
C.	O
For	O
near	O
20	O
Days	O
did	O
no	O
body	O
come	O
into	O
,	O
or	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Ginn	O
.	O
Not	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
is	O
constantly	O
locked	O
up	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
8	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
from	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
killed	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
another	O
Man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
how	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
employed	O
himself	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
?	O
Ginn	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
supplied	O
him	O
with	O
Necessaries	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
We	O
desire	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
as	O
he	O
daily	O
goes	O
out	O
to	O
Work	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
be	O
positive	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
at	O
Home	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
abroad	O
?	O
Ginn	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Breakfast	O
,	O
Dinner	O
and	O
Supper	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ginn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Wife	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Home	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
on	O
Jasper	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
Ill	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
by	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Token	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
Frying-pan	O
,	O
to	O
fry	O
some	O
Flounders	O
for	O
Jasper	O
's	O
Dinner	O
.	O
He	O
continued	O
with	O
Jasper	O
the	O
whole	O
Evening	O
,	O
'till	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
Time	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Room	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
before	O
9	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
sick	O
Man	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
bed	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
while	O
afterwards	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Bedfellow	O
,	O
Oliver	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
fasten	O
the	O
Door	O
for	O
every	O
body	O
was	O
a-bed	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Oliver	O
,	O
has	O
lodged	O
with	O
us	O
7	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
Account	O
has	O
a	O
Key	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
fastened	O
his	O
Door	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Coat	O
which	O
my	O
Husband	O
lent	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
on	O
that	O
Day	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Days	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
Oliver	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
Ginn	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
Key	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
to	O
interrupt	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
Dog	O
which	O
we	O
keep	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
and	O
Atley	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
together	O
.	O
Atley	O
told	O
Berry	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Rhodes	O
's	O
about	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
's	O
Affair	O
;	O
that	O
Rhodes	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
any	O
Thing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Berry	O
advised	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Atley	O
then	O
said	O
Rhodes	O
had	O
used	O
him	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
unless	O
he	O
(	O
Rhodes	O
)	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
Note	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Coach	O
Wheeler	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
out	O
of	O
Business	O
at	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Wild	O
Street	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harball	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
writing	O
Office	O
in	O
Horseshoe-Court	O
near	O
Carey	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
one	O
Beck	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
last	O
March	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
during	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
frequently	O
sat	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
Business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
use	O
to	O
sit	O
up	O
on	O
a	O
Night	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
Harball	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
he	O
has	O
sat	O
up	O
all	O
Night	O
;	O
sometimes	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
Times	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
work	O
longer	O
than	O
nine	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
Lewkener	O
's	O
Lane	O
or	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
Victuals	O
given	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Fetter-Lane	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
.	O
I	O
write	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Harball	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Fellow	O
Clerk	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
was	O
very	O
industrious	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
frequently	O
set	O
up	O
o'Nights	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Bread	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
no	O
Occasion	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
did	O
he	O
usually	O
leave	O
Mr.	O
Harball	O
's	O
?	O
Beck	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
gone	O
Home	O
at	O
eleven	O
and	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Brother	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
dirty	O
Action	O
before	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fetter	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seven	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
that	O
Time	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
,	O
a	O
Proctor	O
in	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Commons	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1740	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
24.	O
Edward	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Edkins	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Linen	O
Sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Bed-quilt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
Stewpan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
Lodging	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Elliot	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Spencer	O
and	O
Edkins	O
;	O
April	O
14	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wagney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Linen	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Linen	O
Mob	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
;	O
May	O
14	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26.	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Cavenagh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Roger	I-pers
Connor	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth-pocket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
1	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Roger	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
;	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Desire	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Plumbtree-Street	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
Butter	O
and	O
Sugar	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
to	O
Denmark-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
at	O
a	O
Distance	O
,	O
standing	O
still	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Face	O
perfectly	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
the	O
Lamps	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
off	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
a	O
Word	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
certainly	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
d.	O
or	O
3	O
Halfpence	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
strove	O
to	O
creep	O
home	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
found	O
by	O
a	O
Milkman	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
agrees	O
exactly	O
with	O
that	O
piece	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
behind	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
know	O
me	O
that	O
Night	O
?	O
Connor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
burst	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
lett	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
Distance	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Connor	O
.	O
About	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
Yards	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
Light	O
could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
them	O
?	O
Connor	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
Light	O
of	O
a	O
Lamp	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Yards	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
how	O
far	O
she	O
was	O
from	O
a	O
House	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
?	O
Connor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
Houses	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
did	O
she	O
leave	O
the	O
Shop	O
where	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
Sugar	O
?	O
Connor	O
.	O
Between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
her	O
pocket	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
she	O
take	O
the	O
Watchman	O
from	O
his	O
Stand	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
me	O
?	O
Connor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Watchman	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
body	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
quite	O
clear	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Atterbury	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Thursday	O
in	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Cobler	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Cobler	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
stab	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
handcuffed	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
that	O
2	O
other	O
Men	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
Humphries	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
by	O
ourselves	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
a	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
some	O
Money	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
puff	O
no	O
body	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
that	O
Day	O
?	O
Atterbury	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
entrusted	O
with	O
me	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
?	O
Atterbury	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
us	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
every	O
particular	O
Word	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
light	O
on	O
me	O
?	O
Atterbury	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Kensington	O
Gravel-pits	O
,	O
to	O
meet	O
Mr.	O
Jenkinson	O
,	O
an	O
Attorney	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
happening	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Mob	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
charged	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
at	O
Work	O
that	O
Week	O
?	O
Atterbury	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
House-carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
at	O
it	O
sometimes	O
,	O
in	O
doing	O
Jobbs	O
for	O
one	O
and	O
another	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Milkman	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
my	O
Business	O
,	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
did	O
he	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
Seven	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Bristol	O
about	O
2	O
Months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
wanting	O
private	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Room	O
in	O
Cornor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
One	O
Night	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
Time	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Connor	O
's	O
Husband	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
returned	O
as	O
dirty	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
rolled	O
in	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
that	O
three	O
Men	O
were	O
concerned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
knocked	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Connor	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Porter	O
.	O
Her	O
Husband	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
why	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
Butter	O
and	O
Sugar	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
fetch	O
'd	O
him	O
some	O
white	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
brown	O
Sugar	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
3	O
pounds	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
each	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Gold	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Connor	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Porter	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
handed	O
the	O
Guinea	O
over	O
the	O
Counter	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
DEFENCE	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
's	O
Husband	O
is	O
a	O
Smugler	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
one	O
Kennedy	O
,	O
a	O
Smugler	O
,	O
who	O
lodges	O
in	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
calling	O
me	O
Informer	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
Discovery	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Tea	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
lying	O
in	O
wait	O
to	O
shoot	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
made	O
this	O
Discovery	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
sworn	O
fastly	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
one	O
Kennedy	O
,	O
a	O
Smugler	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Connor	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
to	O
bail	O
him	O
:	O
accordingly	O
I	O
told	O
Connor	O
the	O
Story	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
bail	O
Kennedy	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Connor	O
threaten	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
informed	O
against	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Lodgers	O
?	O
Kelly	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
nothing	O
else	O
said	O
by	O
Connor	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Katharine	O
Kelly	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Wife	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
say	O
very	O
true	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
Night	O
that	O
Connor	O
says	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
Oatmeal	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
little	O
Broth	O
for	O
himself	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
Supper	O
ready	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
staid	O
'till	O
near	O
one	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
declare	O
on	O
my	O
Oath	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
left	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
my	O
coming	O
away	O
.	O
His	O
Wife	O
is	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Children	O
were	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Longhton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to-day	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Atterbury	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
extravagant	O
Fellow	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
spent	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
perjure	O
himself	O
?	O
Loughton	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
that	O
-	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
judge	O
of	O
people	O
's	O
Consciences	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
troublesome	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Atterbury	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
Gate	O
to	O
Day	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
hang	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
drive	O
all	O
Kensington	O
Gravel-pits	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
5	O
Weeks	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
sick	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Children	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pot	O
boiling	O
on	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Breast	O
of	O
Mutton	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
just	O
as	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Bell	O
rung	O
Nine	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
went	O
Eleven	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Kelly	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
is	O
Gough	O
,	O
behind	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
recollect	O
the	O
Time	O
?	O
Graham	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
