TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS	O
of	O
PEACE	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
16th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Heathcote	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
GEORGE	B-pers
HEATHCOTE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
PARKER	O
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
WRIGHT	O
,	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRANGE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
Mr	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Meakins	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Pyner	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Phillipson	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Winkworth	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Paskal	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Innever	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Northcot	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Deschamps	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sandwith	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Harrop	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bouchier	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Stowell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Tredgold	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Martha	B-pers
Leaver	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
laced	O
Mob	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Apartment	O
at	O
the	O
Treasury	O
,	O
May	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Ann	B-pers
Molloy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
June	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
3.	O
Mary	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bisse	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
one	O
flowered	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Leghorn	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Wastcoats	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
23	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Day	O
three	O
Weeks	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
my	O
Room	O
double	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
this	O
Poker	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Feet	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Staple	O
of	O
the	O
Lock	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodges	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Floor	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Poker	O
belongs	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
:	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
to	O
Mr	O
Matthews	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
my	O
Stays	O
to	O
a	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Bisse	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
this	O
Gown	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
this	O
good	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Chesham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
Wastcoat	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
or	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
showed	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Simpson	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Ruby	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
val	O
.	O
21	O
s.	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Flaxen	O
Sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crachnell	I-pers
,	O
May	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
William	B-pers
Fennymore	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Mantelet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Pilgrim	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
sundry	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Finkell	I-pers
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Finkell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Lodging	O
,	O
in	O
College-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
for	O
a	O
Month	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
at	O
next	O
Door	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Keys	O
of	O
several	O
Houses	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Enquiry	O
,	O
the	O
Neighbours	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
Times	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
let	O
himself	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
Lodging	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Friend	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Rainford	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
his	O
Wife	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
23	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
,	O
called	O
Guineas	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
June	O
21	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
6	O
,	O
7.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Millinton	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Money	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
.	O
Three	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
23	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
2	O
Drawer	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
.	O
I	O
taxed	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
who	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
stood	O
very	O
strongly	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
from	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
till	O
Tuesday	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Millinton	I-pers
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs	O
Millinton	O
should	O
say	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
into	O
the	O
Bag	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
can	O
say	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
at	O
this	O
Juncture	O
Ann	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
came	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
oh	O
!	O
have	O
I	O
caught	O
you	O
;	O
whereupon	O
Millington	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
give	O
Wright	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
she	O
will	O
blow	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
her	O
any	O
promise	O
of	O
showing	O
her	O
Favour	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
confessed	O
.	O
Staples	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
spoke	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
her	O
no	O
Promise	O
.	O
-	O
Dawson	O
proved	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
Justice	O
Dennet	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
Millinton	O
and	O
Wright	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
an	O
Out-House	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr	O
Edward	B-pers
Newins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
three	O
Fowls	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sack	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stockall	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
10.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Alban	I-place
Woodstreet	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
of	O
Portugal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
,	O
called	O
Guineas	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
half	O
Guinea	O
,	O
val	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Bird-Cage	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Wood	O
street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Drawer	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
say	O
how	O
much	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
2	O
Guineas	O
positively	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
counted	O
the	O
Money	O
the	O
Night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
near	O
50	O
Guineas	O
.	O
The	O
Drawer	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bespoke	O
a	O
new	O
Suit	O
of	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Wigg	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Master	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
inquire	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
any	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
borrowed	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
close	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
immediately	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
desired	O
his	O
Box	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
down	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
Key	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
you	O
last	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
mentions	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
three	O
Sixpences	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
promises	O
of	O
Indulgence	O
before	O
he	O
confessed	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Jury	O
will	O
consider	O
that	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Jury	O
will	O
consider	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
16	O
Years	O
with	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
11.	O
William	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
Barkin	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pound	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12.	O
James	B-pers
Maccoy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Wastcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
and	O
other	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Bradock	I-pers
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Bradock	I-pers
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Slop-Shop	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
several	O
Goods	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
redeemed	O
out	O
of	O
Pawn	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
myself	O
over-against	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
deny	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
Mercy	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Mr	O
Stone	O
's	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Balderston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
Stone	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
brought	O
me	O
these	O
Goods	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
private	O
Mark	O
on	O
them	O
to	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Col.	O
De	O
Veil	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
bringing	O
that	O
Wastcoat	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Defence	O
,	O
only	O
desired	O
Mercy	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
confounded	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
can	O
say	O
I	O
ever	O
wronged	O
my	O
Master	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
John	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Martha	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Washington	I-pers
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
High-way	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Leather	O
Pocket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
42	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Washington	I-pers
,	O
June	O
30	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Washington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Denmark	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Young	O
came	O
upon	O
me	O
on	O
a	O
Surprise	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
down	O
my	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Leather	O
Pocket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
42	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
Man	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
;	O
no	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
her	O
.	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ca	O
n't	O
go	O
to	O
Law	O
with	O
us	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
Man	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Purse	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
Answer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
any	O
Time	O
acquainted	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Washington	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Butcher	O
in	O
Clare-Market	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Groat	O
for	O
roasting	O
a	O
Green	O
Goose	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
Wings	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
this	O
Minute	O
to	O
die	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
come	O
before	O
or	O
behind	O
you	O
?	O
Washington	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
upon	O
me	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
the	O
Purse	O
down	O
your	O
Stays	O
?	O
Washington	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
down	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
go	O
strait-laced	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
run	O
his	O
Hand	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
hurt	O
my	O
Flesh	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
under	O
any	O
Surprize	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
your	O
Shoulder	O
?	O
Washington	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
some	O
Surprize	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
Body	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
a	O
Man	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
always	O
put	O
your	O
Money	O
in	O
your	O
Bosom	O
?	O
Washington	O
.	O
I	O
generally	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
declare	O
before	O
Col.	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
People	O
met	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
behind	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
you	O
?	O
Washington	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
For	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
which	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
offer	O
before	O
Col.	O
De	O
Veil	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
Matter	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
general	O
Release	O
?	O
Washington	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
abide	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
till	O
the	O
Day	O
I	O
die	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
my	O
Defence	O
to	O
those	O
Persons	O
who	O
were	O
at	O
Supper	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
done	O
out	O
of	O
Spite	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
against	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
selling	O
of	O
spirituous	O
Liquors	O
,	O
whereby	O
I	O
incurred	O
the	O
Penalty	O
of	O
ten	O
Pounds	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
rioted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
Life	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Times	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Brogden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Col.	O
De	O
Veil	O
's	O
Clerk	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
for	O
obstructing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
his	O
Office	O
as	O
a	O
Bailiff	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
afterwards	O
indeed	O
agree	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
Release	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
do	O
it	O
:	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
Young	O
brought	O
half	O
a	O
Score-Witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
-	O
Saltmarsh	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Young	O
's	O
House	O
from	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Nine	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
,	O
to	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Ten	O
that	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
Young	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
in	O
Eagle-Court	O
,	O
facing	O
Somerset-House	O
.	O
And	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Denmark-Court	O
is	O
about	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
from	O
hence	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
.	O
-	O
Tooly	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
at	O
Young	O
's	O
House	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
this	O
Day	O
Fortnight	O
at	O
Supper	O
on	O
Mackarel	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
at	O
half	O
and	O
Hour	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
9	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
till	O
near	O
11	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
from	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Nine	O
till	O
near	O
Eleven	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Women	O
a	O
scolding	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
Women	O
they	O
are	O
always	O
a	O
scolding	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
Dog	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
revenged	O
on	O
you	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Biggs	O
and	O
Mrs	O
West	O
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutrix	O
is	O
a	O
wicked	O
vile	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
Young	O
had	O
used	O
her	O
ill	O
in	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
inform	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
selling	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Warrant	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
Day	O
Fortnight	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
robbing	O
then	O
.	O
-	O
Halfpenny	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
threaten	O
Young	O
and	O
say	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
hang	O
him	O
herself	O
somebody	O
else	O
should	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Washington	I-pers
desired	O
to	O
call	O
some	O
Persons	O
to	O
her	O
Character	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Poet	I-pers
had	O
known	O
her	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
14.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
Pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
Shoes	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christian	B-pers
Crul	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Christian	B-pers
Crul	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
-	O
Anne	B-pers
Crul	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Neighbour	O
follow	O
her	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
a	O
Bundle	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Cloak	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bretland	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Dunbar	I-pers
,	O
July	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
16.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Elmes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Gallot	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cleaver	I-pers
,	O
July	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
James	B-pers
Nowland	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bryers	I-pers
,	O
July	O
2	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bryers	I-pers
.	O
On	O
July	O
2	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
to	O
Mr	O
Vincent	O
's	O
,	O
some	O
Carpenters	O
who	O
were	O
at	O
Work	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
your	O
young	O
Man	O
has	O
given	O
you	O
the	O
Slip	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Watch	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
last	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
brought	O
before	O
Justice	O
Morrice	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clack	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
sold	O
this	O
Watch	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
12th	O
Instant	O
for	O
37	O
s.	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
30	O
s.	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mannack	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mascall	I-pers
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
his	O
Property	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mascall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Collec	O
tor	O
of	O
the	O
Toll	O
at	O
Fulham	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
this	O
Woman	O
sate	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Step	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
somebody	O
that	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
Bridge	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
opened	O
my	O
Drawer	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
20	O
s.	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
wooden	O
Piggin	O
.	O
About	O
5	O
Weeks	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Place	O
at	O
Fulham	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
it	O
one	O
Shilling	O
per	O
Week	O
,	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
Toil	O
Room	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
before	O
Col.	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
guilty	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
intimated	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
to	O
permit	O
Freedoms	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
however	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
consent	O
;	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
Evidence	O
to	O
support	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
20.	O
William	B-pers
Rusdell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
ravishing	O
Sanders	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
eight	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
ten	O
Years	O
;	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Will	O
and	O
Consent	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sanders	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
carnally	O
knowing	O
the	O
said	O
Sanders	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
May	O
31	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
with	O
this	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
Rusdell	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Sanders	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
together	O
;	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Breeches	O
were	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
and	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Child	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
Child	O
get	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Child	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
also	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
else	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
Bed	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Child	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Oh	O
!	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
pulled	O
up	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
tore	O
my	O
Cap	O
off	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
Bed	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
made	O
him	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
Answer	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
complained	O
of	O
nothing	O
else	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pulled	O
up	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
and	O
tore	O
her	O
Cap	O
off	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
Misfortune	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edmonds	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
her	O
any	O
Damage	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edmonds	O
how	O
it	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
there	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Mr.	O
Edmonds	O
and	O
his	O
Servant	O
both	O
examined	O
the	O
Child	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Edmond	O
's	O
shook	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
proper	O
the	O
Fellow	O
should	O
be	O
secured	O
:	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
received	O
Damage	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Attempt	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
down	O
again	O
by	O
his	O
Order	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
looked	O
upon	O
the	O
Child	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Ointment	O
,	O
to	O
anoint	O
the	O
Child	O
in	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
affected	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edmonds	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
June	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
complained	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
been	O
misused	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Child	O
might	O
be	O
examined	O
;	O
so	O
my	O
Master	O
and	O
I	O
both	O
examined	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
externally	O
there	O
were	O
very	O
great	O
Bruises	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
Part	O
;	O
and	O
internally	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Excoriation	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
Inflammation	O
attending	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
was	O
evident	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
Attempt	O
made	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
Excoriation	O
and	O
Inflammation	O
might	O
be	O
occasioned	O
by	O
an	O
external	O
Attempt	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
Observation	O
when	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
brought	O
again	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
Application	O
of	O
the	O
Medicines	O
given	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
21.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
14	O
Ells	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
called	O
Washed	O
Dowlas	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Setcole	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Setcole	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
West-Smithfield	B-place
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Holland	O
;	O
her	O
Behaviour	O
during	O
the	O
Time	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Servants	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
Mr	O
Walker	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
offered	O
his	O
Service	O
and	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
washed	O
Dowlas	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
about	O
10	O
Minutes	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Cloth	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
running	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
sitting	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Godsehall	I-pers
,	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
Fact	O
privately	O
to	O
us	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
before	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Godschall	I-pers
.	O
-	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
she	O
had	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
Servant	O
show	O
her	O
the	O
Cloth	O
or	O
yourself	O
?	O
Mr	O
Setcole	O
.	O
My	O
Servant	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
agreed	O
for	O
three	O
Ells	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
one	O
Shilling	O
in	O
part	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Mr	O
Setcole	O
's	O
Shop	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
bargaining	O
with	O
Mr	O
Setcole	O
's	O
Servant	O
for	O
some	O
cloth	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
Mr	O
Setcole	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
Cloth	O
;	O
he	O
talked	O
of	O
sending	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
follow	O
her	O
myself	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
a	O
Court	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cloth	O
then	O
coming	O
from	O
under	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
called	O
her	O
Madam	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
fine	O
damask	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
fine	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
-	O
Madam	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr	O
Setcole	O
's	O
the	O
Draper	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
you	O
came	O
;	O
she	O
immediately	O
took	O
the	O
Cloth	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Cloysters	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
one	O
Knee	O
and	O
dropped	O
the	O
Cloth	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
with	O
Design	O
of	O
leaving	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
into	O
Mr	O
Setcole	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
a	O
little	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
run	O
,	O
slipp	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
threw	O
the	O
Cloth	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
another	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
which	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Piece	O
which	O
she	O
brought	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
thrown	O
down	O
before	O
;	O
immediately	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
that	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
and	O
threw	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Mr	O
Setcole	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
your	O
Cloth	O
?	O
for	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Cloth	O
which	O
that	O
Woman	O
took	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
and	O
brought	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
a	O
Mark	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Setcole	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Cloth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Mark	O
by	O
which	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
Property	O
.	O
-	O
Setcole	O
.	O
Yes	O
!	O
the	O
Mark	O
is	O
upon	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Mark	O
.	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Counting-House	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
while	O
Mr	O
Setcole	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
begged	O
hard	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
send	O
her	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
or	O
any	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
she	O
ever	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
4	O
Children	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
her	O
any	O
Promise	O
of	O
Favour	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
Mr	O
Setcole	O
?	O
Mr	O
Setcole	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
her	O
Justice	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mabbs	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
to	O
Mr	O
Setcole	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
some	O
Holland	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
several	O
Pieces	O
,	O
whereof	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
one	O
:	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
we	O
were	O
agreeing	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
Coat	O
,	O
sometimes	O
shuffling	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
should	O
drop	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
immediately	O
imagined	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
us	O
of	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
agreed	O
for	O
the	O
Holland	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
cut	O
off	O
three	O
Ells	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
Paper	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Shilling	O
Earnest	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
agreed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
Servant	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
Mr	O
Walker	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
ten	O
Minutes	O
Time	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Piece	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
;	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
the	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
pull	O
another	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
off	O
the	O
Counter	O
to	O
smother	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
Piece	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
Piece	O
which	O
I	O
before	O
had	O
missed	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
desired	O
my	O
Master	O
to	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
Knees	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
are	O
so	O
much	O
troubled	O
with	O
these	O
Customers	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
Justice	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
,	O
Mr	O
Setcole	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
detected	O
the	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
Charge	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
Affair	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
Friends	O
and	O
make	O
Satisfaction	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
5	O
Children	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
easy	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
to	O
make	O
Water	O
.	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Water	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
pull	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Coats	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
very	O
willingly	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
Manner	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lead	O
her	O
along	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
her	O
getting	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Cloth	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Mark	O
?	O
-	O
Setcole	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
such	O
upon	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
small	O
Children	O
,	O
her	O
Husband	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
a	O
Perriwig-maker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Years	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
Some	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
,	O
or	O
heard	O
,	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
three	O
small	O
Children	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Craven	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mrs	O
Shirley	O
for	O
about	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
Plain-work	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
an	O
industrious	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
Living	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
justly	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
Children	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
the	O
more	O
surprized	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
nursed	O
her	O
2	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
always	O
paid	O
me	O
honestly	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
House-keeper	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
by	O
Eagle-street	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
industrious	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
worked	O
for	O
her	O
Bread	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gillingham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
has	O
made	O
Shirts	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
22.	O
Mary	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
her	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
16th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Husday	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Husday	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Razor	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
1	O
Penny	O
held	O
in	O
her	O
Right-hand	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Throat	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Husday	O
,	O
did	O
give	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
5	O
Inches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
2	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
likewise	O
charged	O
on	O
to	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
feloniously	O
slaying	O
the	O
said	O
Hussey	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Request	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
making	O
merry	O
with	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Birth-Day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
26	O
years	O
of	O
Age	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Tower-Hill	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
lodged	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
Servant	O
at	O
,	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
's	O
,	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
three	O
Half-pence	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
spend	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
a	O
middle	O
sized	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
Molly	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
talk	O
very	O
lovingly	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
Hamburgh	O
Arms	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
Lodging	O
which	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
tired	O
with	O
waiting	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
goes	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
calls	O
,	O
Molly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Room	O
did	O
they	O
go	O
into	O
?	O
Holder	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
backwards	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Debate	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
In	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
Minutes	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
holding	O
a	O
Hat	O
under	O
his	O
Chin	O
to	O
his	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bleeding	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
standing	O
thus	O
,	O
the	O
Head	O
leaning	O
a	O
little	O
forward	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Hat	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Holder	O
.	O
It	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
Hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Hat	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
Woman	O
's	O
Hat	O
?	O
Holder	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
's	O
black	O
Hat	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Molly	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
about	O
?	O
Molly	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
barbarous	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Reason	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
Barbarity	O
?	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
.	O
At	O
first	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
barbarous	O
as	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
stand	O
so	O
long	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Money	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
?	O
And	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
bleeding	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
barbarous	O
to	O
murder	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
old	O
Rogue	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
call	O
her	O
barbarous	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
Notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
never	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Grubstreet	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
shock	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Man	O
alive	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
bleeding	O
and	O
under	O
his	O
Throat	O
?	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
to	O
see	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
down	O
Stairs	O
very	O
much	O
surprized	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
afterwards	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Right-hand	O
was	O
bloody	O
,	O
her	O
Apron	O
and	O
Neck-Handkerchief	O
were	O
both	O
bloody	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
after	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
last	O
Monday	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
Declaration	O
of	O
this	O
sooner	O
?	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
.	O
Because	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
,	O
by	O
all	O
Accounts	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
wicked	O
,	O
vile	O
Creature	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
live	O
with	O
one	O
Glass	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
?	O
Holder	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
lived	O
with	O
any	O
Body	O
there	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
Merry-making	O
with	O
some	O
Friends	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
Birth	O
day	O
,	O
that	O
coming	O
over	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
she	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
?	O
Which	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
into	O
her	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
)	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
presently	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
:	O
She	O
thought	O
she	O
staid	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
so	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Words	O
pass	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
differed	O
;	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
bleeding	O
very	O
plentifully	O
at	O
the	O
Mouth	O
and	O
Nose	O
.	O
I	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
for	O
some	O
Days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
this	O
Man	O
was	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Portington	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
lie	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
accommodate	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
What	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
?	O
One	O
of	O
her	O
Hands	O
was	O
bloody	O
,	O
her	O
Apron	O
and	O
Neck-Handkerchief	O
a	O
little	O
splashed	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
nor	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
never	O
a	O
Witness	O
in	O
any	O
Case	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Ivers	O
?	O
Partington	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
that	O
I	O
remember	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
soleman	O
Transaction	O
,	O
pray	O
recollect	O
your	O
self	O
.	O
Portington	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
punctual	O
Witness	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Question	O
was	O
,	O
Whether	O
you	O
were	O
not	O
a	O
Witness	O
upon	O
any	O
Occasion	O
?	O
Portington	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
remember	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
never	O
an	O
Oath	O
administred	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Portington	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
Witness	O
for	O
her	O
once	O
in	O
Doctors-Commons	O
?	O
Portington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
once	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
there	O
about	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
they	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
Oath	O
upon	O
this	O
Occasion	O
?	O
Portington	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
Questions	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
my	O
Hand	O
upon	O
a	O
Book	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
subscribing	O
Witness	O
to	O
a	O
Will	O
for	O
Mrs	O
Ivers	O
?	O
Portington	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
lying	O
dead	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Throat	O
cut	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
backwards	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
July	O
2	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
which	O
was	O
formerly	O
the	O
Blue-Anchor	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Ditch	O
Side	O
,	O
on	O
Little-Tower-Hill	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
[	O
R.	O
Holder	O
called	O
again	O
.	O
]	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
,	O
Holder	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
you	O
saw	O
her	O
holding	O
a	O
Hat	O
under	O
his	O
Chin	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Blood	O
running	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
what	O
Position	O
was	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
lying	O
or	O
sitting	O
?	O
Holder	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
standing	O
upright	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
;	O
[	O
leaning	O
her	O
Head	O
a	O
little	O
forward	O
]	O
by	O
the	O
Debate	O
there	O
was	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
wanted	O
some	O
Money	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
his	O
Promise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
this	O
?	O
Holder	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Landing-place	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Door	O
was	O
a-Jarr	O
,	O
not	O
open	O
,	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Bed	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
of	O
Flocks	O
or	O
Feathers	O
lying	O
in	O
an	O
odd	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Waistcoat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
this	O
Man	O
thus	O
bloody	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
struggle	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
Holder	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
called	O
him	O
old	O
Rogue	O
,	O
and	O
Son	O
of	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
h.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
Holder	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
these	O
People	O
have	O
often	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
forging	O
of	O
Seamen	O
's	O
Wills	O
and	O
Powers	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
an	O
Information	O
against	O
14	O
Persons	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
before	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
unhappy	O
Widow	O
of	O
that	O
Rhodes	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
these	O
Practices	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
lodged	O
this	O
Indictment	O
against	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
giving	O
Informations	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
so	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
Wickedness	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
voluntary	O
Confession	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
Reason	O
they	O
seek	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
threaten	O
'd	O
it	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wintx	I-pers
,	O
Deputy	O
to	O
Mr	O
King	O
the	O
Coroner	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
Inquisition	O
to	O
view	O
this	O
Body	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
House	O
by	O
Tower-Ditch	O
;	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
in	O
a	O
Back-room	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Body	O
lying	O
with	O
the	O
Head	O
almost	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
full	O
of	O
conjealed	O
Blood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Razor	O
all	O
bloody	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
Spot	O
of	O
Blood	O
on	O
the	O
Floor	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
me	O
conclude	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
not	O
committed	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Candle	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
Floor	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
thoroughly	O
satisfied	O
:	O
The	O
Head	O
lay	O
upon	O
a	O
Heap	O
of	O
Rubbish	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
Head	O
aside	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Blood	O
under	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
moved	O
the	O
Rubbish	O
with	O
my	O
Foot	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
,	O
which	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
murder	O
'd	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
likewise	O
viewed	O
every	O
Room	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
Blood	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
murdered	O
in	O
that	O
House	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
more	O
Blood	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Body	O
than	O
the	O
Quantity	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Hat	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Room	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
washed	O
lately	O
.	O
Coroner	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
murdered	O
sold	O
Sticks	O
upon	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Husday	I-pers
,	O
-	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
lodge	O
sometimes	O
in	O
one	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
at	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
Night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
Information	O
about	O
12	O
Months	O
ago	O
about	O
forging	O
of	O
Wills	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
that	O
do	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
wrong	O
Widows	O
and	O
Children	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
it	O
please	O
God	O
I	O
live	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
of	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
[	O
Holder	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
.	O
]	O
Court	O
.	O
Consider	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
a	O
Woman	O
when	O
her	O
Life	O
is	O
at	O
stake	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
and	O
give	O
an	O
Information	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
Holder	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
this	O
Mary	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
-	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
discover	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
working	O
,	O
honest	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
bring	O
People	O
to	O
my	O
Character	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
an	O
unreasonable	O
Thing	O
to	O
suppose	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
should	O
see	O
a	O
Man	O
standing	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
bleeding	O
into	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Throat	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
directly	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
23.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brannon	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
June	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24.	O
Mary	B-pers
Donoho	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Davison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Adrian	B-pers
Hannor	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
10	O
.	O
Hannor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
of	O
four	O
Guineas	O
and	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Middle-ward	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Poultry-Compter	I-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Debtor	O
there	O
,	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Breeches	O
under	O
the	O
Quilt	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
her	O
Discharge	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
same	O
Evening	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sick	O
in	O
Bed	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
July	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
Fustic	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
How	O
she	O
could	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
persuaded	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
-	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Vere	I-pers
.	O
On	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
all	O
Prisoners	O
for	O
Debt	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
then	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
attended	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
Nurse	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
here	O
again	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
How	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
barbarous	O
as	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
in	O
distressed	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Wife	O
and	O
four	O
Children	O
to	O
maintain	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
persuaded	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
Debt	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Will	O
and	O
Powers	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
That	O
Time	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
Mr	O
Hannor	O
's	O
Pocket	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
persuade	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Debt	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
South	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Kitson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Abraham	B-pers
Kitson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
,	O
1	O
.	O
Agnes	B-pers
Kitson	I-pers
.	O
Cavenagh	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
down	O
a	O
Parcel	O
and	O
show	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
more	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
difficult	O
,	O
bid	O
me	O
less	O
than	O
they	O
cost	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
:	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
immediately	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Shop-door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
those	O
Men	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
pursued	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
were	O
show	O
'd	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
3	O
in	O
one	O
Piece	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
you	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
Breast	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
but	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
Mrs	O
Coleman	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
under	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
Cellar	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
Man	O
and	O
Lot	O
Cavenagh	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
long	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
make	O
a	O
Motion	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
a	O
Minute	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
Girl	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
in	O
our	O
Cellar	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
go	O
down	O
and	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Girl	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs	O
Kitson	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
Lot	O
Cavenagh	O
*	O
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
Agreement	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
away	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
;	O
she	O
showed	O
us	O
several	O
Parcels	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
came	O
pretty	O
near	O
the	O
Price	O
.	O
*	O
Lot	O
Cavenagh	O
was	O
an	O
Evidence	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
Feb.	O
1738-9.	O
against	O
James	B-pers
Lawlor	I-pers
and	O
james	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
then	O
condemn	O
'd	O
for	O
robbing	O
George	B-pers
Lines	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
them	O
or	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
really	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
be	O
ashamed	O
to	O
own	O
it	O
?	O
Cavenagh	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
both	O
the	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Coat	O
was	O
open	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
Cavenagh	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
them	O
between	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Coat	O
,	O
his	O
Coat	O
was	O
button	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
40	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
two	O
Men	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
us	O
back	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
William	B-pers
South	I-pers
threw	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
into	O
a	O
Cellar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
but	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
in	O
Town	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Service	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
disappointed	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
returning	O
to	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
when	O
the	O
Waggon	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Cavenagh	O
.	O
He	O
proposed	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
first	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
Countrymen	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
for	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Years	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Ealy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
House	O
for	O
Lodgers	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
6	O
Weeks	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Ireland	O
directly	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
bound	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
here	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Aunt	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
Mistress	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
kept	O
good	O
Hours	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Morel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
5	O
Weeks	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Years	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
his	O
Father	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
has	O
run	O
out	O
his	O
Fortune	O
by	O
Extravagance	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
good	O
Hours	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Lot	O
Cavenagh	O
.	O
Cavenagh	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
his	O
Wife	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
over	O
from	O
Ireland	O
together	O
.	O
Morel	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
James	I-pers
Glass	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Ann	O
Cox	O
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
unknown	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
assault	O
Catherine	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
12	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Man	O
unknown	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
ravish	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Catherine	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
the	O
said	O
Man	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
said	O
Rape	O
,	O
Feb.	O
5	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
being	O
produced	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
,	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
how	O
old	O
she	O
was	O
?	O
Catherine	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
12	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
last	O
Sunday	O
.	O
[	O
Being	O
then	O
interrogated	O
concerning	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
Answer	O
,	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Catherine	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Ann	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
is	O
my	O
Mother-in-law	O
,	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
her	O
own	O
Son	O
Webly	O
Cox	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Gravel-Pits	O
at	O
Woolwich	O
,	O
near	O
Plumbtree-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
consent	O
to	O
his	O
lying	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Catherine	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
this	O
Ann	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
do	O
?	O
Catherine	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
.	O
She	O
made	O
a	O
Man	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
-	O
one	O
Thomas	O
,	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
-	O
in	O
the	O
Month	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
she	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Case-knife	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
whilst	O
the	O
Man	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Cellar	O
in	O
Grosvenor's-Mews	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
from	O
Ear	O
to	O
Ear	O
if	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
ever	O
lay	O
either	O
with	O
her	O
or	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
that	O
Thomas	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
lay	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Catherine	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
.	O
She	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Case-knife	O
,	O
and	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
cut	O
my	O
Throat	O
from	O
Ear	O
to	O
Ear	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
resist	O
Thomas	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
?	O
Cath	O
.	O
Glass	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
lie	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Cath	O
.	O
Glass	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
enter	O
your	O
Body	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Cath	O
.	O
Glass	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
by	O
Night	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
Day	O
?	O
Cath	O
.	O
Glass	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
complain	O
of	O
this	O
Injury	O
you	O
received	O
?	O
Cath	O
.	O
Glass	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
complained	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
2	O
Months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
persuaded	O
you	O
to	O
complain	O
of	O
it	O
then	O
?	O
Cath	O
.	O
Glass	O
.	O
My	O
Godmother	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mother-in-law	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
,	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Brother-in-law	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
Thomas	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
?	O
Cath	O
.	O
Glass	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
here	O
Yesterday	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
your	O
Father	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
Cath	O
.	O
Glass	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
this	O
being	O
done	O
?	O
Cath	O
.	O
Glass	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
clean	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
Woolwich	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Triphook	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Godmother	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Girl	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
about	O
two	O
Months	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
come	O
in	O
here	O
for	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Dropsy	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
pass	O
'd	O
from	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Workhouse	O
,	O
to	O
Marybone	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Dropsy	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Dr	O
Ross	O
,	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
as	O
an	O
Out-patient	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
Service	O
to	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Friends	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stripp	O
'd	O
her	O
stark	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
Opinion	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Child	O
:	O
This	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
fetched	O
her	O
from	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
Cellar	O
in	O
Grosvenor	O
's	O
Mews	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
Thomas	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Feet	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
stood	O
over	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
Case-knife	O
,	O
while	O
Thomas	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
tell	O
your	O
Father	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Body	O
else	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
cut	O
her	O
Throat	O
from	O
Ear	O
to	O
Ear	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Thomas	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
did	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Tyburn-Road	O
,	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
the	O
Girl	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
make	O
her	O
confess	O
who	O
the	O
Father	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Father	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
Money	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Jury	O
desired	O
the	O
Matron	O
of	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
might	O
be	O
called	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
the	O
Child	O
had	O
over	O
varied	O
in	O
her	O
Account	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
]	O
Ann	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Matron	O
of	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
any	O
Dealings	O
with	O
Man	O
or	O
Boy	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
Disorder	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Dropsy	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
2	O
Months	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
:	O
Hussey	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
some	O
Body	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
Dropsy	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
must	O
confess	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Overseers	O
will	O
send	O
you	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
her	O
Mother-in-law	O
's	O
Son	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
her	O
Mother-in-law	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
concerning	O
Thomas	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
the	O
Boy	O
Webly	O
Cox	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
this	O
till	O
April	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
vary	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Jer	O
.	O
Longbottom	O
.	O
This	O
Girl	O
's	O
Father	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Matross	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pyle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
lying	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
can	O
swear	O
my	O
Husband	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Pyle	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
Child	O
look	O
big	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Hussey	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
doing	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
with	O
Child	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
Neighbours	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
Child	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
27.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Neale	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
Silk	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Heylin	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Heylin	I-pers
.	O
In	O
April	O
and	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
my	O
Service	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Country	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
understood	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Service	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
My	O
Servant	O
was	O
complaining	O
to	O
the	O
Washerwoman	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
(	O
we	O
discovered	O
it	O
by	O
that	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
to	O
Mr	O
Turner	O
's	O
in	O
White	O
Lyon-Yard	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
her	O
Box	O
we	O
could	O
only	O
find	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
;	O
Mr	O
Turner	O
's	O
Son	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
acted	O
the	O
dishonest	O
Part	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
which	O
she	O
sold	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
I	O
showed	O
him	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
his	O
Relalation	O
had	O
bought	O
such	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Mark	O
of	O
H	O
in	O
the	O
Corner	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
H	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Mark	O
of	O
an	O
H	O
remained	O
;	O
her	O
Box	O
being	O
since	O
searched	O
,	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
that	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
of	O
her	O
one	O
Day	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
visiting	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
Crown	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Edw	B-pers
Heylin	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
that	O
was	O
delivered	O
at	O
Mr	O
Turner	O
's	O
into	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
Hand	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Writings	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
This	O
Apron	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Apron	O
perfectly	O
well	O
,	O
by	O
seeing	O
her	O
wear	O
it	O
at	O
Mr	O
Turner	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Apron	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Apron	O
.	O
-	O
Swafield	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Gloves	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
Mr	O
Heylin	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
William	B-pers
Flemmar	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Flemming	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Silver	I-pers
Keels	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
W.	O
Roberts	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
9	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
designed	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
Leadenhall-street	O
,	O
that	O
Side	O
the	O
India-house	O
is	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
very	O
few	O
Persons	O
;	O
but	O
by	B-place
St	I-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
Corner	I-place
of	I-place
Gracechurch-street	I-place
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
self	O
immediately	O
in	O
a	O
Crowd	O
of	O
People	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
just	O
at	O
my	O
Heels	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
before	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
cross	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
run	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
Eye	O
upon	O
the	O
Chain	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Hallow	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
down	O
Gracechurch-street	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
to	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
gone	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
in	O
vain	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
the	O
People	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Mischance	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
:	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Papers	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
were	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
finding	O
that	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
Person	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
Seven-Night	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry-Compter	O
could	O
tell	O
me	O
something	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Cavenagh	I-pers
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Leek	O
in	O
my	O
Hat	O
,	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
Place	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
Watch	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
:	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
procure	O
me	O
my	O
Watch	O
again	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
procure	O
me	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
Watch	O
is	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
vile	O
Villain	O
will	O
swear	O
away	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cavenagh	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Bryers	I-pers
,	O
and	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
to	O
rob	O
any	O
Person	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
conveniently	O
:	O
We	O
went	O
from	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
Mr	O
Roberts	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
W.	O
Bryers	O
passed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
seized	O
his	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
any	O
farther	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
the	O
Watch	O
which	O
is	O
now	O
produced	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Watch	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
run	O
down	O
Gracechurch-street	O
immediately	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
the	O
Watch	O
jointly	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Jack	O
the	O
Sailor	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
of	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
this	O
vile	O
Rogue	O
is	O
only	O
going	O
to	O
swear	O
my	O
Life	O
away	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
now	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Woodstreet-Compter	O
,	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
a	O
Hair	O
of	O
my	O
Head	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
only	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Information	O
stronger	O
than	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Mary	B-pers
Broomhall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Andrew	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Broomhall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Broomhall	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
in	O
bodily	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Stock-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
July	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
Seven-Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Holbourn	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
carry	O
this	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs	O
Savage	O
's	O
,	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
such	O
Person	O
,	O
unless	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
if	O
any	O
such	O
Person	O
lived	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
she	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
lodged	O
there	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
she	O
shut	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Bundle	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Bundle	O
safe	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
lodged	O
,	O
she	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Red	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
searched	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
Silver	O
Knee-Buckles	O
,	O
one	O
Silver	O
Stock-Buckle	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
tearing	O
the	O
Paper	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
strove	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Linnen	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
Linnen	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
,	O
Mr	O
Peter	O
Keysterman	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Hambro	O
Merchant	O
,	O
in	O
Lawrence	O
Pountney-lane	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
sent	O
it	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
has	O
no	O
Servant	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
-	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
Linnen	O
,	O
I	O
complained	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
misused	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Fore-room	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
Shutters	O
to	O
the	O
Windows	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
manage	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Woman	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
but	O
herself	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
more	O
below	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Nath	O
White	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Brother	O
Constable	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Parish	O
,	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
White-Swan	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
lend	O
me	O
your	O
Staff	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Fore-Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Back-Door	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
a	O
Court	O
in	O
Shoe	O
-lane	O
)	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
asked	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
the	O
Thing	O
up	O
as	O
easy	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
any	O
Answer	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
sometimes	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
good	O
Words	O
and	O
sometimes	O
bad	O
,	O
she	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
Promise	O
that	O
no	O
Body	O
should	O
come	O
up	O
Stairs	O
but	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
below	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
Body	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
that	O
Day	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
bid	O
two	O
Women	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
Back-room	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
mov	O
'd	O
a	O
Chair	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Knee-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stock	O
buckle	O
lay	O
under	O
the	O
Chair	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
whether	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
or	O
who	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
will	O
prove	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
this	O
Knee-buckle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Stock-buckle	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
And	O
he	O
pointed	O
immediately	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
he	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
aiding	O
,	O
or	O
assisting	O
,	O
or	O
have	O
the	O
other	O
Buckle	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
me	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
Women	O
in	O
Company	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
touch	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
persidious	O
Case	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
know	O
[	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
]	O
what	O
pasied	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
Back-room	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
such	O
Boys	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
Drams	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
prithee	O
,	O
Boy	O
,	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
Business	O
;	O
says	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
Boy	O
have	O
a	O
Dram	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
2	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Back	O
room	O
with	O
them	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Back-room	O
with	O
these	O
Women	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
assure	O
you	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
all	O
Spight	O
in	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Sister	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Broomhall	I-pers
's	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
Her	O
Name	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
generally	O
reputed	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
of	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30	O
,	O
31.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
their	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
maliciously	O
,	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
did	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
farther	O
sets	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Stephen	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
open	O
Place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
cross	O
a	O
wooden	O
Rail	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
did	O
cast	O
and	O
throw	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
Face	O
,	O
Breast	O
,	O
and	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
several	O
mortal	O
Bruises	O
did	O
give	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Bruises	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
languished	O
from	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
to	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
,	O
and	O
assisting	O
the	O
said	O
Stephen	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
to	O
commit	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Stephen	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
maliciously	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
staying	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
.	O
After	O
the	O
Counsel	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Cause	O
,	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
were	O
called	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Root	I-pers
.	O
Cooke	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
Mourning-Lane	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Hackney	I-place
Parish	I-place
:	O
This	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Mr	O
Price	O
,	O
came	O
riding	O
along	O
the	O
Road	O
by	O
us	O
full	O
speed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
rode	O
over	O
Cooke	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
knocked	O
off	O
their	O
Horses	O
for	O
riding	O
so	O
fast	O
.	O
Clark	O
comes	O
up	O
to	O
Cooke	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
dismounted	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
Cooke	O
held	O
his	O
Spade	O
against	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
,	O
over	O
his	O
own	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
Clark	O
had	O
the	O
Butt	O
End	O
of	O
his	O
Whip	O
over	O
Cooke	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
-	O
Cooke	O
held	O
his	O
Spade	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
was	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
Whip	O
or	O
the	O
Space	O
?	O
Root	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
the	O
Spade	O
was	O
held	O
up	O
before	O
Clark	O
had	O
his	O
Whip	O
up	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
was	O
up	O
first	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
this	O
Mr	O
Price	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
-	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
a	O
few	O
Words	O
more	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
2	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
-	O
Root	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
not	O
you	O
working	O
in	O
a	O
Ditch	O
?	O
Root	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
level	O
Ground	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
Ditch	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
making	O
up	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
Cooke	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
frightned	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
there	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
no	O
Harm	O
done	O
:	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
spoke	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
riding	O
by	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
Horses	O
were	O
just	O
over-against	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
was	O
never	O
a	O
Blow	O
struck	O
on	O
either	O
Side	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
.	O
This	O
was	O
by	O
Mr	O
Rudge	O
's	O
Brew-House	O
in	O
Hackney-Parish	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Mourning-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Soot	O
upon	O
my	O
Back	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
riding	O
along	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
-	O
they	O
rode	O
a	O
full	O
Gallop	O
;	O
my	O
Fellow-Apprentice	O
was	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
rode	O
over	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
threw	O
myself	O
against	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
's	O
Horse	O
came	O
pretty	O
near	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
then	O
Cooke	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
knocked	O
off	O
your	O
Horses	O
for	O
riding	O
so	O
hard	O
:	O
Whereupon	O
Clark	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
tall	O
one	O
,	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
Whip	O
against	O
Cooke	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
thirty	O
Yards	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Cooke	O
lift	O
,	O
up	O
his	O
Spade	O
,	O
so	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
Whip	O
or	O
the	O
Spade	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Blows	O
pass	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shed	O
,	O
shooting	O
my	O
Soot	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sack	O
.	O
Root	O
called	O
again	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Root	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
15th	O
Day	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Flatman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
in	O
Mourning-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
Home	O
after	O
my	O
Boys	O
,	O
this	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
riding	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
Rate	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
by	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
quite	O
up	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
winding	O
in	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
turn	O
of	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Clarke	O
and	O
Mr	O
Cooke	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
Clark	O
dismounted	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
Whip	O
with	O
the	O
butt	O
End	O
upwards	O
against	O
Cooke	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
Whip	O
up	O
against	O
Cooke	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
stepped	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
has	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
shall	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
Mr	O
Price	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
for	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
because	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
hurt	O
my	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
hurt	O
you	O
,	O
nor	O
your	O
Friend	O
neither	O
;	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
knock	O
on	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
soon	O
mounted	O
their	O
Horses	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
afterwards	O
on	O
that	O
Day	O
?	O
Flatman	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
four	O
Hours	O
afterwards	O
in	O
Mourning-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
People	O
had	O
done	O
Work	O
.	O
They	O
passed	O
by	O
,	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
rode	O
into	O
my	O
Yard	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
smoaking	O
a	O
Pipe	O
over	O
the	O
Pales	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
I	O
answered	O
them	O
I	O
sold	O
none	O
;	O
is	O
there	O
no	O
Publick	O
House	O
near	O
,	O
says	O
they	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
drink	O
together	O
;	O
thinks	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
think	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Plough	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
Hammerton	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
full	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
brought	O
,	O
then	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Beer	O
was	O
fetching	O
,	O
Mr	O
Price	O
would	O
have	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
for	O
fighting	O
.	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
brought	O
the	O
Beer	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
asked	O
me	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
House	O
Cooke	O
lived	O
at	O
;	O
one	O
Man	O
pointed	O
at	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
.	O
-	O
Cooke	O
lives	O
about	O
sixty	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Plough	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
Clarke	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
whipped	O
him	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
,	O
-	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Words	O
were	O
well	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Mouth	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Cooke	O
coming	O
towards	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
.	O
Says	O
one	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
Cooke	O
coming	O
along	O
.	O
Clark	O
hailed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Cooke	O
made	O
a	O
short	O
stand	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
beckoned	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Cooke	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Plough	O
Door	O
.	O
Says	O
Clark	O
,	O
Now	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Man	O
fight	O
me	O
.	O
Cooke	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
fight	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
obliged	O
to	O
fight	O
every	O
Fellow	O
,	O
or	O
Words	O
to	O
that	O
Effect	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
fight	O
:	O
Then	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
fight	O
they	O
would	O
Horse-whip	O
him	O
.	O
Said	O
Cooke	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
use	O
your	O
Pleasure	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
let	O
it	O
alone	O
than	O
horse-whip	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr	O
Price	O
went	O
and	O
talked	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
the	O
Words	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
spoke	O
in	O
an	O
angry	O
Way	O
.	O
Mr	O
Price	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Arm	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
fight	O
.	O
Cooke	O
had	O
pitched	O
his	O
Load	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
a	O
Pipe	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
.	O
Price	O
took	O
the	O
butt	O
End	O
of	O
his	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Pipe	O
in	O
Cooke	O
's	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Piece	O
which	O
Cooke	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Bowl	O
End	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
irted	O
at	O
Price	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
hit	O
him	O
.	O
Price	O
then	O
fell	O
upon	O
Cooke	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
him	O
over	O
or	O
cross	O
the	O
Rail	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
blows	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Blows	O
about	O
the	O
Face	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Face	O
was	O
as	O
bloody	O
as	O
a	O
Slaughter-House	O
.	O
-	O
You	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
Face	O
for	O
Blood	O
.	O
-	O
Clark	O
was	O
by	O
,	O
but	O
Clark	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Clark	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
?	O
Flatman	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
Cooke	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
went	O
Home	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
Cooke	O
come	O
by	O
my	O
Door	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Times	O
afterwards	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
this	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
miserable	O
black	O
Condition	O
.	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
make	O
any	O
Complaints	O
?	O
Flatman	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
inward	O
and	O
never	O
should	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
Man	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
beat	O
him	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
it	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
Name	O
then	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
every	O
Time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
grew	O
worse	O
and	O
worse	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
walk	O
as	O
upright	O
as	O
any	O
Man	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
so	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
that	O
he	O
complained	O
of	O
his	O
Lungs	O
.	O
Flatman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
pretty	O
healthy	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
ruddy	O
Complexion	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
this	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
off	O
.	O
Flatman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
too	O
much	O
of	O
that	O
already	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
this	O
Person	O
,	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
,	O
would	O
have	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
bad	O
Condition	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
this	O
Transaction	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
common	O
Quarrel	O
?	O
Flatman	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
as	O
a	O
common	O
Quarrel	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
Men	O
to	O
come	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Hours	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
kill	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
called	O
a	O
common	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rollo	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Cooke	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
Easter	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
(	O
on	O
looking	O
into	O
an	O
Almanack	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
April	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Clarke	O
at	O
the	O
Plough	O
at	O
Hammerton	O
,	O
either	O
on	O
Horse-back	O
or	O
Mare-back	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
Plough	O
to	O
Cooke	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Whip	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
return	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
a	O
Minute	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
Minutes	O
afterwards	O
,	O
as	O
Cooke	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Marsh-Gate	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
Way	O
Home	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
beckon	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
offered	O
him	O
five	O
Shillings	O
to	O
box	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
there	O
were	O
Words	O
arose	O
between	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Price	O
take	O
the	O
butt	O
End	O
of	O
his	O
Whip	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
Cooke	O
was	O
rising	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
half	O
Bend	O
,	O
knocked	O
the	O
Pipe	O
out	O
of	O
Cooke	O
's	O
Mouth	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
overpowered	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Rail	O
,	O
-	O
then	O
he	O
lay	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Face	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
Hand	O
or	O
Fist	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
Difference	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Rollo	O
.	O
With	O
his	O
Fist	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
for	O
Men	O
do	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
fight	O
like	O
Women	O
with	O
their	O
Hands	O
open	O
.	O
-	O
Clark	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
-	O
Cooke	O
was	O
afterwards	O
in	O
a	O
drooping	O
,	O
wasting	O
Condition	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
any	O
Work	O
after	O
this	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dismal	O
Aspect	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
grew	O
worse	O
and	O
worse	O
Day	O
after	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
Time	O
after	O
Time	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
in	O
two	O
Years	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
Day	O
's	O
Illness	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
his	O
Illness	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Rollo	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
's	O
Disorder	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
worse	O
and	O
worse	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sadly	O
used	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
so	O
abused	O
?	O
Rollo	O
.	O
It	O
cost	O
me	O
once	O
,	O
at	O
Hick's-Hall	O
10	O
l.	O
for	O
parting	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
part	O
two	O
Men	O
.	O
-	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
Easter	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Plough	O
Door	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
enquiring	O
(	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
)	O
where	O
Cook	O
lived	O
,	O
Mr	O
Clark	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
Clark	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
come	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
whipp	O
'd	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
afterwards	O
,	O
Cooke	O
was	O
going	O
homeward	O
,	O
and	O
Clark	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
Clark	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
you	O
not	O
a	O
Rogue	O
to	O
serve	O
me	O
as	O
you	O
did	O
,	O
to	O
