TOKEN	NE
THE	O
TRIAL	O
OF	O
JAMES	O
ANNESLEY	O
AND	O
JOSEPH	O
REDDING	O
,	O
AT	O
THE	O
SESSIONS-HOUSE	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1742	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
MURDER	O
of	O
THOMAS	B-pers
EGGLESTONE	I-pers
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
T.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
,	O
1742	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
One	O
Shilling	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
TRIAL	O
OF	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
.	O
ON	O
Friday	O
the	O
fourth	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
1742	O
,	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
(	O
being	O
brought	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
New-Prison	O
)	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
(	O
having	O
surrendered	O
himself	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Trial	O
,	O
pursuant	O
to	O
Notice	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Solicitor	O
)	O
were	O
,	O
upon	O
Application	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
respect	O
of	O
the	O
Quality	O
claimed	O
by	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
,	O
set	O
within	O
the	O
Barr	O
.	O
Proclamation	O
being	O
made	O
for	O
Silence	O
.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
hold	O
up	O
your	O
Hand	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
,	O
hold	O
up	O
your	O
Hand	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
stand	O
indicted	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
Staines	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
Labourer	O
:	O
For	O
that	O
you	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
your	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
moved	O
and	O
seduced	O
by	O
the	O
Instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
fifteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
with	O
Force	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
,	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
said	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
your	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
;	O
And	O
that	O
you	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Gun	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
Powder	O
and	O
Leaden	O
Shot	O
,	O
which	O
Gun	O
you	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
in	O
both	O
your	O
Hands	O
to	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
your	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
discharge	O
and	O
shoot	O
off	O
;	O
you	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
said	O
Gun	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
charged	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
with	O
the	O
leaden	O
Shot	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
discharged	O
and	O
shot	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Gun	O
by	O
Force	O
of	O
the	O
Gun-Powder	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
your	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
penetrate	O
,	O
giving	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
leaden	O
Shot	O
so	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
discharged	O
and	O
shot	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
one	O
Inch	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
then	O
and	O
there	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
And	O
that	O
you	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
committing	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murder	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
your	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
,	O
assisting	O
,	O
comforting	O
and	O
maintaining	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
to	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
in	O
Form	O
aforesaid	O
;	O
And	O
so	O
you	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
,	O
him	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
in	O
Manner	O
and	O
Form	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
your	O
Malice	O
afore-thought	O
,	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
his	O
Crown	O
and	O
Dignity	O
.	O
How	O
say	O
you	O
James	O
Annesley	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murder	O
whereof	O
you	O
stand	O
indicted	O
or	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
observe	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
the	O
lowest	O
Addition	O
my	O
Enemies	O
could	O
possibly	O
make	O
Use	O
of	O
;	O
but	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
claim	O
to	O
be	O
Earl	O
of	O
Anglesey	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Peer	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
I	O
submit	O
to	O
plead	O
Not	O
guilty	O
to	O
this	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
myself	O
immediately	O
upon	O
my	O
Country	O
,	O
conscious	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Innocence	O
,	O
and	O
impatient	O
to	O
be	O
acquitted	O
even	O
of	O
the	O
Imputation	O
of	O
a	O
Crime	O
so	O
unbecoming	O
the	O
Dignity	O
I	O
claim	O
.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
.	O
How	O
say	O
you	O
Joseph	O
Redding	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murder	O
whereof	O
you	O
stand	O
indicted	O
or	O
not	O
guilty	O
?	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
.	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
.	O
Culprit	O
.	O
How	O
will	O
you	O
be	O
tried	O
?	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
.	O
By	O
God	O
and	O
my	O
Country	O
.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
hold	O
up	O
your	O
Hand	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
,	O
hold	O
up	O
your	O
Hand	O
;	O
you	O
stand	O
likewise	O
charged	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
by	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Stains	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
and	O
County	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
Yeoman	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
Year	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
God	O
not	O
having	O
before	O
your	O
Eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
moved	O
and	O
seduced	O
by	O
the	O
Instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
with	O
Force	O
and	O
Arms	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
God	O
and	O
our	O
said	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
your	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
a	O
certain	O
Gun	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
charged	O
with	O
Gunpowder	O
and	O
small	O
leaden	O
Shot	O
,	O
at	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
your	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
discharge	O
and	O
shoot	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
with	O
the	O
said	O
small	O
leaden	O
Shot	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Gun	O
,	O
by	O
Force	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Gunpowder	O
discharged	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Left-side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
near	O
the	O
Hip-Bone	O
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
your	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
strike	O
,	O
giving	O
unto	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
small	O
Shot	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
aforesaid	O
discharged	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
said	O
Left-side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
near	O
the	O
Hip-Bone	O
,	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
two	O
Inches	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
ten	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
he	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
you	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murder	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
in	O
Form	O
aforesaid	O
done	O
and	O
committed	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
your	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
was	O
present	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
,	O
assisting	O
,	O
comforting	O
,	O
and	O
maintaining	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
in	O
Form	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
to	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
you	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
,	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Manner	O
and	O
Form	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
your	O
Malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
said	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
his	O
Crown	O
and	O
Dignity	O
.	O
How	O
say	O
you	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
are	O
you	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murder	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
guilty	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
.	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
.	O
Culprit	O
,	O
how	O
will	O
you	O
be	O
tried	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
.	O
By	O
God	O
and	O
my	O
Country	O
.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
.	O
How	O
say	O
you	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
,	O
are	O
you	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murder	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
guilty	O
?	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
.	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
.	O
Culprit	O
,	O
how	O
will	O
you	O
be	O
tried	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
By	O
God	O
and	O
my	O
Country	O
.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
hold	O
up	O
your	O
Hand	O
.	O
You	O
stand	O
also	O
indicted	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Staines	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Labourer	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
you	O
,	O
not	O
regarding	O
the	O
Laws	O
and	O
Statutes	O
of	O
this	O
Realm	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
Pains	O
and	O
Penalties	O
therein	O
contained	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
1723.	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
Day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
fifteenth	O
Year	O
of	O
the	O
Reign	O
of	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
George	O
the	O
Second	O
now	O
King	O
of	O
Great-Britain	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
Force	O
and	O
Arms	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
Gun	O
loaded	O
with	O
Gun-powder	O
and	O
leaden	O
Shot	O
,	O
which	O
you	O
in	O
both	O
your	O
Hands	O
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
maliciously	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
,	O
did	O
shoot	O
at	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
such	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
Peace	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
his	O
Crown	O
and	O
Dignity	O
.	O
How	O
say	O
you	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
are	O
you	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
Felony	O
whereof	O
you	O
stand	O
indicted	O
or	O
not	O
guilty	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
.	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
.	O
Culprit	O
,	O
how	O
will	O
you	O
be	O
tried	O
?	O
Annesley	O
.	O
By	O
God	O
and	O
my	O
Country	O
.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
.	O
God	O
send	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
Deliverance	O
.	O
The	O
Defendants	O
being	O
thus	O
arraigned	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
thought	O
the	O
Day	O
too	O
far	O
spent	O
to	O
proceed	O
to	O
a	O
Trial	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
Expectation	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
ordered	O
it	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
alledging	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
attend	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
desiring	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
the	O
Trial	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
Sessions	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
were	O
pleased	O
to	O
indulge	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
consenting	O
that	O
the	O
Defendants	O
should	O
be	O
admitted	O
to	O
Bail	O
.	O
Whereupon	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
give	O
four	O
Sureties	O
in	O
250	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
four	O
in	O
50	O
l.	O
each	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
being	O
done	O
in	O
Court	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
immediately	O
set	O
at	O
Liberty	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
Day	O
of	O
July	O
1742	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Council	O
mov	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
Trial	O
might	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
Consent	O
of	O
the	O
Defendants	O
Solicitor	O
was	O
ordered	O
accordingly	O
;	O
notwithstanding	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
when	O
the	O
two	O
Defendants	O
had	O
surrendered	O
themselves	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
ready	O
with	O
their	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
moved	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Trial	O
off	O
for	O
another	O
Day	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
alledging	O
any	O
sufficient	O
Reason	O
for	O
the	O
Delay	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
were	O
pleased	O
to	O
direct	O
the	O
Trial	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
the	O
Defendants	O
were	O
again	O
arraigned	O
and	O
pleaded	O
as	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
Challenges	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
The	O
following	O
Gentlemen	O
were	O
impannelled	O
and	O
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
Names	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Deschamps	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sandwich	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Harrop	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Stowell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Tredgold	I-pers
.	O
Cryer	O
.	O
If	O
any	O
one	O
can	O
inform	O
my	O
Lords	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Justices	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
hold	O
up	O
your	O
Hand	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
,	O
hold	O
up	O
your	O
Hand	O
.	O
You	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
hearken	O
to	O
their	O
Charge	O
.	O
They	O
stand	O
indicted	O
by	O
the	O
Names	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
Staines	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Labourer	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
Labourer	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Indictments	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
upon	O
these	O
Indictments	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
arraigned	O
,	O
and	O
thereunto	O
pleaded	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
their	O
Trial	O
have	O
put	O
themselves	O
upon	O
their	O
Country	O
,	O
which	O
Country	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
your	O
Charge	O
is	O
to	O
enquire	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
an	O
Indictment	O
for	O
Murder	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
sets	O
forth	O
that	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Annesley	O
did	O
discharge	O
the	O
said	O
Gun	O
against	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
did	O
make	O
a	O
Wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
was	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
,	O
to	O
murder	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
prove	O
our	O
Charge	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serjeant	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
stand	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
;	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
was	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
killed	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
he	O
was	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
,	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
Murder	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murder	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
Ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
late	O
Majesty	O
King	O
George	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
Person	O
does	O
wilfully	O
shoot	O
at	O
another	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
Felony	O
without	O
Benefit	O
of	O
Clergy	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
the	O
Case	O
is	O
thus	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
First	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
fish	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Place	O
called	O
the	O
Moor	O
,	O
near	O
Slaines	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
Casting-Net	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
String	O
which	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
Net	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
String	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
right	O
Arm	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
fishing	O
in	O
a	O
Meadow	O
belonging	O
to	O
one	O
Sylvester	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
fishing	O
towards	O
the	O
North	O
of	O
the	O
Enclosure	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
instantly	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
seized	O
the	O
Deceased	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Net	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Deceased	O
cast	O
the	O
Net	O
into	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
Right-Hand	O
;	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Annesley	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
at	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Damn	O
you	O
surrender	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
;	O
he	O
pointed	O
the	O
Gun	O
immediately	O
towards	O
his	O
Side	O
before	O
a	O
Word	O
of	O
Reply	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Force	O
of	O
the	O
Powder	O
drove	O
the	O
Shot	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
Coat	O
into	O
his	O
Body	O
;	O
he	O
clapped	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Rogue	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
?	O
dropped	O
down	O
and	O
died	O
immediately	O
;	O
then	O
John	O
Egglestone	O
,	O
the	O
Son	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
Knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
String	O
of	O
the	O
Net	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Annesley	O
turned	O
the	O
butt	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
Rogue	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
knock	O
your	O
Head	O
off	O
;	O
to	O
avoid	O
which	O
,	O
young	O
Egglestone	O
jump	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
Breast	O
high	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
String	O
of	O
the	O
Net	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Water	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
murdered	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
Persons	O
,	O
Fisher	O
,	O
Bettesworth	O
,	O
and	O
Bowles	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
Hundred	O
and	O
Sixty	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Accident	O
happened	O
;	O
they	O
heard	O
a	O
Gun	O
fired	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
cry	O
out	O
that	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
River	O
Side	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
dragg	O
'd	O
the	O
Net	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
they	O
crossed	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Man	O
dead	O
,	O
or	O
so	O
bad	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
thereupon	O
directed	O
the	O
Son	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
Mr	O
Cole	O
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
at	O
Slaines	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
accordingly	O
to	O
Mr	O
Cole	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
shot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
says	O
Mr	O
Cole	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
signify	O
my	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
him	O
no	O
good	O
;	O
so	O
then	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
Russel	O
,	O
a	O
Constable	O
at	O
Slaines	O
:	O
But	O
I	O
should	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
saw	O
these	O
three	O
Persons	O
,	O
Fisher	O
,	O
Bettesworth	O
,	O
and	O
Bowles	O
,	O
coming	O
towards	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
Russel	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Persons	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
pursue	O
the	O
Murderers	O
:	O
Accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Farm-House	O
where	O
Annesley	O
and	O
Redding	O
used	O
sometimes	O
to	O
lodge	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
found	O
Annesley	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
at	O
Slaines	O
;	O
Redding	O
could	O
never	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
surrendered	O
himself	O
since	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
Trial	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Annesley	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reynall	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Laleham	O
,	O
what	O
that	O
Examination	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
Application	O
to	O
this	O
young	O
Man	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
sell	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Blood	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
we	O
prove	O
our	O
Charge	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
Murder	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
them	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
speak	O
the	O
Truth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
A	O
n't	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
-	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Speak	O
slow	O
and	O
deliberately	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
may	O
hear	O
you	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
A	O
n't	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Father	O
were	O
going	O
up	O
Staines	B-place
River	I-place
,	O
to	O
catch	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Fish	O
in	O
Staines	O
Moor	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Staines	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Casting-Net	O
;	O
we	O
fish	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
Wa	O
y	O
up	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
Ground	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
Possession	O
was	O
the	O
Ground	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
Mr	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
's	O
Meadow	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
turning	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
a	O
n't	O
please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
my	O
Father	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Net	O
upon	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
String	O
was	O
fastened	O
to	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
were	O
coming	O
back	O
from	O
fishing	O
,	O
what	O
happened	O
then	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
By	O
that	O
Time	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
half	O
Way	O
in	O
the	O
Meadow	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
and	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
out	O
run	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
first	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
they	O
did	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Redding	O
took	O
my	O
Father	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Net	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
Net	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
Net	O
afterwards	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Father	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
River	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
were	O
you	O
from	O
the	O
River	O
then	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
Yards	O
from	O
the	O
River	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
Net	O
was	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
Annesley	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
Gun	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
God	O
damn	O
your	O
Blood	O
deliver	O
your	O
Net	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
fir	O
'd	O
off	O
before	O
he	O
received	O
any	O
Answer	O
from	O
my	O
Father	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Manner	O
did	O
Annesley	O
hold	O
his	O
Gun	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
In	O
this	O
Manner	O
.	O
(	O
Pointing	O
the	O
Gun	O
strait	O
forward	O
,	O
holding	O
it	O
about	O
Breast	O
high	O
,	O
stooping	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
)	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
the	O
Gun	O
to	O
your	O
Father	O
when	O
he	O
fir	O
'd	O
it	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Side	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
Gun	O
between	O
Redding	O
and	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
directly	O
into	O
his	O
left	O
Side	O
,	O
here	O
,	O
(	O
holding	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Hip	O
)	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Plate	O
Button	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
bruised	O
to	O
pieces	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
Father	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Rogue	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
dropp	O
'd	O
immediately	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Annesley	O
say	O
before	O
he	O
fir	O
'd	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
He	O
swore	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
the	O
Net	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fir	O
'd	O
immediately	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
after	O
you	O
heard	O
your	O
Father	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
Man	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Knife	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
String	O
of	O
the	O
Net	O
;	O
and	O
Annesley	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Rogue	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
knock	O
out	O
your	O
Brains	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
up	O
the	O
butt	O
End	O
of	O
his	O
Gun	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
jump	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Stream	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
String	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
the	O
Net	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
:	O
then	O
says	O
Annesley	O
,	O
the	O
Rogue	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
Net	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
John	B-pers
Bettesworth	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
when	O
Annesley	O
and	O
Redding	O
saw	O
these	O
three	O
Men	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
directly	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
were	O
Bettesworth	O
,	O
Fisher	O
,	O
and	O
Bowles	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
Annesley	O
and	O
Redding	O
ran	O
away	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
they	O
saw	O
these	O
three	O
Men	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Bettesworth	O
,	O
Fisher	O
,	O
and	O
Bowles	O
came	O
through	O
the	O
River	O
to	O
the	O
Side	O
where	O
my	O
Father	O
lay	O
dead	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
one	O
Side	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
then	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
They	O
bid	O
me	O
get	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Charles	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
at	O
Staines	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
Staines	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
Cole	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
Father	O
was	O
shot	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
or	O
dying	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
came	O
near	O
my	O
Father	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Russel	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
Townsmen	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
old	O
Mr	O
Redding	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
Yeovely	O
Farm	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
kill	O
'd	O
my	O
Father	O
;	O
we	O
beset	O
the	O
House	O
all	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
James	B-pers
Annesley	I-pers
hid	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Corner	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
you	O
there	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
then	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
a	O
n't	O
please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
they	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
he	O
hid	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
which	O
is	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Foot	O
from	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
put	O
old	O
Iron	O
and	O
any	O
Sort	O
of	O
Lumber	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
boarded	O
Place	O
or	O
Room	O
over	O
the	O
Washouse	O
;	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
the	O
Woman	O
makes	O
Medicines	O
for	O
sore	O
Eyes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
Chimney	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
standing	O
up	O
or	O
lying	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
was	O
he	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Cart	O
that	O
brought	O
up	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
at	O
Staines	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
all	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
A	O
n't	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Who	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
Wound	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
your	O
Father	O
's	O
Death	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Go	O
on	O
;	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
have	O
other	O
Things	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
He	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
all	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
Annesley	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
Cart	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Mc	O
.	O
Kercher	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
Mc	O
.	O
Kercher	O
said	O
is	O
no	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
We	O
will	O
let	O
this	O
alone	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
prove	O
he	O
was	O
any	O
ways	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
an	O
Agent	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
can	O
.	O
Foreman	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
Bustle	O
,	O
or	O
Struggling	O
,	O
between	O
Annesley	O
,	O
Redding	O
,	O
and	O
Egglestone	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Gun	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Quarrel	O
or	O
Jostling	O
,	O
my	O
Father	O
never	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
ill	O
Word	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
Father	O
make	O
no	O
Resistance	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
Resistance	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
Jostling	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
pass	O
'd	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
Redding	O
took	O
my	O
Father	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
Annesley	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
happen	O
'd	O
between	O
your	O
Father	O
and	O
Redding	O
before	O
Annesley	O
came	O
up	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
He	O
demanded	O
his	O
Net	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Jostling	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
No	O
other	O
Jostling	O
than	O
laying	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Collar	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Father	O
never	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
were	O
you	O
when	O
Redding	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
your	O
Father	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
Yard	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
off	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
shot	O
off	O
the	O
Gun	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
what	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
shooting	O
off	O
the	O
Gun	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Why	O
he	O
fir	O
'd	O
the	O
Gun	O
to	O
shoot	O
my	O
Father	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
shooting	O
off	O
the	O
Gun	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
directly	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shoot	O
a	O
Dog	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
draw	O
the	O
Trigger	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Gun	O
cock	O
'd	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Pray	O
was	O
any	O
Body	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
No-body	O
near	O
but	O
Bettesworth	O
,	O
Fisher	O
,	O
and	O
Bowles	O
,	O
nor	O
No-body	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
you	O
any	O
Money	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
settle	O
50	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Laleham	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
after	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Death	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
there	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
's	O
at	O
Brentford	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
we	O
put	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Lion	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
Sir	O
Tho	B-pers
Reynell	I-pers
came	O
in	O
and	O
ordered	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Laleham	O
,	O
accordingly	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mr	O
Lee	O
's	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
Jack	O
Lane	O
,	O
Mrs	O
Chester	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
Young	O
John	O
Lane	O
offered	O
me	O
100	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
settle	O
100	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
more	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
settle	O
50	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
on	O
me	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
Presence	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
you	O
50	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
for	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Because	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
as	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Reason	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
comply	O
with	O
this	O
Offer	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Blood	O
at	O
any	O
Rate	O
?	O
[	O
The	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
done	O
with	O
this	O
Witness	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
cross	O
examined	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
in	O
what	O
Manner	O
did	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
,	O
Redding	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
Father	O
stand	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
Accident	O
happened	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Redding	O
stood	O
between	O
Annesley	O
and	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
hold	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
William	B-pers
Duffel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
you	O
some	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
your	O
Father	O
's	O
Death	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Conversation	O
with	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
at	O
Laleham	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
offered	O
that	O
Money	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
take	O
the	O
Money	O
and	O
not	O
hang	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
about	O
the	O
Manner	O
in	O
which	O
your	O
Father	O
was	O
killed	O
?	O
Eggleston	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
point	O
the	O
Gun	O
to	O
your	O
Father	O
:	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
cock	O
the	O
Gun	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
cock	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Gun	O
was	O
cock	O
'd	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Giffard	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
first	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
before	O
or	O
since	O
your	O
Father	O
's	O
Death	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
After	O
my	O
Father	O
was	O
killed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Staines	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
there	O
before	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
Orders	O
or	O
Authority	O
to	O
prosecute	O
upon	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
your	O
Father	O
's	O
Death	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Williams	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
He	O
keeps	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
in	O
Pickadilly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
Staines	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
want	O
with	O
you	O
when	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
was	O
you	O
of	O
,	O
when	O
your	O
Father	O
died	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
worked	O
with	O
my	O
Father	O
as	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
Williams	O
to	O
find	O
you	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
Servant	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Ever	O
since	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
seen	O
my	O
Lord	O
-	O
at	O
Williams	O
's	O
?	O
-	O
[	O
Here	O
the	O
Court	O
interpos	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Question	O
was	O
improper	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
are	O
Williams	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
not	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
Table	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
dine	O
at	O
his	O
Table	O
now	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
you	O
were	O
sent	O
from	O
dining	O
at	O
his	O
Table	O
to	O
draw	O
Beer	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Paul	B-pers
Keating	I-pers
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
a	O
Note	O
he	O
drew	O
for	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
He	O
did	O
draw	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
tore	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
made	O
you	O
tear	O
the	O
Note	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
his	O
Proceedings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
read	O
the	O
Note	O
before	O
you	O
tore	O
it	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
Note	O
to	O
be	O
wrote	O
?	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
writing	O
of	O
a	O
Note	O
before	O
he	O
wrote	O
it	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
Nothing	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
copy	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
he	O
desired	O
you	O
to	O
copy	O
the	O
Note	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
Nothing	O
;	O
it	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
and	O
I	O
tore	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
tear	O
it	O
for	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
read	O
it	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
Because	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
things	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
desire	O
you	O
to	O
copy	O
the	O
Note	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
then	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
at	O
New-Prison	O
to	O
see	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
.	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
for	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
what	O
you	O
went	O
for	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
Fancy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
send	O
up	O
Word	O
to	O
him	O
you	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
might	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
you	O
thought	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
,	O
in	O
speaking	O
of	O
your	O
Father	O
's	O
Death	O
,	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
accidentally	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
say	O
to	O
Keating	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
200	O
l.	O
or	O
had	O
a	O
Promise	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
Security	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
whom	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
same	O
Account	O
with	O
Respect	O
to	O
the	O
holding	O
of	O
the	O
G	O
as	O
you	O
do	O
now	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
give	O
two	O
Accounts	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
;	O
part	O
at	O
one	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Remainder	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
?	O
Egglest	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
butt	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
was	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Muzzel	O
pointed	O
downward	O
.	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
any	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Manner	O
of	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
's	O
drawing	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Feet	O
back	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
No	O
never	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
which	O
of	O
his	O
Legs	O
he	O
drew	O
back	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
he	O
drew	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
say	O
which	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
No-body	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Oxford-Arms	O
with	O
Keating	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
relating	O
to	O
a	O
Note	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
Offer	O
made	O
to	O
you	O
there	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
You	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Paper	O
that	O
was	O
tore	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Contents	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Egglestone	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
[	O
John	B-pers
Bettesworth	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Tell	O
us	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
you	O
were	O
when	O
you	O
heard	O
a	O
Gun	O
fir	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
and	O
his	O
Son	O
were	O
a	O
Fishing	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
169	O
Yards	O
some	O
odd	O
Inches	O
from	O
the	O
River	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
measure	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Ground	O
was	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Ground	O
called	O
Mr	O
Sylvester	O
's	O
Rents	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
many	O
Hedges	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
where	O
the	O
Deceased	O
was	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
pretty	O
many	O
Willows	O
,	O
but	O
any	O
Body	O
might	O
see	O
through	O
them	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
and	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
come	O
over	O
the	O
Hedge	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
What	O
Hedge	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
The	O
Hedge	O
that	O
parted	O
Mr	O
Sylvester	O
's	O
Ground	O
from	O
Mr	O
Redding	O
's	O
Ground	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
over	O
the	O
Stile	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
run	O
after	O
Egglestone	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
;	O
young	O
Redding	O
came	O
up	O
first	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
Egglestone	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
his	O
Collar	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
it	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
or	O
Collar	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
Redding	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Hand	O
upon	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
or	O
Collar	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
positively	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
or	O
Collar	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
Annesley	O
came	O
up	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
was	O
gone	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
from	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
he	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
when	O
this	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
near	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Yards	O
off	O
.	O
-	O
Annesley	O
and	O
Redding	O
came	O
up	O
almost	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
Annesley	O
came	O
up	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Gun	O
went	O
off	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Smoak	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
were	O
169	O
Yards	O
off	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
called	O
to	O
us	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
killed	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Who	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
River	O
just	O
against	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
Mr	O
Egglestone	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
over	O
there	O
without	O
being	O
up	O
thus	O
high	O
;	O
(	O
putting	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Middle	O
)	O
but	O
we	O
went	O
over	O
in	O
a	O
shallower	O
Place	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Were	O
Annesley	O
and	O
Redding	O
there	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
over	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
run	O
away	O
before	O
that	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Was	O
Egglestone	O
dead	O
or	O
alive	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
up	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
dead	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Who	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
River	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
all	O
three	O
come	O
away	O
together	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
rather	O
before	O
the	O
Boy	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
drop	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Boy	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
Net	O
from	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Arm	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Boy	O
come	O
cross	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
Net	O
was	O
brought	O
cross	O
the	O
River	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Grapper	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
Egglestone	O
lie	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
upon	O
his	O
Face	O
;	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
he	O
groan	O
'd	O
pretty	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
Boy	O
for	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
Surgeon	O
came	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
What	O
Place	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Wash-house	O
,	O
a	O
Back-house	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
throw	O
up	O
Hoops	O
and	O
Iron	O
,	O
and	O
any	O
Sort	O
of	O
old	O
Lumber	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
lie	O
upon	O
his	O
Face	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
him	O
down	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
at	O
Staines	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
himself	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
down	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
accord	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
heard	O
the	O
Gun	O
go	O
off	O
whose	O
Hand	O
was	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
's	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Position	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
when	O
it	O
went	O
off	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
Struggle	O
between	O
Annesley	O
,	O
Redding	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
No	O
other	O
than	O
their	O
striving	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Net	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
passed	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
?	O
-	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
there	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
kill	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
accessary	O
to	O
such	O
an	O
innocent	O
Man	O
's	O
Death	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
besides	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
home	O
for	O
more	O
Men	O
,	O
but	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
want	O
more	O
Men	O
for	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
To	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Net	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Answer	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
Redding	O
made	O
him	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
can	O
do	O
it	O
well	O
enough	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Council	O
having	O
done	O
with	O
this	O
Witness	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
cross	O
examin	O
'd	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
and	O
Redding	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Deceased	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
making	O
any	O
Use	O
of	O
his	O
Gun	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
offer	O
to	O
shoot	O
at	O
a	O
Crow	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
that	O
before	O
this	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Crow	O
flying	O
or	O
sitting	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
Flying	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
shoot	O
at	O
the	O
Crow	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
Not	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
were	O
you	O
off	O
then	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
About	O
as	O
far	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
as	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Position	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
up	O
running	O
.	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
this	O
Manner	O
,	O
[	O
holds	O
it	O
as	O
if	O
the	O
Gun	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Muzzle	O
hanging	O
a	O
little	O
Slanting	O
towards	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
]	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
saw	O
Annesley	O
and	O
Redding	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
Ground	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
that	O
Ground	O
which	O
belongs	O
to	O
Sylvester	O
-	O
what	O
were	O
they	O
doing	O
there	O
,	O
were	O
they	O
standing	O
,	O
sitting	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
sitting	O
or	O
lying	O
under	O
the	O
Hedge	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
Purpose	O
do	O
you	O
imagine	O
they	O
were	O
sitting	O
or	O
lying	O
there	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
imagine	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Net	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
imagine	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Boy	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
River	O
?	O
Bettesworth	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
after	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
shot	O
.	O
[	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr	O
Redding	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Mr	O
Redding	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
Mr	O
Egglestone	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
?	O
-	O
Look	O
at	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Fisher	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
Men	O
lie	O
under	O
the	O
Hedge	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Piece	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
Hands	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
In	O
which	O
Ground	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
Mr	O
Redding	O
's	O
Ground	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Ground	O
was	O
Egglestone	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
Sylvester	O
's	O
Ground	O
.	O
Bettesworth	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
Redding	O
running	O
after	O
Egglestone	O
,	O
and	O
Redding	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Egglestone	O
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
touched	O
him	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Manner	O
did	O
Redding	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
Distance	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
Did	O
Egglestone	O
make	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bounds	O
that	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
fishing	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Struggle	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
Net	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
Redding	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
did	O
both	O
,	O
snatch	O
at	O
the	O
Net	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Gun	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
Hand	O
was	O
the	O
Gun	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Not	O
in	O
Redding	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Hand	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
attentive	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
in	O
what	O
Manner	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
Gun	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
or	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Gun	O
against	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
he	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Very	O
nigh	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
above	O
the	O
Length	O
of	O
a	O
Gun	O
.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
by	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
came	O
up	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
River	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
Boy	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
killed	O
;	O
-	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
my	O
Father	O
is	O
killed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
directly	O
cross	O
the	O
River	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
What	O
then	O
became	O
of	O
Annesley	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
They	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
hallooed	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
shot	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Smoak	O
and	O
Fire	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
River	O
first	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
together	O
almost	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
was	O
over	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Boy	O
then	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Nothing	O
;	O
only	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Some	O
Body	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
Bettesworth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
run	O
away	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Surgeon	O
brought	O
there	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
came	O
there	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Mr	O
Sylvester	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceased	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
Murder	O
was	O
committed	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
examined	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
What	O
Distance	O
was	O
there	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Gun	O
went	O
off	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
One	O
Hundred	O
and	O
Sixty-nine	O
Yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
include	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
the	O
River	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Yes	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
[	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
both	O
Redding	O
and	O
Annesley	O
snatch	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Net	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
possible	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
hear	O
what	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
one	O
Word	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
whether	O
young	O
Egglestone	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
by	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reynell	I-pers
,	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Gun	O
did	O
go	O
off	O
by	O
Accident	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
wilfully	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
into	O
a	O
Room	O
with	O
Chester	O
and	O
Lane	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
Money	O
offered	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
by	O
John	O
Lane	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
him	O
100	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
100	O
l.	O
-	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
50	O
l.	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
others	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
sell	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Blood	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
as	O
my	O
Friends	O
direct	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Fisher	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
your	O
Father	O
is	O
dead	O
;	O
the	O
Money	O
will	O
do	O
you	O
good	O
;	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
accidentally	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Money	O
will	O
do	O
me	O
good	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
wilfully	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
not	O
some	O
Conversation	O
together	O
,	O
after	O
his	O
Examination	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
Q	O
That	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
who	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr	O
Williams	O
the	O
Clergyman	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
make	O
a	O
Declaration	O
of	O
this	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
now	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
what	O
passed	O
between	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr	O
Williams	O
,	O
that	O
Egglestone	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
really	O
believed	O
that	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
wilfully	O
.	O
Q.	O
Repeat	O
all	O
that	O
you	O
said	O
to	O
Mr	O
Williams	O
.	O
Fisher	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Boy	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
had	O
offered	O
him	O
50	O
l.	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Money	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
good	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
wilfully	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
wilfully	O
done	O
as	O
you	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
Way	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
wilfully	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
talking	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
wilfully	O
.	O
[	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
dead	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
that	O
I	O
rent	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
River	O
Side	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
about	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
Death	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
my	O
Ground	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Cattle	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
two	O
Pints	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
within	O
two	O
Hundred	O
Yards	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
of	O
my	O
Ground	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
three	O
Men	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
old	O
Egglestone	O
was	O
killed	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
then	O
pointed	O
to	O
my	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
lies	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
People	O
there	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
common	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
Tom	O
.	O
Egglestone	O
lie	O
dead	O
in	O
my	O
Ground	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Annesley	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
Building	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr	O
Redding	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
searching	O
the	O
Rooms	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
People	O
say	O
,	O
here	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
there	O
,	O
come	O
down	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Place	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Place	O
was	O
it	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Place	O
to	O
put	O
odd	O
things	O
in	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
boarded	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Top	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
he	O
come	O
down	O
voluntarily	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
he	O
pulled	O
down	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
pulled	O
him	O
down	O
or	O
helped	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Fit	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
trembled	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Round-House	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
search	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
Redding	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
Laleham	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
the	O
Boy	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
sleep	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
refreshed	O
afterwards	O
.	O
[	O
Upon	O
the	O
cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
received	O
Money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
attending	O
here	O
on	O
this	O
Cause	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
whom	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
Mr	O
Giffard	O
's	O
direction	O
who	O
subpoena	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
paid	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
a	O
Day	O
for	O
my	O
Time	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
earn	O
at	O
my	O
Business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
is	O
this	O
Giffard	O
of	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Stranger	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
you	O
send	O
Notice	O
of	O
this	O
Accident	O
to	O
any	O
Body	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
killed	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr	O
Williams	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Company	O
upon	O
this	O
Occasion	O
.	O
Q	O
What	O
Business	O
does	O
young	O
Egglestone	O
follow	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
Business	O
he	O
follows	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
draws	O
Beer	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
was	O
he	O
bred	O
to	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
out	O
at	O
Service	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
in	O
the	O
Business	O
of	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
draw	O
Beer	O
now	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
at	O
Mr	O
Williams	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
in	O
Pickadilly	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
Williams	O
I	O
was	O
speaking	O
of	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
never	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Conversation	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
this	O
Affair	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Pickadilly	O
since	O
this	O
Business	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
Hand	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
this	O
Trial	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
this	O
Williams	O
down	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
Staines	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
of	O
Staines	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
the	O
Accident	O
happened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
Egglestone	O
,	O
there	O
since	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Staines	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
Williams	O
ever	O
since	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
whether	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
Williams	O
's	O
House	O
every	O
Time	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
rest	O
it	O
here	O
;	O
And	O
having	O
observed	O
upon	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
concluded	O
with	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
it	O
had	O
fully	O
made	O
out	O
the	O
Charge	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Ground	O
where	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
killed	O
being	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Sylvester	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
Trespassers	O
by	O
coming	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
answerable	O
for	O
the	O
Consequences	O
.	O
That	O
as	O
to	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
only	O
implied	O
,	O
but	O
express	O
Malice	O
proved	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
the	O
Father	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
beating	O
out	O
the	O
Son	O
's	O
Brains	O
,	O
only	O
because	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
their	O
Net	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
indicted	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
unhappy	O
Case	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
unable	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
proper	O
Defence	O
,	O
having	O
by	O
the	O
Cruelty	O
of	O
those	O
,	O
whose	O
Duty	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
protect	O
me	O
,	O
been	O
deprived	O
of	O
the	O
Advantages	O
of	O
an	O
Education	O
I	O
was	O
entituled	O
to	O
by	O
my	O
Birth	O
.	O
All	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
melancholy	O
Accident	O
in	O
Question	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
Day	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
my	O
Gun	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
my	O
innocent	O
Fellow-Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
shoot	O
Sparrows	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
usually	O
did	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
Mr	O
Redding	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
Game-Keeper	O
to	O
the	O
Lord	O
of	O
the	O
Manour	O
,	O
saw	O
some	O
People	O
a	O
poaching	O
within	O
the	O
Royalty	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
proposed	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
seize	O
their	O
Nets	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
threw	O
the	O
Net	O
into	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
jump	O
'd	O
in	O
to	O
pull	O
it	O
across	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
stoop	O
'd	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Ropes	O
that	O
trailed	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Instant	O
,	O
the	O
fatal	O
Instrument	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
other	O
Hand	O
,	O
hanging	O
by	O
my	O
Side	O
,	O
went	O
off	O
without	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
Grief	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Surprize	O
.	O
My	O
Behaviour	O
,	O
immediately	O
after	O
the	O
Accident	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
inconsistent	O
with	O
a	O
Temper	O
that	O
could	O
murder	O
a	O
Man	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
before	O
,	O
without	O
one	O
Word	O
of	O
Provocation	O
.	O
Whatever	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
Determination	O
of	O
your	O
Lordship	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
great	O
as	O
the	O
Misfortunes	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
have	O
been	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
always	O
consider	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
Accident	O
as	O
the	O
greatest	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Mr	O
Redding	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
Game-Keeper	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Dolben	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
of	O
the	O
Manour	O
of	O
Yeoveney	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
Mr	O
Annesly	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
walking	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
Crow	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
made	O
an	O
Offer	O
to	O
shoot	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
fire	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
too	O
far	O
off	O
:	O
Soon	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
Egglestone	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
a	O
fishing	O
with	O
a	O
Casting-Net	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
endeavour	O
to	O
take	O
their	O
Net	O
away	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Duty	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
according	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Net	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
deliver	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
one	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
String	O
being	O
about	O
his	O
Arm	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
String	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
,	O
whilst	O
the	O
Boy	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
cross	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Gun	O
go	O
off	O
(	O
my	O
Back	O
being	O
towards	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
)	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Man	O
fall	O
down	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
,	O
I	O
hoped	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
shot	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
turning	O
up	O
the	O
Flap	O
of	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
shot	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
What	O
shall	O
I	O
do	O
!	O
and	O
expressed	O
so	O
much	O
Concern	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
an	O
accidental	O
Thing	O
.	O
Mr	O
Hume	O
Campbell	O
,	O
of	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
although	O
he	O
knew	O
by	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
at	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Liberty	O
to	O
observe	O
upon	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Evidence	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
apprehended	O
,	O
that	O
for	O
the	O
Ease	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
just	O
open	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
the	O
Defence	O
,	O
without	O
making	O
any	O
Observations	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Defence	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
insisted	O
upon	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Gun	O
went	O
off	O
meerly	O
by	O
Accident	O
;	O
that	O
Redding	O
was	O
Game-Keeper	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Dolben	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
of	O
the	O
Manour	O
of	O
Yeovency	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
proper	O
and	O
legal	O
Deputation	O
for	O
seizing	O
of	O
Nets	O
and	O
other	O
Engines	O
,	O
for	O
destroying	O
of	O
Game	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
his	O
Son	O
were	O
poaching	O
with	O
a	O
Casting-Net	O
within	O
the	O
Manour	O
;	O
that	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
went	O
in	O
Aid	O
of	O
the	O
Game-Keeper	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
about	O
a	O
lawful	O
Act	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
Trespassers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Death	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
accidental	O
Consequence	O
of	O
that	O
Act	O
,	O
would	O
,	O
in	O
Point	O
of	O
Law	O
,	O
make	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
guilty	O
only	O
of	O
Chance	O
Medley	O
.	O
[	O
Mr	O
Thomas	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Manour	O
of	O
Yeoveney	O
?	O
Mr	O
Staples	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
Deputy	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
Steward	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Dolben	I-pers
,	O
as	O
Lord	O
of	O
the	O
Manour	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Dean	O
and	O
Chapter	O
of	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Manour	O
?	O
Mr	O
Staples	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Grant	O
of	O
the	O
Manour	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Dean	O
and	O
Chapter	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
any	O
Copy-Holders	O
?	O
Mr	O
Staples	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
admitted	O
some	O
Copy-Holders	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Manour	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
have	O
held	O
one	O
Court	O
there	O
for	O
my	O
Father	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
hold	O
several	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
Mansion-House	O
belonging	O
to	O
this	O
Manour	O
?	O
Mr	O
Staples	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Mansion-House	O
belonging	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
is	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
Mr	O
Redding	O
lives	O
in	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
What	O
Court	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
held	O
there	O
?	O
Mr	O
Staples	O
.	O
A	O
Court-Baron	O
.	O
[	O
Mr	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burlingson	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
Mr	O
Burlingson	O
,	O
look	O
upon	O
this	O
Deputation	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
subscribing	O
Witness	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
executed	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
whom	O
.	O
Mr	O
Burlingson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
Name	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Dolben	I-pers
execute	O
it	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
Seal	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
executed	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
it	O
bears	O
Date	O
.	O
Mr	O
Burlingson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
on	O
the	O
very	O
Day	O
.	O
[	O
Mr	O
James	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
Mr	O
Edmonds	O
,	O
look	O
upon	O
that	O
Endorsement	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
Hand	O
that	O
is	O
?	O
Mr	O
Edmonds	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
acknowledge	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
entred	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Entry	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Mr	O
Edmonds	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
entred	O
,	O
and	O
acknowledged	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
was	O
sufficient	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
we	O
pray	O
the	O
Deputation	O
may	O
be	O
read	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Book	O
itself	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
entred	O
.	O
The	O
Clerk	O
reads	O
.	O
Sign	O
'd	O
J.	O
Dolben	O
,	O
dated	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1741	O
.	O
KNOW	O
all	O
Men	O
by	O
these	O
Presents	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Dolben	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shindon	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Northampton	O
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
and	O
Doctor	O
of	O
Divinity	O
,	O
Lord	O
of	O
the	O
Manour	O
of	O
Yeoveney	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Staines	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
By	O
Virtue	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
Acts	O
of	O
Parliament	O
lately	O
made	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Preservation	O
of	O
the	O
Game	O
,	O
have	O
made	O
,	O
nominated	O
,	O
authorized	O
,	O
constituted	O
,	O
and	O
appointed	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
these	O
Presents	O
do	O
make	O
,	O
nominate	O
,	O
authorize	O
,	O
constitute	O
,	O
and	O
appoint	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
the	O
Younger	O
,	O
of	O
Yeoveney	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Parish	O
of	O
Staines	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
Husbandman	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Game-Keeper	O
of	O
and	O
within	O
my	O
Manour	O
of	O
Yeoveney	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
of	O
all	O
and	O
all	O
Manner	O
of	O
Game	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
Kind	O
or	O
Nature	O
soever	O
,	O
which	O
now	O
is	O
,	O
or	O
hereafter	O
shall	O
be	O
,	O
upon	O
or	O
within	O
the	O
Bounds	O
,	O
Limits	O
,	O
or	O
Precincts	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
with	O
full	O
Power	O
and	O
Authority	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Directions	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
to	O
kill	O
any	O
Hares	O
,	O
Patridges	O
,	O
Pheasants	O
,	O
Fish	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Game	O
whatsoever	O
,	O
upon	O
or	O
within	O
my	O
said	O
Manour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Bounds	O
,	O
Limits	O
,	O
and	O
Precincts	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
And	O
also	O
to	O
take	O
and	O
seize	O
all	O
such	O
Guns	O
,	O
Grey-Hounds	O
,	O
Setting-Dogs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Dogs	O
,	O
Hare-Pipes	O
,	O
Snares	O
,	O
Low-Bells	O
,	O
Ferress	O
,	O
Tramels	O
,	O
Hays	O
,	O
Tunnels	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Nets	O
or	O
Engines	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
taking	O
,	O
killing	O
,	O
or	O
destroying	O
of	O
Hares	O
,	O
Patridges	O
,	O
Pheasants	O
,	O
Fish	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Game	O
,	O
within	O
my	O
said	O
Manour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Precincts	O
thereof	O
,	O
that	O
shall	O
be	O
kept	O
or	O
used	O
by	O
any	O
Person	O
or	O
Persons	O
,	O
not	O
legally	O
qualified	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
And	O
further	O
to	O
act	O
and	O
do	O
all	O
and	O
every	O
Thing	O
and	O
Things	O
which	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
Office	O
of	O
a	O
Game-Keeper	O
,	O
pursuant	O
to	O
the	O
Directions	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
.	O
And	O
lastly	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
direct	O
that	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
he	O
entred	O
as	O
such	O
Game-Keeper	O
of	O
my	O
said	O
Manour	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
pursuant	O
or	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Act	O
or	O
Acts	O
of	O
Parliament	O
in	O
that	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
J.	O
DOLBEN	O
.	O
Sealed	O
and	O
Delivered	O
,	O
being	O
first	O
duly	O
stamped	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Presence	O
of	O
JAMES	B-pers
AFFLICK	I-pers
,	O
THO	O
.	O
BURLINGSON	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
certify	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
the	O
within	O
mentioned	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
is	O
this	O
Day	O
entred	O
in	O
my	O
Office	O
,	O
pursuant	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
such	O
Case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
Dated	O
this	O
29th	O
Day	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1741	O
.	O
P.	O
WALTER	O
,	O
Clerk	O
of	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
[	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
the	O
Elder	O
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
this	O
unhappy	O
Case	O
happened	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
.	O
Redding	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Field	O
called	O
Chantry	O
Mead	O
.	O
This	O
where	O
the	O
Accident	O
happened	O
,	O
is	O
called	O
the	O
Hare	O
Mead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Manour	O
is	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
Yeoveney	O
Manour	O
,	O
which	O
belongs	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Dolben	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
you	O
when	O
this	O
happened	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Chantry	O
Mead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
were	O
you	O
off	O
then	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
As	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
it	O
is	O
about	O
forty	O
Pole	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
observe	O
there	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Son	O
and	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
immediately	O
after	O
the	O
Accident	O
happened	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
presently	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
they	O
behave	O
upon	O
this	O
Occasion	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
so	O
troubled	O
they	O
could	O
hardly	O
wag	O
or	O
speak	O
;	O
my	O
Son	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
killed	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
's	O
going	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
observe	O
them	O
when	O
the	O
Accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
Gun	O
carried	O
when	O
it	O
went	O
off	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
I	O
may	O
hold	O
this	O
Sword	O
.	O
(	O
Holding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Right-Hand	O
,	O
hanging	O
down	O
near	O
the	O
Pocket	O
a	O
few	O
Inches	O
from	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
almost	O
upon	O
a	O
Level	O
)	O
He	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
one	O
Hand	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Sword	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
express	O
himself	O
concerned	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
so	O
concerned	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
ten	O
Pole	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
beat	O
himself	O
thus	O
upon	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
of	O
any	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
Never	O
.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
(	O
on	O
the	O
cross	O
examination	O
)	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
stand	O
when	O
the	O
Accident	O
happened	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
In	O
Chantry	O
Mead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
Hedge	O
between	O
Chentry	O
Mead	O
and	O
Hare	O
Mead	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
see	O
through	O
the	O
Hedge	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
new	O
Hedge	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
Yard	O
high	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
doing	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
clear	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
see	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Annesley	O
with	O
his	O
Face	O
or	O
his	O
Back	O
towards	O
you	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Side-ways	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Why	O
Chantry	O
Mead	O
is	O
North	O
of	O
Hare	O
Mead	O
,	O
then	O
his	O
Face	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
towards	O
you	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
say	O
his	O
Side	O
was	O
towards	O
me	O
.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
speaking	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
being	O
a	O
Manour	O
;	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Manour	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
Because	O
there	O
have	O
been	O
Courts	O
kept	O
there	O
.	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
By	O
whom	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
By	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Dolben	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Sylvester	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
He	O
occupies	O
this	O
Ground	O
:	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
Farm	O
to	O
Sanders	O
,	O
and	O
Sanders	O
lets	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
which	O
Side	O
of	O
Hare	O
Mead	O
does	O
the	O
River	O
lie	O
;	O
is	O
it	O
East	O
,	O
West	O
,	O
North	O
,	O
or	O
South	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
South	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
not	O
this	O
River	O
belong	O
to	O
another	O
Person	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
not	O
Sir	O
John	O
granted	O
the	O
Fishery	O
to	O
any	O
Body	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
I	O
rent	O
the	O
Fishery	O
,	O
the	O
Fishery	O
belongs	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
depute	O
your	O
Son	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Dolben	I-pers
deputes	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Dolben	I-pers
to	O
appoint	O
your	O
Son	O
to	O
be	O
Game-Keeper	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
Because	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
daily	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
assign	O
'd	O
that	O
Fishery	O
to	O
any	O
Body	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
owns	O
the	O
Land	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
Lord	O
Dunmore	O
is	O
the	O
Landlord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
standing	O
up	O
when	O
the	O
Gun	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
sitting	O
?	O
Redding	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
up	O
.	O
[	O
William	B-pers
Duffell	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Son	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
?	O
Duffell	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
had	O
any	O
Conversation	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Duffell	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
On	O
this	O
Occasion	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
Truth	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
were	O
fishing	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Redding	O
,	O
coming	O
up	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
his	O
Father	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
Net	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
Father	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
then	O
Redding	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
Net	O
:	O
that	O
Thomas	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
threw	O
the	O
Net	O
into	O
the	O
River	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
shot	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
jump	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
River	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
Line	O
of	O
the	O
Net	O
to	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
Gun	O
went	O
off	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
dropped	O
down	O
,	O
Mr	O
Redding	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
!	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
run	O
Home	O
:	O
Mr	O
Abraham	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
pull	O
the	O
Trigger	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
answered	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Quarrel	O
or	O
Words	O
that	O
had	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
surprizing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
should	O
come	O
and	O
shoot	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
nothing	O
more	O
pass	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
in	O
what	O
Manner	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
Gun	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
in	O
what	O
Manner	O
the	O
Gun	O
was	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
thus	O
,	O
(	O
in	O
his	O
Right-Hand	O
,	O
the	O
Arm	O
hanging	O
down	O
near	O
the	O
Pocket	O
,	O
some	O
Inches	O
from	O
his	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
upon	O
a	O
Level	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Manner	O
that	O
old	O
Redding	O
said	O
the	O
Gun	O
was	O
held	O
)	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
wilfully	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
Discourse	O
after	O
this	O
Accident	O
happened	O
?	O
Duffell	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
Hours	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
this	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
before	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
knows	O
nothing	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Duffell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
eight	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
frequently	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Character	O
has	O
he	O
?	O
Duffell	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
in	O
his	O
Behalf	O
;	O
his	O
Father	O
could	O
not	O
manage	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
did	O
he	O
follow	O
?	O
Duffell	O
.	O
His	O
Father	O
was	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
leave	O
Staines	O
?	O
Duffell	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
this	O
Accident	O
happened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
has	O
he	O
been	O
ever	O
since	O
?	O
Duffell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
,	O
in	O
Pickadilly	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
at	O
Staines	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
come	O
down	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
Staines	O
?	O
Duffell	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
you	O
Directions	O
about	O
advising	O
him	O
to	O
speak	O
the	O
Truth	O
?	O
Duffell	O
.	O
No-body	O
:	O
Mr	O
Abraham	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
advised	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Duffell	O
.	O
No-body	O
but	O
Mr	O
Abraham	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
and	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
how	O
the	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
killed	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
wilfully	O
done	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
accidentally	O
done	O
?	O
Duffell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
apprehend	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
by	O
the	O
Barrel	O
near	O
the	O
Lock	O
?	O
Duffell	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
by	O
Egglestone	O
's	O
Manner	O
of	O
holding	O
the	O
Stick	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
meant	O
that	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Gun	O
about	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Barrel	O
.	O
[	O
John	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Discourse	O
had	O
you	O
with	O
young	O
Egglestone	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Laleham	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
:	O
The	O
Company	O
dined	O
at	O
the	O
Grey-Hound	O
at	O
Laleham	O
,	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
and	O
drank	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Wine	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
afterwards	O
John	O
Egglestone	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
ask	O
my	O
Advice	O
concerning	O
this	O
Accident	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wonder	O
you	O
should	O
ask	O
my	O
Advice	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
Relations	O
to	O
advise	O
with	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
sit	O
to	O
ask	O
you	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
my	O
Master	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
persuading	O
the	O
Boy	O
to	O
sell	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Blood	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
,	O
you	O
Fool	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Master	O
is	O
persuading	O
me	O
to	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
accidentally	O
done	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
accidental	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
any	O
other	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
think	O
so	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
examined	O
when	O
you	O
come	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reynell	I-pers
,	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
forswear	O
yourself	O
,	O
but	O
be	O
very	O
careful	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Character	O
has	O
the	O
Boy	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
irregular	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Trade	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Butcher	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
forswear	O
himself	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
had	O
this	O
Discourse	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Grey-Hound	O
at	O
Laleham	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
talk	O
of	O
Money	O
then	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Blood	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
came	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
persuading	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
Blood	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
said	O
my	O
Master	O
did	O
not	O
persuade	O
me	O
to	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
true	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
Yes	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
my	O
Senses	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
Friend	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
best	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
to	O
take	O
Money	O
,	O
than	O
hang	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
by	O
what	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
in	O
no	O
Danger	O
of	O
being	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
take	O
Money	O
than	O
endeavour	O
to	O
hang	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
designedly	O
.	O
(	O
Mr	O
Higgs	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
being	O
sworn	O
,	O
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
Book	O
wherein	O
all	O
the	O
Game-Keepers	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Manours	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
are	O
enter	O
'd	O
;	O
(	O
Reads	O
)	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Dolben	I-pers
of	O
Northampton	O
,	O
Baronet	O
,	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Redding	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
dated	O
2	O
July	O
,	O
1741	O
.	O
Enter	O
'd	O
29	O
January	O
,	O
1741	O
.	O
[	O
Mr	O
Richard	B-pers
Chester	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
us	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
.	O
Chester	O
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
Chaise	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Red-Lion	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
Grey-Hound	O
at	O
Laleham	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
young	O
Egglestone	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
Thing	O
happen	O
'd	O
;	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
designedly	O
,	O
or	O
happen	O
'd	O
by	O
Accident	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Chester	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
Laleham	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
accidental	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
any	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
cool	O
Blood	O
would	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
wilfully	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
Net	O
?	O
Chester	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
was	O
stooping	O
to	O
the	O
Net	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gun	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
Thing	O
how	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
held	O
the	O
Gun	O
?	O
Chester	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Chaise-Whip	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
show	O
me	O
how	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
held	O
the	O
Gun	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Whip	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
so	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
Position	O
as	O
Redding	O
and	O
Duffell	O
said	O
he	O
held	O
it	O
in	O
)	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
rather	O
nearer	O
the	O
Handle	O
than	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Whip	O
that	O
he	O
held	O
it	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Wound	O
;	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
Wound	O
?	O
Chester	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
it	O
was	O
somewhere	O
about	O
the	O
Hip	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
whether	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
shot	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Hip	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
held	O
the	O
Gun	O
that	O
Way	O
?	O
Chester	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
shot	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
held	O
it	O
any	O
other	O
Way	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Pray	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
Money	O
being	O
offered	O
by	O
any	O
Person	O
in	O
your	O
Presence	O
to	O
young	O
Egglestone	O
?	O
Chester	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
Nor	O
any	O
Reward	O
of	O
any	O
Sort	O
?	O
Chester	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
forgot	O
to	O
mention	O
one	O
thing	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
Egglestone	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
shook	O
Hands	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
Egglestone	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
designedly	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
drank	O
a	O
Glass	O
of	O
Wine	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
shake	O
Hands	O
,	O
or	O
drink	O
the	O
Wine	O
first	O
?	O
Chester	O
.	O
Both	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
?	O
Chester	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
is	O
not	O
married	O
to	O
your	O
Daughter-in-Law	O
?	O
Chester	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
if	O
your	O
Lordship	O
thinks	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
answer	O
this	O
Question	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Relation	O
is	O
very	O
small	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
they	O
insist	O
on	O
their	O
Question	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
answer	O
it	O
.	O
Chester	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
married	O
to	O
my	O
Daughter-in-Law	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
They	O
ask	O
this	O
Question	O
in	O
Hopes	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
of	O
Service	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
another	O
Affair	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
of	O
any	O
in	O
this	O
;	O
though	O
I	O
hope	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Wife	O
.	O
[	O
John	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
Mr	O
Paterson	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
did	O
attend	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
Occasion	O
;	O
please	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
Egglestone	O
behaved	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
Mr	O
Paterson	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
;	O
but	O
first	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
make	O
an	O
Apology	O
,	O
for	O
appearing	O
as	O
a	O
Witness	O
on	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
unhappy	O
Gentleman	O
for	O
whom	O
I	O
am	O
concerned	O
as	O
an	O
Attorney	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
it	O
because	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
Affair	O
of	O
so	O
great	O
Consequence	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
my	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
less	O
Scruple	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Attorney	O
without	O
Fee	O
or	O
Reward	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Staines	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Jury	O
;	O
though	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
Time	O
to	O
enquire	O
into	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
prepare	O
for	O
Mr	O
Annesley	O
's	O
Defence	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
do	O
him	O
but	O
little	O
Service	O
more	O
,	O
than	O
by	O
cross	O
examining	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
Observations	O
on	O
their	O
Evidence	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
,	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
examined	O
here	O
.	O
-	O
Court	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
any	O
Thing	O
in	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
you	O
may	O
give	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
that	O
was	O
reduced	O
into	O
writing	O
.	O
Mr	O
Paterson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
speak	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
admit	O
the	O
Depositions	O
taken	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
were	O
reduced	O
into	O
writing	O
by	O
the	O
Coroner	O
or	O
his	O
Clerk	O
.	O
[	O
Mr	O
King	O
the	O
Coroner	O
sworn	O
,	O
who	O
produced	O
his	O
Minutes	O
of	O
the	O
Depositions	O
made	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
]	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
drawn	O
up	O
when	O
Egglestone	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
or	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Mr	O
King	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
drawn	O
up	O
afterwards	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
drawn	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Read	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
they	O
relate	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Egglestone	I-pers
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
Did	O
Egglestone	O
sign	O
his	O
Deposition	O
?	O
Mr	O
King	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mr	O
Serj	O
.	O
Gapper	O
.	O
