TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
ON	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
TUESDAY	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
15th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1742	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Godschall	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
T.	O
PAYNE	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
South-Sea-House	O
.	O
M	O
,	O
DCC.XLII	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
SIX-PENCE	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
AT	O
THE	O
Sessions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
For	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
GODSCHALL	I-pers
.	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
PARKER	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WRIGHT	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
ABNEY	I-pers
;	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRANGE	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Deputy-Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Pinkney	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Pine	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Grudee	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Granville	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Whipham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Delancy	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Peat	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Blagdon	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gilmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wren	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
House	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brackley	I-pers
.	O
1	O
,	O
2.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
Moses	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
Tame	O
Pheasants	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
tame	O
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
.	O
John	O
Hill	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
himself	O
and	O
his	O
Partner	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
stole	O
15	O
Brace	O
of	O
Pheasants	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
Bag	O
while	O
Brown	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
Way	O
from	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
's	O
House	O
they	O
killed	O
21	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
they	O
brought	O
to	O
Town	O
alive	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
tell	O
you	O
from	O
whence	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
's	O
Pens	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
keep	O
these	O
Pheasants	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
have	O
Pens	O
made	O
for	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
about	O
the	O
Compass	O
of	O
this	O
Court	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
hear	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
me	O
before	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Holt	B-pers
Crowther	I-pers
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
's	O
Servant	O
(	O
Hill	O
)	O
informing	O
me	O
that	O
his	O
Master	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
some	O
Pheasants	O
,	O
we	O
agreed	O
together	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
and	O
ask	O
his	O
Advice	O
.	O
He	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
Moses	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
:	O
We	O
accordingly	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
was	O
brought	O
down	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Brown	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Fact	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
's	O
Name	O
?	O
Crowther	O
.	O
I	O
mention	O
'd	O
that	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
had	O
lost	O
15	O
Brace	O
of	O
Pheasants	O
from	O
Farnham-Royal	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
owned	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Brown	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pens	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
Bag	O
while	O
Brown	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
that	O
Way	O
some	O
Time	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Cock	O
Pheasants	O
crow	O
,	O
which	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Pens	O
now	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
brought	O
9	O
only	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
30	O
alive	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
fed	O
them	O
with	O
Bread	O
and	O
Meat	O
at	O
the	O
Cart	O
and	O
Horse	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lipscomb	O
's	O
Shop	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
6	O
Pheasants	O
for	O
Sale	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
this	O
seen	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
of	O
some	O
Pheasants	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
for	O
farther	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
Pheasants	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
tall	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Wig	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bred	O
them	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
imagined	O
at	O
first	O
that	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Essex	O
's	O
Pheasants	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
Pheasant-Keeper	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
directly	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
Brown	O
contradicted	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
Pheasants	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
Q	O
When	O
Brown	O
was	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
did	O
he	O
confess	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Davis	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
my	O
Lord	O
Essex	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
's	O
.	O
Jervis	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Cart	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Brown	O
was	O
my	O
Lodger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
Davis	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
confess	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
.	O
The	O
Confession	O
which	O
I	O
speak	O
of	O
was	O
not	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
repeated	O
the	O
same	O
next	O
Day	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Brogdon	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Colonel	O
the	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
Essex	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
began	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
whole	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Brown	O
then	O
desir	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Hurry	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
Brown	O
perceived	O
that	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
would	O
be	O
admitted	O
to	O
give	O
Evidence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Davis	O
,	O
now	O
you	O
have	O
begun	O
tell	O
the	O
whole	O
Truth	O
.	O
Then	O
Davis	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Walk	O
to	O
Farnham-Royal	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
that	O
himself	O
and	O
Brown	O
stole	O
about	O
15	O
Brace	O
of	O
Pheasants	O
from	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
's	O
Pens	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Brown	O
confess	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Brogdon	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
Davis	O
took	O
the	O
Pheasants	O
.	O
Q	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
Menaces	O
or	O
Threats	O
made	O
Use	O
of	O
to	O
induce	O
them	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
Confession	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Brogdon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
first	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
,	O
Davis	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
refused	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
hear	O
us	O
called	O
Deer-stealers	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Brogdon	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
Word	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
confirmed	O
Mr.	O
Brogdon	O
's	O
Deposition	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
.	O
When	O
these	O
2	O
Persons	O
were	O
first	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
Davis	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
private	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
began	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
at	O
Farnham-Royal	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
concerning	O
my	O
Lord	O
Essex	O
's	O
Pheasants	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
his	O
Family	O
admit	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
absolutely	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
that	O
Robbery	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
A	O
Day	O
or	O
two	O
afterwards	O
there	O
came	O
full	O
Evidence	O
of	O
both	O
Robberies	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
again	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Davis	O
then	O
confessed	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
's	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Place	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
Farnham	O
Royal	O
,	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
Poulterers	O
where	O
the	O
Pheasants	O
were	O
sold	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
my	O
Lord	O
Essex	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Deveil	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Davis	O
had	O
gone	O
a	O
great	O
Way	O
in	O
his	O
Confession	O
,	O
Brown	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
Defence	O
attempted	O
to	O
prove	O
their	O
buying	O
the	O
Pheasants	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
Satisfaction	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
2d	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
19	O
tame	O
Pheasants	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Essex	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
convicted	O
on	O
this	O
Indictment	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Transportation	O
for	O
7	O
Years	O
.	O
3.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sword	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Hilt	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Ocarrol	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4	O
,	O
5.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pinks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Francis	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Leonard	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
36	O
Fowls	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
-	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
hawking	O
Bags	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
d	O
,	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
3	O
d	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Simmonds	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Dec.	O
1st	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Higler	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
Town	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Fowls	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
of	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Pinks	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
off	O
my	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
Ditch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
search	O
'd	O
my	O
Pockets	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
Men	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
(	O
Jenkins	O
)	O
beat	O
me	O
several	O
Times	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
and	O
Pistol	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
Silver	O
except	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
Town	O
to	O
pay	O
away	O
for	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
deals	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
lost	O
15	O
d.	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Money	O
,	O
four	O
dozen	O
of	O
Fowls	O
all	O
but	O
five	O
,	O
a	O
Sack	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Hawking-bags	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
which	O
were	O
all	O
my	O
Property	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Pinks	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
6	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
8	O
Weeks	O
since	O
he	O
accused	O
us	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Simmonds	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
Time	O
exactly	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
abused	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
myself	O
since	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Haine	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
When	O
Pinks	O
was	O
first	O
taken	O
into	O
Custody	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
about	O
27	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
and	O
some	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sav	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Labour	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Reason	O
for	O
making	O
me	O
come	O
after	O
him	O
so	O
often	O
for	O
Money	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
half	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
keep	O
and	O
shew	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
:	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
to	O
be	O
busie	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
Headboroughs	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
Money	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
kept	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
being	O
Headborough	O
,	O
search	O
'd	O
Pinks	O
's	O
House	O
for	O
some	O
Fowls	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
Pink	O
's	O
at	O
Dinner	O
with	O
four	O
Fowls	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
ready	O
dress	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
body	O
that	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Fowls	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
discharg	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
took	O
an	O
Inventory	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
(	O
Simmonds	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
then	O
absconded	O
for	O
eight	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Town	O
again	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
half	O
Crown	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Haine	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Haine	O
.	O
This	O
half	O
Crown	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
Pinks	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
Simmonds	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
half	O
Crown	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
cut	O
on	O
the	O
Head	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
.	O
Pinks	O
.	O
Ask	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
Money	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
?	O
Simmonds	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Weeks	O
off	O
and	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
receive	O
this	O
Money	O
to	O
bring	O
to	O
Town	O
?	O
Simmonds	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
.	O
This	O
half	O
Crown	O
I	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
refus	O
'd	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
then	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Opinion	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
and	O
a	O
sleep	O
when	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
,	O
6.	O
Richard	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
glass	O
Salts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
glass	O
Candlestick	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
glass	O
Crewit	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
glass	O
Castor	O
tipp	O
'd	O
with	O
Brass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
,	O
And	O
,	O
7.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Merriton	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
8.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Friend	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
Dish	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
Fitzwalter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
House	O
,	O
Dec.	O
26	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Longmore	I-pers
.	O
We	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
Dish	O
from	O
my	O
Lord	O
Fitzwalter	O
's	O
in	O
Pall-Mall	B-place
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
away	O
:	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Jervis	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
on	O
Board	O
a	O
Ship	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
Dish	O
away	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Morris	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Cook	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Fitzwalter	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
of	O
Dec.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
House	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
his	O
who	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
Work	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Dish	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
very	O
great	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Longmore	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Jervis	O
went	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
such	O
Things	O
?	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
the	O
Dish	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
an	O
hundred	O
Times	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
scrap	O
'd	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dish	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
cut	O
it	O
into	O
Pieces	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Arms	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Dish	O
,	O
nor	O
cut	O
it	O
to	O
Pieces	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Shipmates	O
did	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jervis	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Desire	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Fitzwalter	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Longmore	O
,	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
seems	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
somebody	O
that	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Defence	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Coates	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
examined	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
directed	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Augustus	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Townshend	O
Accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Board	O
the	O
Augustus	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Mate	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
Silver	O
Dish	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
lost	O
,	O
therefore	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Chest	O
upon	O
the	O
Quarter-deck	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
search	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Mate	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
Dish	O
,	O
cut	O
into	O
four	O
Pieces	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Conversation	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Jervis	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Quarter-deck	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
rob	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
where	O
his	O
Aunt	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Aunt	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Dish	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
Gangway	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
prove	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
Dish	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Discourse	O
with	O
him	O
afterwards	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
him	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Butler	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
Dish	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Wm	O
Saunders	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
down	O
to	O
Gravesend	O
with	O
my	O
Lord	O
Fitzwalter	O
's	O
Butler	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
ashore	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
Gravesend	O
Goal	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
putting	O
on	O
his	O
Hand-cuffs	O
,	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
the	O
Dish	O
was	O
as	O
safe	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
Ann	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Silver	O
Dishes	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Dresser	O
in	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
House	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Edge	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
a	O
little	O
Turn	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Pewter	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
Dish	O
off	O
the	O
Dresser	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
it	O
lye	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
John	B-pers
Joice	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leather	O
Saddle	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Stable	O
.	O
Jan.	O
4th	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
10.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Elms	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
Copper	O
Frying-pan	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Ainsley	I-pers
December	O
25	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
11.	O
John	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Wooden	O
Cask	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Pipe	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
12.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mildred	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Susannah	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Street	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
green	O
Silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
Steel	O
Seal	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
.	O
Jan.	O
4	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Newgate	B-place
street	I-place
towards	I-place
the	I-place
Poultry	I-place
Compter	I-place
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
me	O
fast	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
from	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Middle	O
of	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Fellows	O
jostled	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
me	O
close	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Immediately	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
stuck	O
so	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
any	O
but	O
her	O
's	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
Purse	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Steel	O
Seal	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
my	O
Purse	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
Murder	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
loosed	O
her	O
Hold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
your	O
Purse	O
in	O
your	O
Pocket	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Newgate	O
street	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
received	O
ten	O
Shillings	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
Purse	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
did	O
she	O
walk	O
that	O
Night	O
before	O
this	O
besel	O
her	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Place	O
that	O
is	O
called	O
Blowbladder	O
street	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Mile	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
you	O
not	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
taken	O
privately	O
from	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
met	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
go	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
Moon-light	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
shop	O
shut	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
behind	O
you	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
take	O
Notice	O
of	O
her	O
Face	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
.	O
With	O
my	O
struggling	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
with	O
my	O
Face	O
to	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Offley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
the	O
Compter	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
(	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
)	O
as	O
near	O
together	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
for	O
two	O
Women	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
surrounded	O
by	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Men	O
.	O
I	O
knowing	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
her	O
cry	O
out	O
Murder	O
,	O
I	O
stepp	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
way	O
through	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Mob	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
run	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
went	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
usual	O
Manner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
so	O
near	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
?	O
Offley	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
complain	O
of	O
being	O
robbed	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Offley	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
Minutes	O
after	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
stepped	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Croud	O
of	O
People	O
;	O
were	O
not	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
as	O
near	O
to	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
as	O
I	O
?	O
Offley	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Person	O
so	O
near	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Garnal	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
about	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
King	O
Street	O
,	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
Yards	O
of	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Men	O
hauling	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
,	O
and	O
pushing	O
her	O
to	O
and	O
fro	O
'	O
.	O
She	O
cryed	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
certain	O
what	O
the	O
Words	O
were	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
Murder	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
certain	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
pretty	O
near	O
the	O
Compter	O
Passage	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
even	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
separated	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
to	O
herself	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
observed	O
her	O
clap	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
her	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
her	O
Watch	O
!	O
her	O
Watch	O
!	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
crossed	O
the	O
Way	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Poultry	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
an	O
exceeding	O
Pace	O
,	O
sometimes	O
walked	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
ran	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
Pace	O
with	O
her	O
without	O
sometimes	O
running	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
coming	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
such	O
Haste	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
concerned	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Walbrook	O
,	O
she	O
turned	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
dozen	O
Yards	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
to	O
see	O
where	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Corner	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
off	O
her	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
with	O
full	O
Speed	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
thought	O
she	O
certainly	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
grasp	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
a	O
Watch	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Poulterer	O
's	O
Shop	O
that	O
I	O
first	O
seized	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
my	O
Assistance	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
likewise	O
.	O
Immediately	O
I	O
heard	O
two	O
Blows	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Arm	O
reel	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
.	O
Soon	O
afterwards	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
Blow	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sprang	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Arms	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
up	O
Buckler	O
's	O
Bury	O
,	O
I	O
overtook	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
her	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
Assistance	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
strike	O
about	O
very	O
smartly	O
with	O
his	O
Stick	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
Door	O
I	O
seized	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
bring	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
Door	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Bingham	O
,	O
a	O
Silk-Dyer	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
a	O
Purse	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
She	O
pretended	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
Walbrook	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Friend	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
staid	O
some	O
Time	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bingham	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
that	O
follow	O
'd	O
us	O
,	O
striking	O
those	O
that	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Man	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
Purse	O
and	O
shook	O
some	O
Silver	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
been	O
carried	O
next	O
Day	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
then	O
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
green	O
Purse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
a	O
light	O
blue	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
take	O
my	O
Oath	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
George	B-pers
Lesley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Walbrook	O
towards	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Poulterer	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
facing	O
the	O
Mantron-house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Man	O
(	O
Garnal	O
)	O
holding	O
that	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Loss	O
whether	O
I	O
should	O
stop	O
or	O
go	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
rush	O
'd	O
from	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
she	O
was	O
innocent	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
repeating	O
these	O
Words	O
,	O
he	O
redoubled	O
his	O
Blows	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
ran	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
struck	O
us	O
,	O
up	O
Buckler	O
's	O
Bury	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
crying	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
The	O
other	O
People	O
ran	O
faster	O
than	O
I	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
distanc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
'till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
End	O
of	O
Buckler's-Bury	O
,	O
and	O
perceiving	O
the	O
Man	O
using	O
his	O
Stick	O
as	O
smartly	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
somebody	O
else	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
together	O
they	O
denied	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
each	O
other	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
that	O
Man	O
when	O
they	O
ran	O
off	O
together	O
?	O
Lesley	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
so	O
near	O
that	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
fix	O
any	O
Distance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
each	O
other	O
?	O
Lesley	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
innocent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
hearing	O
then	O
?	O
Lesley	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
near	O
enough	O
to	O
hear	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
contradict	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
her	O
struggling	O
with	O
this	O
Man	O
might	O
not	O
prevent	O
her	O
hearing	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lambkin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
in	O
Buckler's-Bury	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
very	O
fast	O
up	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
struggled	O
with	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
James	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
ran	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
.	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
Blow	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
go	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
run	O
above	O
forty	O
Yards	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
Garnal	O
.	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Master	O
of	O
a	O
Ship	O
at	O
Wapping	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
them	O
cry	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
Noise	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
know	O
Country	O
People	O
generally	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Clock	O
over	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Man	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Lady	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
Watch	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
neither	O
Gold	O
nor	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
seven-night	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
Wapping	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
some	O
Country	O
People	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
hurt	O
her	O
Foot	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
Arm	O
in	O
Arm	O
down	O
the	O
City	O
;	O
and	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Poultry-Compter	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
)	O
a	O
Croud	O
of	O
People	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
shov	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
C.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
Out-cry	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
then	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
whole	O
Heap	O
of	O
People	O
came	O
along	O
and	O
parted	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
tumbled	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
C.	O
When	O
you	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
what	O
Distance	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
shov	O
'd	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
.	O
C.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
ask	O
for	O
your	O
Companion	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
up	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Who	O
should	O
I	O
ask	O
among	O
Strangers	O
?	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
C	O
Were	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
near	O
the	O
Poultry-Compter	O
Door	O
?	O
Smith	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
was	O
against	O
the	O
Church	O
.	O
C.	O
Was	O
there	O
nothing	O
said	O
of	O
the	O
Loss	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
in	O
your	O
hearing	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
up	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
some	O
Business	O
at	O
Wapping	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoe	O
lane	O
;	O
my	O
Husband	O
is	O
a	O
Journeyman	O
Brasier	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Chair-woman	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
Months	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
a	O
Week	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
pains-taking	O
Woman	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
16	O
or	O
17	O
Years	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
Newcastle-Bridge	O
.	O
I	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
sent	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Swinton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
about	O
9	O
Months	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
her	O
with	O
every	O
Thing	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
addicted	O
to	O
pilfering	O
.	O
The	O
Night	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Wapping	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
Relation	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Newcastle	O
upon	O
Tyne	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
Woman	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
Parish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Swinton	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Whittington	O
and	O
his	O
Cat	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
Market	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Gammon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
last	O
Summer	O
:	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
Wapping	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Masters	O
of	O
Ships	O
in	O
Newcastle	O
,	O
who	O
very	O
often	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
little	O
Presents	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
3d	O
Day	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
Child	O
's	O
Birth-Day	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
three	O
Years-old	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
this	O
young	O
Woman	O
(	O
Smith	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
to	O
wait	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Littleton	O
Westley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
her	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
my	O
Family	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
13.	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
Ells	O
of	O
checqu	O
'd	O
Linnen	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Crookshank	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lumley	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salver	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
2	O
Silver	O
Pepper-Castors	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Punch	O
Ladle	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
6	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Tongs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
.	O
4	O
Cloth	O
Coats	O
,	O
2	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
6	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
2	O
Shirts	O
,	O
3	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Garnet	O
and	O
4	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Cypher	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Ear	O
Rings	O
set	O
with	O
Garnets	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
23	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
15.	O
Richard	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
a	O
Silver	O
Mug	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Cup	O
,	O
2	O
Pepper	B-pers
Castors	I-pers
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Punch	O
Ladle	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
Salt	O
,	O
6	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Tea	O
Tongs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Cloth	O
Breeches	O
,	O
3	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
with	O
a	O
Cypher	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
Garnet	O
and	O
4	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Dec.	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
spending	O
the	O
Evening	O
at	O
a	O
public	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Daughter	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Inform	O
'd	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
directly	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Goldsmith's-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
advertised	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Day	O
following	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
by	O
whom	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Daughter	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
Lumley	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
din	O
'd	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
clean	O
Apron	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Fleet	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
my	O
Sister	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Man	O
(	O
Burgess	O
)	O
came	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Church	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
.	O
She	O
(	O
Lumley	O
)	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
on	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
her	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Sister	O
parted	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
then	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
along	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
we	O
called	O
at	O
another	O
Place	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
six	O
o'Clock	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
Home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Condition	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
House	O
then	O
?	O
Simmonds	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
and	O
the	O
Parlour	O
Window	O
both	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
directly	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
advertised	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Christmas-Day	O
,	O
this	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Manners	O
,	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
Tavern	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Newport	O
Market	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Instructions	O
from	O
several	O
of	O
our	O
Relations	O
,	O
how	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
the	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Maid	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
Woman	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
her	O
Lodging	O
in	O
May-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
Burgess	O
)	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
baited	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Burgess	O
afterwards	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
Door	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
this	O
Sack	O
.	O
She	O
likewise	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Gown	O
and	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Ring	O
with	O
6	O
Diamonds	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
pawn	O
in	O
Marlborough-Meuse	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
.	O
At	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
Newport	O
Market	O
we	O
found	O
my	O
Garnet	B-pers
Ear	I-pers
Rings	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Diamond	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cypher	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Burgess	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
give	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
(	O
Lumley	O
)	O
or	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
?	O
Simmonds	O
.	O
He	O
first	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
afterwards	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
Uncle	O
and	O
Cousin	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Manner	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
describing	O
the	O
Woman	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
agreed	O
that	O
Mr	O
.	O
Manners	O
's	O
Girl	O
and	O
my	O
Sister	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
their	O
Room	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
Manners	O
's	O
Servant	O
knowing	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
their	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
both	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Tavern	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fraser	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Entry	O
with	O
the	O
Woman	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Locks	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
Sheet	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
and	O
ty	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
gave	O
a	O
Man	O
3	O
d	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
into	O
Hanover	O
Yard	O
,	O
where	O
her	O
Husband	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
(	O
Burgess	O
)	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
May-Fair	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Justice	O
had	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
Burgess	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
till	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
Lumley	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
:	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
shew	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Coaches	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
May-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Room	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
this	O
Sack	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
herself	O
pull	O
'd	O
a	O
Tile	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Hearth	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
2	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ear	O
Bobs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Gold	O
Buttons	O
.	O
We	O
afterwards	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
Gown	O
,	O
and	O
Diamond	O
Rings	O
at	O
Marlborough-Meuse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
in	O
West	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
On	O
Christmas	O
Day	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fraser	O
,	O
who	O
examin	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Passage	O
with	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
that	O
Gentlewoman	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Things	O
and	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Sheet	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
she	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
Cup	O
or	O
the	O
Mug	O
,	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
:	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
she	O
ty	O
'd	O
the	O
Things	O
up	O
tight	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
Man	O
3	O
d.	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Hanover-Yard	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
if	O
he	O
discharg	O
'd	O
the	O
Man	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
secure	O
the	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Justice	O
refusing	O
to	O
detain	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
aid	O
and	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
refused	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
again	O
insisted	O
on	O
his	O
being	O
confin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Round-house	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Burgess	O
!	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
!	O
No	O
,	O
(	O
said	O
he	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
not	O
:	O
Why	O
(	O
said	O
I	O
)	O
when	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
you	O
just	O
now	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
Pocket	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Key	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
very	O
Key	O
unlock	O
'd	O
the	O
Door	O
in	O
May	O
Fair	O
where	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
Lumley	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
's	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
in	O
Marlborough-Meuse	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Gown	O
,	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
Rings	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Sheets	O
we	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
Direction	O
pawn	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
Neighbours	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
Things	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Manners	O
's	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
large	O
Spoon	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
the	O
Silversmith	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
melted	O
down	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
near	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Night	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
(	O
Simmonds	O
,	O
jun	O
.	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
Room	O
in	O
Newport-Market	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
Pockets	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Prison	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Things	O
concealed	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
often	O
heard	O
her	O
Husband	O
talk	O
of	O
hiding	O
Things	O
under	O
the	O
Bricks	O
and	O
Tiles	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
Hearth	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Tile	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
Rings	O
and	O
these	O
Buttons	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Burgess	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
deny	O
the	O
Key	O
when	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Warner	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
deny	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Manners	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
Lumley	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
Ring	O
to	O
my	O
Mistress	O
.	O
Emery	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
.	O
About	O
3	O
Weeks	O
before	O
this	O
Thing	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
Burgess	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
took	O
a	O
Lodging	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
May-Fair	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Burgess	O
had	O
a	O
Bundle	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
his	O
Wife	O
a	O
Candle	O
to	O
light	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Bundle	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
Candle	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
upon	O
his	O
Finger	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Dec.	O
the	O
Woman	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Ring	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
Money	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
?	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
1	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Name	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Elderson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Burgess	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
me	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
?	O
Young	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
where	O
my	O
Brother	O
Simmonds	O
lives	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
draw	O
up	O
an	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Hall	O
.	O
On	O
Christmas-Day	O
this	O
Ring	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Manners	O
and	O
were	O
told	O
by	O
her	O
Maid	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
Woman	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
we	O
agreed	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
my	O
Neice	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
Manners	O
's	O
Maid	O
should	O
go	O
together	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Woman	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
Robbery	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
told	O
before	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
Man	O
to	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Round-house	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
(	O
Lumley	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
Burgess	O
!	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
Key	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
not	O
:	O
but	O
the	O
Constable	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
Side	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
Key	O
directly	O
to	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Coaches	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
this	O
Sack	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
some	O
Part	O
of	O
Lumley	O
's	O
Confession	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
He	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
above	O
Depositions	O
,	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
they	O
related	O
to	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Lodgings	O
in	O
May-Fair	O
.	O
Lumley	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
(	O
Burgess	O
)	O
is	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
My	O
two	O
Cousins	O
din	O
'd	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
that	O
Day	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Fleet	O
to	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
no	O
farther	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
Newport-Market	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
for	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
My	O
Cousin	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
very	O
Night	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
their	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
Street	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
these	O
Things	O
.	O
I	O
hired	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
Plumbtree-Court	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
May-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
his	O
Trouble	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
May	O
Fair	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Man	O
(	O
Burgess	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
Home	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
concealed	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
under	O
my	O
own	O
Cloaths	O
because	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Milson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pringley	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Freer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Story	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
Burgess	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
Gerard	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Capgny	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Farrit	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
had	O
known	O
Lumley	O
different	O
Numbers	O
of	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
Guilty	O
,	O
and	O
earnestly	O
desired	O
that	O
Lumley	O
might	O
be	O
recommended	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
as	O
an	O
Object	O
of	O
Mercy	O
.	O
[	O
Lumley	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Burgess	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
John	B-pers
Broadbridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
(	O
after	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1731	O
.	O
)	O
56	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Hannam	I-pers
,	O
with	O
lntent	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
Dec.	O
21	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
17.	O
John	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
China	O
Cups	O
and	O
Saucers	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Bently	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Train	O
Oyl	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stawks	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pig	I-pers
of	O
Harmonsworth	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Singer	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
9	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Skins	O
of	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Sheep	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
Skins	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
marked	O
with	O
R	O
S.	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
what	O
he	O
always	O
marks	O
his	O
Sheep	O
with	O
.	O
We	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Chance	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reynell	I-pers
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
either	O
own	O
'd	O
or	O
denied	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Hearing	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Singer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
Weather	O
Sheep	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Shepherd	O
informing	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
suspected	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pig	I-pers
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
in	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Widow	O
Souch	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
we	O
first	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
we	O
had	O
finish	O
'd	O
our	O
Search	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
We	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
just	O
put	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Beer	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
off	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Closet	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
Tallow	O
:	O
After	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
the	O
Bed-chamber	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
cover	O
'd	O
up	O
with	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
away	O
and	O
then	O
saw	O
my	O
two	O
Sheep-skins	O
lie	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
R.	O
S.	O
on	O
the	O
Hind	B-pers
Leg	I-pers
.	O
Under	O
the	O
Skins	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Guts	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Carcase	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Sheep	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
cut	O
into	O
Quarters	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
which	O
was	O
Sunday	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Men	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
above	O
3	O
Miles	O
from	O
his	O
House	O
before	O
we	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
bad	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Chance	I-pers
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
likewise	O
,	O
we	O
then	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
Morning	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Reywell	I-pers
who	O
committed	O
one	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
at	O
Home	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
?	O
Singer	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Anchor	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Tillier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Shepherd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Singer	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Four	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Chance	O
and	O
another	O
go	O
by	O
my	O
Fold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
two	O
Sheep	O
.	O
I	O
inform	O
'd	O
my	O
Master	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
Pig	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
that	O
Pig	O
had	O
any	O
Intention	O
to	O
steal	O
your	O
Sheep	O
?	O
Tillier	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
baddish	O
Character	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Chance	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Carpenter	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
a	O
wholesale	O
Shop	O
at	O
Harlingston	O
;	O
but	O
meeting	O
Pig	O
's	O
Mother	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
seperate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
Home	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
the	O
same	O
Night	O
we	O
went	O
from	O
Pig	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
Sack	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
this	O
Shop	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
disappointed	O
in	O
that	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Designs	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
Home	O
without	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Sheep	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Fold	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
gone	O
past	O
that	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Pig	O
caught	O
one	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Sack	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
caught	O
another	O
and	O
tied	O
the	O
Legs	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pig	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
we	O
stead	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
Bread	O
and	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
his	O
Wife	O
some	O
Men	O
were	O
coming	O
to	O
search	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Sheep	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Closet	O
;	O
the	O
Guts	O
and	O
the	O
Skins	O
I	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Chimney	O
,	O
and	O
cover	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
Rug	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
pretty	O
leisurely	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
run	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
far	O
before	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Pig	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
cross	O
the	O
Thames	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
our	O
Escape	O
to	O
East-Ham	O
:	O
Accordingly	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Will	O
.	O
Clement	O
's	O
at	O
Shugg's-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
having	O
nothing	O
to	O
offer	O
in	O
his	O
Defence	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
20.	O
Jesse	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
White-chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Law	I-pers
,	O
about	O
2	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
Stewpan	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
brass	O
Sauce-pans	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
camblet	O
Cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6d	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Law	I-pers
,	O
December	O
13	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Law	I-pers
On	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
my	O
Doors	O
were	O
bolted	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
6	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
outer	O
and	O
inner	O
Doors	O
both	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Law	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
Joseph	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
Shoes	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
robbing	O
me	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
whether	O
any	O
Body	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Apartment	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Law	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
Place	O
that	O
is	O
inclosed	O
with	O
Windows	O
and	O
Shutters	O
in	O
the	O
Night-time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
Communication	O
between	O
your	O
House	O
and	O
this	O
Place	O
?	O
Law	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
small	O
Passage	O
that	O
leads	O
from	O
that	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
dress	O
your	O
Victuals	O
in	O
this	O
Place	O
?	O
Law	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Occasion	O
I	O
can	O
lye	O
there	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
where	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
eat	O
any	O
Victuals	O
but	O
in	O
that	O
Place	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
it	O
from	O
your	O
Dwelling	O
Apartment	O
?	O
Law	O
.	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
from	O
hence	O
to	O
the	O
Bench	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Have	O
a	O
great	O
Caution	O
for	O
my	O
Life	O
is	O
at	O
Stake	O
.	O
Law	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
Yard	O
over	O
or	O
under	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
the	O
Thief-catchers	O
never	O
prompted	O
him	O
to	O
say	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
.	O
Law	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
Times	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
this	O
Man	O
's	O
Apartment	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Moon	O
shining	O
so	O
bright	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
afraid	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
almost	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
we	O
resolved	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Back-gate	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
leads	O
into	O
Bell-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
2	O
Sauce-pans	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
new	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Riding	O
hood	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
and	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposes	O
only	O
a	O
Cloak	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
Cloak	O
and	O
a	O
Head	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Law	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
a	O
Riding-hood	O
with	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
fasten	O
'd	O
together	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Davis	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
Hands	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
same	O
Shoes	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
21.	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
Victualler	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
on	O
Mary	B-pers
Grayling	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
about	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
nine	O
Years	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
feloniously	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
endeavour	O
and	O
attempt	O
carnally	O
to	O
know	O
and	O
abuse	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
did	O
most	O
grievously	O
lacerate	O
and	O
abuse	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
which	O
Laceration	O
she	O
languished	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
charg	O
'd	O
by	O
Vertue	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
third	O
Time	O
for	O
ravishing	O
Mary	B-pers
Grayling	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
Form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mr.	O
Cowling	O
Surgeon	O
and	O
Man-Midwife	O
,	O
inspected	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
its	O
Death	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
aparticular	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Condition	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Opinion	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
so	O
great	O
an	O
Injury	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
she	O
could	O
live	O
.	O
Several	O
Witnesses	O
were	O
produced	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Declarations	O
in	O
extremis	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
the	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
not	O
of	O
competent	O
Years	O
to	O
make	O
such	O
Declaration	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
offered	O
in	O
Support	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
22.	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Marble	O
Table	O
,	O
Value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bosworth	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Edward	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
11	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
ripping	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Copper	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Possession	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bosworth	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Edward	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23	O
,	O
24.	O
Ann	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pot	O
with	O
a	O
Cover	O
,	O
a	O
Brass	O
Ladle	O
,	O
a	O
Copper	O
Tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
10th	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Leg	O
of	O
Mutton	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Wnt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
26th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bent	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
Pounds	O
Weight	O
of	O
Juniper	B-pers
Berries	I-pers
.	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
December	O
9th	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Value	O
9	O
d	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tinney	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
Pounds	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
Value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
15th	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
John	B-pers
Hinds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
80	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Iron	O
Bars	O
,	O
Value	O
5s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tipper	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Colt	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Court	O
call	O
'd	O
Hartshorn	B-place
court	I-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
Value	O
7s	O
.	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
Jan.	O
12	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Colt	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
,	O
at	O
almost	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Long-lane	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asking	O
Charity	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
relieve	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
Power	O
to	O
relieve	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Red-lion	O
in	O
Aldersgate	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
accept	O
of	O
Part	O
of	O
a	O
Tankard	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
welcome	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Golden-horse	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
destitute	O
of	O
a	O
Lodging	O
as	O
he	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
one	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
Barbican	O
into	O
Golden-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
into	O
Hartshorn-Court	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Sw	O
eetheart	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
Looks	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
therefore	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
shewed	O
me	O
another	O
Place	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Light	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
there	O
neither	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
determined	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
Lodging	O
;	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
gone	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
or	O
a	O
Weapon	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Face	O
was	O
very	O
black	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
Hankerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
recovered	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
some	O
Alleys	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Watch	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Watchman	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
Alleys	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
the	O
Beadle	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
afterwards	O
went	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Horse	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
denied	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
to	O
tie	O
about	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
Home	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
about	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Place	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
whom	O
they	O
suspected	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
Cook	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
set	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bench	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
full	O
View	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Presently	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Men	O
were	O
dispatch	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
so	O
sure	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
he	O
repeated	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
sure	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Man	O
?	O
Colt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
light	O
on	O
me	O
first	O
?	O
Colt	O
.	O
In	O
Long-Lane	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
?	O
Colt	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Golden-Horse	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
there	O
?	O
Colt	O
.	O
Some	O
Drink	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
?	O
Colt	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
Hackney	O
Coachmen	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
People	O
.	O
C.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Face	O
?	O
Colt	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
C.	O
Was	O
you	O
Sober	O
?	O
Colt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Austen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
in	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
Golden-Lane	O
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
at	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
beating	O
my	O
Rounds	O
in	O
Hartshorn-Court	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
call	O
Watch	O
!	O
Just	O
by	O
the	O
Pump	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Blow	O
on	O
the	O
Right	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
'd	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
some	O
Alleys	O
to	O
no	O
Purpose	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
to	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Goal	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
About	O
2	O
o'Clock	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
,	O
this	O
Thomas	B-pers
Colt	I-pers
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
without	O
either	O
Hat	O
or	O
Wig	O
,	O
imagin	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
,	O
therefore	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Beadle	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Gin-shop	O
in	O
Hartshorn-Court	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Quartern	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
immediately	O
saw	O
the	O
Person	O
whom	O
I	O
suspected	O
:	O
That	O
was	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
told	O
Colt	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
got	O
the	O
same	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Beadle	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Man	O
up	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
still	O
insisted	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
from	O
ten	O
Thousand	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
directly	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
do	O
n't	O
prosecute	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Charles	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
to	O
take	O
this	O
Man	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Ginshop	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
before	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Goal	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
certainly	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Whistler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
at	O
Dinner	O
time	O
with	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
according	O
to	O
Custom	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
to	O
take	O
Christopher	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
with	O
some	O
Persuasions	O
I	O
consented	O
.	O
Hunt	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
Thompson	O
and	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
who	O
sat	O
facing	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Beadle	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
He	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
do	O
n't	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
so	O
sure	O
shall	O
I	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
he	O
repeated	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Times	O
.	O
-	O
Dyer	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
to	O
assist	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
and	O
desired	O
Colt	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
he	O
swore	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Coachmen	O
here	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
7-night	O
,	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
Mistress	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
lie	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
and	O
sup	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
twelve	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
were	O
a-bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
remember	O
that	O
Day	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
Because	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
do	O
you	O
follow	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Frame	O
Maker	O
by	O
Trade	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
Business	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
I	O
run	O
on	O
Errands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
House	O
is	O
this	O
in	O
Hartshorn-Court	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Brandy-shop	O
kept	O
by	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Bagley	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Beversley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
on	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
only	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Golden	O
Horse	O
Alehouse	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
last	O
Monday	O
7-night	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Beversley	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
particular	O
Notice	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
there	O
?	O
Beversley	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
Twelve	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
of	O
Night	O
.	O
Beversley	O
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
Club	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
angry	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
let	O
Strangers	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
take	O
on	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Beversley	O
.	O
Because	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Saturday	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
quite	O
otherwise	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
short	O
siz	O
'd	O
Man	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
dark	O
Complection	O
,	O
and	O
pretty	O
much	O
pock-broken	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
Room	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Bit	O
of	O
a	O
Supper	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
bolted	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
Fire-side	O
when	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
some-body	O
cry	O
,	O
Aye	O
Boy	O
!	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
presently	O
one	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Watchman	O
came	O
almost	O
Two	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
call	O
Watch	O
!	O
and	O
the	O
Watchman	O
cryed	O
,	O
Aye	O
Boy	O
!	O
What	O
's	O
the	O
matter	O
now	O
?	O
My	O
Wife	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
to	O
visit	O
a	O
Woman	O
who	O
was	O
dying	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
no-body	O
went	O
out	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Man	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Golden	O
Horse	O
with	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
?	O
Bradford	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Coachman	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
you	O
say	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
?	O
Bradford	O
.	O
A	O
thin	O
,	O
squat	O
Man	O
,	O
fresh-colour	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Face	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
brownish	O
Coat	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Bradford	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
fronting	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
Two-penny	O
Purl	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodcrost	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Dinner	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Horse	O
in	O
Golden-Lane	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
Horse	O
in	O
Aldersgate	O
street	O
and	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Two-penny	O
Purl	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
under	O
Pretence	O
of	O
getting	O
him	O
a	O
Lodging	O
:	O
I	O
hearing	O
this	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
was	O
there	O
last	O
Night	O
:	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
swarthy	O
Man	O
,	O
thin	O
visag	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
brown	O
Cloaths	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bradford	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gearing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
16	O
Years	O
:	O
We	O
work	O
'd	O
together	O
as	O
Wheel-boys	O
in	O
the	O
Gold	O
and	O
Silver	O
Way	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Morson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
him	O
10	O
Years	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
Errands	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
Fish	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
Thing	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
much	O
these	O
6	O
Years	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
6	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
12	O
Months	O
ago	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
my	O
Husband	O
at	O
some	O
Houses	O
in	O
Cold	O
Bath	O
Fields	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
him	O
all	O
over	O
my	O
House	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
where	O
his	O
Mother	O
lives	O
,	O
in	O
Featherstone-street	O
by	O
Moorfields	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
cry	O
Fish	O
about	O
the	O
Streets	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
almost	O
every	O
Day	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
out	O
of	O
Place	O
at	O
present	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
Place	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hinton	O
's	O
,	O
Cashier	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
any	O
Relation	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Warner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Acquaintance	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
31.	O
Mary	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Holland	O
Shirts	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Holland	O
Night	O
Caps	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Raper	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
Mary	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
Cambrick	O
Apron	O
,	O
a	O
Common	O
Prayer-Book	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Bible	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Grape	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Netherwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Iron	O
Barrs	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hagar	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
6	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
34.	O
John	B-pers
Low	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Pumps	O
,	O
2	O
Woollen	O
Blankets	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buckles	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
2	O
Blankets	O
and	O
3	O
Shirts	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Jan.	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Vink	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
107	O
Red	O
Herrings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Payton	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pomel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Bolster	O
,	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Napkin	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Towels	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
37.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pilgrim	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Brass	O
Pottage	O
Pots	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
38	O
,	O
39.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Shambler	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
2	O
Silk	O
Gowns	O
,	O
a	O
Silk	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
a	O
Callamanco	O
quilted	O
Coat	O
,	O
6	O
Mobs	O
,	O
a	O
Straw	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Stuff	O
Damask	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Silk	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Callamanco	O
Coat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
8	O
.	O
Shambler	O
guilty	O
Felony	O
only	O
;	O
Thompson	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
lac	O
'd	O
Hat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Men	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41.	O
Prior	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
willful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
Perjury	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Councel	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecution	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Indictment	O
set	O
forth	O
,	O
that	O
before	O
the	O
issuing	O
of	O
the	O
Commission	O
of	O
Bankrupt	O
,	O
the	O
Defendant	O
was	O
a	O
Brasier	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
his	O
Living	O
by	O
buying	O
and	O
selling	O
in	O
that	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
one	O
Jean	B-pers
Brifort	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Sum	O
of	O
one	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
for	O
Goods	O
sold	O
and	O
delivered	O
:	O
That	O
after	O
the	O
Defendant	O
was	O
so	O
indebted	O
,	O
he	O
became	O
a	O
Bankrupt	O
in	O
the	O
true	O
Intent	O
and	O
Meaning	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
Petition	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jean	B-pers
Brifort	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
in	O
the	O
14th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
a	O
Commission	O
of	O
Bankrupt	O
issued	O
out	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Roger	B-pers
Coningsby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
directed	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
proceed	O
to	O
put	O
that	O
Commission	O
in	O
Execution	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
they	O
(	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
Oaths	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Statute	O
)	O
declar	O
'd	O
the	O
Defendant	O
a	O
Bankrupt	O
,	O
within	O
the	O
true	O
Intent	O
and	O
Meaning	O
of	O
the	O
Act	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
they	O
caused	O
a	O
public	O
Notice	O
to	O
be	O
published	O
in	O
the	O
London	O
Gazette	O
,	O
whereby	O
the	O
Defendant	O
was	O
required	O
to	O
surrender	O
himself	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
(	O
then	O
]	O
Instant	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
thirtieth	O
of	O
Dec.	O
following	O
:	O
That	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
surrender	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
submitted	O
to	O
be	O
examin	O
'd	O
on	O
Oath	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
Course	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Discovery	O
,	O
the	O
Defendant	O
took	O
his	O
Corporal	O
Oath	B-pers
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
1740	O
:	O
that	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
a	O
Paper	O
Writing	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Letter	O
D	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Books	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Letters	O
A	O
,	O
B	O
,	O
and	O
C	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
other	O
Papers	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Letters	O
E	O
and	O
F	O
,	O
were	O
shewn	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
as	O
follows	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Paper	O
Writing	O
mark	O
'd	O
D	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
several	O
Books	O
mark	O
'd	O
A	O
,	O
B	O
,	O
and	O
C	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Paper	O
Writings	O
mark	O
'd	O
E	O
and	O
F	O
,	O
did	O
contain	O
a	O
full	O
Disclosure	O
of	O
all	O
his	O
Effects	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
what	O
Consideration	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
Merchandise	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
Effects	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
Books	O
and	O
Writings	O
relating	O
thereto	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
any	O
W	O
interested	O
;	O
or	O
whereby	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
any	O
Profit	O
;	O
except	O
only	O
such	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Effects	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
disposed	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
such	O
Sums	O
of	O
Money	O
as	O
had	O
been	O
laid	O
out	O
in	O
Expences	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
likewise	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
his	O
Examination	O
he	O
delivered	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
major	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
all	O
Books	O
,	O
Papers	O
,	O
and	O
Writings	O
relating	O
thereto	O
as	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
or	O
Power	O
,	O
his	O
necessary	O
wearing	O
Apparel	O
excepted	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
removed	O
,	O
concealed	O
or	O
embezzled	O
any	O
Part	O
of	O
his	O
Effects	O
with	O
Intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
his	O
Creditors	O
:	O
Whereas	O
in	O
Truth	O
and	O
in	O
Fact	O
,	O
the	O
Defendant	O
had	O
concealed	O
one	O
Copper	O
with	O
the	O
Iron-work	O
thereto	O
belonging	O
,	O
not	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Paper	O
Writings	O
;	O
and	O
whereas	O
in	O
Truth	O
and	O
in	O
Fact	O
he	O
had	O
concealed	O
2	O
Stove	O
Grates	O
,	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
mentioned	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
whereas	O
he	O
had	O
concealed	O
a	O
Shop	O
Book	O
of	O
Accompts	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
Shop	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
contained	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Books	O
or	O
Papers	O
mark	O
'd	O
as	O
above	O
;	O
and	O
whereas	O
he	O
had	O
conceal	O
'd	O
6	O
dozen	O
Flower	B-pers
Boxes	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
odd	O
Money	O
,	O
no	O
Account	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
mentioned	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Books	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
It	O
was	O
farther	O
urg	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Councel	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Side	O
,	O
that	O
although	O
the	O
Articles	O
with	O
which	O
the	O
Defendant	O
stood	O
charg	O
'd	O
might	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
but	O
inconsiderable	O
,	O
yet	O
that	O
where	O
some	O
Things	O
were	O
conceal	O
'd	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
great	O
Reason	O
to	O
apprehend	O
that	O
others	O
had	O
been	O
conceal	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
Perjury	O
in	O
one	O
Instance	O
would	O
in	O
others	O
:	O
That	O
it	O
appeared	O
from	O
the	O
Face	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
4	O
Instances	O
of	O
Perjury	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
should	O
be	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
be	O
sufficient	O
to	O
convict	O
the	O
Defendant	O
.	O
That	O
although	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
general	O
Oath	O
to	O
reveal	O
all	O
his	O
Effects	O
according	O
to	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
yet	O
notwithstanding	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
actually	O
possess	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Copper	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
mention	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
his	O
Account	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Commissioners	O
;	O
likewise	O
2	O
Stove	O
Grates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Shop	O
Book	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
material	O
;	O
and	O
besides	O
these	O
he	O
had	O
conceal	O
'd	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
Brasiery	O
Goods	O
:	O
That	O
Crimes	O
of	O
this	O
Sort	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
aggravated	O
,	O
being	O
exceeding	O
heinous	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
Nature	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
People	O
would	O
take	O
those	O
Libertien	O
to	O
forswear	O
themselves	O
,	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
an	O
End	O
of	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
Security	O
of	O
Men	O
's	O
Lives	O
or	O
Properties	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Cardel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Prior	O
Green	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Brasier	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
follow	O
that	O
Trade	O
?	O
Cardel	O
.	O
These	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
Years	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
John	B-pers
Brifort	I-pers
?	O
Cardel	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
dealt	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
for	O
French	O
Plate	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
Master	O
indebted	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
French	O
Plate	O
?	O
Cardel	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
above	O
100	O
Pounds	O
and	O
upwards	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Brifort	O
's	O
Books	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
above	O
100	O
l.	O
Counc	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
these	O
Goods	O
bought	O
of	O
Brifort	O
?	O
Cardel	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Year	O
forty	O
,	O
between	O
March	O
and	O
November	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
Green	O
's	O
denying	O
himself	O
to	O
his	O
Creditors	O
?	O
Cardel	O
.	O
I	O
myself	O
have	O
denied	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Orders	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
Persons	O
Names	O
to	O
whom	O
you	O
have	O
denied	O
him	O
?	O
Cardel	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Giles	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
present	O
Assignees	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
one	O
Waters	O
,	O
a	O
Baker	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
whether	O
you	O
denied	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
Orders	O
,	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
Head	O
?	O
Cardel	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
be	O
troubled	O
with	O
these	O
People	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
before	O
the	O
Commission	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
those	O
Persons	O
that	O
you	O
denied	O
him	O
to	O
,	O
come	O
for	O
?	O
Cardel	O
.	O
For	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
Creditors	O
:	O
By	O
one	O
Person	O
I	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
judg	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
come	O
a	O
dunning	O
for	O
Money	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
several	O
Times	O
before	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
Errand	O
.	O
Pris	O
What	O
Sum	O
did	O
the	O
Creditors	O
ask	O
for	O
?	O
Cardel	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
for	O
any	O
particular	O
Sum	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Servant	O
asked	O
me	O
several	O
Times	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
Money	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
Creditors	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
Cardel	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Brewer	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Clerk	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
