TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
16th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Willimott	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
.	O
1743	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILLIMOTT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr	O
Baron	B-pers
CARTER	I-pers
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
DENISON	O
,	O
Mr	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Watton	I-pers
,	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Hesketh	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Nathan	B-pers
Mawbey	I-pers
,	O
*	O
Oliver	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lovejoy	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Horne	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chisholm	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Journard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickett	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Blanchard	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Cumming	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wellbeloved	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Dechamps	I-pers
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
Day	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
were	O
sworn	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
Mr	O
West	O
,	O
Mr	O
Mawbey	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
Pannel	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
attend	O
on	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
probable	O
Mr	O
Waite	O
might	O
except	O
against	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Mr	O
West	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Proprietor	O
of	O
Bank-Stock	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
proper	O
Person	O
to	O
serve	O
on	O
that	O
Jury	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
therefore	O
not	O
called	O
.	O
135.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
the	I-place
Less	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
Yards	O
of	O
checked	O
Linnen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
13	O
s.	O
sixteen	O
Yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
Linnen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
1	O
Yard	O
of	O
Callico	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
Yards	O
and	O
a	O
Half	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
l	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
Part	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
twenty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
one	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
two	O
Mocha	O
Stone	O
Buttons	O
for	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Church	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
8	O
.	O
William	O
Church	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
deals	O
in	O
Linnen-Drapery	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
sells	O
them	O
among	O
our	O
Friends	O
and	O
Acquaintance	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
keep	O
an	O
open	O
Shop	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
;	O
upon	O
missing	O
these	O
Things	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
Sister	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
some	O
checked	O
Linnen	O
at	O
a	O
Pawn-Broker	O
's	O
in	O
Horselydown	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
redeemed	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
This	O
Pocket-Book	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
Buttons	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Set	O
which	O
is	O
upon	O
this	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
near	O
twenty	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
in	O
her	O
Sister	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Church	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Watermans-Hall	B-place
,	O
this	O
Check	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
a	O
Piece	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Goods	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Cambrick	O
and	O
Irish	O
Cloth	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
at	O
her	O
Sister	O
's	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
several	O
more	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Check	O
which	O
were	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
-	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Trunk	O
at	O
her	O
Sister	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
too	O
big	O
to	O
bring	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
had	O
several	O
Pieces	O
just	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
cut	O
off	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
Handkerchief	O
is	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
C	O
upon	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
more	O
Things	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
yet	O
found	O
.	O
-	O
Bowles	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
for	O
the	O
Borough	O
of	O
Southwark	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Horsely-down	O
,	O
several	O
of	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Irish	O
Cloth	O
,	O
belonged	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
136	O
,	O
137.	O
Honor	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Gloucestershire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
weighing	O
15	O
lb	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
January	O
19	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
this	O
Cheese	O
is	O
mine	O
;	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
confessed	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
A	O
Girl	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
14	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
:	O
Between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr	O
Lane	O
's	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Cheese	O
for	O
my	O
Mother	O
;	O
these	O
2	O
Women	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
wanted	O
some	O
Bacon	O
,	O
the	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
Bacon	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
Ham	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
for	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
buy	O
a	O
Pound	O
of	O
Cheese	O
there	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
where	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
Bits	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
the	O
tallest	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Cheese	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
run	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
Porter	O
to	O
Mr	O
Lane	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
back	O
from	O
delivering	O
a	O
Burthen	O
;	O
says	O
this	O
Girl	O
,	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
has	O
stole	O
a	O
Cheese	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
down	O
my	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
which	O
Way	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
tallest	O
had	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Apron	O
of	O
the	O
shortest	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Oh	O
!	O
you	O
brazenfac	O
'd	O
Hussies	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
under	O
the	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
a	O
Cheese	O
?	O
The	O
shortest	O
one	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Bull-head	O
Court	O
.	O
Rowland	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
for	O
something	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
any	O
Crime	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
before	O
:	O
Ask	O
my	O
Fellow-Prisoner	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
138	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Anne	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
;	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
Leather	O
Bag	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Dozen	O
of	O
four	O
pronged	O
Silver	O
Forks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
four	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
val	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
Pans	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Copper	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Neville	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Craig	I-pers
,	O
January	O
28	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
16	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
a	O
Month	O
ago	O
,	O
next	O
Friday	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
Leicester-Fields	B-place
,	O
about	O
30	O
Minutes	O
after	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
and	O
had	O
my	O
Things	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
Blows	O
upon	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
one	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
Silver	O
4	O
pronged	O
Forks	O
;	O
4	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Silver	O
Snuff	O
Pans	O
:	O
These	O
Goods	O
were	O
all	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
-	O
Mrs	O
Craig	O
is	O
Partner	O
with	O
my	O
Master	O
:	O
I	O
take	O
these	O
Goods	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
John	O
Neville	O
's	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
many	O
were	O
in	O
Company	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
Apprentice	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
-	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Blue	O
Coat	O
and	O
a	O
laced	O
Hat	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knows	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
my	O
Dress	O
?	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knows	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
a	O
tall	O
Man	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Blue	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gold	O
laced	O
Hat	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
does	O
not	O
accuse	O
you	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
so	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
other	O
Evidence	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
pretty	O
safe	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Neville	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Partner	O
with	O
Mrs	O
Craig	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Leather	O
Bag	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
Name	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
Mr	O
Neville	O
,	O
repeated	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
as	O
mention	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Boy	O
and	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Copper	O
the	O
Boy	O
bought	O
by	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
have	O
such	O
a	O
Charge	O
of	O
Plate	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
?	O
Neville	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Hall	O
to	O
be	O
marked	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
bringing	O
them	O
home	O
-	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
what	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Boy	O
:	O
-	O
They	O
are	O
not	O
much	O
in	O
Fashion	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
made	O
by	O
Order	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
:	O
Here	O
is	O
directly	O
half	O
the	O
Plate	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
weighed	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
Orders	O
,	O
to	O
send	O
out	O
Warnings	O
from	O
Goldsmiths	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
Means	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
Mason	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
him	O
this	O
angle	O
Fork	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
Somebody	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
seen	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Advertisements	O
;	O
Mr	O
Mason	O
,	O
detained	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Way	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
only	O
that	O
single	O
Fork	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
kicked	O
it	O
before	O
him	O
in	O
Bri	O
Mouse	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
Silver	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
Bag	O
with	O
my	O
Name	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Wentworth-street	O
,	O
Spital	O
fields	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
House	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Bag	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
a	O
pretty	O
Fellow	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Fool	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
I	O
shall	O
find	O
my	O
Bag	O
and	O
Plate	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Bag	O
:	O
The	O
Plate	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
concealed	O
in	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
sent	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
what	O
Mr	O
Neville	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
found	O
but	O
one	O
Fork	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
I	O
found	O
but	O
one	O
Fork	O
.	O
Neville	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
that	O
stands	O
here	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
mentioned	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
tell	O
Mr	O
Neville	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Bag	O
and	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
.	O
-	O
Storer	O
.	O
(	O
Mr	O
Neville	O
's	O
Servant	O
)	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
Mr	O
Mason	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Bewton	O
's	O
Mouse	O
,	O
and	O
kicked	O
the	O
Fork	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Silver	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Bag	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
the	O
Search-Warrant	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr	O
Neville	O
said	O
,	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
by	O
Day	O
light	O
.	O
-	O
Storer	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Moon-light	O
Night	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
never	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Neville	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
was	O
cut	O
to	O
the	O
Skull	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
his	O
Bed	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
Days	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
On	O
January	O
29	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
this	O
Fork	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Mr	O
Neville	O
's	O
Man	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
Warnings	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Forks	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
Account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Warnings	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
you	O
hear	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
said	O
I.	O
I	O
must	O
stop	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
Fork	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
my	O
Boy	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
some	O
where	O
by	O
Grosvenor-square	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
Porter	O
for	O
Mr	O
Neville	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Mr	O
Neville	O
came	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
Fork	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
there	O
?	O
Mason	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
that	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
Fork	O
till	O
the	O
Trial	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
Mrs	O
Roberts	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
Find	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
my	O
Husband	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
Partner	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
Plate	O
;	O
five	O
Forks	O
,	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Snuffers	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Snuff-Pan	O
.	O
Neville	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Goods	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
Woman	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Things	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
only	O
found	O
the	O
Bag	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
to	O
this	O
Woman	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Plate	O
sewed	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
that	O
Witness	O
,	O
who	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
sew	O
the	O
Things	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
by	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
Wife	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
order	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
Hearing	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr	O
Neville	O
's	O
Boy	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
some	O
Plate	O
Home	O
from	O
Goldsmiths-Hall	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Foster-Lane	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Warning	O
brought	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
mentioning	O
the	O
Particulars	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
Masons	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
four-pronged	O
Silver	O
Fork	O
;	O
said	O
Mr	O
Mason	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
finished	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Forks	O
that	O
Mr	O
Neville	O
's	O
Boy	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
him	O
where	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Warning	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
one	O
Fork	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
Bruton's-Mouse	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Bag	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
Neville	O
,	O
St	O
James	O
's	O
Market	O
,	O
1742	O
,	O
wrote	O
upon	O
it	O
in	O
large	O
Characters	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
Mark	O
upon	O
the	O
Bag	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alderhead	I-pers
,	O
Mr	O
Mason	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
examined	O
.	O
Another	O
of	O
Mr	O
Mason	O
's	O
Servants	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
only	O
found	O
that	O
one	O
Fork	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Silver	O
or	O
Copper	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Mr	O
Mason	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
Wife	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
called	O
her	O
)	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Bag	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Marlow	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
to	O
offer	O
two	O
four-	O
pronged	O
Forks	O
unfinished	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
looked	O
pretty	O
suspicious	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
most	O
fair	O
and	O
reputable	O
Way	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
Warnings	O
out	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
presently	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
once	O
found	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
Case	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
Warnings	O
were	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
what	O
Time	O
the	O
Warnings	O
were	O
out	O
.	O
Marlow	O
.	O
Mr	O
Neville	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Warnings	O
were	O
out	O
at	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
later	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
of	O
Spital-Fields	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
Bag	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Drawers	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Neville	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
is	O
his	O
Wife	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
lay	O
Claim	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Servant	O
)	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
Ten	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
then	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
Home	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
waked	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
laughing	O
and	O
singing	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
Find	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
without	O
Aldgate	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Forks	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
Silver	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
an	O
Ounce	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
bid	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
then	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
ask	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
Silver	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
forty	O
Ounces	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
brown	O
Paper	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
them	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
these	O
Things	O
are	O
certainly	O
stole	O
;	O
whether	O
you	O
found	O
them	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
act	O
like	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
keep	O
them	O
by	O
you	O
;	O
or	O
leave	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
will	O
certainly	O
be	O
Warnings	O
out	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
once	O
found	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch-Case	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Owner	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Coat	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
was	O
so	O
ungenerous	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
Thing	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
somebody	O
else	O
directly	O
-	O
there	O
were	O
thirty	O
three	O
Ounces	O
three	O
Quarters	O
.	O
I	O
dogged	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Shop	O
into	O
Mr	O
Marlow	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
offer	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Forks	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Marlow	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
nod	O
his	O
Head	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr	O
Marlow	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
Man	O
has	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Advertisement	O
concerning	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Name	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Wentworth	O
street	O
,	O
Spital-fields	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
were	O
Warnings	O
out	O
to	O
describe	O
the	O
Things	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
Constable	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
Time	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
Constable	O
over-against	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
Neville	O
's	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
Information	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
has	O
spoke	O
the	O
Truth	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
have	O
subpoena	O
'd	O
him	O
myself	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
called	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Morning	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Forks	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
count	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
Things	O
like	O
Snuffers	O
-	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
put	O
together	O
-	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
twice	O
a	O
Week	O
.	O
Neville	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
robbed	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
,	O
15	O
or	O
20	O
Minutes	O
after	O
Seven	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lady	O
keeps	O
a	O
Chair	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
her	O
Chairman	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
my	O
Lady	O
down	O
,	O
in	O
Dover-street	O
,	O
at	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Partner	O
;	O
we	O
my	O
Lady	O
down	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
we	O
parted	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
;	O
was	O
then	O
5	O
Minutes	O
after	O
Seven	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
these	O
Things	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
my	O
Lady	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
about	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Henry	O
Story	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
House	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
this	O
poor	O
unfortunate	O
Man	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
a	O
Quarter	O
before	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
disrespectful	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
Half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Seven	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Work	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Dial	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Mr	O
Story	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
25	O
Minutes	O
after	O
Seven	O
.	O
-	O
Hutchinson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
some	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
-	O
Camfield	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
Dishonestly	O
in	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
139.	O
William	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
27	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Guinea	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Drawer	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
Key	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Key	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
tried	O
whether	O
it	O
fitted	O
the	O
Drawer	O
before	O
Colonel	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
opened	O
the	O
Lock	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
about	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
nine	O
Guineas	O
and	O
an	O
Half	O
,	O
a	O
Three	O
Pound	O
Twelve	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
Money	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
my	O
Wife	O
nine	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Three	O
Pound	O
Twelve	O
Piece	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Drawer	O
till	O
the	O
27th	O
:	O
That	O
Morning	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Child	O
said	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
Door	O
unlock	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
a	O
prodigious	O
squeaking	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
this	O
Money	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
some	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
How	O
is	O
our	O
Money	O
converted	O
?	O
Here	O
is	O
but	O
four	O
Guineas	O
out	O
of	O
nine	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
Use	O
but	O
of	O
four	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
out	O
now	O
.	O
Monday	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
within	O
Doors	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
taxed	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Guinea	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
Lock	O
with	O
this	O
Key	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Jan.	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
before	O
Col.	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
Wife	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
Mistress	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
before	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
left	O
this	O
Money	O
with	O
me	O
January	O
26	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lay	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Drawer	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
nine	O
Guineas	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
fetched	O
another	O
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
my	O
Husband	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
How	O
much	O
Money	O
have	O
you	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
3	O
Guineas	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
five	O
Guineas	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
there	O
is	O
but	O
four	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Three	O
Pound	O
Twelve	O
Piece	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Knowing	O
myself	O
to	O
be	O
innocent	O
:	O
My	O
Husband	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
to	O
his	O
Collar	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
:	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
rob	O
you	O
?	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
There	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
a	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
a	O
Farthing	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Key	O
:	O
He	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Guinea	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Purnell	I-pers
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Guinea	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
Key	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
open	O
the	O
Drawer	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Mr	O
Palmer	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
Thing	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Guinea	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawer	O
with	O
that	O
Key	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
140.	O
William	B-pers
Mecan	I-pers
*	O
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Pumps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bedwin	I-pers
,	O
December	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
tried	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
Means	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
from	O
Newgate	O
Robert	O
Bedwin	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Pumps	O
.	O
-	O
Hamphill	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pumps	O
off	O
the	O
Shelf	O
in	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Cellar	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
Minutes	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
Notice	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
attempting	O
to	O
take	O
three	O
Pair	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
these	O
Pumps	O
under	O
his	O
Arm	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Fair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
stumble	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Hand	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Shelf	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
141.	O
Dickin	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Deal	O
Boards	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
three	O
Mahogany	O
Boards	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12s	O
.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Black	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
three	O
Mahogany	O
Boards	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Mahogany	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Deals	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
at	O
one	O
Mr	O
Barrow	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Boards	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
particular	O
Mark	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
two	O
Fineres	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Fineres	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Boy	O
saw	O
me	O
take	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Customer	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Boy	O
brought	O
me	O
back	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
142.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Purgess	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Mary-le-Bow	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
February	O
13th	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
Eight	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cheapside	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
another	O
hussled	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
my	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
in	O
Ludgate-street	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
She	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
particular	O
Piece	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Six-pence	O
with	O
a	O
Letter	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
that	O
S.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
that	O
Piece	O
of	O
Money	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
set	O
my	O
Watch	O
being	O
Beadle	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
:	O
A	O
Man	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Woman	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
set	O
my	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Hand	O
to	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
Wrist	O
,	O
(	O
before	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
particular	O
Six-pence	O
)	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
Pocket	O
or	O
some	O
other	O
Place	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Six	O
pence	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
followed	O
me	O
from	O
Stock-Market	O
to	O
Honey-Lane-Market	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
up	O
my	O
Petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
Six-pence	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
but	O
Three-pence	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
Three-pence	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
into	O
Honey-Lane-Market	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
laid	O
me	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
Stall	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
143.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Camell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Brass	O
Candlesticks	O
,	O
one	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Pewter	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
January	O
27	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Room	O
in	O
Black-Friers	B-place
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Fleet-Lane	O
with	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
Goods	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Father	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
poor	O
Girl	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
troubled	O
with	O
the	O
Falling-Sickness	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Bitters	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Draught	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
made	O
herself	O
out	O
of	O
Order	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
foolish	O
between	O
whiles	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
Nine-pence	O
half-penny	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
carried	O
them	O
openly	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
which	O
shows	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
:	O
She	O
is	O
all	O
the	O
Children	O
I	O
have	O
out	O
of	O
Fifteen	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
use	O
her	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
If	O
she	O
is	O
released	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
far	O
enough	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
into	O
ill	O
Company	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
you	O
.	O
Things	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
Because	O
my	O
Brother	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
two	O
Candlesticks	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
144.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
Feb	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
145	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Dobney	I-pers
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
1	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
20s	O
.	O
1	O
Cloth	O
Mantelet	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
Piece	O
of	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
Value	O
1	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Dobney	I-pers
;	O
2	O
Red	O
Damask	O
Skirts	O
,	O
Value	O
12	O
s.	O
2	O
Quilted	O
Coats	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Knell	I-pers
,	O
February	O
1	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dobney	I-pers
.	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
Window-Shutters	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Windows	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
away	O
:	O
This	O
Gown	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Girl	O
found	O
this	O
Gown	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
in	O
this	O
Bag	O
-	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knell	I-pers
was	O
called	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
readily	O
answer	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
here	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
ashamed	O
to	O
look	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knell	I-pers
.	O
These	O
Things	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Children	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
they	O
found	O
?	O
Where	O
had	O
them	O
you	O
again	O
?	O
Knell	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
had	O
again	O
-	O
the	O
Constable	O
had	O
them	O
-	O
the	O
Constable	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
between	O
Seven	O
and	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
Man	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
Chissel	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dobney	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Gown	O
and	O
Mantelet	O
-	O
he	O
took	O
these	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
dropped	O
them	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
ten	O
Doors	O
off	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Knell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
dropped	O
and	O
my	O
Sister	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
There	O
were	O
Thieves	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
dropped	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
Knell	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
the	O
Fact	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dobney	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
about	O
Six	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
I	O
shut	O
up	O
all	O
the	O
Windows	O
and	O
made	O
them	O
very	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
Seven	O
and	O
Eight	O
they	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
Parlour-Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
half	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
half	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
getting	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
to	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
directly	O
-	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
'till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
-	O
a	O
little	O
Boy	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
playing	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
Bag	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
Candle	O
Light	O
-	O
between	O
Seven	O
and	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
-	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Lamp	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Dobney	I-pers
.	O
Not	O
before	O
six	O
o'Clock	O
that	O
Evening	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
my	O
Windows	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Midwife	O
lived	O
there	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
want	O
her	O
by-and-by	O
for	O
his	O
Sister	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
I	O
saw	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
A	O
Girl	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
13	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
afraid	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
will	O
speak	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
Truth	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
Man	O
threw	O
a	O
Bag	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
Bag	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
afterwards	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
easily	O
get	O
the	O
Things	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
John	B-pers
Knell	I-pers
apprehend	O
him	O
?	O
Girl	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Sight	O
'till	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
John	B-pers
Knell	I-pers
is	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Sake	O
of	O
the	O
Reward	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Knee	O
against	O
that	O
Boy	O
before	O
Justice	O
Wroth	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
say	O
every	O
Thing	O
he	O
said	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
bought	O
the	O
Boy	O
that	O
Coat	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
(	O
The	O
Boy	O
was	O
not	O
examined	O
.	O
)	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
Justice	O
Wroth	O
,	O
that	O
Knell	O
had	O
tutored	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
putting	O
Words	O
in	O
his	O
Mouth	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
it	O
.	O
Penelope	B-pers
Sussaker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
Number	O
of	O
People	O
by	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
to	O
hear	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
possible	O
-	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
Power	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Crowd	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
Smith	O
ask	O
Knell	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Brother	O
named	O
James	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
another	O
Rogue	O
like	O
himself	O
;	O
and	O
Knell	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
bear	O
it	O
with	O
Patience	O
.	O
-	O
Marriot	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Needlemaker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
hard	O
a	O
working	O
Man	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
Kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
kept	O
him	O
Company	O
;	O
'till	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
18	O
or	O
19	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Ill	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
frequently	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Cross	O
,	O
in	O
Red-Cross-street	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
frequently	O
with	O
his	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
an	O
universal	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
10	O
Years	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
almost	O
next	O
Door	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
his	O
Brother	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
by	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Cross	O
,	O
in	O
Red-Cross-street	O
-	O
I	O
rent	O
a	O
Room	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
delivered	O
him	O
many	O
a	O
Tankard	O
with	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
took	O
Care	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Tankard	O
to	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Theop	O
.	O
Thorp	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
best	O
Part	O
of	O
30	O
Years	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
worked	O
Journey-Work	O
with	O
me	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Master	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
Casualties	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
off	O
it	O
now	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
'till	O
lately	O
,	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
his	O
Brother	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
works	O
for	O
him	O
sometimes	O
.	O
Rebecca	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
14	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Dishonesty	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
Fellow	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
House	O
on	O
Snow-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
Plate	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
Money	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
charged	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
Years	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
:	O
When	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
home	O
at	O
Night	O
in	O
good	O
Time	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
pilfer	O
,	O
or	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Knell	I-pers
.	O
Was	O
I	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
or	O
from	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Knell	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dobney	I-pers
,	O
junior	O
(	O
called	O
again	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Dobney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
Body	O
else	O
then	O
:	O
-	O
The	O
two	O
Keys	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
were	O
found	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Surprise	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Man	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
she	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Person	O
?	O
Dobney	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sensible	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
called	O
again	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
Man	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
throw	O
the	O
Bag	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
146.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Coarse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Great-Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Rowls	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rowls	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
half	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Hay	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
Load	O
of	O
Straw	O
to	O
Mr	O
Collet	O
's	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
lead	O
your	O
Fore	O
Horse	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr	O
Collet	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
Mr	O
Collet	O
's	O
Son	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
,	O
came	O
running	O
back	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Stable	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
your	O
Horses	O
a	O
Month	O
full	O
of	O
Hay	O
:	O
Make	O
Haste	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
Passion	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Minutes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
bit	O
of	O
Hay	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
was	O
flung	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Shafts	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
thinks	O
I	O
,	O
surely	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
steal	O
any	O
Thing	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
and	O
my	O
Coat	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
lower	O
End	O
of	O
Harrow-Alley	B-place
,	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
;	O
the	O
Coat	O
hung	O
upon	O
the	O
Cops	O
of	O
the	O
Cart	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
by	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Boys	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
he	O
proved	O
very	O
rustical	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bit	O
my	O
Hand	O
to	O
the	O
Bone	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
should	O
see	O
me	O
another	O
Time	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Magpye	O
Tavern	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Brother	O
Waggoner	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
pay	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
you	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
another	O
Man	O
stole	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
two	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
Six-pence	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
Almighty	O
bless	O
you	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
forgive	O
me	O
this	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
never	O
go	O
about	O
stealing	O
Great-Coats	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
Occasions	O
;	O
another	O
Man	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
taken	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
Waggoner	O
's	O
Great-Coat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Magpye	O
Tavern	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
Villain	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
poor	O
Fellow	O
's	O
Coat	O
;	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
worse	O
,	O
in	O
biting	O
him	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
hindered	O
from	O
getting	O
his	O
Bread	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
sold	O
it	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
dropped	O
6	O
d.	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
Stone	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
upon	O
a	O
Brick	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
he	O
never	O
would	O
go	O
a	O
Coat-stealing	O
with	O
any	O
Man	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
6	O
d.	O
lie	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Great-Coat	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
147.	O
Jane	B-pers
Winnell	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Andrew	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Brass	O
Sauce-pan	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
a	O
Blanket	O
and	O
a	O
Pillowbier	O
,	O
3	O
Earthen	O
Plates	O
,	O
a	O
Copper-Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
January	O
24	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
produced	O
were	O
theirs	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Singleton	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
Sister	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Room	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Winnell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Martin	O
;	O
that	O
Ann	O
took	O
the	O
Room	O
and	O
promised	O
Payment	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
Grand-Jury	O
had	O
not	O
found	O
the	O
Bill	O
against	O
Ann	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Jane	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
consented	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
Goods	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
Servant	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
Master	O
was	O
willing	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
]	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
148.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Brockley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Sheets	O
,	O
2	O
Bolster-Cases	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
Pillow-Cases	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Prouse	I-pers
,	O
February	O
8	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Sister	O
having	O
lost	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Tabby	B-pers
Stays	I-pers
,	O
insisted	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
the	O
Marks	O
are	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
all	O
except	O
one	O
Sheet	O
:	O
Mr	O
Baker	O
and	O
Mr	O
Prouse	O
are	O
Partners	O
in	O
Trade	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Linnen	O
belongs	O
to	O
both	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dark	O
Closet	O
and	O
cut	O
the	O
Names	O
out	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Prouse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
some	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prevent	O
Disputes	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
was	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
Box	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
some	O
Sheets	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
my	O
Brother	O
's	O
Name	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Catherine	O
you	O
had	O
these	O
Sheets	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dark	O
Closet	O
:	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
Pray	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
let	O
my	O
Master	O
and	O
Mistress	O
know	O
it	O
:	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
Catherine	O
take	O
your	O
Things	O
and	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
Business	O
;	O
(	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Servant	O
)	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
Knees	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
before	O
and	O
never	O
would	O
again	O
;	O
-	O
We	O
are	O
Sisters	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
are	O
Brothers-in-law	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Madam	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
I	O
a	O
good	O
Servant	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Prouse	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
you	O
were	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
honest	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
without	O
a	O
Character	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
so	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
149	O
.	O
+	O
Catherine	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
11	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Perthy	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Property	O
,	O
January	O
23	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Perthy	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Home	O
;	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
down	O
an	O
Alley	O
and	O
stay	O
'till	O
the	O
Watchman	O
was	O
gone	O
by	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Words	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Hand	O
was	O
under	O
her	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
behind	O
some	O
Casks	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
Watch	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
just	O
before	O
-	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
Watchman	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
at	O
the	O
Bars	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
and	O
had	O
but	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
feel	O
in	O
this	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
it	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wardley	I-pers
.	O
Sunday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
12	O
,	O
this	O
Man	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
with	O
this	O
Woman	O
and	O
a	O
Watchman	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
Conversation	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
Money	O
and	O
pursued	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Money	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
because	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
Watchman	O
a	O
Half-penny	O
for	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
she	O
bid	O
him	O
feel	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
in	O
his-Coat	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
6	O
s.	O
Oh	O
you	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
;	O
Mr	O
Constable	O
,	O
shall	O
I	O
make	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
drink	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
charge	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
her	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
150.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Le	I-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Philip	I-pers
Dupuis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1730	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St	O
Ann	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
did	O
marry	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Lewis	O
Le	O
Drew	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
afterwards	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1742	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
marry	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
wife	O
take	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Clar	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
his	O
said	O
Wife	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
and	O
in	O
full	O
Life	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
observed	O
by	O
the	O
Council	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
by	O
Birth	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Trade	O
a	O
Lock-Smith	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
France	O
,	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Dupuis	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
Father-in-law	O
,	O
in	O
France	O
,	O
whose	O
Name	O
is	O
Le	O
Drew	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
Artist	O
in	O
making	O
Spring-Window-Curtains	O
,	O
he	O
changed	O
his	O
Name	O
from	O
Dupuis	O
,	O
and	O
assumed	O
that	O
of	O
Le	O
Drew	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
paid	O
his	O
Addresses	O
to	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Clar	I-pers
,	O
and	O
having	O
insinuated	O
himself	O
into	O
the	O
good	O
Opinion	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
possessed	O
himself	O
of	O
some	O
Part	O
of	O
her	O
Fortune	O
,	O
they	O
lived	O
together	O
for	O
the	O
Space	O
of	O
three	O
Weeks	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
bad	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
another	O
Wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
advised	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
Friends	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
but	O
a	O
single	O
Felony	O
and	O
the	O
Punishment	O
hardly	O
equal	O
to	O
the	O
Offence	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Whitehall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
13	O
Years	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
which	O
Name	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Le	O
Drew	O
now	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
Marriage	O
,	O
at	O
St	O
Ann	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
Soho	O
,	O
about	O
13	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Person	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
present	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
away	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
dead	O
;	O
they	O
bedded	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
that	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
some	O
few	O
Weeks	O
with	O
me	O
'till	O
they	O
were	O
settled	O
-	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
say	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Commons	O
for	O
a	O
Licence	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Pipping	I-pers
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
Name	O
now	O
;	O
my	O
Name	O
was	O
Rumbald	O
then	O
;	O
my	O
Husband	O
gave	O
her	O
away	O
in	O
Marriage	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
dead	O
-	O
they	O
did	O
live	O
together	O
,	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
lived	O
together	O
as	O
such	O
,	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
Years	O
-	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
Business	O
of	O
a	O
Bell-hanger	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Wedding	O
.	O
Justice	O
De	O
Veil	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
Neighbourhood	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
Leicester-Fields	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
Business	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
with	O
that	O
Woman	O
as	O
his	O
Wife	O
-	O
he	O
passed	O
for	O
the	O
Husband	O
of	O
that	O
Woman	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
2	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Le	I-pers
Drew	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
;	O
they	O
lived	O
together	O
as	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Dupuis	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
true	O
Copy	O
of	O
the	O
Register	O
of	O
St	O
Ann	O
Westminster	O
,	O
I	O
compared	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
Original	O
.	O
August	O
29	O
,	O
1730	O
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Dupuis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
this	O
Parish	O
,	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Dod	I-pers
of	O
St	O
Clement-Danes	O
;	O
Licence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clar	I-pers
.	O
(	O
The	O
second	O
Wife	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
18	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
Brewer's-Street	O
,	O
one	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
away	O
-	O
one	O
Butler	O
married	O
me	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Chaplain	O
to	O
the	O
Portuguese	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
's	O
Habit	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
married	O
in	O
a	O
Church	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
-	O
the	O
Ceremony	O
was	O
said	O
over	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
cohabit	O
together	O
after	O
the	O
Marriage	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Clar	I-pers
.	O
Three	O
Weeks	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
Friends	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
Wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
my	O
leaving	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Butler	O
before	O
?	O
Clar	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Chaplain	O
;	O
Can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Clergyman	O
?	O
Clar	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Priest	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
the	O
Romish	O
Persuasion	O
myself	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
Romish	O
Ceremony	O
that	O
was	O
said	O
over	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Ceremony	O
is	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
Ceremony	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
just	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
Marriage	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
away	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
private	O
Room	O
in	O
Brewer's-street	B-place
;	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
by	O
Mr	O
Butler	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Chaplains	O
to	O
the	O
Portuguese	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
but	O
once	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
his	O
former	O
Wife	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tickeridge	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Le	O
Drew	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
his	O
first	O
Wife	O
;	O
his	O
Goods	O
are	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Du	O
Puis	O
,	O
only	O
Le	O
Drew	O
;	O
what	O
they	O
say	O
is	O
quite	O
false	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
beg	O
your	O
Pardon	O
,	O
there	O
never	O
was	O
any	O
Body	O
could	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
:	O
She	O
went	O
for	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
never	O
were	O
married	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
151.	O
John	B-pers
Hyth	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Butts	O
with	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Dove	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Simeon	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Dove	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Servant	O
left	O
three	O
Butts	O
at	O
the	O
White-Hart	B-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
February	O
4	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
three	O
different	O
Places	O
:	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
Partner	O
;	O
I	O
understand	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
five	O
Times	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
for	O
these	O
Practices	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hatch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Butts	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
Mr	O
Nicholls	O
's	O
Yard	O
;	O
one	O
in	O
Five-Inkborn-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
at	O
the	O
Green-Man	O
in	O
Newcastle	O
street	O
in	O
White-chapel	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
roll	O
a	O
Butt	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
some	O
Hoops	O
upon	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
next	O
Door	O
Neighbour	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
Treachery	O
in	O
this	O
.	O
We	O
put	O
the	O
Head	O
of	O
the	O
Butt	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Wind-Mill	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
belongs	O
to	O
Execution-Dock	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
knocked	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Green-Man	O
Yard	O
,	O
in	O
Newcastle-street	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Wind-Mill	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
Mr	O
Dove	O
's	O
Mark	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
Mark	O
in	O
another	O
Place	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
Butt	O
in	O
Five-Inkborn-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
roll	O
the	O
Butt	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Butt	O
was	O
knocked	O
to	O
Pieces	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Hoops	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Another	O
Person	O
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
rolling	O
a	O
Butt	O
down	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
Day-light	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
stout	O
Fellow	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Hair	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Pemeroy	I-pers
.	O
Mr	O
Dove	O
sent	O
his	O
Servant	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
send	O
some	O
Butts	O
into	O
my	O
Yard	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White-Hart	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Butts	O
roll	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Lad	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
rolling	O
a	O
Butt	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Foresee	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Beale	I-pers
,	O
and	O
-	O
Bond	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
152	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Laycock	I-pers
;	I-pers
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Twelve	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
Cambrick	O
Stock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
two	O
Quart	O
Silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
l.	O
two	O
Silver	O
Pint	O
Mugs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Porringer	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
Silver	O
Tea-pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Milk-pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
large	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
17	O
s.	O
a	O
small	O
Ditto	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
six	O
Tea-spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
24	O
s.	O
a	O
Dram-cup	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Shoe-Buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Knee-Buckles	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Stock-Clasp	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Laycock	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
5th	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Laycock	I-pers
.	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
Feb.	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
the	O
Fence	O
was	O
broke	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Sewer	O
in	O
Summer-street	B-place
,	O
by	O
Hockley	O
in	O
the	O
Hole	O
:	O
They	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
Window	O
,	O
by	O
breaking	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
opening	O
the	O
Casement	O
:	O
No-body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
it	O
about	O
Twelve	O
at	O
Noon	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
home	O
about	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
the	O
Chamber-Door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Staple	O
wrenched	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Street-Door	O
was	O
locked	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
unlocked	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Yard-Door	O
open	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
No-body	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
put	O
but	O
himself	O
:	O
He	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Rumford	O
,	O
and	O
unload	O
Carts	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Poulterer	O
,	O
and	O
stand	O
in	O
Clare-Market	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
borrowed	O
a	O
Ripping	O
Chissel	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Laycock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
often	O
in	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
in	O
our	O
Bed	O
chamber	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
and	O
has	O
dined	O
with	O
us	O
often	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
Compassion	O
to	O
his	O
Children	O
and	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
Family	O
:	O
The	O
Box	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
,	O
was	O
carried	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Sewer	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
with	O
a	O
Ripping	O
Chissel	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Box	O
with	O
my	O
Husband	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Linnen	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Sewer	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
taken	O
away	O
but	O
the	O
Plate	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Spade	O
which	O
was	O
one	O
Farmer	O
Bowden	B-pers
's	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
he	O
buried	O
them	O
with	O
that	O
Spade	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
all	O
Saturday	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Ditch-Market	O
,	O
and	O
borrowed	O
a	O
Chissel	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
a	O
Lock	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
Ask	O
her	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Laycock	I-pers
.	O
He	O
kept	O
a	O
bad	O
House	O
in	O
Black-Mary's-Hole	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
suffer	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
upon	O
that	O
Account	O
;	O
the	O
Parish	O
allowed	O
him	O
a	O
Crown	O
a	O
Week	O
for	O
his	O
Children	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
Chissel	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
a	O
Lock	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
an	O
one	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
153	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Thackham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Rich	O
.	O
Hollingsworth	O
,	O
between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Clogs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Pattens	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hollingsworth	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
January	O
8	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hollingsworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Blackmoor-street	B-place
,	I-place
Clare-Market	I-place
:	O
On	O
January	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
:	O
The	O
Window-Shutter	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
Pin	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
Shutter	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Shutters	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
Glass	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fixed	O
Sash	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
moved	O
.	O
Missing	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
Bills	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Shoemakers	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
sold	O
to	O
some-body	O
of	O
the	O
Trade	O
:	O
Mr	O
Laws	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Goods	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
plain	O
Clogs	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
Man	O
with	O
another	O
Pair	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
secured	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
my	O
Cloge	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
served	O
his	O
Time	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
out	O
about	O
fourteen	O
Months	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
Morris	O
,	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
robbery	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
watched	O
my	O
Wife	O
into	O
the	O
Closet	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Key	O
and	O
Pin	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
about	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Bar	O
and	O
Shutter	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
divided	O
them	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
Six-pence	O
a	O
Pair	O
less	O
than	O
they	O
cost	O
me	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Laws	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
Clogs	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
several	O
Times	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
Mr	O
Hollingsworth	O
's	O
Advertisement	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Hollingsworth	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
late	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
he	O
watched	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
good	O
Woman	O
's	O
Back	O
was	O
turned	O
,	O
and	O
whipt	O
the	O
Key	O
and	O
Pin	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window-Shutter	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
till	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
Shutter	O
down	O
,	O
broke	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
twenty	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Pattens	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
divided	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
seven	O
Pair	O
a	O
Piece	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
impeached	O
two	O
others	O
.	O
-	O
Colonel	O
De	O
Veil	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Body	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
the	O
Colonel	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
the	O
Truth	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
of	O
saving	O
himself	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
his	O
Accomplices	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Projector	O
of	O
the	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
buy	O
them	O
of	O
other	O
People	O
so	O
?	O
Laws	O
.	O
We	O
always	O
buy	O
cheaper	O
of	O
them	O
than	O
we	O
do	O
of	O
a	O
Shop-Keeper	O
.	O
They	O
will	O
sometimes	O
give	O
their	O
Labour	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
can	O
afford	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
cheaper	O
than	O
a	O
Shop-Keeper	O
can	O
.	O
I	O
detected	O
him	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
says	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Shutter	O
down	O
till	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
at	O
Two	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
the	O
Watchman	O
go	O
by	O
so	O
often	O
without	O
seeing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
letting	O
him	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
Hollingsworth	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
question	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
was	O
five	O
Weeks	O
,	O
I	O
landed	O
at	O
Somerset-House	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Billings-gate	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Clogs	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
Eighteen-pence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
Sixteen-pence	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
fitted	O
the	O
Shoes	O
I	O
have	O
on	O
,	O
[	O
set	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
Clogs	O
]	O
Let	O
me	O
see	O
,	O
-	O
these	O
are	O
not	O
them	O
,	O
-	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Clogs	O
that	O
the	O
Woman	O
offered	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
from	O
fifty	O
Pair	O
.	O
Hollingsworth	O
.	O
This	O
Creature	O
goes	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
for	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
Reward	O
for	O
convicting	O
a	O
Man	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thinks	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
Life	O
for	O
the	O
Reward	O
.	O
Hollingsworth	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
Court	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
offered	O
me	O
the	O
Clogs	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
together	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
selling	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Grew	I-pers
said	O
they	O
have	O
trusted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
Things	O
of	O
Value	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
acquitted	O
*	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
*	O
As	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
thought	O
by	O
some	O
Persons	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Verdict	O
is	O
not	O
exactly	O
agreeable	O
to	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
presumed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Reason	O
which	O
the	O
Jury	O
went	O
upon	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
least	O
advised	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
encouraged	O
,	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
in	O
Hopes	O
of	O
being	O
made	O
easy	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
this	O
Confession	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
,	O
under	O
publick	O
Faith	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
might	O
very	O
well	O
throw	O
that	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Case	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
for	O
Mr	O
Hollingsworth	O
knew	O
not	O
that	O
his	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
till	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
done	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
Light	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Case	O
the	O
Offence	O
is	O
not	O
Burglary	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
154	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Ealing	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
six	O
Linnen	O
Caps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
Dimitty	O
Mantle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
February	O
16	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Ealing	B-place
:	O
My	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
16th	O
Day	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
about	O
Eight	O
in	O
the	O
Forenoon	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Daughter	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
Door	O
fast	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
leave	O
any	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
Farmer	O
Squire	B-pers
's	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
House	O
open	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
Word	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Door	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
some-how	O
by	O
the	O
Lock	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hanged	O
.	O
They	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Things	O
-	O
These	O
are	O
Mr	O
Clarke	O
's	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Field	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Shoulder	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hanged	O
:	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
Basket	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
them	O
over	O
a	O
Hedge	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen-Garden	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Freebourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
a	O
House	O
open	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
this	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
,	O
that	O
Way	O
nearer	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
Things	O
might	O
be	O
worth	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
about	O
30	O
s.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
||	O
||	O
The	O
Offence	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
is	O
made	O
capital	O
by	O
39	O
Eliz	O
.	O
c.	O
13.	O
but	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
so	O
highly	O
penal	O
,	O
the	O
Jury	O
must	O
find	O
a	O
breaking	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
to	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
5	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
155	O
,	O
156	O
.	O
+	O
Henry	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bulley	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
Hospital	B-place
of	I-place
Bridewell	I-place
,	O
about	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silver	O
Cup	O
and	O
Cover	O
;	O
2	O
Silver	O
Muggs	O
;	O
six	O
Salvers	O
;	O
3	O
dozen	O
of	O
Spoons	O
;	O
2	O
dozen	O
Silver	O
handled	O
Knives	O
;	O
37	O
Forks	O
;	O
1	O
Silver	O
Sauce-pan	O
;	O
3	O
Salts	O
;	O
3	O
Salt-Spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Value	O
80	O
l.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
February	O
15	O
.	O
-	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
charged	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
said	O
Goods	O
in	O
a	O
Dwelling-House	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Butler	O
to	O
Mr	O
Taylor	O
,	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
the	O
Plate	O
over	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Day	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
when	O
my	O
Master	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Back-Parlour	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Beauset	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Stanmore	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
Master	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Beauset	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
gone	O
,	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
the	O
biggest	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Plate	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Cup	O
and	O
Cover	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Beauset	O
,	O
locked	O
up	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
.	O
(	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Silver	O
Sauce-pan	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Plate	O
produced	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Mr	O
Taylor	O
's	O
.	O
)	O
Rachel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
was	O
seven-Night	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Beauset	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Plate	O
gone	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Boat	O
and	O
a	O
Sauce-pan	O
which	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Dresser	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
gone	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Door	O
was	O
locked	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
barred	O
:	O
-	O
They	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
;	O
the	O
Sash	O
was	O
pushed	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Sash	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positively	O
sure	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
Sash	O
was	O
up	O
or	O
down	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Blind	O
before	O
the	O
Sash	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
:	O
That	O
was	O
in	O
its	O
Place	O
then	O
;	O
the	O
Blind	O
goes	O
with	O
Pullies	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
its	O
Place	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Job	O
Steele	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
first	O
Place	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
,	O
his	O
Wife	O
Ann	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Ben	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
's-Head	O
,	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
there	O
three	O
Times	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
)	O
The	O
last	O
Night	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
Monday	O
was	O
seven-Night	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
rob	O
Esquire	O
Taylor	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
that	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
Taylor	O
?	O
Steele	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
his	O
Servant	O
.	O
-	O
And	O
accordingly	O
,	O
departing	O
from	O
that	O
House	O
;	O
we	O
entered	O
into	O
Bridewell	O
undiscovered	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
Suspicion	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
a	O
winding	O
Fair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
-	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
know	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
Stories	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
high	O
we	O
went	O
:	O
But	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
;	O
all	O
Three	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
that	O
entered	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
by	O
what	O
Method	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
concealed	O
upon	O
the	O
Stairs	O
till	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
asleep	O
.	O
-	O
At	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
inner	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
into	O
the	O
outer	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
Bulley	O
helped	O
me	O
up	O
over	O
the	O
Pallisades	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Sash-Window	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
and	O
entered	O
in	O
,	O
as	O
better	O
knowing	O
the	O
House	O
than	O
he	O
did	O
(	O
though	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
pretty	O
well	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
struck	O
a	O
Light	O
with	O
their	O
Tinder-box	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
Beauset	O
up	O
;	O
they	O
filled	O
two	O
Bags	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
carried	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
left	O
more	O
Plate	O
behind	O
,	O
than	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
:	O
They	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
Plates	O
and	O
Dishes	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
said	O
were	O
Pewter	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
Plate	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
than	O
this	O
Trumpery	O
.	O
[	O
Meaning	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
of	O
Ralph	O
Sleigh	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Staw	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
which	O
were	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
]	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Window	O
close	O
down	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Steele	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
close	O
down	O
by	O
near	O
a	O
Foot	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
into	O
it	O
without	O
pushing	O
it	O
up	O
-	O
They	O
took	O
away	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
for	O
your	O
Pains	O
?	O
Steele	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
for	O
my	O
Pains	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
they	O
get	O
in	O
?	O
Steele	O
.	O
I	O
unbarred	O
and	O
unbolted	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
-	O
at	O
the	O
outer	O
Door	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
-	O
they	O
went	O
directly	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
struck	O
a	O
Light	O
with	O
their	O
Tinder-Box	O
,	O
and	O
lighted	O
a	O
Candle	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
where	O
the	O
Beauset	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
Gimblet	O
and	O
a	O
Knife	O
they	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
what	O
they	O
pleased	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
themselves	O
up	O
2	O
Packs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
that	O
Sauce-pan	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
blacker	O
than	O
that	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
:	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Silver	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
took	O
enough	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
too	O
much	O
too	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
2	O
Prisoners	O
are	O
the	O
Persons	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
away	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
known	O
the	O
Woman	O
above	O
three	O
Months	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
20	O
Years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
is	O
his	O
Wife	O
?	O
Steele	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
is	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
Wives	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pice	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
last	O
,	O
Mr	O
Taylor	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Message	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Person	O
who	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Plate	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
Person	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Horselydown	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
that	O
Night	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
with	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
Doors	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
2	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Fore	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Back-Door	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
Person	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
Henry	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
believed	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Account	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
then	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
they	O
lodged	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Search-Warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
search	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
Word	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Wooden-Chest	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
Chest	O
a	O
Brass	O
Pistol	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Plate	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
:	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Boatswain	O
and	O
Call	O
,	O
in	O
Horselydown	O
,	O
Fair-street	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Man	O
's	O
Name	O
is	O
Redrosse	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
Bulley	O
came	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
Guest	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
there	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
Thing	O
about	O
me	O
?	O
Richard	B-pers
Pice	I-pers
.	O
In	O
the	O
Room	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Ashes	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
burning	O
a	O
pretty	O
many	O
Papers	O
:	O
This	O
little	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Spoons	O
were	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
marked	O
J.	O
T.	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
marked	O
M.	B-pers
H.	I-pers
B	I-pers
.	I-pers
A.	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Bulley	I-pers
said	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
Spoon	O
;	O
and	O
Mr	O
Taylor	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
M.	O
was	O
for	O
Mustard	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Mustard	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Letters	O
H.	O
B	O
.	O
A.	O
were	O
fresh	O
made	O
]	O
This	O
Spoon	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Ashes	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
We	O
shall	O
now	O
prove	O
how	O
this	O
Plate	O
was	O
carried	O
about	O
from	O
one	O
Place	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gyles	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Coachman	O
)	O
My	O
Stand	O
is	O
by	O
White-Chapel	O
Bars	O
:	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
was	O
sen'night	O
,	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
(	O
the	O
Man	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Hackney-Coachman	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Dulwich	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
a	O
Hackney-man	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
Shillings	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
six	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
him	O
a	O
Chaise	O
and	O
Pair	O
for	O
7	O
Shillings	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Wentworth-street	O
,	O
Spital-fields	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Portmantean-Trunk	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Hay-Bag	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
square	O
Box	O
,	O
with	O
Nobs	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
very	O
heavy	O
-	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Chaise	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
Trunk	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
at	O
Dulwich	O
,	O
and	O
unluckily	O
the	O
Portmanteau	O
burst	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
Road	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
there	O
was	O
Plate	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Pewter	O
or	O
Silver	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
sat	O
him	O
down	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
that	O
Woman	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
Dogs	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
left	O
this	O
Box	O
and	O
Trunk	O
with	O
Henry	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
at	O
Dulwich	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
paid	O
my	O
Mistress	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Shooler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Flying-horse	O
,	O
in	O
Lambeth-street	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Fox	O
under	O
the	O
Hill	O
,	O
at	O
Camberwell	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
at	O
Dulwich	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
a	O
four	O
cornered	O
Box	O
:	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hairy	O
Portmanteau	O
Trunk	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
the	O
Trunk	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
Horselydown	O
,	O
Fair-street	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Boatswain	O
and	O
Call	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
both	O
the	O
Man	O
and	O
the	O
Woman	O
down	O
there	O
:	O
She	O
took	O
another	O
four	O
cornered	O
Trunk	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
Trunk	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Trunk	O
and	O
the	O
Box	O
there	O
below	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Trunk	O
;	O
Mr	O
Taylor	O
's	O
Plate	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
:	O
-	O
There	O
is	O
all	O
the	O
Reason	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
to	O
believe	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
behind	O
me	O
:	O
But	O
there	O
are	O
the	O
Marks	O
of	O
the	O
Blows	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
made	O
with	O
the	O
Hammer	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Plate	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Bag	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
Trunk	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
desire	O
that	O
Box	O
may	O
be	O
opened	O
:	O
(	O
Which	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pistol	O
taken	O
out	O
)	O
Whose	O
Pistol	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
It	O
is	O
his	O
Pistol	O
.	O
Job	O
Steele	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Pistol	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
own	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Pistol	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
.	O
Whose	O
Things	O
are	O
those	O
?	O
(	O
A	O
Pair	O
of	O
Pistols	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
dark	O
Lanthorns	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Box	O
.	O
)	O
Job	O
Steele	O
.	O
What	O
signifies	O
my	O
knowing	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
These	O
Pistols	O
are	O
your	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
you	O
handle	O
them	O
many	O
a	O
Time	O
:	O
-	O
These	O
two	O
Dark	O
Lanthorns	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
are	O
the	O
Lanthorns	O
we	O
made	O
Use	O
of	O
at	O
Mr	O
Taylor	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
-	O
All	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
were	O
Bulley	O
's	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
Pistol	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Man	O
who	O
is	O
the	O
Evidence	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
who	O
sent	O
the	O
Box	O
with	O
the	O
Plate	O
in	O
it	O
under	O
our	O
Care	O
:	O
He	O
sent	O
it	O
by	O
an	O
unknown	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Elliot	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Job	O
Steele	O
come	O
into	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Man	O
and	O
a	O
Woman	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
was	O
se'ennight	O
,	O
a	O
small	O
Matter	O
before	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
Persons	O
.	O
-	O
Elliot	O
.	O
By	O
their	O
Size	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
their	O
Faces	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Job	O
Steele	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
more	O
than	O
an	O
hundred	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Culley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Shrove-Tuesday	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Five	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
loaded	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
a	O
Country-Journey	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
Bag	O
and	O
Baggage	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
stopped	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
.	O
Are	O
you	O
married	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Henry	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
.	O
She	O
is	O
my	O
Wife	O
.	O
[	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
offered	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
Wife	O
;	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
not	O
enter	O
into	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
acknowledged	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
.	O
]	O
Henry	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
ask	O
Steele	O
some	O
Questions	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
Box	O
may	O
be	O
opened	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Brass	O
Pistol	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
Whose	O
Pistol	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
Job	O
Steele	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Box	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Brass	O
Pistol	O
.	O
These	O
other	O
two	O
Pistols	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
often	O
enough	O
;	O
you	O
had	O
them	O
when	O
you	O
lived	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
that	O
other	O
Pistol	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
.	O
Steele	O
sent	O
this	O
Plate	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
an	O
unknown	O
Hand	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bulley	I-pers
acquitted	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
present	O
with	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
supposed	O
to	O
act	O
under	O
his	O
Direction	O
.	O
157	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kendred	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
William	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Acornley	I-pers
,	O
November	O
9	O
.	O
Widow	O
Acornley	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
my	O
Husband	O
went	O
out	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
returned	O
wounded	O
and	O
bruised	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
barbarous	O
Manner	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
House	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kenared	I-pers
used	O
him	O
very	O
ill	O
.	O
Hearing	O
a	O
Noise	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
with	O
other	O
Company	O
that	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
:	O
My	O
Husband	O
was	O
never	O
well	O
afterwards	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
Blithman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Painter	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
sitting	O
by	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Castle-Court	B-place
,	O
among	O
some	O
young	O
Fellows	O
who	O
had	O
picked	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Candle	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kendred	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
I	O
