TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
KING	O
'S	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
PEACE	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
HELD	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
AND	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
on	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
16th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Willimott	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-Noster-Row	O
.	O
1748	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
ROBERT	B-pers
WILLIMOTT	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
BURNET	O
,	O
Mr	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
Aly	O
Thompson	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wentworth	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Windsor	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Millington	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Linney	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Basnett	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawker	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Kirks	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Durno	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Brickland	I-pers
.	O
N.	B-pers
B.	I-pers
John	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
on	O
the	O
Jury	O
the	O
Second	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
Mr	O
Basnett	O
.	O
248.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Cremer	I-pers
,	O
May	O
3	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Cremer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
grey	O
Stockings	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
Price	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
about	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
looked	O
on	O
several	O
Pair	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
hardly	O
fine	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
Eyes	O
on	O
one	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
shuffle	O
this	O
Pair	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
hardly	O
got	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
you	O
design	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
that	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
you	O
have	O
in	O
your	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
I	O
took	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Pair	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
a	O
darker	O
Colour	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
certain	O
whether	O
you	O
have	O
them	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
Collar	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
Knock	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
Maid	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
Knees	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
Mercy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
committed	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
was	O
for	O
running	O
her	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Stockings	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
pulled	O
out	O
two	O
Pair	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
Pair	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pair	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
search	O
me	O
yourself	O
before	O
your	O
Wife	O
and	O
Maid	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
?	O
Cremer	O
.	O
No	O
indeed	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Standen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Noise	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
249.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Weblin	I-pers
+	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Silk	O
Damask	O
Skirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
April	O
25	O
.	O
+	O
Samuel	B-pers
Weblin	I-pers
was	O
tried	O
in	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
Mr	O
Alderman	O
Perry	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
11.	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Cheshire	O
Cheeses	O
out	O
of	O
Mr	O
Freeman	O
's	O
Shop	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Skirt	O
of	O
Mr	O
Spencer	O
's	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Hat	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
Skirt	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
Mr	O
Dyer	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
again	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Ceeley	I-pers
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ceeley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
Boys	O
lurking	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
Mr	O
Dyer	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
.	O
His	O
two	O
Confederates	O
waited	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
Crown-Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Skirt	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Dorset-Court	O
,	O
by	O
Channel	O
Row	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	B-pers
:	O
Mr	O
Fairbourne	O
's	O
Boy	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
into	O
Channel-Row	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
directly	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
250.	O
Jane	B-pers
Pearse	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
James	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Pewter	O
Pots	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Humston	I-pers
,	O
April	O
21	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Humston	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
pretty	O
often	O
for	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
past	O
,	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Purl	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
her	O
one	O
Day	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
melted	O
down	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Pewterer	O
for	O
Six-Pence	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
Quart	O
Pot	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
Pots	O
(	O
three	O
Pints	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Quart	O
Pot	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
did	O
take	O
a	O
Pint	O
Pot	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
down-right	O
Want	O
and	O
Necessity	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
251.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Wooden	O
Vessel	O
called	O
a	O
Barrel	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Iron	O
Hoops	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
252.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Vedast	I-place
Foster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
Yards	O
of	O
black	O
Silk	O
Lace	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sage	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Gopp	I-pers
,	O
April	O
28	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sage	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
Woman	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
Three	O
and	O
Four	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
black	O
Silk	O
Lace	O
;	O
I	O
showed	O
her	O
some	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
like	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Customers	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
more	O
next	O
Week	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
then	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
do	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
Lace	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
Next-door	O
Neighbour	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Lace	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
;	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
it	O
hanging	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Box	O
of	O
Lace	O
away	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
deceived	O
by	O
her	O
shuffling	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Box	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
Lace	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
has	O
my	O
Mark	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
Design	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
as	O
a	O
Pattern	O
(	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
by	O
Chance	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
)	O
.	O
Mr	O
Tomkins	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
our	O
Family	O
as	O
a	O
Chamber-Maid	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
about	O
three	O
Months	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
mistrusted	O
her	O
Honesty	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
kept	O
her	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
nor	O
was	O
she	O
turned	O
away	O
upon	O
any	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
that	O
Kind	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
from	O
a	O
Relation	O
of	O
ours	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Barnabas	B-pers
Tunstal	I-pers
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
her	O
Character	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
good	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
in	O
several	O
Places	O
,	O
particularly	O
the	O
last	O
Place	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
all	O
her	O
Friends	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
very	O
good	O
Friends	O
in	O
Yorkshire	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
Lace	O
was	O
loose	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
;	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
opened	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
have	O
fell	O
down	O
:	O
Since	O
her	O
Commitment	O
,	O
several	O
Gentlemen	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
first	O
Offence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
253	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
the	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
Pewter-Plates	O
,	O
2	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
1	O
Silver	O
Tea-spoon	O
,	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
2	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Hat	O
,	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
,	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
,	O
1	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
1	O
black	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
7	O
Shirts	O
,	O
1	O
Sheet	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Pockets	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Dwelling-House	O
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
;	O
had	O
been	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
lately	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pretended	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
stripped	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
Mercy	O
she	O
had	O
saved	O
her	O
Gold	O
Necklace	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
catched	O
a	O
great	O
Cold	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
show	O
you	O
what	O
was	O
preceding	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Robbery	O
itself	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
the	O
13th	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
sore	O
Throat	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
again	O
till	O
Tuesday	O
se'ennight	O
following	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
26th	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
Interim	O
of	O
Time	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
a	O
Message	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
somebody	O
might	O
do	O
her	O
Business	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
27th	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
(	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
this	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
washed	O
)	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
ten	O
Gallon	O
Kettle	O
which	O
we	O
wash	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Hole	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
imagine	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
made	O
by	O
herself	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
never	O
observed	O
it	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
perswaded	O
my	O
Wife	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Kettle	O
go	O
to	O
be	O
mended	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
Pots	O
and	O
Kettles	O
wanted	O
tinning	O
,	O
and	O
perswaded	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
:	O
She	O
carried	O
that	O
great	O
Kettle	O
,	O
a	O
Pot	O
,	O
5	O
Saucepans	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stew-pan	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
home	O
but	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Saucepans	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
washing	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
hanging	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
upon	O
a	O
wooden	O
Horse	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
little	O
Small-Beer	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
Rush-light	O
burning	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Plates	O
lying	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
the	O
Candle	O
's	O
being	O
left	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
designed	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Wife	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
the	O
House	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
a	O
Curd	O
)	O
I	O
suppose	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
prevent	O
our	O
minding	O
of	O
it	O
if	O
we	O
should	O
hear	O
any	O
rustling	O
or	O
Noise	O
:	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
6	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Back-Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Garden-Door	O
unbolted	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
always	O
take	O
Care	O
to	O
see	O
fast	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
upon	O
returning	O
in	O
again	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
a	O
gossipping	O
with	O
some	O
Neighbour	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
Imagination	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
)	O
I	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
my	O
Wife	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
get	O
up	O
too	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
we	O
were	O
stripp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
Judgment	O
in	O
doing	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
pulled	O
these	O
Papers	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Coat-Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
upon	O
a	O
Chair	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
Shoes	O
and	O
Coat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
worn	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
carry	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
an	O
hundred	O
Weight	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Keys	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
several	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Keys	O
on	O
the	O
Table	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
when	O
I	O
bolted	O
the	O
Garden-Door	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
recollect	O
where	O
her	O
Friends	O
liv	O
'd	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
formerly	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
somewhere	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
Friends	O
lived	O
in	O
More-lane	O
by	O
Morefields	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
her	O
Person	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
three	O
Jews	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
pretending	O
they	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
sold	O
among	O
their	O
Jews	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mylock	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
one	O
Jacobs	O
came	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
Persons	O
afterwards	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
sworn	O
it	O
on	O
Jacob	B-pers
Lopez	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mylock	I-pers
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mylock	O
and	O
Lopez	O
had	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
You	O
tell	O
us	O
your	O
Suspicions	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Law	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
should	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
speak	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
positive	O
of	O
;	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
positive	O
Notice	O
of	O
what	O
Linnen	O
lay	O
there	O
?	O
Mr	O
Martin	O
.	O
No	O
indeed	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
she	O
took	O
your	O
Wife	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
your	O
Wife	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
Head	O
?	O
Mr	O
Martin	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Strings	O
of	O
it	O
hang	O
down	O
by	O
her	O
Head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Drawers	O
were	O
lock	O
'd	O
?	O
Mr	O
Martin	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
your	O
Chamber-Door	O
fastened	O
?	O
Mr	O
Martin	O
.	O
My	O
Chamber-Door	O
was	O
fastened	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Door	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
Rooms	O
was	O
not	O
fastened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
impeached	O
Lopez	O
and	O
Mylock	O
,	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
indict	O
them	O
?	O
Mr	O
Martin	O
.	O
Mylock	O
behaved	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
him	O
innocent	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
a	O
Person	O
I	O
could	O
convict	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
sufficient	O
Evidence	O
to	O
convict	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Bretter	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Mr	O
Scott	O
's	O
Brewhouse	O
in	O
the	O
Broad-Way	O
,	O
with	O
six	O
Gallons	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
my	O
Wife	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
dull	O
of	O
hearing	O
)	O
heard	O
somebody	O
say	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
earn	O
Sixpence	O
?	O
my	O
Wife	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
helped	O
me	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
my	O
Back	O
,	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Artillery-Wall	O
near	O
Tothill	O
Fields	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
200	O
Yards	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
's	O
House	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
ordinary	O
Sheet	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
two	O
Parts	O
,	O
that	O
Part	O
which	O
hung	O
upon	O
my	O
Back	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
Copper	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
tied	O
so	O
close	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Inside	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Horse-Ferry	O
Whars	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Waterman	O
(	O
Henry	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
)	O
lifted	O
them	O
off	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
down	O
the	O
Wharf	O
himself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
the	O
Waterman	O
down	O
the	O
Wharf	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Woman	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
nor	O
since	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Lambeth	O
,	O
and	O
happened	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Fare	O
to	O
Westminster	O
Horse-Ferry	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
to	O
stay	O
to	O
get	O
another	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
get	O
one	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
this	O
Man	O
(	O
Bretter	O
)	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
on	O
his	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Sculler	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Woman	O
coming	O
behind	O
who	O
wanted	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
Sculler	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
What	O
must	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
Cranes	O
;	O
Nine-Pence	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
For	O
with	O
that	O
Bundle	O
it	O
deserves	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
Six-Pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
no	O
Pint	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
but	O
Six-Pence	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
Porter	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Little	O
Morefields	O
)	O
but	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
upon	O
my	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
heavy	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
a	O
Waterman	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
earn	O
a	O
Jobb	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
The	O
Things	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Cloth	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Plates	O
fell	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
half	O
a	O
Dozen	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
fell	O
out	O
;	O
(	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
Plates	O
and	O
Linnen	O
)	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
Porter	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
who	O
undertook	O
the	O
Jobb	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Plates	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Bundle	O
again	O
herself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Artillery-Wall	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Ferry	O
?	O
Bretter	O
.	O
Full	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Ware	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Ware	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
full	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Five	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
against	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Clock	O
struck	O
Six	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Clock	O
strikes	O
Six	O
now	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
Monday	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
recollect	O
this	O
Particular	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
?	O
Ware	O
.	O
Because	O
Mr	O
Martin	O
had	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Paper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
does	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
out	O
?	O
Ware	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Guild-Hall	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
me	O
.	O
Mr	O
Martin	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
carry	O
such	O
a	O
Fare	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
could	O
know	O
a	O
Fare	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
carried	O
last	O
Friday	O
?	O
Ware	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
could	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
Woman	O
;	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
take	O
so	O
much	O
Notice	O
of	O
every	O
Fare	O
I	O
carry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
this	O
Man	O
(	O
Bretter	O
)	O
could	O
carry	O
that	O
Bundle	O
of	O
Things	O
so	O
far	O
in	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
;	O
't	O
is	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
Mile	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
older	O
Man	O
than	O
you	O
?	O
Ware	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
done	O
.	O
Burgess	O
Yerwood	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Sancepans	O
to	O
be	O
tinned	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
Pots	O
,	O
Kettles	O
,	O
and	O
Sauce-pans	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Mistress	O
sent	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Name	O
was	O
Martin	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
a	O
very	O
plausible	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
Thing	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
careful	O
of	O
buying	O
stolen	O
Goods	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
Body	O
)	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
Fifteen	O
Shillings	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
tell	O
her	O
Mistress	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
Fifteen	O
Shillings	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
old	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knocked	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
Pieces	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
,	O
or	O
after	O
the	O
Robbery	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Saucepans	O
were	O
tinned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
Thursday	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
weighed	O
the	O
Pots	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
paid	O
her	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
A	O
Boy	O
,	O
about	O
Fourteen	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Court	O
a	O
satisfactory	O
Answer	O
,	O
with	O
relation	O
to	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
examined	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
12th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
pretending	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
a	O
Servant	O
's	O
Character	O
for	O
her	O
Aunt	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
enquired	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
your	O
Aunt	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
sooner	O
live	O
with	O
a	O
Stranger	O
,	O
than	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
then	O
ask	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
I	O
hired	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
:	O
The	O
Sunday	O
following	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
sore	O
Throat	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
17th	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
staid	O
till	O
the	O
26th	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
she	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
before	O
my	O
Husband	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
this	O
Boy	O
[	O
He	O
that	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
examined	O
]	O
runs	O
of	O
Errands	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Nine	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bed	O
betimes	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
hard	O
Day	O
's	O
Work	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Servant	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
to	O
lie	O
by	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
Husband	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
up	O
very	O
early	O
,	O
and	O
wash	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
as	O
white	O
as	O
a	O
Curd	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
wake	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
her	O
up	O
at	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
too	O
soon	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
after	O
such	O
a	O
hard	O
Day	O
's	O
Work	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
take	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Mrs	O
Martin	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
every	O
Thing	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Shift	O
left	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
on	O
:	O
[	O
She	O
then	O
mentioned	O
the	O
Things	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
a	O
China	O
Tea-Pot	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spout	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
wake	O
and	O
call	O
her	O
?	O
Mrs	O
Martin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
to	O
produce	O
?	O
Mrs	O
Martin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
sober	O
when	O
she	O
laid	O
down	O
by	O
you	O
?	O
Mrs	O
Martin	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sober	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
slept	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
tired	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
Reason	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Council	O
pleaded	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
amount	O
to	O
a	O
Felony	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
put	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Care	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Court	O
were	O
of	O
a	O
different	O
Opinion	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Kettle	O
and	O
Pot	O
my	O
Mistress	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
Mr	O
Yerwood	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Saucepans	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
15	O
s.	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
18	O
d.	O
for	O
tinning	O
the	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
Surgeon	O
for	O
curing	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
harrasses	O
me	O
Night	O
and	O
Day	O
,	O
sending	O
me	O
about	O
one	O
trifling	O
Errand	O
or	O
another	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
is	O
either	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Senses	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
has	O
drank	O
herself	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
sent	O
me	O
about	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Nurse-Child	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
knows	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
always	O
sending	O
me	O
about	O
one	O
idle	O
thing	O
or	O
another	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
Mrs	O
Martin	O
send	O
her	O
about	O
any	O
Nurse	O
Children	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Senses	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
always	O
used	O
her	O
well	O
;	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
Child	O
than	O
a	O
Servant	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
has	O
had	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Cloaths	O
off	O
my	O
Back	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Davis	O
knows	O
she	O
carried	O
the	O
Spoon	O
to	O
pawn	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
carry	O
any	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Kidder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
twenty	O
Years	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Servant	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
twelve	O
Months	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
Pound	O
at	O
a	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
she	O
ever	O
did	O
any	O
Wrong	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
knew	O
her	O
turned	O
away	O
upon	O
any	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
sucked	O
at	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
Breast	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
twice	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
always	O
acted	O
honestly	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
twice	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
in	O
the	O
Time	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Mrs	O
Martin	O
wanted	O
a	O
Nurse-Child	O
.	O
Mr	O
Martin	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
ask	O
Pardon	O
for	O
it	O
dashes	O
me	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
Wife	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
Drunkard	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
Ruin	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr	O
Martin	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
her	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
Babe	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hardman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mother	O
these	O
twenty	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Ramsay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
best	O
Part	O
of	O
seven	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
miss	O
Word	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Another	O
Witness	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Girl	O
in	O
Frocks	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
turned	O
away	O
from	O
any	O
Place	O
upon	O
the	O
Account	O
of	O
any	O
Wrong	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
ever	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
Crime	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
254.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Davenport	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
black	O
Velvet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
ten	O
Yards	O
of	O
Silk	O
Damask	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
forty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lustring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Swan	I-pers
,	O
April	O
16	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
having	O
robbed	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
one	O
Madam	O
Deson	O
's	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
several	O
Sorts	O
of	O
Silk	O
which	O
were	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
Mr	O
Swan	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
my	O
Partner	O
,	O
three	O
Years	O
)	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
acquainted	O
with	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
hired	O
a	O
Coach	O
,	O
in	O
Order	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
France	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
certainly	O
have	O
gone	O
that	O
Evening	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
made	O
up	O
into	O
Garments	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
have	O
our	O
own	O
Mark	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
white	O
Damask	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lustrings	O
were	O
made	O
into	O
Dresses	O
,	O
for	O
Madam	O
Deson	O
's	O
Use	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
black	O
Velvet	O
was	O
made	O
into	O
a	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
these	O
are	O
your	O
Goods	O
?	O
Buck	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
regular	O
Method	O
of	O
entering	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
Number-Book	O
,	O
and	O
keeping	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
is	O
cut	O
off	O
each	O
Piece	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
we	O
are	O
defrauded	O
by	O
our	O
Servants	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
particular	O
Patterns	O
which	O
we	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
compared	O
this	O
Pattern	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Damask	O
in	O
our	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
Piece	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
deficient	O
by	O
the	O
Number-Book	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
forty	O
Yards	O
of	O
Lustring	O
deficient	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
Partner	O
are	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
any	O
Person	O
comes	O
to	O
buy	O
any	O
Lustring	O
or	O
Damask	O
,	O
has	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
Right	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Buck	O
.	O
We	O
do	O
allow	O
a	O
Right	O
to	O
our	O
Servants	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
to	O
fifteen	O
Yards	O
of	O
Damask	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Yards	O
of	O
black	O
Velvet	O
being	O
cut	O
off	O
our	O
Pieces	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Remembrance	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
our	O
Marks	O
on	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Remnants	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
before	O
Colonel	O
De	O
Veil	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
were	O
our	O
Property	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
through	O
Madam	O
Deson	O
's	O
Means	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
this	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
indicted	O
but	O
the	O
Bill	O
was	O
thrown	O
out	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
Patterns	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs	O
Gost	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gost	I-pers
was	O
examined	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
French	O
Sack	O
of	O
the	O
white	O
Damask	O
;	O
and	O
four	O
other	O
Patterns	O
of	O
Lustring	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
being	O
shown	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
French	O
Sack	O
of	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
Madam	O
Deson	O
.	O
Buck	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
before	O
several	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Madam	O
Deson	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
own	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Madam	O
Deson	O
?	O
Buck	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Madam	O
Deson	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
(	O
Vid	O
.	O
Ante	O
,	O
p.	O
107	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
leave	O
to	O
bring	O
another	O
Kind	O
of	O
Indictment	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
255.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Lambs	O
,	O
price	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Sleith	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Sleith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
East	B-place
Barnet	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
small	O
Lambs	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Noon	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
Week	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
Howel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
were	O
seen	O
with	O
two	O
Lambs	O
at	O
Holloway	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Howel	O
and	O
Cole	O
in	O
Morefields	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
remarkable	O
Lambs	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
old	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Holloway	O
;	O
one	O
Saturday	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Howel	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
two	O
Lambs	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
alive	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Howel	O
said	O
at	O
East-Barnet	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
old	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
in	O
two	O
Butchers	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Howel	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
two	O
Lambs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
to	O
Cole	O
,	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
these	O
two	O
Lambs	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
Hitchin	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mr	O
Sleith	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
East-Barnet	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
Mr	O
Sleith	O
's	O
owed	O
him	O
38	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
home	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
something	O
for	O
his	O
Sunday	O
's	O
Dinner	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
through	O
a	O
Church-Yard	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saw	O
two	O
young	O
Lambs	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
his	O
Knife	O
into	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
256	O
+	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Beaugrand	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	O
Anne	O
Westminster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Legier	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
him	O
one	O
mortal	O
Wound	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Breadth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
Inch	O
and	O
the	O
Depth	O
of	O
four	O
Inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
And	O
257	O
+	O
Lewis	B-pers
Brunet	I-pers
for	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
,	O
assisting	O
,	O
and	O
comforting	O
the	O
said	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Beaugrand	I-pers
to	O
commit	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
indicted	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
Murder	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pillet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
White	B-place
Bear	I-place
in	I-place
Newport-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
Lewis	B-pers
Legier	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
Gentleman	O
whom	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
Lewis	B-pers
Legier	I-pers
seeing	O
a	O
Sailor	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Beaugrand	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
Brother	O
Sailor	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
out	O
a	O
Place	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sea	O
;	O
says	O
Beaugrand	O
,	O
Where	O
?	O
Legier	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
yet	O
:	O
Then	O
Beaugrand	O
asked	O
the	O
Cook	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
Legier	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Commodore	O
Anson	O
's	O
Cook	O
)	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Brother	O
Sailor	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
Beaugrand	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
shew	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
showed	O
him	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
Beaugrand	O
said	O
,	O
Then	O
we	O
are	O
Brother	O
Sailors	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
talk	O
about	O
Ships	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
was	O
most	O
esteemed	O
in	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
a	O
Sailor	O
or	O
the	O
Cook	O
;	O
and	O
Beaugrand	O
said	O
a	O
Sailor	O
was	O
more	O
esteemed	O
than	O
the	O
Cook	O
;	O
the	O
Cook	O
(	O
Legier	O
)	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
more	O
esteemed	O
than	O
him	O
:	O
Then	O
there	O
arose	O
Words	O
,	O
and	O
Legier	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
Kick	O
Beaugrand	O
;	O
and	O
Beaugrand	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
yet	O
;	O
and	O
Beaugrand	O
took	O
a	O
Pewter	O
(	O
Pint	O
)	O
Pot	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
Legier	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Legier	O
flew	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Who	O
made	O
the	O
first	O
Attack	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
Beaugrand	O
did	O
strike	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
fought	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
stand	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
Pillet	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
struck	O
one	O
another	O
over	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
several	O
Blows	O
over	O
the	O
Table	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
Blows	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
part	O
of	O
one	O
Blow	O
upon	O
my	O
Eye	O
in	O
going	O
to	O
separate	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
Blow	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
separated	O
Brunet	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
Nephew	O
Beaugrand	O
's	O
Part	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
fight	O
with	O
Lewis	B-pers
Legier	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
Legier	O
flew	O
upon	O
Beaugrand	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
mean	O
by	O
flying	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
Legier	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
Hands	O
.	O
After	O
Legier	O
and	O
Brunet	O
engaged	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
Floor	O
together	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
parted	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
parted	O
,	O
Legier	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
Brunet	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
younger	O
one	O
(	O
Beaugrand	O
)	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
Lewis	B-pers
Legier	I-pers
again	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Punches	O
on	O
the	O
Belly	O
thus	O
-	O
here	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
With	O
what	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
fight	O
de	O
English	O
Fashion	O
;	O
so	O
says	O
I	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Go	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
Legier	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
died	O
immediately	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Go	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
hurt	O
.	O
-	O
Legier	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Brunet	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
fight	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
Passage	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
Brunet	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
again	O
,	O
before	O
Legier	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
Legier	O
fall	O
down	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Entry	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
fell	O
down	O
after	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
then	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Wound	O
or	O
no	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
He	O
bled	O
pretty	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
any	O
more	O
after	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Distance	O
of	O
Time	O
between	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
with	O
the	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
Brunet	O
's	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
Legier	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
Not	O
above	O
two	O
Minutes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
you	O
parted	O
Brunet	O
and	O
Legier	O
,	O
that	O
Beaugrand	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Thrusts	O
at	O
his	O
Belly	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
Presently	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
the	O
Scuffle	O
between	O
Brunet	O
and	O
Legier	O
be	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
Legier	O
had	O
a	O
Pot	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
Beaugrand	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
bloody	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
it	O
after	O
the	O
Struggle	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
his	O
Head	O
to	O
be	O
bloody	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
with	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Who	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Pot	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
Why	O
Legier	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
Pot	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
first	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Pot	O
in	O
Beaugrand	O
's	O
Hand	O
first	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
Beaugrand	O
's	O
Head	O
was	O
bloody	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
Legier	O
those	O
Punches	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
by	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
to	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
his	O
Knife	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Body	O
meddle	O
with	O
a	O
Poker	O
.	O
Pillet	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
No-body	O
had	O
a	O
Poker	O
in	O
their	O
Hands	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Is	O
Beaugrand	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
an	O
Acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
three	O
Weeks	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mr	O
Brunet	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
think	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
sudden	O
Quarrel	O
over	O
Liquor	O
?	O
Pillet	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
bad	O
Expressions	O
made	O
Use	O
of	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bermier	O
examined	O
by	O
an	O
Interpreter	O
,	O
his	O
Evidence	O
was	O
,	O
That	O
between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Pillet	O
's	O
House	O
with	O
Legier	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
drinking	O
;	O
that	O
at	O
first	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
Legier	O
and	O
Beaugrand	O
spoke	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
in	O
English	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
spoke	O
French	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
,	O
friendly	O
Manner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
them	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
French	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
born	O
at	O
Calais	O
,	O
in	O
France	O
;	O
that	O
talking	O
about	O
Sea-Affairs	O
,	O
Beaugrand	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sea	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
the	O
Station	O
of	O
a	O
Cook	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
beneath	O
a	O
Sailor	O
's	O
Dignity	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
Legier	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Captain	O
's	O
Cook	O
was	O
inferior	O
to	O
a	O
Sailor	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
Commodore	O
's	O
Cook	O
,	O
was	O
preferable	O
to	O
a	O
Sailor	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
Beaugrand	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Lye	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
lying	O
Rascal	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
such	O
Expression	O
as	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Sailor	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Beaugrand	O
)	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Pewter	O
Pot	O
,	O
and	O
attempted	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
Cook	O
(	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
)	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
Upon	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
laid	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Table	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Pot	O
out	O
of	O
Beaugrand	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
several	O
Blows	O
over	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Pot	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Could	O
not	O
Beaugrand	O
have	O
hit	O
Legier	O
with	O
the	O
Pot	O
over	O
the	O
Table	O
?	O
Bermier	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
hit	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
forward	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
do	O
it	O
then	O
?	O
Bermier	O
.	O
Because	O
immediately	O
as	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
Motion	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
Legier	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
Table	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Was	O
Beangrand	O
fitting	O
or	O
standing	O
when	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
Motion	O
?	O
Bermier	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
fitting	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
Motion	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
Motion	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
Mr.	O
Pillet	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
they	O
were	O
parted	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Legier	O
,	O
Let	O
us	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
possible	O
that	O
Frenchmen	O
can	O
fight	O
so	O
in	O
a	O
strange	O
Country	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
asked	O
for	O
his	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
Wig	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
Uncle	O
(	O
Brunet	O
)	O
made	O
a	O
Motion	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
Legier	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
Beangrand	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Stab	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
Beaugrand	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
of	O
his	O
giving	O
him	O
the	O
Thrust	O
?	O
Bermier	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
prevented	O
the	O
Mischief	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knows	O
whether	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
had	O
any	O
Knife	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Bermier	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
Wound	O
?	O
Mr	O
Bermier	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Belly	O
near	O
the	O
Navel	O
.	O
-	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
putting	O
his	O
Wig	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Push	O
made	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Wound	O
after	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
dead	O
?	O
Bermier	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
look	O
upon	O
Beaugrand	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
Condition	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
?	O
Bermier	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
Blows	O
given	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Wounds	O
:	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
bleed	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Watchman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pillet	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
One	O
from	O
my	O
Stand	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
standing	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Wall	O
,	O
supported	O
by	O
two	O
Men	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Pillet	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
Men	O
?	O
Rawlins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Pillet	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Candle	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shook	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Minutes	O
he	O
dropped	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
come	O
to	O
himself	O
after	O
he	O
dropped	O
down	O
?	O
Rawlins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
Hand	O
once	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
Blood	O
come	O
out	O
from	O
about	O
his	O
Navel	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
over	O
the	O
Waistband	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
and	O
my	O
Brother	O
Watchman	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Wound	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Wound	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Rawlins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
pickedish	O
Wound	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
almost	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
blooded	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
did	O
it	O
look	O
like	O
the	O
Prick	O
of	O
a	O
Launcet	O
?	O
Rawlins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
two	O
Men	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
came	O
rushing	O
out	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
their	O
Escapes	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
Man	O
(	O
Brunet	O
)	O
came	O
running	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
by	O
God	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
any	O
Name	O
?	O
Rawlins	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
any	O
Name	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
killed	O
him	O
already	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
neighbouring	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
Watchman	O
apprehended	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
shut	O
a	O
Door	O
against	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pushed	O
hard	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Latch	O
flew	O
open	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Sailor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
surrender	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
surrendered	O
immediately	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Bog-house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bog-house	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Scissars	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
afterwards	O
)	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
all	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
Landlord	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
Sheath	O
and	O
Fork	O
under	O
the	O
Table	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Knife	O
that	O
was	O
bloody	O
found	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
Horse-pond	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
's	O
Yard	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Deceased	O
had	O
three	O
Wounds	O
.	O
The	O
Coroner	O
produced	O
a	O
Knife	O
with	O
a	O
sharp	O
pointed	O
Blade	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Inches	O
long	O
.	O
This	O
Knife	O
was	O
found	O
next	O
Day	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
Yard	O
,	O
which	O
can	O
be	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
If	O
a	O
Man	O
had	O
a	O
sharp	O
Knife	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
might	O
it	O
not	O
run	O
into	O
his	O
Body	O
by	O
Accident	O
?	O
Stephen	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Assistance	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
White-Bear	O
in	O
Newport-street	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Man	O
sitting	O
upon	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
supported	O
by	O
the	O
Chimney-Piece	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
his	O
Pulse	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
inspected	O
the	O
Body	O
and	O
found	O
three	O
Wounds	O
,	O
one	O
within	O
an	O
Inch	O
of	O
the	O
left	O
Nipple	O
,	O
another	O
within	O
an	O
Inch	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Cartilage	O
of	O
the	O
Breast-Bone	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
Inches	O
above	O
the	O
Navel	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
between	O
the	O
fifth	O
and	O
sixth	O
Rib	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Body	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
first	O
Wound	O
upon	O
the	O
Breast	O
near	O
the	O
Nipple	O
had	O
penetrated	O
to	O
the	O
Diaphragma	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
entered	O
into	O
the	O
Liver	O
and	O
Vena	O
Cava	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
entered	O
into	O
the	O
Cawl	O
:	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
Opinion	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
given	O
into	O
the	O
Liver	O
was	O
immediate	O
Death	O
;	O
that	O
into	O
the	O
Lungs	O
might	O
have	O
proved	O
mortal	O
;	O
the	O
Consequence	O
of	O
the	O
third	O
Wound	O
was	O
dubious	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Eterneau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
known	O
Beaugrand	O
long	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Uncle	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Years	O
;	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Man	O
killed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
handcuffed	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Beaugrand	O
had	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Head	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
Wounds	O
upon	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
the	O
Pot	O
had	O
made	O
Marks	O
like	O
Horseshoes	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Wounds	O
gaped	O
so	O
that	O
you	O
might	O
put	O
your	O
Finger	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
well	O
of	O
them	O
yet	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Uncle	O
's	O
Company	O
five	O
hundred	O
Times	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
played	O
at	O
Cards	O
with	O
him	O
frequently	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
Passion	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
addicted	O
to	O
quarrelling	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
malicious	O
Action	O
.	O
Josias	O
Hutchinson	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
Wounds	O
,	O
all	O
large	O
Wounds	O
,	O
upon	O
Beaugrand	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
most	O
terrible	O
Condition	O
;	O
the	O
Blows	O
were	O
given	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
Will	O
.	O
Beaugrand	O
guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
Brunet	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
258	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Linnen	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
May	O
5	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
Play	I-place
-House	I-place
,	I-place
into	I-place
the	I-place
Play-House	I-place
Passage	I-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
Mr	O
Tracy	O
's	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Bosom	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
Hand	O
in	O
his	O
Bosom	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
clapped	O
Mr	O
Tracy	O
on	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
This	O
Villain	O
has	O
picked	O
your	O
Pocket	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
the	O
Steps	O
into	O
the	O
Passage	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Piazzas	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Mob	O
rose	O
upon	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
murdered	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Piazzas	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
Spring	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
deadly	O
strong	O
Fellow	O
)	O
and	O
threw	O
my	O
Hat	O
and	O
Wig	O
off	O
my	O
Head	O
,	O
in	O
struggling	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
with	O
Design	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
should	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
got	O
some	O
Assistance	O
,	O
two	O
Soldiers	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
Mr	O
Mitton	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Shakespear	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
some	O
more	O
Soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
certainly	O
be	O
rescued	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rich	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
go	O
through	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
agreed	O
upon	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Mob	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
us	O
with	O
Stones	O
,	O
Brickbats	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
they	O
threw	O
into	O
the	O
Shakespear	O
's	O
Head	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
Degree	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
expected	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
murdered	O
;	O
but	O
Mr	O
Rich	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
Soldiers	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
Assistance	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Play-House	O
,	O
through	O
his	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
were	O
consined	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
and	O
durst	O
not	O
venture	O
out	O
all	O
that	O
Time	O
,	O
though	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
Soldiers	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Harding	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
in	O
the	O
Skustle	O
throw	O
away	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Handkerchief	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
Mr	O
Tracy	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
Play-House	O
;	O
that	O
Gentleman	O
(	O
Mr	O
Harding	O
)	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
struggled	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
throw	O
away	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Mr	O
Mitton	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Shakespear	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
joining	O
to	O
the	O
Play-House	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
Blow	O
over	O
my	O
Eye	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
a	O
Glass	O
Bottle	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
Bar	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
Rum	O
to	O
wash	O
it	O
with	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
washing	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Disturbance	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
stepped	O
out	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
pull	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
how	O
or	O
other	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
we	O
put	O
our	O
Hands	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
broken	O
Glass	O
Bottles	O
;	O
You	O
Villain	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
Rascal	O
that	O
cut	O
my	O
Eye	O
just	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Answer	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Fellows	O
who	O
broke	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
Windows	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
paid	O
39s	O
.	O
4d	O
.	O
for	O
mending	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
murdered	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
such	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
you	O
stand	O
at	O
your	O
Doors	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
Danger	O
of	O
being	O
murdered	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Pint	O
Bottle	O
with	O
some	O
Gin	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
by	O
Mischance	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
Glass	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Mitton	O
.	O
I	O
smelt	O
to	O
the	O
Bottle	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Smell	O
of	O
Gin	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
259	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Donald	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Donald	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Snow-Hill	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
by	O
Mr	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
his	O
Way	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
fleeing	O
me	O
-	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
he	O
sted	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
jumped	O
over	O
some	O
Stairs	O
to	O
get	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Foot	O
of	O
those	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
gript	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
upon	O
his	O
Thigh	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
one	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
off	O
my	O
Neck	O
:	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
two	O
Handkerchiefs	O
before	O
I	O
plead	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Liquor	O
?	O
Donald	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
understood	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
Liquor	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
another	O
walk	O
up	O
Snow-hill	O
Side	O
by	O
Side	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pull	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
as	O
he	O
passed	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
Hand	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
draw	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
wrap	O
it	O
up	O
close	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
That	O
Man	O
has	O
taken	O
your	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Parrot	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Green-Arbor	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
then	O
produced	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
such	O
an	O
one	O
as	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
whether	O
he	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
?	O
there	O
are	O
several	O
Handkerchiefs	O
in	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Sort	O
.	O
Donald	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Parrot	O
in	O
Green	O
Arbor-Court	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
and	O
pray	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
two	O
more	O
Handkerchiefs	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
those	O
were	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
,	O
my	O
Beadle	O
saw	O
him	O
offer	O
to	O
drop	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
Neck	O
then	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
jump	O
'd	O
down	O
a	O
sleep	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
that	O
goes	O
towards	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Market	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
commonly	O
call	O
'd	O
Break-Neck-Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Madam	O
Compton	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
when	O
I	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
red	O
Ground	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
yellow	O
Flower	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Donald	O
's	O
Handkerchief	O
being	O
produced	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
an	O
India	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
's	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
Lydia	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
's	O
)	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
260	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
Yards	O
of	O
Diaper	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Conran	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Conran	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Linnen-Draper	O
in	O
Bridges	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
Goods	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Apron	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
(	O
Mr	O
Tingey	O
,	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
something	O
off	O
Mr.	O
Conran	O
's	O
Counter	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Conran	O
said	O
he	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
piece	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Conran	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
Woman	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
Check	O
for	O
Aprons	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
Apple	O
by	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
show	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
stay	O
and	O
show	O
me	O
some	O
Check	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
stay	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
Wife	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
for	O
Check	O
,	O
and	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
Farthing	O
of	O
Money	O
in	O
their	O
Pockets	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
another	O
Indictment	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Nature	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
pester	O
'd	O
with	O
these	O
Creatures	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
261	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
Yards	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Conran	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
Eliz	O
Conran	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
Morning	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
Shop	O
;	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Cambrick	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
Price	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Yard	O
;	O
(	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Basket	O
with	O
Butter	O
and	O
Eggs	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
sells	O
Butter	O
and	O
Eggs	O
)	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Mistress	O
,	O
you	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
price	O
it	O
is	O
mark	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
cut	O
her	O
a	O
Nail	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
16th	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
Yard	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
at	O
7	O
s.	O
per	O
Yard	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
5	O
d.	O
farthing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
5	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
show	O
her	O
some	O
Lawn	O
;	O
I	O
showed	O
her	O
some	O
Long	O
Lawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
apprehend	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
Rack	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
Lawn	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
several	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
)	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Cambrick	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
trembling	O
came	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
suspecting	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
Woman	O
's	O
Face	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
she	O
shifted	O
her	O
Elbow	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
rustle	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Mistress	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
ask	O
your	O
Pardon	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
something	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
very	O
unhandsome	O
Language	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
Adam	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
some	O
Assistance	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
red	O
Cloak	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
it	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Cambrick	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
;	O
I	O
snatch	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
second	O
Pull	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Cambrick	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
Mr	O
and	O
Mrs	O
Conran	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
Arm	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
liked	O
it	O
better	O
than	O
any	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
thought	O
of	O
stealing	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
Minute	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Conran	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
forgot	O
one	O
thing	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
Mind	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
measure	O
the	O
Lawn	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
Basket	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs	O
Conran	O
take	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cloth	O
,	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Arm	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs	O
Conran	O
pull	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Cambrick	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Woman	O
that	O
works	O
hard	O
for	O
my	O
three	O
Childen	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Buchanan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
takes	O
Care	O
of	O
her	O
Children	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
for	O
her	O
Bread	O
;	O
and	O
has	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dawes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
fifteen	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
stain	O
her	O
Character	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
three	O
small	O
Children	O
;	O
her	O
Husband	O
is	O
in	O
Flanders	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
Corran	O
's	O
Shop	O
about	O
this	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
get	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
about	O
the	O
Affair	O
that	O
has	O
happened	O
to	O
this	O
poor	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
perhaps	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
Mistake	O
;	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Face	O
was	O
never	O
from	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Langwill	I-pers
,	O
-	O
Mac	B-pers
Fun	I-pers
,	O
and	O
-	O
Murran	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
Woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
262	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Luke	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cuttle	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Infant	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
Age	O
of	O
four	O
Years	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
Fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Shirt	O
,	O
a	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
Skirt	O
,	O
a	O
Cap	O
,	O
a	O
Knot	O
,	O
a	O
Frock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Stay	O
;	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cuttle	I-pers
,	O
May	O
11	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Cuttle	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Child	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
about	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
to	O
me	O
stark	O
naked	O
,	O
about	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
bout	O
four	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
old	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
on	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
stripped	O
my	O
Child	O
,	O
they	O
sat	O
her	O
over	O
a	O
Vault	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
straddled	O
over	O
the	O
Seat	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
*	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
Place	O
called	O
Crown	O
Alley	O
;	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
found	O
the	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
washed	O
her	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Child	O
told	O
her	O
her	O
Name	O
was	O
Cuttle	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
Frock	O
for	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Saffron-Hill	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
it	O
;	O
tho	O
'	O
she	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
Skirt	O
,	O
and	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
in	O
Mrs	O
Peirce	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
Cloaths	O
Woman	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Child	O
.	O
*	O
Ann	O
Pendegrass	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Church	O
,	O
was	O
committed	O
by	O
Mr	O
Alderman	O
Bernard	O
,	O
on	O
Oath	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cuttle	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
stripping	O
her	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
dropping	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
Vault	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
discharged	O
on	O
the	O
Goal	O
delivery	O
.	O
-	O
Mrs	O
Cuttle	O
,	O
does	O
not	O
give	O
Evidence	O
here	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
yet	O
from	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
being	O
washed	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
is	O
sworn	O
by	O
Mrs	O
Stone	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
seem	O
the	O
Child	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vault	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Shop	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
an	O
old	O
Pair	O
of	O
Child	O
's	O
Shoes	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
old	O
Shift	O
,	O
a	O
Flannel	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
Skirt	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Child	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
Necessity	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
wanted	O
Money	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
Care	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
too	O
old	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
bid	O
Six-Pence	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
an	O
old	O
Cloaths	O
W	O
oman	O
;	O
Ann	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
lodged	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
Six-pence	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
Peirce	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
Things	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cuttle	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
Daughter	O
's	O
Cloaths	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
*	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
seven-night	O
,	O
this	O
Girl	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Girl	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
agree	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
Cloaths	O
Woman	O
for	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
these	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
worth	O
but	O
little	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
Mother	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
a	O
few	O
Farthings	O
to	O
buy	O
something	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
believe	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
took	O
Six-pence	O
for	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
*	O
This	O
Witness	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
Oath	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Ann	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cuttle	I-pers
,	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
White	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Custody	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
Eleven	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-Time	O
,	O
my	O
Child	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
stripped	O
;	O
she	O
stripped	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
Child	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
Question	O
;	O
you	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
give	O
any	O
Account	O
of	O
any	O
foreign	O
Matter	O
:	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
stripped	O
this	O
Girl	O
?	O
Stone	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
it	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
the	O
Things	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cuttle	I-pers
down	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
,	O
she	O
stripped	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Things	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
Woman	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
carried	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Philpot	O
,	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
:	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Frock	O
off	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
herself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
off	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Back	O
?	O
Stone	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
off	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
Mrs	O
Peirce	O
's	O
in	O
Grub-Street	O
,	O
three	O
Nights	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Peirce	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
the	O
Frock	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
sometimes	O
to	O
pawn	O
things	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
Mother	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
in	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
Workhouse	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Father	O
is	O
dead	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
263	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Mockridge	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hanwell	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
Deborah	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Day-Time	O
,	O
no	O
Person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silk	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Camblet	O
Gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
Tablecloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Punch-Ladle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Silver	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Deborah	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
.	O
May	O
18	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
.	O
My	O
House	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
the	O
old	O
Hatch	O
at	O
Hanwell	B-place
,	O
just	O
before	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Common	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
yesterday	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
Window-Shutters	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Windows	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
locked	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
three	O
Girls	O
were	O
weeding	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
mentioned	O
the	O
Goods	O
which	O
she	O
lost	O
,	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
done	O
up	O
in	O
two	O
Bundles	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
large	O
Box	O
in	O
a	O
Room	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
we	O
have	O
nothing	O
above	O
Stairs	O
)	O
the	O
Linnen	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Trunk	O
under	O
the	O
Dresser	O
;	O
the	O
Camblet	O
Cloaths	O
were	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
Fashion	O
great	O
Chest	O
in	O
the	O
Chamber	O
;	O
my	O
Son	O
sent	O
me	O
Word	O
that	O
some	O
Body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Things	O
all	O
bundled	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
my	O
Son	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Deb	O
.	O
Wild	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Man	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
Man	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
asked	O
the	O
Man	O
where	O
the	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
?	O
Deb	O
.	O
Wild	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
once	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
ever	O
live	O
in	O
your	O
Town	O
?	O
Deb	O
.	O
Wild	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
Home	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Victuals	O
yesterday	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
Mother	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Key	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
unlock	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
Door	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
Distance	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
over	O
a	O
Hedge	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
)	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
Business	O
she	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
Windows	O
?	O
Henry	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
done	O
up	O
in	O
Appearance	O
as	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
they	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Casement	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
so	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
last	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Bundle	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
Chair	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Bundle	O
on	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
Man	O
was	O
there	O
chopping	O
of	O
Sticks	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
Mrs	O
Wild	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
Bed	O
my	O
Husband	O
had	O
bargained	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
fetched	O
away	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Time	O
appointed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
Deb	O
.	O
Wild	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
but	O
once	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
Turnham-Green	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
lives	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
that	O
goes	O
for	O
her	O
Husband	O
(	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
her	O
Husband	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
bargained	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Brentford	O
.	O
Deb	O
.	O
Wild	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
once	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
at	O
Brentford	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
Acquaintance	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Clitheroe	O
yesterday	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
Custody	O
all	O
Night	O
at	O
a	O
Publick-House	O
at	O
Hanwell	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
here	O
this	O
Morning	O
by	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
a	O
Boy	O
to	O
her	O
Husband	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
264	O
.	O
+	O
Rachael	B-pers
Prick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pidgeon	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
Person	O
,	O
April	O
23	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pidgeon	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Drury-Lane	O
Play-House	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Catherine-street	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Shop	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Dram	O
;	O
I	O
drank	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Glasses	O
of	O
some	O
Sort	O
of	O
strong	O
Liquor	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
Rum	O
,	O
Brandy	O
,	O
or	O
Gin	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
better	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
about	O
ten	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
after	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
her	O
drink	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
Watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
o'Clock	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
Arm	O
round	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
fond	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
Court	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
something	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
hurry	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
to	O
feel	O
for	O
my	O
Watch	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
-	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
wondered	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
so	O
soon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
Person	O
near	O
you	O
?	O
Pidgeon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
neither	O
Man	O
nor	O
Woman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
three	O
other	O
Women	O
,	O
Betty	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
tossing	O
up	O
for	O
Gin	O
?	O
Pidgeon	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
with	O
another	O
Woman	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
with	O
three	O
Women	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
she	O
promised	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
his	O
Watch	O
again	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
allow	O
her	O
a	O
Guinea	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
her	O
Liberty	O
without	O
going	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
Justice	O
Frasier	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
back	O
again	O
till	O
Monday	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
something	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
the	O
Watch	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Lodging	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
Women	O
came	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
myself	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Landlord	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
this	O
Paper	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Viling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
Body	O
knocked	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Times	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
answered	O
,	O
a	O
Friend	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
Parcel	O
for	O
Mr	O
Pidgeon	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Mr	O
Pidgeon	O
expected	O
a	O
Parcel	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
Watch	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Paper	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
through	O
the	O
Key-hole	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
those	O
Women	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
enquire	O
into	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
Care	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
away	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
prevented	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
rather	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
Watch	O
than	O
have	O
been	O
seen	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
White-Fryers	O
fourteen	O
Years	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Velvet	O
Cap	O
Maker	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
New-Market	O
Caps	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
my	O
Bread	O
.	O
The	O
People	O
of	O
our	O
Trade	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
my	O
Behalf	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
do	O
not	O
Care	O
what	O
becomes	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
265	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
of	O
St	B-place
Olave	I-place
,	I-place
Southwark	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
Pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Hose	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
19	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
April	O
23	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Hose	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
ten	O
Pair	O
of	O
others	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
our	O
Boy	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Spouse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
our	O
Shop	O
;	O
(	O
at	O
the	O
Bridge	O
Foot	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
in	O
our	O
Shop	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Yarn	O
Hose	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
8	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
hummed	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Prithee	O
,	O
Girl	O
,	O
go	O
about	O
Business	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
in	O
her	O
Basket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
came	O
these	O
in	O
your	O
Basket	O
;	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
brought	O
nothing	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
carry	O
any	O
Thing	O
out	O
:	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
says	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
She	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
Bundle	O
of	O
rough	O
Hose	O
,	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
;	O
the	O
Boy	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Bundle	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
:	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
through	O
the	O
Postern	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
be	O
so	O
wicked	O
as	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
;	O
you	O
must	O
come	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
Mr	O
Bennet	O
,	O
the	O
Silversmith	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
over	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Basket	O
was	O
over	O
them	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
Tripp	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Master	O
bid	O
me	O
run	O
after	O
that	O
Woman	O
with	O
the	O
Basket	O
over	O
her	O
Shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Hose	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
running	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
her	O
just	O
through	O
the	O
Gate	O
upon	O
London	O
Bridge	O
;	O
my	O
Master	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
ten	O
Pair	O
of	O
Hose	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Hose	O
,	O
I	O
marked	O
them	O
myself	O
.	O
-	O
Bennet	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr	O
Dodson	O
take	O
ten	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
Shop	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
Apron	O
under	O
her	O
Arm	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Stockings	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
an	O
Infant	O
;	O
and	O
have	O
hired	O
her	O
to	O
chair	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
her	O
honest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
266.	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
receiving	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
*	O
,	O
26	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
November	O
26	O
.	O
Of	O
which	O
Felony	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
was	O
last	O
Sessions	O
convicted	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
last	O
April	O
Sessions	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
195	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Record	O
of	O
his	O
Conviction	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
]	O
Josias	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
26	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Chocolate	O
stole	O
from	O
my	O
Shop	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
Information	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
Persons	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
David	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
was	O
last	O
Sessions	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
Fact	O
:	O
I	O
begged	O
the	O
Favour	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
to	O
continue	O
Shields	O
in	O
Custody	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
Evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Receivers	O
of	O
these	O
Goods	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
indulge	O
me	O
in	O
:	O
David	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
was	O
examined	O
before	O
Justice	O
Rickards	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Examination	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Writing	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Cutos	O
)	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
lifted	O
up	O
a	O
Grate	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr	O
Taylor	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
26	O
Pound	O
Weight	O
of	O
Chocolate	O
:	O
-	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
with	O
Relation	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
Evidence	O
here	O
last	O
Sessions	O
:	O
We	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Yorkshire-Grey	O
,	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
staid	O
there	O
while	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
Jane	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
's	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
lived	O
in	O
Cable	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Shorter	O
street	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
abominable	O
Receiver	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
Time	O
)	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
Oh	O
?	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
It	O
comes	O
far	O
enough	O
off	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
a	O
Search	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
Pound	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
18	O
d	O
a	O
Pound	O
was	O
the	O
common	O
Price	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
but	O
a	O
Shilling	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
Companions	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
it	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
they	O
always	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
Pound	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
a	O
proper	O
Place	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
at	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
26	O
s.	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
Shilling	O
a	O
Pound	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
knew	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
deliver	O
the	O
Chocolate	O
in	O
a	O
Hand-Basket	O
to	O
one	O
Isaac	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
she	O
showed	O
me	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
some	O
Part	O
of	O
it	O
melted	O
down	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
melted	O
down	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
stamped	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
that	O
we	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Duty	O
on	O
this	O
Chocolate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
the	O
Chocolate	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
The	O
Excise	O
Duty	O
is	O
18	O
d.	O
per	O
Pound	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
the	O
Chocolate	O
besides	O
is	O
about	O
2	O
s.	O
which	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
is	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
Pound	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
some	O
Time	O
in	O
her	O
House	O
in	O
Cable	O
Street	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
lived	O
there	O
on	O
and	O
off	O
about	O
three	O
Years	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
lived	O
there	O
when	O
these	O
Things	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
brought	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
Month	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
these	O
Goods	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
otherwise	O
than	O
by	O
their	O
being	O
advertised	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
