TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
On	O
FRIDAY	O
January	O
13	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
14	O
,	O
and	O
MONDAY	O
16	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
17th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Robert	B-pers
Westley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1744	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
ROBERT	O
Westley	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WRIGHT	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
ABNEY	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Serjeant	O
URLIN	O
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Newton	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Pickersgill	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sydegraves	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Westbrook	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stromer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Prater	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gillmore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wrenn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hows	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bracket	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Rabbitts	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Tofft	I-pers
.	O
100.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Gaffney	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Casey	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
bays	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
camblet	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Blanchard	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
indictment	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
101	O
,	O
102	O
,	O
103.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
*	O
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
McCoy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Gaffney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
camblet	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
poplin	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
Nov.	O
29th	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
indicted	O
in	O
October	O
Sessions	O
1742	O
,	O
with	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Murder	O
of	O
Patrick	O
Smith	O
,	O
in	O
Chelsea	O
Fields	O
.	O
See	O
Trial	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Torbett	O
,	O
136	O
,	O
p.	O
77.	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
Nov	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Tho	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
McCoy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Patty	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
stole	O
six	O
gowns	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
High	B-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
.	I-place
-	O
Benjamin	B-pers
McCoy	I-pers
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
shelf	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
you	O
then	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
We	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
take	O
what	O
he	O
got	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
shop	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
shop	O
where	O
they	O
sell	O
clothes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
We	O
pawned	O
two	O
for	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
sold	O
one	O
for	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
Talbot	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
ago	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Talbot	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
remember	O
what	O
time	O
o'night	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
or	O
light	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lamp	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
McCoy	O
's	O
name	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
originally	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
was	O
Benjamin	B-pers
McCoy	I-pers
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
name	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
keeps	O
a	O
clothes	O
shop	O
and	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
High	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
-	O
the	O
clothes	O
shop	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
of	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
gowns	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
lay	O
upon	O
one	O
shelf	O
.	O
Talbot	O
.	O
[	O
to	O
Hawkins	O
]	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
positively	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
seven	O
gowns	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
there	O
were	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
many	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
,	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
more	O
or	O
less	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
six	O
.	O
Talbot	O
.	O
Did	O
we	O
commit	O
any	O
other	O
robberies	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Casey	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
innocent	O
.	O
Casey	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
were	O
not	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Benjamin	B-pers
McCoy	I-pers
these	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
are	O
very	O
honest	O
people	O
,	O
he	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
shoes	O
for	O
my	O
wife	O
last	O
July	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
honesty	O
?	O
Travers	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
?	O
Travers	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
for	O
whoring	O
and	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
quarrelling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
addicted	O
to	O
stealing	O
?	O
Travers	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
M'Coy	O
's	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
were	O
very	O
honest	O
industrious	O
people	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
otherways	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
other	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
given	O
to	O
drinking	O
-	O
his	O
father	O
is	O
living	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Brag	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
about	O
12	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
honest	O
and	O
diligent	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
known	O
much	O
of	O
him	O
these	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
All	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
104	O
,	O
105.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Gaffney	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
perriwig	O
value	O
60	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
November	O
29th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Coventry-street	B-place
just	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
perriwig	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop-window	O
November	O
29th	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
after	O
candle-light	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
perriwig	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
fellow	O
who	O
prevented	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
pursuit	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
*	O
,	O
Patty	O
Casey	O
,	O
Tom	O
.	O
Talbot	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
stole	O
a	O
large	O
perriwig	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
barber	O
's	O
shop	O
within	O
a	O
door	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
shop	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
*	O
Hawkins	O
said	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
trial	O
be	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
be	O
committed	O
any	O
other	O
robbery	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
ago	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
6	O
weeks	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
candle-light	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
the	O
wig	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
hand	O
in	O
taking	O
out	O
the	O
wig	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
far	O
off	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
their	O
hands	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
wig	O
out	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
Patty	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
had	O
the	O
wig	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
hussling	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Patty	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
put	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
apron	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
the	O
barber	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
against	O
me	O
and	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
endeavour	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
running	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
directly	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
their	O
lodging	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
Black-Horse	O
in	O
Church-lane	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
wig	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
barber	O
's	O
in	O
Dyot-street	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
wig	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
wig	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
barber	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Penny	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
that	O
barber	O
's	O
?	O
Penny	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
and	O
has	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
barber	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
wig	O
in	O
Talbot	O
's	O
possession	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Both	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
the	O
wig	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
on	O
;	O
none	O
of	O
us	O
had	O
it	O
on	O
above	O
4	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
barber	O
.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
barber	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
us	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
we	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
selling	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
4	O
s.	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
Talbot	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
large	O
wig	O
for	O
a	O
hoop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
a	O
hoop	O
?	O
Talbot	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
a	O
brass	O
ring	O
such	O
as	O
they	O
sell	O
for	O
gold	O
ones	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
wig	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
too	O
big	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believed	O
would	O
not	O
fetch	O
much	O
;	O
was	O
you	O
ever	O
in	O
my	O
company	O
before	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
master	O
baker	O
and	O
lived	O
within	O
5	O
miles	O
of	O
Bath	O
but	O
have	O
had	O
misfortunes	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Talbot	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
his	O
brother	O
and	O
he	O
get	O
their	O
living	O
by	O
gaming	O
and	O
selling	O
brass	O
rings	O
for	O
gold	O
ones	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
106.	O
William	B-pers
Eales	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
113	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
32	O
yards	O
of	O
German	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
of	O
cambrick	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
41	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
48	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
July	O
8	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
and	O
Key	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
porter	O
these	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
1742	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
a	O
truss	O
to	O
him	O
myself	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
a	O
carrier	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
what	O
goods	O
were	O
in	O
that	O
truss	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
memorandum	O
of	O
them	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
that	O
memorandum	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
copy	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
day	O
book	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
deliver	O
them	O
with	O
your	O
own	O
hands	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
hands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
truss	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
ribbons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
five	O
pieces	O
of	O
white	O
Irish	O
linen	O
,	O
113	O
yards	O
;	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
called	O
32	O
yards	O
of	O
German	O
linen	O
;	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
cambrick	O
;	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
these	O
goods	O
stitched	O
up	O
in	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
stitched	O
up	O
in	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
hessen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ordered	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
in	O
Aldersgate-Street	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
directed	O
to	O
Robert	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
of	O
Donnington	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
from	O
a	O
fortnight	O
to	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
,	O
My	O
correspondent	O
wrote	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
might	O
come	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
concerning	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
entered	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
book	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suffer	O
him	O
to	O
scribble	O
in	O
my	O
journal	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
ordered	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
fault	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
directions	O
to	O
sue	O
the	O
person	O
he	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
some	O
farther	O
information	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ferguson	O
's	O
in	O
Barbican	O
.	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ferguson	O
was	O
so	O
honest	O
that	O
he	O
searched	O
all	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
some	O
goods	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
found	O
.	O
-	O
[	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hodges	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
]	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Eales	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
is	O
my	O
brother-in-law	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eales	I-pers
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
bringing	O
any	O
goods	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
packed	O
up	O
?	O
Eales	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
stitched	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
carried	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
do	O
a	O
thing	O
for	O
him	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
was	O
ruined	O
for	O
ever	O
-	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
fire-office	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
badge	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pawn	O
some	O
things	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
ruined	O
for	O
ever	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
cut	O
open	O
the	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
things	O
.	O
-	O
the	O
first	O
things	O
he	O
took	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
were	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
apron	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
them	O
?	O
Eales	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
Barbican	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
it	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Stone	O
-	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
beautiful	O
piece	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
stand	O
to	O
that	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
carried	O
that	O
piece	O
there	O
?	O
Eales	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
had	O
you	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
?	O
Eales	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
guineas	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
many	O
times	O
I	O
went	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
money	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
?	O
Eales	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
-	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
all	O
this	O
money	O
,	O
be	O
it	O
more	O
or	O
less	O
?	O
Eales	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
the	O
things	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
.	O
Eales	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
entrusted	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
my	O
sister	O
is	O
guilty	O
of	O
perjury	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
scorn	O
to	O
tell	O
a	O
lie	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
to	O
die	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
guinea	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
than	O
only	O
to	O
prove	O
her	O
perjured	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cadwallader	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ferguson	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eales	I-pers
brought	O
all	O
these	O
goods	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
money	O
had	O
she	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Cadwallader	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
she	O
had	O
nine	O
pound	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Eales	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Eales	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Ivy-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
Where	O
are	O
your	O
witnesses	O
,	O
you	O
said	O
you	O
would	O
prove	O
this	O
woman	O
perjured	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
these	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
inn	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
Robinson	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
week	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Drury	O
's	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
house	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
week	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
she	O
refused	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
denied	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
speak	O
with	O
as	O
much	O
truth	O
and	O
justice	O
as	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
god	O
of	O
heaven	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
converted	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
use	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Eales	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
all	O
by	O
his	O
desire	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
whole	O
money	O
if	O
there	O
's	O
belief	O
in	O
a	O
Christian	O
.	O
Prison	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
wicked	O
liar	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
tell	O
such	O
a	O
story	O
you	O
lying	O
wicked	O
jade	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
107.	O
John	B-pers
Holbrook	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Field	I-place
's	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cover	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
22	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanhope	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
eating-house	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
New-street	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Quillet	O
at	O
the	O
Ring	O
and	O
Pearl	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
December	O
22	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Quillet	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
serve	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Quillet	I-pers
.	O
December	O
22	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
showed	O
it	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
aunt	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
fetch	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
in	O
about	O
5	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
aunt	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
without	O
his	O
aunt	O
was	O
present	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
fetch	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
minutes	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
aunt	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
that	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
aunt	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
a	O
porter	O
and	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Bear	O
and	O
Ragged-staff	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
aunt	O
kept	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
lad	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
belive	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
of	O
you	O
to	O
enquire	O
into	O
people	O
's	O
characters	O
before	O
you	O
buy	O
things	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
does	O
not	O
satisfy	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
your	O
aunt	O
and	O
know	O
from	O
her	O
own	O
mouth	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
her	O
's	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
where	O
his	O
aunt	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Stanhope	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
-	O
it	O
weighs	O
7	O
ounces	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
lid	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
ever	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
liberty	O
since	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
Quillet	O
.	O
It	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
custody	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
108.	O
John	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
camblet	O
cloak	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
December	O
18	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
before	O
Christmas-day	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
in	O
New-street	B-place
by	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
many	O
there	O
were	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
knocked	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
their	O
fists	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
men	O
or	O
women	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
blow	O
light	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
either	O
upon	O
my	O
head	O
or	O
shoulders	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
cloak	O
,	O
I	O
begged	O
of	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
you	O
going	O
then	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pensioner	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
workhouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
my	O
cloak	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
work-house	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
lost	O
cloak	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
my	O
cloak	O
again	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
do	O
me	O
no	O
harm	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
cloaks	O
in	O
your	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
do	O
her	O
any	O
harm	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
night	O
before	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Patty	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
get	O
money	O
or	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
thieving	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
robbed	O
this	O
woman	O
of	O
a	O
cloak	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
did	O
you	O
set	O
out	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
.	O
Patty	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
up	O
that	O
night	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Roundhouse	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
New	O
street	O
very	O
near	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
Read	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
,	O
Read	O
knocked	O
her	O
down	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
cloak	O
off	O
her	O
shoulders	O
,	O
the	O
cloak	O
was	O
very	O
dirty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
did	O
you	O
knock	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
hit	O
her	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
woman	O
that	O
he	O
knocked	O
down	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
cloak	O
again	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
cloak	O
to	O
our	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Margaret	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
cloak	O
away	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
-	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
cloak	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
lived	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
before	O
Christmas	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Hawkins	O
offered	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
cloak	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
got	O
it	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
by	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
the	O
cloak	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Casey	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
laid	O
the	O
cloak	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
box	O
.	O
-	O
Both	O
of	O
them	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
me	O
-	O
they	O
offered	O
it	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
farthing	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Casey	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Atney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
for	O
farther	O
examination	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
him	O
there	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
more	O
than	O
Hawkins	O
could	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
produce	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
's	O
cloak	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Bess	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
in	O
Cross-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
particular	O
enquiry	O
made	O
into	O
this	O
before	O
?	O
Alney	O
.	O
Hawkins	O
had	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
evidence	O
before	O
that	O
and	O
confessed	O
this	O
particular	O
fact	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
knew	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
Atney	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
were	O
,	O
Casey	O
went	O
in	O
first	O
and	O
I	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
my	O
mother	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
friends	O
are	O
gone	O
to	O
her	O
burial	O
.	O
-	O
She	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
buried	O
to	O
day	O
at	O
Clermont	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Richardson	O
declared	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
her	O
cloak	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
cloak	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
and	O
begged	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
cloak	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
a	O
complete	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Richardson	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
really	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
before	O
you	O
lost	O
the	O
cloak	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
did	O
fall	O
.	O
The	O
putting	O
in	O
fear	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
.	O
+	O
109	O
,	O
110.	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
*	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Appleby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Cobler	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
woollen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Moses	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
17	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
an	O
accomplice	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
evidence	O
against	O
Richard	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
tried	O
in	O
June	O
sessions	O
;	O
see	O
trial	O
335	O
,	O
page	O
203	O
.	O
And	O
also	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
tried	O
in	O
September	O
sessions	O
;	O
see	O
trial	O
417	O
,	O
and	O
418.	O
page	O
242.	O
who	O
were	O
all	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
James	B-pers
Fennel	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Taylor	O
,	O
near	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
;	O
and	O
last	O
sessions	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
transportation	O
for	O
14	O
years	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
nine	O
my	O
maid	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
me	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
shop	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
believed	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
some	O
caps	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
to	O
two	O
double-seamed	O
worsted	O
caps	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
by	O
my	O
servant	O
-	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
not	O
shut	O
up	O
then	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
fastened	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
shutters	O
were	O
not	O
put	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
from	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
together	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
rob	O
any	O
body	O
we	O
could	O
,	O
or	O
get	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
shop	O
John	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
broke	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
name	O
)	O
he	O
broke	O
one	O
pane	O
first	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
at	O
the	O
show-glass	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
broke	O
another	O
with	O
design	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
some	O
worsted	O
caps	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
show	O
glass	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
glass	O
between	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
took	O
any	O
caps	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
look	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
window	O
's	O
being	O
broke	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
wife	O
whittled	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
presently	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
caps	O
you	O
had	O
there	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
There	O
might	O
be	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
dozen	O
lying	O
there	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
lose	O
more	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
out	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
broke	O
it	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
below	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
something	O
break	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
caught	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
caps	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
hand	O
did	O
you	O
catch	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Burrough	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
caps	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
him	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
blue	O
gray	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
then	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
dout	O
the	O
candle	O
to	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
hold	O
of	O
any	O
more	O
caps	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
caps	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
caps	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
drawn	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
caps	O
drawn	O
through	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
servant	O
found	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
how	O
many	O
they	O
got	O
before	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
places	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
was	O
there	O
between	O
the	O
panes	O
that	O
were	O
broke	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
pane	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
showglass	O
with	O
some	O
silver	O
ribbons	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
broke	O
one	O
pane	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
at	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
glass	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
run	O
away	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
run	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
door	O
to	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
open	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
but	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
-	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
Thorne	O
was	O
immediately	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Shippey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cooper	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Hoop	O
and	O
Adze	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
window	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
do	O
?	O
Shippey	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
thought	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
tout	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
hinder	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
design	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
blue	O
coat	O
,	O
[	O
Burroughs	O
]	O
Jack	O
,	O
shall	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
or	O
can	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
dream	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
particular	O
remark	O
of	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
the	O
Hoop	O
and	O
Adze	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
-	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
clock	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
.	O
Burroughs	O
had	O
his	O
hat	O
flapping	O
over	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
looked	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
their	O
gin	O
,	O
Burroughs	O
gave	O
the	O
accomplice	O
(	O
Thorne	O
)	O
three	O
half-pence	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
Appleby	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
gin	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
he	O
held	O
down	O
his	O
head	O
to	O
spit	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
stooped	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
complaining	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
being	O
worn	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
standing	O
pretty	O
near	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
somebody	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
made	O
him	O
so	O
cold	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
went	O
as	O
near	O
the	O
ground	O
as	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
cold	O
too	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
these	O
three	O
fellows	O
look	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
break	O
their	O
necks	O
in	O
going	O
to	O
Paddington	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Spriggs	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
rob	O
somebody	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
they	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
rob	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Spriggs	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
my	O
heart	O
is	O
ready	O
to	O
burst	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
against	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
window	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
presently	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
run	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
keep	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
Shippey	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
sear	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
quick	O
in	O
catching	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
,	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Hoop	O
and	O
Adze	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
ashamed	O
to	O
rob	O
people	O
who	O
work	O
hard	O
for	O
their	O
living	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
rob	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
We	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
of	O
Long	O
Charles	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Charles	B-pers
Reddington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
thief-taker	O
,	O
and	O
conversant	O
with	O
such	O
sort	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
we	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
affair	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Long	O
Charles	O
,	O
and	O
Billy	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
thief-takers	O
,	O
brought	O
that	O
man	O
to	O
swear	O
against	O
us	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cammock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Travers	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
December	O
30th	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
follows	O
a	O
dust	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Travers	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
for	O
the	O
dust	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
spoon	O
which	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Dec.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
spoon	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Parson	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
spoon	O
has	O
a	O
crest	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
look	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
property	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
one	O
Miller	O
a	O
master	O
brick-maker	O
at	O
the	O
Pinner	O
of	O
Wakefield	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
come	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
his	O
master	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Gray's-Inn-Gate	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
satisfaction	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
spoon	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
stopt	O
the	O
spoon	O
and	O
advertised	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
spoon	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
told	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
dust	O
cart	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
,	O
the	O
brickmaker	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
refused	O
money	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
dust	O
cart	O
.	O
-	O
He	O
does	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
.	O
he	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
trouncer	O
that	O
follows	O
the	O
dust	O
carts	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
has	O
whipped	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
yard	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
112.	O
William	B-pers
Ricketts	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dimitty	O
gown	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
,	O
January	O
1st	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Stiles	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
gown	O
off	O
a	O
line	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Macklecan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
supper	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Stiles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
would	O
persuade	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
listened	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
so	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
frighten	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
landing	O
place	O
I	O
threw	O
the	O
candle	O
and	O
candlestick	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
threw	O
a	O
brush	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
tumbled	O
over	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
fellow	O
with	O
him	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
sooner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
knocked	O
o	O
'	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
likely	O
such	O
a	O
boy	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
Man	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
afraid	O
-	O
[	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
lad	O
about	O
15	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
's	O
house	O
over-against	O
Mr.	O
Stiles	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
white	O
lie	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
gown	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
neither	O
dry	O
nor	O
wet	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
friends	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
transported	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
place	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
113.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
tin	O
canisters	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
bohea	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
pound	O
of	O
snuff	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
January	O
4th	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
joining	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
somebody	O
had	O
been	O
playing	O
the	O
rogue	O
,	O
not	O
suspecting	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
thieves	O
,	O
but	O
looking	O
down	O
Plumber's-Court	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
woman	O
or	O
mistress	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
open	O
my	O
sash-window	O
?	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
canister	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
dropped	O
another	O
canister	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bladder	O
of	O
about	O
4	O
pound	O
of	O
snuff	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
-	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Robinson	O
keeps	O
a	O
coffee-house	O
in	O
Plumber	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
cry	O
out	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
canisters	O
and	O
the	O
snuff	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
-	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Sherrard	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
surgeon	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
leg	O
dressed	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
drop	O
these	O
canisters	O
,	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
run	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
She	O
might	O
find	O
them	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
throw	O
the	O
sash	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
for	O
corporal	O
punishment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
114.	O
Simon	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
*	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Meager	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
3	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
2	O
stuff	O
gowns	O
,	O
12	O
caps	O
,	O
12	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
12	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
hood	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
2	O
callimanco	O
peticoats	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cambric	O
ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
amounting	O
to	O
about	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	B-pers
Meager	I-pers
,	O
November	O
15th	O
.	O
And	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
has	O
made	O
another	O
information	O
against	O
Bailey	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fawler	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
at	O
Walthamslow	O
.	O
115.	O
Mary	B-pers
Disson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stole	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Meager	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Blue-anchor	B-place
Alley	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
White-cross	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
about	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
goods	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Meager	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
4	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
door	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
street-door	O
quite	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
cut	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
glass	O
taken	O
out	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
had	O
one	O
rag	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
+	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Bailey	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stocking-weaver	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Bailey	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
months	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Meager	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Blue-anchor	O
,	O
in	O
White-cross	O
Street	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
yard	O
before	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
outer	O
gate	O
was	O
shut	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
lifted	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
leaned	O
over	O
and	O
unbolted	O
the	O
gate	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
two	O
panes	O
of	O
glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wyenn	O
shop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Grid	O
Iron	O
,	O
in	O
White-cross	O
Street	O
-	O
we	O
took	O
first	O
,	O
below	O
,	O
a	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
pankin	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
left	O
them	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lent	O
us	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
Exise-Office	O
)	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
Meager	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
opened	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
five	O
gowns	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
peticoats	O
,	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
aprons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
the	O
Pri	O
soner	O
repeated	O
the	O
things	O
pretty	O
exact	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
]	O
we	O
tied	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
took	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
55	O
s.	O
-	O
she	O
paid	O
us	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Silver	O
.	O
+	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
upon	O
two	O
indictments	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
Sept	O
.	O
Sessions	O
and	O
acquitted	O
;	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Pass	I-pers
,	O
lately	O
executed	O
,	O
was	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
See	O
Trials	O
381	O
,	O
382	O
,	O
383.	O
p.	O
228	O
,	O
229	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
so	O
little	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Clay	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
those	O
that	O
buy	O
these	O
things	O
always	O
buy	O
good	O
bargains	O
-	O
we	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
between	O
us	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mrs.	O
Wilson	O
ask	O
you	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
questions	O
about	O
them	O
?	O
Clay	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
any	O
questions	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
knew	O
how	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
-	O
we	O
told	O
her	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
more	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
take	O
the	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
can	O
find	O
-	O
she	O
has	O
often	O
bought	O
things	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
with	O
you	O
when	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
?	O
Clay	O
.	O
You	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
we	O
bought	O
a	O
half-penny-worth	O
of	O
small	O
beer	O
at	O
the	O
chandlers	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
bring	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
prove	O
what	O
you	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
?	O
Clay	O
.	O
How	O
should	O
I	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
nobody	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Wilson	O
who	O
bought	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
us	O
knows	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Meager	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
get	O
knowledge	O
of	O
this	O
Clay	O
?	O
Meager	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
out	O
an	O
advertisement	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
Clay	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
form	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
-	O
The	O
thief	O
catchers	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
in	O
one	O
robbery	O
.	O
Clay	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Osman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gardener	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
Low-layton	O
these	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Bailey	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Low-layton	O
,	O
his	O
character	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hollingsworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
I	O
worked	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
breaking	O
the	O
pipe-maker	O
's	O
ouse	O
-	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
He	O
served	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
apprentice	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
justly	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
in	O
Essex	O
and	O
London	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
served	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
a	O
brother-in-law	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
turned	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nettleford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighterman	O
,	O
I	O
pressed	O
Simon	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Endeavour	O
Tender	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Princess	O
Royal	O
at	O
the	O
Nore	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
has	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
5	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
16	O
years	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Burkitt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Purvey	I-pers
some	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
witnesses	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
him	O
within	O
these	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
About	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
she	O
stopt	O
it	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
-	O
Hartley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Archendel	O
,	O
who	O
deals	O
in	O
hard	O
metal	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
an	O
errand	O
boy	O
robbed	O
us	O
and	O
carried	O
goods	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
she	O
stopped	O
them	O
and	O
informed	O
us	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cax	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
alehouse	O
by	O
Cow-cross	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
pewter	O
pots	O
one	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
stepped	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
known	O
the	O
thieves	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
seven	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
-	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
paper-maker	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
buy	O
rags	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
infancy	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
her	O
god-father	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Burrel	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
just	O
woman	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
buy	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
houshold	O
goods	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
+	O
116.	O
Joseph	B-pers
*	I-pers
Isaacs	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
M'Coy	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
pot	O
,	O
lamp	O
and	O
stand	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
large	O
two	O
handled	O
silver	O
cup	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
six	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
,	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
a	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
November	O
6th	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
December	O
sessions	O
1742.	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
and	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Cordosa	I-pers
.	O
See	O
trials	O
41	O
,	O
42	O
and	O
43	O
.	O
Page	O
30	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
and	O
accomplice	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Jude	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Solomon	B-pers
Athorne	I-pers
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
Nov.	O
9th	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
tried	O
Decem	O
.	O
12th	O
in	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
convicted	O
,	O
but	O
M'Coy	O
was	O
not	O
committed	O
till	O
Decem	O
.	O
14th	O
.	O
Trial	O
74	O
,	O
75	O
,	O
and	O
76	O
.	O
Page	O
30.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
White	B-place
's	I-place
Alley	I-place
in	I-place
Little	I-place
Moorfields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
panes	O
of	O
glass	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
casement	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
inside	O
shutters	O
were	O
burst	O
open	O
,	O
they	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
corner	O
cupboard	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
panes	O
of	O
glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
casement	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
opened	O
the	O
casement	O
and	O
pushed	O
the	O
shutters	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
casement	O
was	O
so	O
narrow	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
without	O
taking	O
off	O
my	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
held	O
them	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
handed	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
plate	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
corner	O
cupboard	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
we	O
sold	O
the	O
plate	O
to	O
one	O
Akares	O
a	O
Jew	O
for	O
five	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
for	O
four	O
shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Wilson	O
was	O
tried	O
with	O
Simon	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
in	O
the	O
preceding	O
trial	O
as	O
an	O
aecessary	O
]	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
equally	O
divided	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
discovery	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
Clay	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
then	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
a	O
particular	O
account	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
do	O
but	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
Clay	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Clay	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
this	O
to	O
save	O
your	O
own	O
life	O
and	O
take	O
away	O
mine	O
,	O
pray	O
my	O
Lord	O
enquire	O
into	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Clay	O
.	O
Your	O
character	O
is	O
like	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
proved	O
myself	O
a	O
rogue	O
and	O
so	O
have	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
were	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Cordosa	O
and	O
Robinson	O
,	O
so	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
brag	O
of	O
your	O
honesty	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
[	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
]	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
after	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
Dick	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Jack	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
committed	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Clay	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
threw	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
upon	O
Paine	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
miller	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
this	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
The	O
beginning	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
November	O
?	O
Balley	O
.	O
The	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
-	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
laughed	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
mistaken	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
at	O
ten	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
was	O
this	O
said	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
sixth	O
day	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
discovery	O
of	O
this	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
bragging	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
Jack	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
had	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sober	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
such	O
wicked	O
men	O
as	O
these	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
No	O
farther	O
than	O
by	O
drinking	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
else	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Nobody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
Mrs.	O
Wilson	O
there	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
No	O
-	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
men	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Newgate	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
week	O
and	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
was	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
that	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
either	O
Tuesday	O
or	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Clay	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
night	O
that	O
we	O
committed	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Ward	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Sunday	O
November	O
6th	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
England	O
till	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
and	O
other	O
Jews	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
.	O
Is	O
not	O
this	O
your	O
Sabbath	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
hold	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
lawful	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
on	O
your	O
Sabbath	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
attend	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
upon	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
arrived	O
at	O
Amsterdam	O
the	O
1st	O
or	O
2d	O
of	O
Oct.	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
Not	O
long	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
by	O
seeing	O
him	O
in	O
England	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
-	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
business	O
.	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
very	O
well	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
leather	O
breeches	O
to	O
sell	O
in	O
Holland	O
-	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
Hague	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
passport	O
from	O
the	O
Ambassador	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
the	O
packet	O
boat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
arrive	O
here	O
from	O
the	O
Hague	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
at	O
night	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
to	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
Old	O
Stile	O
or	O
New	O
Stile	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
English	O
reckoning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Old	O
Stile	O
from	O
the	O
New	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
is	O
11	O
days	O
difference	O
-	O
we	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Hague	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
we	O
were	O
10	O
days	O
in	O
coming	O
from	O
Holland	O
to	O
England	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sea-sick	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
's	O
to	O
lodge	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lodged	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
sick	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
8	O
s.	O
-	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
any	O
body	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
visit	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
sick	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
visited	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
in	O
town	O
on	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
town	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
then	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
here	O
then	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
child	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Lyon	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
14th	O
day	O
of	O
last	O
Nov.	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
sick	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
bargain	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
stay	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
from	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
'till	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
Monday	O
and	O
stayed	O
'till	O
Sunday	O
following	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Colchester	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
9th	O
or	O
10th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
Old	O
Stile	O
or	O
New	O
Stile	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
speak	O
according	O
to	O
our	O
computation	O
?	O
Isaac	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
-	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Lyon	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
somebody	O
sick	O
with	O
him	O
from	O
Holland	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
eat	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
nothing	O
else	O
but	O
sea-sick	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
fowl	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
half	O
the	O
fowl	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
this	O
sick	O
person	O
?	O
Isaac	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
McCoy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
?	O
Isaac	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
else	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
English	O
camp	O
in	O
the	O
army	O
in	O
Flanders	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Dettingen	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
King	O
George	O
very	O
often	O
there	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
King	O
George	O
and	O
other	O
Kings	O
too	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
?	O
Jacob	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
speak	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Holland	O
to	O
stock	O
myself	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
rum	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
coffee-house	O
at	O
Brussels	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Jacob	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
the	O
9th	O
or	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
Holland	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
else	O
?	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
England	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
desire	O
was	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
their	O
quarters	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
when	O
your	O
wife	O
received	O
the	O
letter	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
Brussels	O
-	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
letter	O
the	O
10th	O
or	O
11th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
or	O
Wednesday	O
-	O
we	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
stile	O
of	O
the	O
English	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Navarro	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
for	O
debt	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
came	O
in	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
Abraham	B-pers
Pass	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
hanged	O
about	O
two	O
sessions	O
ago	O
-	O
Clay	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
for	O
robbing	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Abraham	B-pers
Pass	I-pers
did	O
peach	O
Dick	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
and	O
this	O
Clay	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
Jews	O
before	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
cleared	O
by	O
the	O
act	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
fellow	O
in	O
Sun-Street	O
,	O
by	O
Bishop-Gate-Street	O
,	O
and	O
Clay	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
50	O
of	O
was	O
hanged	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
's	O
time	O
.	O
Clay	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Custom	O
house	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
tide	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
the	O
husband	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
come	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
what	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
said	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Jew	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
information	O
good	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
Clay	O
about	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
hard	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
information	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Nov.	O
last	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
wife	O
under	O
her	O
misfortunes	O
.	O
Clay	O
.	O
This	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
saw	O
McCoy	O
and	O
I	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
you	O
there	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Clay	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
your	O
wife	O
bought	O
stolen	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
your	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Custom-House	O
officer	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
thieving	O
with	O
-	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
+	O
117.	O
Anne	B-pers
Sonee	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
velvet	O
hood	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
damask	O
shoes	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
clogs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
three	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
cambrick	O
mobs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
cambrick	O
head	O
clothes	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cambrick	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
pockets	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
salver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
10th	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawer	O
and	O
trunk	O
,	O
in	O
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
Lamb	B-place
's	I-place
Conduit	I-place
Passage	I-place
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
t	O
o	O
the	O
House	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
some	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
under	O
her	O
clothes	O
-	O
I	O
purchased	O
these	O
things	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
;	O
but	O
since	O
I	O
am	O
grown	O
deaf	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
-	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
broke	O
open	O
4	O
locks	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
whether	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
what	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
unfortunately	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
daughter	O
was	O
accused	O
with	O
taking	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
desire	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
her	O
coats	O
and	O
apron	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
untied	O
her	O
petticoats	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
fright	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Reynolds	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
at	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
desire	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
a	O
lock	O
upon	O
my	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
things	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
118.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cawdell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pink	O
coloured	O
silk	O
damask	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
white	O
silk	O
damask	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
sattin	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
blue	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
flowered	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
some	O
linen	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
a	O
velvet	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
childrens	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Dec.	O
12th	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missed	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Corbet	O
.	O
My	O
gowns	O
were	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
children	O
's	O
clothes	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lay	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
something	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
gowns	O
last	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
dress	O
myself	O
much	O
in	O
winter	O
time	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
when	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
?	O
Corbet	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
them	O
?	O
Charles	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
talk	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
them	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
closet	O
above	O
stairs	O
-	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
?	O
Charles	B-pers
Corbet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
by	O
my	O
advertisement	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
offered	O
five	O
guineas	O
reward	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
pledged	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
;	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
had	O
given	O
out	O
advertisements	O
by	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
gowns	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
six	O
hours	O
before	O
I	O
lent	O
any	O
money	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
suffered	O
very	O
severely	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
3	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
hard	O
to	O
lose	O
that	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
offered	O
a	O
reward	O
of	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
paid	O
that	O
.	O
Corbet	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
ready	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
very	O
readily	O
paid	O
the	O
five	O
guineas	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
119.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Clavey	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
27	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Clavey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
is	O
an	O
accomplice	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
a	O
footman	O
of	O
mine	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
several	O
goods	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
in	O
particular	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
this	O
first	O
?	O
Clavey	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
found	O
?	O
Clavey	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
Clavey	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
Clavey	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
my	O
mark	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
marked	O
in	O
three	O
places	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
?	O
Clavey	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
an	O
accomplice	O
with	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
like	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
:	O
upon	O
this	O
information	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
apprentice	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
and	O
enquire	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
pawned	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
very	O
handsomly	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
directly	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
notorious	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
oath	O
whether	O
I	O
ever	O
pawned	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
that	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Liscomb	O
Price	O
.	O
On	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
sent	O
his	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
pawned	O
any	O
linen	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
company	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
then	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Christmas	O
week	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
acquaint	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parcel	O
entered	O
in	O
my	O
book	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Parker	O
;	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pledged	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
remnant	O
of	O
a	O
coarse	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
apprehended	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
fag	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
by	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
satisfy	O
himself	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
looked	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
some	O
marks	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
pledged	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
pledged	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
man	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
watch	O
of	O
me	O
within	O
these	O
twelve	O
months	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
pawned	O
the	O
things	O
about	O
five	O
months	O
ago	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
's	O
servant	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
them	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
some	O
service	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
try	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
pawned	O
some	O
things	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
there	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
this	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
.	O
Clavey	O
.	O
There	O
's	O
another	O
material	O
witness	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
sent	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
frequently	O
about	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Clavey	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
frequently	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
oftner	O
than	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
witness	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
's	O
man	O
William	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
he	O
can	O
clear	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
choose	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
sworn	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
obliged	O
to	O
answer	O
any	O
questions	O
that	O
might	O
tend	O
to	O
accuse	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
paused	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
consented	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
nine	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
goods	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
of	O
them	O
here	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Clavey	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
some	O
goods	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
prove	O
when	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
goods	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Randall	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
bill	O
of	O
parcels	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
]	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
charged	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
ago	O
since	O
you	O
bought	O
that	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
?	O
Randall	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
it	O
of	O
?	O
Randall	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hodgkins	O
the	O
youngest	O
apprentice	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
afford	O
to	O
sell	O
this	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
120.	O
William	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Clavey	I-pers
,	O
December	O
21st	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Clavey	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
linen	O
for	O
a	O
customer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
first	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
cut	O
pile	O
as	O
we	O
call	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
there	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
this	O
remnant	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
10	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
do	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
measure	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
eight	O
yards	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
quantity	O
not	O
sufficient	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
pile	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
a	O
whole	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
compare	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
remnant	O
I	O
had	O
looked	O
upon	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
rebuked	O
my	O
man	O
for	O
carelessness	O
in	O
not	O
puting	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
paper	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
)	O
this	O
being	O
pretty	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
no	O
shoplifter	O
could	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
by	O
any	O
stratagem	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
my	O
suspicion	O
rested	O
upon	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
enquiry	O
among	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
whether	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
mislaid	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
is	O
absolutely	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
satisfied	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
middle	O
apprentice	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
impatient	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
find	O
it	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
suspicion	O
rested	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
thorough	O
search	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
under	O
some	O
coolers	O
,	O
or	O
brewing	O
vessels	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
enquired	O
after	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
(	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
fully	O
satisfied	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
thief	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
)	O
and	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
I	O
planted	O
my	O
apprentice	O
at	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
eye	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
he	O
could	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
the	O
piece	O
was	O
rolled	O
up	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
square	O
form	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
and	O
moved	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
my	O
apprentice	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
his	O
shoes	O
might	O
crack	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
moved	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
seen	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
he	O
will	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Jupe	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
try	O
if	O
we	O
can	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
soul	O
linen	O
about	O
him	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
all	O
this	O
linen	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
suspicion	O
that	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
rogue	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
making	O
an	O
enquiry	O
after	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
that	O
is	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
day	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
hide	O
it	O
in	O
this	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
hid	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
fellow	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
consummate	O
impudence	O
to	O
deny	O
this	O
,	O
for	O
Ralph	O
has	O
seen	O
you	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
friend	O
interposed	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
confess	O
the	O
thing	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
your	O
master	O
will	O
forgive	O
you	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Will	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
now	O
produce	O
it	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
thorough	O
search	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
find	O
it	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
you	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
By	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
Constable	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
whimper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
a	O
prickle	O
of	O
straw	O
,	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
flat	O
form	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
coolers	O
then	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
the	O
more	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
tardy	O
before	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
very	O
hard	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
sent	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
wronged	O
me	O
or	O
injured	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
clothes	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
old	O
frock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
bundle	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Clavey	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
had	O
injured	O
me	O
or	O
robbed	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
word	O
rob	O
?	O
Clavey	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
safely	O
say	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
word	O
rob	O
.	O
-	O
Jupe	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
's	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
business	O
with	O
him	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
compting-house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
making	O
a	O
discovery	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
give	O
directions	O
to	O
his	O
servant	O
to	O
conceal	O
himself	O
and	O
watch	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
the	O
apprentice	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
tubs	O
or	O
coolers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
some	O
clothes	O
from	O
under	O
them	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
some	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
conveyed	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
reason	O
he	O
gave	O
his	O
master	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
candle	O
to	O
the	O
lettice	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
sent	O
his	O
servant	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
rolling	O
up	O
some	O
soul	O
linen	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
up	O
his	O
shirts	O
or	O
linen	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
rogue	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
linen	O
that	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
tubs	O
or	O
coolers	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
said	O
tubs	O
or	O
coolers	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
,	O
we	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
removed	O
it	O
within	O
these	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
afterwards	O
somebody	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
send	O
you	O
to	O
Newgate	O
as	O
sure	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
alive	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
prickle	O
or	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
straw	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
shape	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
livery	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
cried	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
his	O
master	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
wronged	O
him	O
before	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
time	O
that	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
,	O
was	O
this	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
mentions	O
.	O
-	O
Jupe	O
.	O
The	O
very	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Hodgkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
Irish	O
pile	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
Irish	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
endeavour	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
orders	O
I	O
watched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
between	O
two	O
coolers	O
or	O
under	O
the	O
coolers	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
look	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
removed	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
's	O
order	O
to	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
knives	O
to	O
clean	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
cleaned	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
of	O
them	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
coolers	O
and	O
lifted	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
and	O
half	O
out	O
)	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
-	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
long	O
form	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
tied	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
this	O
square	O
form	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
afterwards	O
and	O
stood	O
upon	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
candle	O
through	O
the	O
lettice	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
nor	O
I	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
begged	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
to	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
spoke	O
then	O
?	O
Hodgkins	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
words	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Clavey	O
to	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
whether	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
entrusted	O
with	O
money	O
from	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
to	O
another	O
?	O
Clavey	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
true	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
entrusted	O
him	O
with	O
money	O
unless	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
porter	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
parcel	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
trusted	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
portmanteau	O
and	O
his	O
money	O
?	O
Clavey	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
travelling	O
the	O
country	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
as	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
4	O
or	O
500	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
apprehend	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
trusting	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Greenly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sadler	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
sadler	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
last	O
July	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
7	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
honestly	O
and	O
justly	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
wrong	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
opportunities	O
of	O
wronging	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Willoughby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
years	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Greenly	O
did	O
business	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
carry	O
goods	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
121.	O
James	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
4th	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Dec.	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
me	O
this	O
spoon	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
crest	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
suspicion	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
light	O
account	O
,	O
such	O
