TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
19th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Eighth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1745	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
HENRY	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
LEE	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
REYNOLDS	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
James	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Mascall	I-pers
John	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
William	B-pers
Lapper	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
John	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hyder	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Pyke	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
William	B-pers
Vultjohn	I-pers
William	O
Abram	O
*	O
Marine	O
Ingram	O
served	O
on	O
the	O
Jury	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Abram	I-pers
who	O
was	O
indisposed	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Kilpin	I-pers
Stephen	B-pers
Race	I-pers
.	O
364	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Braningham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stepney	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
ear	O
rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Braningham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
Oct.	O
1	O
st	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Braningham	I-pers
.	O
My	O
wife	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
work-house	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
clothed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
)	O
which	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
one	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
snuff-box	O
to	O
one	O
Greg	O
in	O
Barnaby	O
street	O
,	O
Southwark	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
rings	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
to	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
keepers	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
work-house	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
owed	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
half-pence	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
one	O
was	O
sold	O
for	O
19	O
shillings	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
she	O
had	O
tied	O
the	O
things	O
up	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coachman	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Reilly	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
snuff-box	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
knows	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
365	O
.	O
+	O
Hannah	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Sept.	O
24	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
Inn	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
tap-house	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
some	O
lemons	O
,	O
the	O
mug	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
with	O
my	O
man	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Blue	O
Balls	O
in	O
Barbican	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
it	O
Mr.	O
Edwards	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
cup	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
in	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
afterwards	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
-	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
demand	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
it	O
then	O
.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Beaumont	O
's	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
stole	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
if	O
Mrs.	O
Beaumont	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
her	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
better	O
on	O
her	O
side	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Beaumont	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Blue	O
Balls	O
in	O
Barbican	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
to	O
whom	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
there	O
for	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
.	O
Beanmont	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
366.	O
Mary	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
muslin	O
hood	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Sep.	O
14	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Mister	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
chareing	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
lodger	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
lodger	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
gown	O
for	O
six	O
shillings	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hutchins	O
.	O
Hutchins	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
often	O
brought	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
gown	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
bid	O
her	O
bring	O
her	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whether	O
the	O
gown	O
was	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
six	O
shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
367.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Portugal	O
gold	O
coin	O
,	O
36	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
24	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
hostler	O
at	O
the	O
White	B-place
Bear	I-place
Inn	I-place
in	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
under	O
hostler	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
with	O
29	O
pound	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
box	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Grubst-reet	O
;	O
a	O
place	O
he	O
sometimes	O
went	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
14	O
guineas	O
from	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
garters	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
haylost	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
with	O
a	O
stable	O
fork	O
tire	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
29	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
discharged	O
him	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
chamber	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
lie	O
with	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
hear	O
people	O
knock	O
.	O
Lyonel	O
Daeth	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
29	O
l.	O
from	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
14	O
guineas	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
garters	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
36	O
s.	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
he	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Ireland	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
give	O
me	O
2	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
but	O
I	O
forgot	O
that	O
Daeth	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
privateer	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bressingham	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
hired	O
servant	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
to	O
me	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
because	O
my	O
place	O
was	O
too	O
hard	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
368.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
,	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
shirts	O
and	O
shifts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
sundry	O
persons	O
in	O
the	O
workhouse	O
of	O
that	O
parish	O
,	O
Sept.	O
24	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
[	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
workhouse	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
John	O
,	O
Hackney	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
work-house	O
.	O
These	O
goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
work-house	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
Castle	O
street	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
broke	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
about	O
26	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
and	O
able	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
but	O
does	O
not	O
love	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
says	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
shall	O
maintain	O
her	O
without	O
working	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
senses	O
sometimes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
hanged	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
workhouse	O
has	O
cut	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
.	O
Fletcher	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
cut	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
She	O
can	O
sham	O
mad	O
when	O
she	O
pleases	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
mad	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
ever	O
attempt	O
to	O
hang	O
herself	O
?	O
Fletcher	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
when	O
we	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
cart	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
put	O
a	O
string	O
about	O
her	O
neck	O
sometimes	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
us	O
believe	O
she	O
would	O
hang	O
herself	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
more	O
wit	O
than	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
.	O
A	O
person	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
work-house	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
work-house	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
Castle	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
,	O
lodging	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
house	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
for	O
robbing	O
the	O
work-house	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
shift	O
and	O
a	O
hood	O
on	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
their	O
people	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
she	O
brought	O
there	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Grosvenor	I-pers
proved	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
others	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
proved	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
bundle	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
apron	O
the	O
bundle	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
London	O
house	O
.	O
Jemima	B-pers
Kirton	I-pers
,	O
said	O
when	O
she	O
first	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
wash-house	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
disorder	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
mad	O
?	O
Kirton	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
more	O
politick	O
than	O
mad	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
more	O
knave	O
than	O
fool	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
very	O
woman	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
cut	O
the	O
halter	O
off	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
surgeon	O
to	O
bleed	O
me	O
.	O
Kirton	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
halter	O
about	O
your	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
never	O
shall	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
369.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
holland	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
Sep.	O
27	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
shift	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
370.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Lying	I-pers
Joe	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
5	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
was	O
seven-night	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
goods	O
brought	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Charles	B-pers
Cavendish	I-pers
's	O
house	O
in	O
a	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
goods	O
for	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
as	O
the	O
others	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
there	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
porter	O
[	O
Henwood	O
]	O
said	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
for	O
bringing	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
other	O
charges	O
for	O
bringing	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
Said	O
Howell	O
;	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
tell	O
her	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
?	O
and	O
Henwood	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
14	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
Henwood	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
changed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
men	O
were	O
there	O
?	O
Cooke	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
besides	O
this	O
Howell	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Cooke	O
.	O
He	O
snatched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fingers	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
drowned	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
men	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
you	O
:	O
said	O
they	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
thought	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
this	O
was	O
my	O
Lord	O
Charles	B-pers
Cavendish	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
brought	O
some	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
men	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
them	O
their	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
it	O
once	O
already	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
lose	O
their	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
hard	O
enough	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
lose	O
the	O
7	O
s.	O
Council	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
your	O
money	O
again	O
?	O
Cooke	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
again	O
next	O
night	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
only	O
got	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
forgot	O
himself	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Henwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
this	O
was	O
my	O
Lord	O
Cavendish	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
what	O
parcels	O
we	O
had	O
for	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
three	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
gentlewoman	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
12	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
say	O
all	O
at	O
once	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
14	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
She	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
down	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Queen	O
Anne	O
's	O
guinea	O
with	O
the	O
head	O
uppermost	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
change	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
snatched	O
the	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
change	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
guinea	O
and	O
change	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Henwood	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
cap	O
and	O
a	O
chew	O
of	O
tobacco	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Lying	O
Joe	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
villain	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
lose	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
believed	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Barber	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
direct	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
Joe	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Charles	B-pers
Cavendish	I-pers
's	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
guinea	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
coat	O
on	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cooke	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
could	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
again	O
that	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
guinea	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
guinea	O
.	O
-	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
the	O
thing	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
wife	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
we	O
deserved	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
gave	O
us	O
another	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
pulled	O
out	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
then	O
?	O
Henwood	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
then	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
his	O
wife	O
readily	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Henwood	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
paid	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cooke	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seventeen	O
or	O
eighteen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
subject	O
to	O
get	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
does	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
sober	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
100	O
l.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
any	O
man	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
with	O
'Squire	O
Mitchel	O
in	O
Grub	O
Street	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
dead	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
house-keeper	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
coalware-house	O
and	O
a	O
joiner	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
many	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
change	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Philpot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
a	O
hundred	O
times	O
to	O
shut	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
371.	O
James	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bedsont	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
October	O
11	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
coronation	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
church	O
,	O
the	O
bells	O
were	O
then	O
ringing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
divert	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
then	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
horse	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
London	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cried	O
so	O
too	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
fellow	O
who	O
lay	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
nights	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
because	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
his	O
work	O
.	O
His	O
master	O
declared	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
his	O
going	O
away	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
Hunt	O
his	O
nag	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hooker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
man	O
that	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
man	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
372.	O
Paul	B-pers
Pond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
butter	O
cup	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
18	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
butter	O
cup	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
Mitre	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
it	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
trunk	O
in	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
there	O
are	O
seventeen	O
pieces	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
have	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
letters	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Quillet	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
me	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
went	O
farther	O
than	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
do	O
n't	O
leave	O
your	O
silver	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
come	O
back	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
very	O
willing	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
by	O
force	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
advertisements	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
advertisement	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
kitchen	O
stairs	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Quillet	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
ask	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
his	O
master	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
committed	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
for	O
corporal	O
punishment	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
373.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Dells	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
15	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Rayner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
money	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
key	O
away	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
her	O
gown	O
:	O
pray	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
tried	O
on	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
fit	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
's	O
who	O
lodged	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
tore	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
owed	O
her	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
her	O
.	O
Rayner	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hyam	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
gown	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Rayner	O
to	O
mend	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
torn	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Furlong	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
she	O
took	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Rayner	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
bailiff	O
's	O
follower	O
,	O
and	O
Rayner	O
keeps	O
a	O
bawdy-house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
own	O
sister	O
debauched	O
for	O
ten	O
guineas	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
374.	O
William	B-pers
Bruin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Lestrand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cossoy	O
cushion	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
14	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
cushion	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
chair	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
crossing	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
the	O
poles	O
of	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
this	O
cushion	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chair	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
channel	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
right	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
left	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
staid	O
there	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
proper	O
authority	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
pulled	O
me	O
about	O
like	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
mad	O
dogs	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
cordially	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
375.	O
Ann	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
brass	O
flower	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
two	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
pictures	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
27	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Stratford	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
by	O
getting	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
and	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
she	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
so	O
often	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
keep	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
to	O
save	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
gallows	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
anchor	O
smith	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
376	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
by	O
striking	O
and	O
stabbing	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
on	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
belly	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
her	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
one	O
inch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
five	O
inches	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
October	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
till	O
the	O
sixth	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
mortal	O
wound	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
charged	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
(	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
)	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
Mrs.	O
Graham	O
:	O
a	O
lad	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
journeymen	O
's	O
wives	O
had	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
almost	O
killed	O
herself	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
belly	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
caul	O
hung	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
you	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
again	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
very	O
bad	O
symptoms	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
must	O
die	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
enquired	O
more	O
particularly	O
into	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
any	O
difference	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
difference	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sometimes	O
troubled	O
with	O
fits	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
satisfied	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Jury	O
that	O
this	O
wound	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
form	O
any	O
judgment	O
,	O
whether	O
this	O
wound	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
it	O
came	O
by	O
accident	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
by	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
such	O
a	O
wound	O
may	O
happen	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
falling	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
knife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
sensible	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Very	O
sensible	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
get	O
all	O
the	O
information	O
I	O
could	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
of	O
opinion	O
she	O
would	O
die	O
soon	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mrs.	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
wound	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
died	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
by	O
that	O
wound	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
stabbed	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
live	O
at	O
variance	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
always	O
lived	O
a	O
happy	O
couple	O
till	O
this	O
thing	O
happened	O
;	O
and	O
Graham	O
never	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
offered	O
to	O
strike	O
her	O
but	O
once	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
stabbed	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
bad	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
stabbed	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
subject	O
to	O
convulsion	O
fits	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
sometimes	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
men	O
to	O
hold	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
by	O
the	O
knife	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
fit	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Mcdaniel	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
other	O
advice	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
fit	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fit	O
,	O
and	O
stabbed	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
fit	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
North	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
cousin	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
subject	O
to	O
fits	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
died	O
raving	O
mad	O
in	O
Bethlehem	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
till	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
thing	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Jenny	O
,	O
no	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
fits	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
sensible	O
.	O
Another	O
witness	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
after	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
her	O
husband	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
any	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
fit	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
witness	O
had	O
seen	O
ten	O
men	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
up	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fit	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
he	O
lived	O
very	O
peaceably	O
and	O
quietly	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
strike	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
fit	O
last	O
Summer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
almost	O
bit	O
his	O
tongue	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
ill	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
printer	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lived	O
very	O
justly	O
and	O
very	O
well	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
intimate	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
the	O
least	O
complaint	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
troubled	O
with	O
convulsion	O
fits	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
sometimes	O
fall	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
press	O
in	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
one	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
fit	O
since	O
his	O
wife	O
died	O
?	O
Phillips	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
they	O
may	O
be	O
counterfeits	O
?	O
Phillips	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Two	O
other	O
witnesses	O
proved	O
his	O
being	O
troubled	O
with	O
convulsion	O
fits	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
and	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
death	O
by	O
accident	O
.	O
377.	O
William	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
October	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
Evidence	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ritherdon	I-pers
,	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Winne	O
at	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
a	O
spoon	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Bryan	B-pers
Roper	I-pers
produced	O
a	O
spoon	O
of	O
his	O
Master	O
Mr.	O
Montgomery	O
's	O
to	O
match	O
with	O
the	O
spoon	O
which	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Montgomery	O
's	O
property	O
in	O
the	O
spoon	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
378.	O
Edward	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
Jury	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
48	O
yards	O
of	O
broad	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Percivall	I-pers
,	O
March	O
30	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Percivall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
:	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
September	O
was	O
twelve	O
months	O
he	O
stole	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
supersine	O
broad	O
cloth	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
he	O
stole	O
another	O
piece	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
good	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
shops	O
cut	O
out	O
into	O
remnants	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
three	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
by	O
an	O
advertisement	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
news-papers	O
about	O
some	O
goods	O
being	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
cloth	O
:	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
entered	O
on	O
board	O
o'ship	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
leave	O
of	O
the	O
regulating	O
captains	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
shore	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
warehouse	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
superfine	O
cloth	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
September	O
was	O
twelvemonths	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Percivall	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
board	O
of	O
ship	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloths	O
?	O
Percivall	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
ask	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
colours	O
and	O
the	O
marks	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
!	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Percivall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
you	O
said	O
you	O
knew	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Crew	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pledged	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
March	O
following	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
superfine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Percivall	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
both	O
superfine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
cloths	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
commission	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
at	O
15	O
s.	O
per	O
yard	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marsh	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
which	O
was	O
pledged	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Goodman	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Percivall	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
cloth	O
;	O
he	O
found	O
some	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
:	O
it	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
again	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Butcher	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
was	O
twelvemonths	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
long	O
ago	O
.	O
[	O
Mr.	O
Percivall	O
proved	O
his	O
property	O
in	O
all	O
these	O
clothes	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
pawned	O
any	O
cloth	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Percivall	O
's	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
's	O
else	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
yards	O
of	O
drab-coloured	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
81.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Josiah	B-pers
Buckhurst	I-pers
,	O
April	O
19	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
27	O
yards	O
of	O
broad	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
:	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
cloths	O
in	O
their	O
possession	O
readily	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
owners	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
these	O
indictments	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
379	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Dolfe	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
October	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
without	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
did	O
personate	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Masterson	I-pers
,	O
as	O
chief	O
mate	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
Frederick	O
privateer	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
name	O
did	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Threlkeld	I-pers
of	O
London	O
,	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
several	O
goods	O
and	O
chattels	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Threlkeld	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
29	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
for	O
securing	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
sum	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Threlkeld	I-pers
,	O
he	O
proposed	O
to	O
leave	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
certain	O
promissory	O
note	O
under	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
commander	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
privateer	O
,	O
made	O
payable	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Masterson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
one	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
sterling	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Wolfe	I-pers
did	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
feloniously	O
utter	O
and	O
publish	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Threlkeld	I-pers
a	O
certain	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
paper	O
writing	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
subscribed	O
thereon	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
under	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	O
as	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
true	O
promissory	O
note	O
,	O
which	O
said	O
paper	O
writing	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
Twenty	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
arrival	O
of	O
the	O
Marquis	O
De	O
Antin	O
and	O
Luovis	O
Erasmus	O
privateers	O
in	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
,	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Masterson	I-pers
,	O
chief	O
mate	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
Frederick	O
private	O
ship	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
under	O
my	O
command	O
,	O
100	O
l.	O
sterling	O
,	O
in	O
default	O
of	O
returning	O
him	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
ten	O
ounces	O
of	O
Spanish	O
pieces	O
of	O
eight	O
lodged	O
by	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
.	O
As	O
witness	O
my	O
hand	O
this	O
20th	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
1745	O
.	O
In	O
Kinsale	O
Harbour	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
.	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Thelkeld	I-pers
.	O
He	O
the	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Wolfe	I-pers
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
said	O
James	B-pers
Wolfe	I-pers
was	O
further	O
charged	O
in	O
a	O
second	O
count	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
indictment	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
as	O
true	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
paper	O
writing	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Threlkeld	I-pers
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
James	O
Talbot	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
William	B-pers
Threlkeld	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
brought	O
me	O
notice	O
that	O
a	O
gentleman	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
goods	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
him	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
your	O
customer	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
sold	O
you	O
some	O
dollars	O
a	O
while	O
ago	O
[	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
it	O
;	O
]	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
since	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Prince	O
Frederick	O
privateer	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Talbot	O
commander	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Masterson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
chief	O
mate	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
Frederick	O
privateer	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
goods	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
want	O
some	O
watches	O
,	O
some	O
buckles	O
,	O
some	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
gold	O
buttons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
strongest	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
looked	O
out	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
watches	O
in	O
double	O
cases	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
buttons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
laid	O
out	O
?	O
Threlkeld	O
.	O
Not	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
knee-buckles	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
looked	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
plain	O
gold	O
rings	O
;	O
then	O
this	O
note	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
my	O
security	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
question	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
The	O
note	O
was	O
signed	O
by	O
Capt	O
.	O
Talbot	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
note	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
]	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
note	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
security	O
for	O
the	O
goods	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
back	O
again	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
if	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
false	O
note	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
loss	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
where	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
:	O
they	O
advised	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
person	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
talk	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
talked	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
post	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
mate	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
Frederick	O
privateer	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Masterson	O
,	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Talbot	O
was	O
his	O
commander	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
fortune	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
four	O
gentlemen	O
there	O
who	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
who	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
that	O
ship	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	O
McNamar	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
over	O
as	O
a	O
passenger	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
villain	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
an	O
officer	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
accept	O
of	O
that	O
note	O
as	O
a	O
security	O
for	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
mentioned	O
no	O
quantity	O
or	O
kind	O
of	O
goods	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Threlkeld	O
produced	O
only	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
whether	O
those	O
were	O
large	O
enough	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
his	O
apprentice	O
,	O
I	O
desi	O
re	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
sworn	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
watches	O
or	O
rings	O
produced	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
[	O
Capt	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
appeared	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
interested	O
in	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
admitted	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
.	O
]	O
Edward	B-pers
Masterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
Capt	O
.	O
Talbot	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Masterson	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
writing	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
often	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Masterson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Masterson	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
like	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Comyn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
Capt	O
.	O
Talbot	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
writing	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
not	O
spelt	O
right	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
?	O
Comyn	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
carefully	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
you	O
are	O
sure	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
?	O
Comyn	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
very	O
carefully	O
on	O
it	O
before	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
my	O
evidence	O
so	O
strong	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Court	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Ephraim	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
,	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Capt	O
.	O
Talbot	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Talbot	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
letters	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
that	O
ago	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
some	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
since	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
since	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
;	O
neither	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
name	O
;	O
the	O
name	O
is	O
not	O
spelt	O
right	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
he	O
spell	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
Talbot	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
note	O
it	O
is	O
with	O
double	O
(	O
ll	O
)	O
and	O
double	O
(	O
tt	O
)	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Masterson	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
Capt	O
.	O
Talbot	O
spell	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Masterson	O
.	O
He	O
spells	O
it	O
Talbot	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
the	O
night	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
false	O
note	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
that	O
be	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Robert	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Counter	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
some	O
questions	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
note	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
some	O
people	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
from	O
who	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
trouble	O
himself	O
to	O
prove	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bad	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
expected	O
to	O
receive	O
no	O
money	O
at	O
all	O
but	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Talbot	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
might	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
note	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
bad	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Chariot	I-pers
(	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Threlkeld	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
as	O
a	O
security	O
for	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ask	O
for	O
any	O
goods	O
in	O
particular	O
?	O
Chariot	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ask	O
for	O
no	O
sort	O
of	O
goods	O
?	O
Chariot	O
.	O
He	O
mentioned	O
rings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
whether	O
your	O
master	O
asked	O
me	O
about	O
any	O
sort	O
of	O
goods	O
?	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
ask	O
me	O
about	O
watches	O
?	O
how	O
did	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
?	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
goods	O
but	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
.	O
Chariot	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
watches	O
shewed	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Chariot	O
.	O
The	O
shop	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
please	O
to	O
have	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
nobody	O
do	O
but	O
my	O
master	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
dollars	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
fetched	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
told	O
him	O
some	O
dollars	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
chief	O
mate	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
Frederick	O
privateer	O
:	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
glad	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Masterson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
say	O
my	O
name	O
was	O
Masterson	O
?	O
Chariot	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
master	O
deliver	O
me	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
goods	O
?	O
Chariot	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
deliver	O
them	O
?	O
Chariot	O
.	O
He	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
?	O
Chariot	O
.	O
One	O
pair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
shew	O
you	O
any	O
watches	O
?	O
Chariot	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Then	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
you	O
tell	O
a	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
lie	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
watches	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
me	O
none	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
none	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
shewed	O
me	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
shall	O
I	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
note	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
enquire	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
satisfy	O
himself	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Masterson	O
,	O
is	O
your	O
name	O
Robert	B-pers
Masterson	I-pers
?	O
Masterson	O
.	O
My	O
name	O
is	O
Edward	B-pers
Masterson	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
note	O
says	O
Robert	B-pers
Masterson	I-pers
,	O
so	O
this	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
money	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
note	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
note	O
first	O
mate	O
,	O
or	O
chief	O
mate	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Masterson	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
first	O
mate	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
Frederick	O
?	O
Masterson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
first	O
lieutenant	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Then	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
deficiencies	O
between	O
the	O
note	O
and	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
note	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
380.	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Gregory	I-place
by	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
shoe-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
21	O
.	O
And	O
381.	O
John	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
father	O
cleans	O
my	O
shoes	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
buckles	O
being	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
strap	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
his	O
father	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
searched	O
for	O
his	O
son	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
son	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
porters	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
see	O
Robinson	O
's	O
boy	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
5	O
s.	O
I	O
threatened	O
to	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
asked	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Market	O
.	O
Penn	O
sells	O
old	O
buckles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Penn	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
a	O
buckle	O
of	O
a	O
boy	O
to	O
day	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
his	O
finger	O
upon	O
one	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
a	O
half-penny	O
:	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
fellow	O
buckle	O
to	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
fellow	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
boy	O
but	O
a	O
penny	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
child	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
silver	O
.	O
Job	O
Lilly	O
.	O
Penn	O
brought	O
this	O
buckle	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
it	O
weighs	O
twelve	O
penny	O
wt	O
.	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
standard	O
marked	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Penn	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
buckle	O
maker	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
as	O
good	O
silver	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
standard	O
marked	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
it	O
may	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
probable	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Rave	I-pers
.	O
The	O
boy	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
buckle	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shoe	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Penn	O
,	O
and	O
Penn	O
owned	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lilly	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
Several	O
witnesses	O
appeared	O
for	O
Penn	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
thirty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lilly	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
ill	O
word	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
382	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Jack	I-pers
*	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Precinct	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Catharine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stutwell	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stutwell	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
the	O
mayoralty	O
of	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Willimott	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
moidores	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
money	O
shovel	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Sheere	I-pers
,	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
in	O
Lambard	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
aquitted	O
.	O
See	O
April	O
Sessions	O
Paper	O
in	O
that	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
IV	O
.	O
Part	O
II	O
.	O
page	O
159	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Turky	O
Jew	O
,	O
and	O
pretending	O
not	O
to	O
understand	O
English	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stutwell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dent	O
's	O
(	O
my	O
partner	O
)	O
at	O
cole	B-place
wharf	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Catharine	I-place
's	I-place
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
six	O
sacks	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
the	O
price	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
there	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pretty	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
change	O
in	O
half	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
change	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
poured	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
my	O
lap	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
lap	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
seized	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
drop	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
at	O
noon	O
day	O
?	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
guinea	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
the	O
guinea	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
Butler	O
's	O
wharf	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Dennett	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offered	O
the	O
guinea	O
then	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
understand	O
him	O
?	O
Stutwell	O
.	O
He	O
spoke	O
broken	O
English	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
change	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
money	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
spoke	O
pretty	O
good	O
English	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Justice	O
Dennett	O
's	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
understand	O
any	O
English	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Hyam	O
Aaron	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Aaron	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
something	O
else	O
to	O
say	O
before	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
accidentally	O
to	O
come	O
this	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
grocer	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Shoe-maker	O
Row	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
deal	O
in	O
900	O
or	O
1000	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
:	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
oil	O
,	O
sand	O
,	O
and	O
coals	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
wharf	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
sand	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
side	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
should	O
sit	O
there	O
but	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
[	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Stutwell	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
the	O
sand	O
was	O
a	O
load	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
seven	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
gave	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
six	O
shillings	O
for	O
white	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
for	O
red	O
:	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
get	O
down	O
you	O
Jew	O
son	O
of	O
a	O
bitch	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
wharf	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
serve	O
me	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
enquire	O
into	O
my	O
character	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
enough	O
here	O
that	O
know	O
me	O
.	O
Now	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
more	O
or	O
less	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
shop	O
as	O
most	O
people	O
.	O
He	O
first	O
bought	O
necessaries	O
for	O
himself	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
shop	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
goods	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Zipporah	B-pers
Silver	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
him	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
goods	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Jamaica	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hoop	O
petticoat	O
maker	O
.	O
Give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
speak	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
behalf	O
:	O
when	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
she	O
charges	O
him	O
with	O
six	O
guineas	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Aaron	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sell	O
Birmingham	O
ware	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
paid	O
me	O
as	O
honestly	O
as	O
the	O
day	O
is	O
long	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
justice	O
and	O
honesty	O
by	O
him	O
Guilty	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
383	O
.	O
+	O
Grace	B-pers
Usop	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Tarras	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
her	O
female	O
bastard	O
child	O
,	O
by	O
throwing	O
the	O
said	O
child	O
into	O
a	O
privy	O
belonging	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Leger	I-pers
,	O
wherein	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
filth	O
and	O
excrement	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
which	O
throwing	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
filth	O
and	O
excrement	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
child	O
was	O
choaked	O
and	O
suffocated	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
choaking	O
and	O
suffocating	O
the	O
said	O
female	O
bastard	O
child	O
died	O
,	O
September	O
1	O
.	O
And	O
384	O
,	O
385	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Leger	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Magdalen	B-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Maudin	I-pers
Leger	I-pers
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
,	O
and	O
maintaining	O
the	O
said	O
Grace	B-pers
Usop	I-pers
to	O
commit	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
:	O
and	O
therefore	O
they	O
the	O
said	O
Grace	B-pers
Usop	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Leger	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Magdalen	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Maudlin	O
Leger	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
female	O
bastard	O
child	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
their	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
A	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
thing	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Leger	O
's	O
house	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
there	O
but	O
herself	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
mistress	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
presently	O
her	O
mistress	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
flurry	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Leger	O
himself	O
came	O
in	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
flurry	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Tarras	O
,	O
my	O
girl	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
Maudlin	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
bed	O
warmed	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Maudlin	O
,	O
my	O
poor	O
girl	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
faithful	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
bad	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
strained	O
herself	O
with	O
carrying	O
coals	O
,	O
she	O
wants	O
the	O
bed	O
warmed	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
should	O
give	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
ale	O
with	O
sugar	O
and	O
spice	O
:	O
and	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Lewis	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
murder	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
boy	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
:	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
vault	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
nothing	O
but	O
soil	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fourth	O
time	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
but	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
girl	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
circumstances	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
navel	O
string	O
hung	O
between	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
by	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
married	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
this	O
girl	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
thought	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
dead	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
dead	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Grace	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
married	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
a	O
child	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
any	O
.	O
Coroner	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
rolls	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
with	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
bones	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Leger	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Leger	O
said	O
that	O
Tarras	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
so	O
bad	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
mop	O
and	O
a	O
pail	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Leger	O
,	O
with	O
your	O
leave	O
shall	O
I	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
see	O
her	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Tarras	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
clothes	O
on	O
:	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
wet	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
to	O
wash	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
mistress	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
mop	O
and	O
pail	O
,	O
and	O
cleaned	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
order	O
:	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
not	O
you	O
miscarried	O
?	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
what	O
makes	O
you	O
think	O
so	O
?	O
I	O
was	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
all	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Leger	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
does	O
Tarras	O
do	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
indeed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
well	O
of	O
the	O
months	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
one	O
Bellache	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
after	O
Tarras	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
makes	O
you	O
ask	O
after	O
her	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
vault	O
and	O
satisfy	O
yourself	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Leger	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
vault	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
something	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Tarras	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Tarras	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
your	O
child	O
;	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
Lord	O
Jesus	O
!	O
Lord	O
Jesus	O
!	O
Molly	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Leger	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
;	O
what	O
in	O
yours	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
?	O
no	O
,	O
in	O
yours	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
said	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
together	O
.	O
Coroner	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
talk	O
with	O
her	O
afterwards	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
sick	O
,	O
sick	O
,	O
sick	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
leaned	O
upon	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
Grace	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
leaning	O
upon	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
she	O
delivered	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Leger	O
's	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
whether	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
or	O
alive	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
delivered	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
or	O
alive	O
.	O
Usop	O
's	O
Council	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
child-bed	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
Usop	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
against	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Dorcas	O
Randolph	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Usop	O
's	O
birth-day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
abroad	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
born	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
on	O
the	O
ninth	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
child	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
any	O
preparation	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Randolph	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
best	O
able	O
to	O
stoop	O
,	O
put	O
your	O
hand	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Leger	O
had	O
threatened	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
lay	O
it	O
upon	O
James	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Baker	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
must	O
I	O
tell	O
a	O
lie	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
ouy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Randolph	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
September	O
Mrs.	O
Leger	O
did	O
own	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
a	O
bruise	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
the	O
child	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
bruise	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
out	O
of	O
malice	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
emptied	O
the	O
pot	O
with	O
the	O
after	O
birth	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pleaded	O
ignorance	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
for	O
people	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
labour	O
know	O
more	O
than	O
those	O
who	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
discourse	O
was	O
with	O
Tarras	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
talk	O
whether	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
or	O
alive	O
?	O
Randolph	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
master	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
helped	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
birth	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
one	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
child	O
dead	O
or	O
alive	O
?	O
Randolph	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Joachim	B-pers
Bellache	I-pers
.	O
One	O
of	O
my	O
shop-mates	O
discovered	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
on	O
Friday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Bellache	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
that	O
looks	O
like	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
Rags	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
something	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
curious	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
finger	O
into	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
flesh	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
finger	O
upon	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
the	O
ribs	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
what	O
really	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Leger	O
about	O
it	O
then	O
:	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Leger	O
,	O
it	O
does	O
not	O
signify	O
any	O
thing	O
talking	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
before	O
that	O
your	O
maid	O
was	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
ague	O
and	O
fever	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
too	O
much	O
bark	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
hindered	O
the	O
courses	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
surprized	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ordered	O
one	O
Paul	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
beadle	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
midwife	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
child	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
vault	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
born	O
dead	O
or	O
alive	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
judge	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
born	O
dead	O
or	O
alive	O
.	O
Coroner	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
child	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
full	O
time	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
judge	O
whether	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
its	O
full	O
time	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
of	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gundy	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
about	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
child	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
putrified	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
upon	O
examining	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
violent	O
pressure	O
upon	O
the	O
skull	O
,	O
which	O
if	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
when	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
alive	O
,	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
its	O
death	O
.	O
Coroner	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
child	O
full	O
grown	O
?	O
Grundy	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
opinion	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Leger	O
's	O
Council	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
pressure	O
upon	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
was	O
that	O
given	O
before	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
or	O
after	O
?	O
Grund	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
whether	O
the	O
wound	O
was	O
given	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
.	O
Leger	O
's	O
Council	O
argued	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
evidence	O
to	O
affect	O
Mr.	O
Leger	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
hardly	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
principal	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
Mr.	O
Leger	O
has	O
a	O
wife	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
very	O
unlikely	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
a	O
murder	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
first	O
proved	O
that	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
born	O
alive	O
.	O
[	O
Vide	O
Statute	O
21	O
.	O
James	O
I	O
.	O
]	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
called	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
the	O
Coroner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
happened	O
after	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
into	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Leger	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
terrible	O
case	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
Tarras	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
women	O
in	O
her	O
care	O
are	O
never	O
well	O
of	O
the	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bellache	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
clapped	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
my	O
belly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
your	O
belly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
drop	O
it	O
as	O
somebody	O
has	O
done	O
.	O
Another	O
thing	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
child	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
bled	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
ears	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
left	O
ear	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
Tarras	O
's	O
mother	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Leger	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
tell	O
Tarras	O
's	O
mother	O
to	O
bribe	O
the	O
midwife	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
Tarras	O
will	O
be	O
hanged	O
.	O
Coroner	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
not	O
answered	O
the	O
question	O
yet	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
what	O
Tarras	O
said	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
child	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
yours	O
:	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
an	O
acknowledgment	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
the	O
father	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
where	O
her	O
master	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
call	O
my	O
master	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wept	O
bitterly	O
:	O
they	O
talked	O
together	O
in	O
French	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
understand	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
her	O
master	O
said	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
I	O
must	O
lay	O
it	O
to	O
James	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Baker	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
hanged	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dalbiac	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Leger	O
forty	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
his	O
character	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
reputation	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sober	O
diligent	O
man	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Simon	B-pers
Dalbiac	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
forty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
natured	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
industrious	O
woman	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newland	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Leger	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
are	O
both	O
people	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
characters	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Perim	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
These	O
gentlemen	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
believed	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
still	O
born	O
.	O
386	O
.	O
+	O
Martha	B-pers
Orton	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Ford	B-pers
Boley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
steel	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
Ford	O
Boley	O
*	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
15th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Ratcliff	O
Cross	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Walter	O
's	O
a	O
jeweller	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
home	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
that	O
I	O
deal	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
by	O
Moses	B-place
and	I-place
Aaron	I-place
Alley	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
assaulted	O
by	O
five	O
women	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
money	O
,	O
damned	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
cut	O
cross	O
the	O
nose	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
edged	O
tool	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
mark	O
on	O
my	O
nose	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
tobacco	O
box	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
stopped	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Moses	O
and	O
Aaron	O
Alley	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
some	O
jewelling	O
work	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
pounds	O
.	O
*	O
Judith	O
Tilley	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
last	O
September	O
Sessions	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
robbery	O
,	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
death	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
other	O
women	O
in	O
custody	O
last	O
sessions	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Boley	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
quite	O
postive	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
discharged	O
at	O
that	O
goal	O
delivery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
robbery	O
committing	O
?	O
Boley	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
had	O
gagged	O
me	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
house	O
they	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
was	O
kept	O
by	O
one	O
Susan	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
whose	O
husband	O
was	O
impressed	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Nova	B-pers
Scotia	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
notorious	O
gambler	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Black	O
Boy	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
harboured	O
several	O
of	O
those	O
street	O
robbers	O
who	O
were	O
convicted	O
last	O
December	O
sessions	O
)	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
they	O
put	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
:	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
not	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Boley	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
Alley	O
gang	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
in	O
order	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
neighbours	O
I	O
got	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
several	O
that	O
frequented	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
people	O
who	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
and	O
one	O
Remmington	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
three	O
women	O
last	O
sessions	O
who	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
Betty	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
and	O
two	O
others	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
Betty	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
's	O
information	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
get	O
Betty	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
to	O
come	O
and	O
give	O
evidence	O
?	O
Boley	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
her	O
living	O
only	O
by	O
whoring	O
and	O
thieving	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
hid	O
herself	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
such	O
particular	O
notice	O
as	O
to	O
remember	O
the	O
persons	O
who	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Boley	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
a	O
lamp	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
particular	O
opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
notice	O
of	O
faces	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
Boley	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
once	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
from	O
crying	O
out	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
what	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
?	O
Boley	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Tilley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
convicted	O
,	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
tobacco	O
box	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
held	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
resist	O
,	O
stopped	O
my	O
mouth	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
dragged	O
me	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
jewelling	O
work	O
:	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
?	O
Boley	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
do	O
?	O
Boley	O
.	O
She	O
held	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
resisted	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
then	O
?	O
Boley	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
defend	O
myself	O
with	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boddington	I-pers
,	O
a	O
jeweller	O
in	O
Alderigate	O
Street	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
bring	O
the	O
watchmen	O
here	O
?	O
Boley	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
occasion	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
them	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
387.	O
William	B-pers
Beeson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswick	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Whitlaw	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
18	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Whitlaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Counsellor	O
Fazakerly	B-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
stable-door	O
on	O
Turnham	B-place
Green	I-place
;	O
and	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
stable	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
postilion	O
,	O
and	O
second	O
coachman	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
(	O
coachman	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fazakerly	O
.	O
)	O
Upon	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
evening	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
playing	O
at	O
cards	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
Whitlaw	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
him	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
unlocked	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
open	O
.	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
Turnham	O
Green	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
at	O
six	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
informed	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horlock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Angel	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
:	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
watch	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
broke	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
glasses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
watch	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Horlock	O
.	O
How	O
should	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
this	O
watch	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
glass	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Coare	I-pers
(	O
Constable	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Gibbon	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Fazakerly	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Young	O
man	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
make	O
an	O
ingenuous	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
Whitlaw	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
serve	O
a	O
man	O
so	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
kind	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
devil	O
was	O
in	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
devil	O
possessed	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
off	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
short	O
off	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
drunk	O
and	O
lost	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Gibbon	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
twice	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
handsomly	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
388.	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
medal	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
October	O
8	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
(	O
About	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stockes	O
,	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
post	O
house	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
medal	O
out	O
.	O
Then	O
says	O
she	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
it	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
not	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
silver	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watchman	O
seeing	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
child	O
does	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
one	O
Morris	O
:	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
watchman	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
the	O
watchman	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
she	O
doing	O
all	O
this	O
time	O
from	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
to	O
eleven	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
dragging	O
me	O
from	O
one	O
place	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
she	O
stopped	O
my	O
mouth	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
girl	O
were	O
coming	O
down	O
Drury-Lane	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
one	O
Morris	O
's	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
?	O
And	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
silver	O
medal	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
this	O
does	O
not	O
look	O
like	O
one	O
that	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
the	O
medal	O
was	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
was	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
girl	O
say	O
then	O
?	O
Watchman	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
into	O
an	O
alley	O
and	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
by	O
force	O
.	O
Mark	O
Harding	O
(	O
Constable	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
when	O
this	O
child	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
:	O
she	O
trembled	O
and	O
was	O
frightened	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
wits	O
:	O
she	O
shook	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
an	O
ague	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pocket	O
piece	O
of	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
piece	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
threw	O
down	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
child	O
claimed	O
that	O
as	O
her	O
medal	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
washing	O
at	O
Grosvenor	O
's	O
Meuse	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
this	O
child	O
.	O
She	O
find	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
lodging	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
you	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
creditable	O
person	O
's	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
as	O
if	O
you	O
wanted	O
a	O
lodging	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
staid	O
out	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wilson	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
she	O
met	O
you	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
says	O
he	O
saw	O
you	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
eleven	O
:	O
what	O
did	O
she	O
do	O
with	O
you	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
court	O
into	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
from	O
place	O
to	O
place	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
your	O
mistress	O
live	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
In	O
Arundel-street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
letter	O
to	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
Temple	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
a	O
publick	O
place	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
called	O
to	O
your	O
assistance	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
come	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
odd	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
carried	O
all	O
this	O
way	O
by	O
force	O
;	O
you	O
went	O
thought	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
stopped	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
met	O
her	O
at	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
to	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
,	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
place	O
by	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
all	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
form	O
two	O
hours	O
together	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stokes	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
send	O
this	O
girl	O
