TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
19th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Henry	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Gre	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1745	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pen	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
HENRY	B-pers
MARSHALL	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BURNETT	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
DENISON	O
,	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLIN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richford	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Babb	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Burchall	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gainsborough	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stratton	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Lyne	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Deschamps	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sandwith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boozshire	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Harroo	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wilxon	I-pers
.	O
298	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Spence	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Golden	B-place
Anchor	I-place
house	I-place
on	I-place
Saffron	I-place
Hill	I-place
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
my	O
family	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
my	O
boy	O
lies	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
candle	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
something	O
black	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
soot	O
upon	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
when	O
the	O
boy	O
made	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
the	O
boy	O
get	O
in	O
?	O
Wills	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
casement	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
apprehend	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
casement	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
your	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
?	O
Wills	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
customer	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Wills	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
all	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
do	O
to	O
me	O
is	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
serve	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
served	O
the	O
King	O
before	O
now	O
[	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
sailor	O
.	O
]	O
Mr.	O
Wills	O
's	O
Boy	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
twelve	O
his	O
master	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
waked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
master	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
To	O
make	O
a	O
burglary	O
there	O
must	O
either	O
be	O
a	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
or	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
299	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lynn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Barker	O
's	O
in	O
White	B-place
Lion	I-place
Court	I-place
to	O
drink	O
a	O
poot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
side	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
above	O
stairs	O
with	O
her	O
above	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
purse	O
with	O
five	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
shake	O
this	O
purse	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tax	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
it	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
it	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
directly	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
then	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
presence	O
of	O
mind	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
she	O
might	O
fall	O
upon	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Mr.	O
Anderson	O
,	O
look	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
you	O
do	O
me	O
Justice	O
:	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
would	O
look	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
my	O
Lord	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
leave	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
me	O
:	O
And	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
has	O
known	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
five	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
?	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
several	O
other	O
houses	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
company	O
was	O
you	O
in	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
no	O
other	O
company	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
300	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Potbury	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Quincey	I-pers
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
damask	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
stuff	O
damask	O
shoe	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
silver	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Feb.	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
was	O
the	O
reputed	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Potbury	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Jack	O
the	O
Sailor	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
Alley	O
gang	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
last	O
December	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
executed	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Quincey	I-pers
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
locked	O
my	O
shop	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
sash	O
had	O
been	O
shoved	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
shoes	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
were	O
gone	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
silver	O
lace	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
keep	O
a	O
sale	O
shop	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
for	O
shew	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bye	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
one	O
Lucas	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
condemned	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
executed	O
.	O
On	O
Shrove	O
Tuesday	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Leather	B-place
Lane	I-place
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sall	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
let	O
us	O
wait	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
till	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
by	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
put	O
my	O
arm	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
shoes	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
newly	O
heel	O
pieced	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
down	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
stuff	O
damask	O
shoes	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
reach	O
any	O
more	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
whole	O
body	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
down	O
three	O
pair	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
(	O
we	O
frequented	O
one	O
Hawkins	O
's	O
in	O
Golden	O
Lane	O
who	O
harbours	O
nothing	O
but	O
thieves	O
:	O
)	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
came	O
one	O
Tom	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
printer	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
designed	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
shoes	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
that	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
out	O
all	O
night	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
womens	O
shoes	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
brought	O
nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
half	O
the	O
money	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
they	O
sold	O
them	O
or	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
Accomplice	O
agreed	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
shoes	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Quincey	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
pawned	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Boomer	O
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
ticket	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
pawned	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
positive	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquited	O
.	O
301.	O
Jane	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
moidores	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Woodroffe	I-pers
,	O
July	O
6	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Woodroffe	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
about	O
noon	O
I	O
lost	O
10	O
moidores	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
chest	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	B-place
Ann	I-place
from	O
Boston	O
in	O
New-England	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
in	O
a	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
chest	O
locked	O
?	O
Woodroffe	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
steerage	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
5	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Butcher	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
stay	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
dinner	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
?	O
Woodroffe	O
.	O
By	O
Mrs.	O
Butcher	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
steerage	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
both	O
sitting	O
upon	O
my	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
they	O
were	O
sitting	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
what	O
made	O
you	O
leave	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
your	O
chest	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
mistrust	O
of	O
her	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
by	O
a	O
rash	O
word	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Butcher	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
wished	O
the	O
devil	O
had	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
expression	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
mistrust	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
board	O
o'ship	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Woodroffe	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
been	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
in	O
Coleman	O
street	O
?	O
Woodroffe	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
board	O
o'ship	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
uncle	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
old	O
gentleman	O
[	O
Woodroffe	O
]	O
was	O
her	O
uncle	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
board	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Woodroffe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
unlocked	O
his	O
chest	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
upon	O
deck	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
old	O
uncle	O
has	O
taken	O
a	O
French	O
prize	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
any	O
linen	O
in	O
his	O
chest	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
shame	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
look	O
into	O
your	O
uncle	O
's	O
chest	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
old	O
gentleman	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
shut	O
down	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
?	O
Butcher	O
.	O
Her	O
hand	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
back	O
being	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
anything	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
uncle	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
leave	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
your	O
chest	O
?	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
locked	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
made	O
you	O
mistrust	O
her	O
taking	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Butcher	O
.	O
Because	O
she	O
paid	O
her	O
creditors	O
in	O
moidores	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
half	O
peny	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
-	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
pay	O
any	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Seager	I-pers
.	O
[	O
a	O
baker	O
]	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
bout	O
3	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
[	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
]	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
moidore	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
s.	O
she	O
owed	O
me	O
.	O
Vincent	B-pers
Clinton	I-pers
[	O
a	O
baker	O
.	O
]	O
Much	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
moidore	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
5	O
s.	O
she	O
owed	O
me	O
.	O
W.	O
Ward	O
[	O
a	O
distiller	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owed	O
me	O
8	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
on	O
Saturday	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mulliner	I-pers
[	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owed	O
me	O
22	O
s.	O
upon	O
goods	O
she	O
had	O
pledged	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
Saturday	O
she	O
came	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
moidore	O
.	O
Woodroffe	O
.	O
We	O
dined	O
on	O
board	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
after	O
dinner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
lain	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Woodroffe	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
late	O
in	O
town	O
-	O
I	O
lay	O
there	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
she	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
made	O
you	O
mistrust	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Woodroffe	O
.	O
Because	O
Mrs.	O
Butcher	O
came	O
on	O
board	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
having	O
some	O
moidores	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
looked	O
for	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
an	O
injury	O
that	O
her	O
daughter	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Woodroffe	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
guinea	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
tax	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
undone	O
my	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
seven	O
moidores	O
to	O
hold	O
my	O
tongue	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
expose	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
my	O
child	O
all	O
her	O
life	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
sister	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New	O
Gravel	O
Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
not	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
been	O
at	O
your	O
sister	O
's	O
house	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
days	O
together	O
?	O
Boyd	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
hear	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Woodroffe	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
seven	O
moidores	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
-	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
about	O
8	O
days	O
ago	O
-	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
it	O
was	O
-	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
day	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
ago	O
-	O
my	O
sister	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
your	O
sister	O
send	O
for	O
you	O
for	O
?	O
Boyd	O
.	O
To	O
ask	O
me	O
if	O
she	O
owed	O
me	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
for	O
lodging	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
speak	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
ashamed	O
to	O
speak	O
*	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
smother	O
the	O
injury	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
a	O
child	O
about	O
7	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
sister	O
and	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
7	O
moidores	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
deposed	O
that	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
injured	O
in	O
her	O
private	O
parts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
conversation	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
Boyd	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
loved	O
her	O
very	O
dearly	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
material	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
matter	O
?	O
Boyd	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
speaking	O
of	O
moidores	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
about	O
them	O
?	O
Boyd	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
given	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
hers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
he	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
was	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
Boyd	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
it	O
her	O
for	O
?	O
Boyd	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
[	O
here	O
she	O
paused	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
]	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
what	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
for	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
child	O
was	O
used	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
base	O
manner	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
hold	O
my	O
tongue	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
child	O
was	O
used	O
in	O
a	O
base	O
manner	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
base	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
was	O
the	O
child	O
used	O
?	O
Boyd	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
explain	O
it	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
lose	O
my	O
life	O
-	O
my	O
dear	O
sister	O
's	O
child	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
bleeding	O
capacity	O
in	O
the	O
private	O
parts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
Boyd	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
sister	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
poor	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
about	O
this	O
?	O
Boyd	O
.	O
Lord	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
passion	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
has	O
brought	O
this	O
indictment	O
against	O
my	O
sister	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Woodroffe	O
gave	O
my	O
wife	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
whore	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
beat	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
7	O
moidores	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
about	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
302.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mumford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
in	O
Newgate	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Till	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
marked	O
18	O
peny	O
worth	O
of	O
half-pence	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
nine	O
peny	O
worth	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
9	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
303.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
Mar	O
y	O
Rogers	O
.	O
Deposed	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
shop	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
presently	O
after	O
to	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
she	O
missed	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
other	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
groat	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
304.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4s	O
.	O
three	O
shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
five	O
aprons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
womens	O
caps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bigg	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
Isabella	O
Bigg	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
voluntarily	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
shift	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
mine	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
caps	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
slipped	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
305	O
,	O
306.	O
John	B-pers
Hewett	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hewett	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
their	O
lodging	O
,	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
307.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Butolph	I-place
,	I-place
without	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
whalebone	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
44	O
yards	O
of	O
striped	O
linen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
hoop-petticoat	O
shop	O
in	O
Artillery	B-place
lane	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
journey	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
goods	O
,	O
the	O
bone	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smurford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Matthews	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
bone	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
well	O
carry	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
among	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
bone	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
might	O
do	O
what	O
she	O
pleased	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
Mrs.	O
May	O
down	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
maid	O
take	O
the	O
bone	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Woolcock	I-pers
.	O
About	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
this	O
parcel	O
of	O
holland	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Spittlefields	O
,	O
sewed	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
it	O
might	O
lie	O
till	O
she	O
wanted	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
308	O
,	O
309.	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
saucepan	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
their	O
lodgings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bridge	I-pers
,	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
310.	O
Rose	B-pers
Lincoln	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Legg	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
slipped	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopped	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
,	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
shirts	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
311	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bride	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
snuffers	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
snuff	O
pan	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Leprimandy	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
May	O
21	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Leprimandy	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
about	O
4	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
my	O
maid	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bolt	O
unbolted	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hole	O
cut	O
through	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
plate	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
sew	O
days	O
after	O
Mr.	O
White	O
stopped	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
snuff	O
pan	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
of	O
arms	O
-	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
are	O
worth	O
about	O
nine	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tea	O
pot	O
about	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
pounds	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Slaney	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
hole	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Fuller	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Noble	O
street	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
old	O
broken	O
silver	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
an	O
ounce	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
[	O
the	O
snuff	O
pan	O
]	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
doubled	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
strange	O
manner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
again	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
friend	O
's	O
.	O
My	O
partner	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
the	O
silver	O
and	O
him	O
too	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
spoke	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
Noble	O
street	O
(	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
alarmed	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
)	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
down	O
Oat	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
Staining	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
partner	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Lillipot	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
partner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
run	O
out	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
hurly	O
burly	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hague	O
came	O
over	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
rogue	O
,	O
and	O
accused	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
over	O
a	O
tea	O
pot	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
advertisement	O
published	O
by	O
this	O
lady	O
with	O
a	O
reward	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
acquainted	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
of	O
arms	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
snuffer	O
pan	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
coat	O
of	O
arms	O
appeared	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fray	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
partner	O
]	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
old	O
silver	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
snuffer	O
pan	O
rolled	O
up	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
friend	O
's	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
White	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
fancy	O
it	O
is	O
stole	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
silver	O
too	O
;	O
Mr.	O
White	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Lillipot	O
lane	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
travelled	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
old	O
sterling	O
went	O
now	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
new	O
sterling	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
gave	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
give	O
about	O
4	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
lump	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
do	O
butter	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
fancy	O
you	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
silver	O
in	O
Mary	O
le	O
Bone	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
four	O
pounds	O
,	O
odd	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
Mrs.	O
Leprimandy	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
vice	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
her	O
arms	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hague	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
bought	O
old	O
silver	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
silver	O
lace	O
burnt	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
ounce	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
ounce	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
lump	O
of	O
melted	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
essay	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
essay	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
took	O
off	O
all	O
suspicion	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
11	O
ounces	O
and	O
odd	O
peny	O
weights	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
tea	O
pot	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
bent	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
travelled	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
,	O
for	O
people	O
do	O
that	O
to	O
old	O
silver	O
,	O
either	O
for	O
lightness	O
of	O
carriage	O
or	O
ease	O
in	O
packing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
a	O
neighbour	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
selling	O
any	O
plate	O
to	O
desire	O
Mr.	O
White	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hue	O
and	O
cry	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
villain	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
the	O
plate	O
is	O
stolen	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
Mary	O
le	O
Bone	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
tea-pot	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
warnings	O
from	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
getting	O
the	O
pot	O
open	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
spoiling	O
the	O
coat	O
of	O
arms	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
agreed	O
with	O
the	O
advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
an	O
evidence	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
concerned	O
but	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
impeach	O
nobody	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Shute	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Deputy	O
Bailey	O
in	O
Forster	O
Lane	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
silver	O
unburnt	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
burn	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
burning	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
melt	O
silver	O
in	O
a	O
kitchen	O
grate	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
was	O
to	O
build	O
a	O
forge	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
snuffers	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
ounce	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
mark	O
or	O
coat	O
of	O
arms	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
burnt	O
silver	O
came	O
to	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
Mary	O
le	O
Bone	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
old	O
plate	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
thought	O
by	O
my	O
bag	O
that	O
I	O
dealt	O
in	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
bargain	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
nor	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
French	O
prize	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
4	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
French	O
plate	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
English	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Portland	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sailor	O
pulled	O
some	O
silver	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
pot	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
snuffer	O
pan	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
in	O
a	O
lump	O
;	O
the	O
silver	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
French	O
ship	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
trowzers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
four	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
for	O
it	O
-	O
the	O
tea-pot	O
was	O
rolled	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
discern	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
tea-pot	O
.	O
Weldon	O
Bride	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
brother	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
apartment	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hume	I-pers
,	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
shutting	O
up	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
:	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
without	O
my	O
knowing	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
.	O
The	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sixteen	O
or	O
seventeen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
near	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
service	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
a	O
farm	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Colonel	O
Frasier	O
's	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bride	I-pers
[	O
wife	O
of	O
Weldon	O
Bride	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
laid	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Frasier	O
[	O
Nephew	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Frasier	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
grandfather	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
uncle	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
entrusted	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
and	O
goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
bills	O
:	O
Col.	O
Frasier	O
has	O
entrusted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
to	O
receive	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
recommended	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Colonel	O
did	O
not	O
discharge	O
him	O
for	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
feloniously	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
acquitted	O
of	O
stealing	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
312	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Pancras	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Hannah	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
June	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
my	O
aunt	O
Howard	O
towards	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stopped	O
my	O
aunt	O
between	O
Pancras	B-place
and	O
the	O
Turnpike	B-place
,	O
and	O
she	O
begged	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
alone	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
big	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
ill	O
language	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
tore	O
my	O
apron	O
off	O
my	O
sides	O
,	O
and	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
apron	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
murder	O
and	O
thieves	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
people	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
salute	O
the	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
salute	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
.	O
The	O
three	O
men	O
were	O
going	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
crying	O
out	O
thieves	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
my	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
back	O
with	O
my	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
in	O
Pancras	O
Church	O
Yard	O
:	O
they	O
searched	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
pistol	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
common	O
walking	O
stick	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
pardon	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
towards	O
Pancras	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
men	O
met	O
us	O
and	O
saluted	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
on	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
an	O
imposturous	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
-	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
apron	O
before	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
preposterous	O
creature	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
kiss	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
apron	O
.	O
[	O
John	B-pers
Proctor	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
produced	O
Herring	O
's	O
apron	O
]	O
Q.	O
to	O
Herring	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
carry	O
the	O
apron	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
he	O
drop	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
Herring	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
my	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
fifteen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
hair	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
perriwig	O
maker	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rossell	I-pers
[	O
Curate	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Cripplegate	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
year	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
is	O
only	O
from	O
his	O
being	O
a	O
constant	O
attender	O
at	O
church	O
for	O
five	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
communicant	O
once	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
sacrament	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
fact	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
much	O
surprized	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
hardly	O
think	O
he	O
can	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shad	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
small	O
sums	O
of	O
four	O
,	O
five	O
,	O
or	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
paid	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
says	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
church	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
313.	O
William	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Dix	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
William	I-pers
Dix	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Lombard	I-place
Street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
dozen	O
of	O
fowls	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poulterer	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Market	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
third	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Leadenhal	B-place
Market	I-place
,	O
and	O
bought	O
ten	O
dozen	O
of	O
fowls	O
and	O
chickens	O
dead	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
8	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
packed	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Dix	O
stood	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
knot	O
,	O
a	O
rope	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
ticket	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
looked	O
on	O
his	O
ticket	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
ticket	O
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
at	O
Fetter	O
Lane	O
,	O
freeman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
ticket	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
safe	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
fowls	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
fowls	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
all	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Basset	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
Deptford	O
with	O
some	O
fowls	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
heard	O
of	O
my	O
losing	O
some	O
fowls	O
,	O
secured	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Deptford	O
,	O
tied	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
arms	O
,	O
paid	O
the	O
reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
ten	O
shillings	O
for	O
a	O
landau	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Sharrock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
and	O
carman	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
;	O
he	O
bought	O
ten	O
dozen	O
and	O
seven	O
fowls	O
and	O
chickens	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
some	O
goods	O
for	O
another	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
by	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
knot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
his	O
ticket	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
upon	O
it	O
Matthew	O
Turner	O
,	O
Fetter	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
master	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
very	O
safe	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
ticket	O
porter	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Basset	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
horse	O
for	O
a	O
ride	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Deptford	O
town	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
fellows	O
at	O
an	O
alehouse	O
door	O
with	O
some	O
fowls	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
fowls	O
,	O
but	O
their	O
master	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Boot	O
and	O
Crown	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
got	O
one	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
men	O
I	O
believed	O
their	O
master	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
fowls	O
:	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
care	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
item	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
very	O
boldly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
fowls	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
fowls	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
patience	O
to	O
stand	O
talking	O
with	O
him	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
charge	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
six	O
dozen	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
fowls	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
rode	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Deptford	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
hired	O
a	O
landau	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
314	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Warden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St	B-place
.	I-place
Brides	I-place
in	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
not	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
upon	O
Winifred	B-pers
Strolger	I-pers
,	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
to	O
vit	O
of	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
wickedly	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Winifred	O
did	O
carnally	O
know	O
and	O
abuse	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
May	O
20	O
Winifred	O
Strolger	O
was	O
asked	O
what	O
age	O
she	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
asked	O
what	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
consequence	O
if	O
she	O
should	O
speak	O
what	O
was	O
not	O
true	O
;	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
God	O
Almighty	O
will	O
not	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
admitted	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
[	O
I	O
he	O
could	O
behaved	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
becoming	O
manner	O
,	O
though	O
in	O
tear	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
difficulty	O
she	O
expressed	O
herself	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
man	O
[	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
]	O
Strolger	O
.	O
Yes	O
-	O
he	O
is	O
Bob	O
-	O
he	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
my	O
aunt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Strolger	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Strolger	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Strolger	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
senseless	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
hart	O
's	O
horn	O
drops	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
up	O
my	O
nose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
your	O
self	O
?	O
Strolger	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
aunt	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
your	O
aunt	O
?	O
Strolger	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Strolger	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
sit	O
upon	O
my	O
chair	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ill.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
illness	O
?	O
Strolger	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
other	O
disorder	O
had	O
you	O
?	O
Strolger	O
.	O
Nothing	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
sick	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
[	O
Apothecary	O
.	O
]	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
examine	O
the	O
part	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
laceration	O
?	O
Mills	O
.	O
Really	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
reckon	O
myself	O
a	O
competent	O
judge	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
Mr.	O
Mills	O
gave	O
some	O
reasons	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
it	O
appeared	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
been	O
injured	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
of	O
that	O
age	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
to	O
Strolger	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
hurt	O
in	O
your	O
private	O
parts	O
?	O
Strolger	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Strolger	O
,	O
[	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
mother	O
]	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
the	O
child	O
first	O
complained	O
of	O
any	O
hurt	O
?	O
Strolger	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
by	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
torn	O
and	O
cerated	O
.	O
She	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
aunt	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
examine	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
not	O
being	O
so	O
full	O
a	O
proof	O
as	O
the	O
law	O
requires	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
.	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
upon	O
this	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
in	O
custody	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
bill	O
prefixed	O
against	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
sessions	O
,	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
commit	O
a	O
rape	O
.	O
315	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Rigleton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Stanmore	B-place
Magna	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
by	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
upon	O
the	O
throat	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
4	O
inches	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
depth	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Truman	O
,	O
a	O
brewer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Stanmore	B-place
to	O
see	O
my	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Vine	O
,	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
.	O
A	O
quarter	O
before	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
daughter	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
her	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
father	O
was	O
her	O
mother	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
I	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
about	O
40	O
rob	O
from	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
coat	O
over	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
on	O
but	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
shoes	O
buckled	O
,	O
without	O
stockings	O
or	O
breeches	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
shut	O
sleeves	O
were	O
all	O
over	O
blood	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
refuse	O
going	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Vine	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
threw	O
his	O
knife	O
into	O
a	O
pond	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
throw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
pond	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
knife	O
.	O
A	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
several	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
lower	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
body	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
partly	O
naked	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
bed	O
clothes	O
over	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
chamber	O
pot	O
standing	O
upon	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
bleed	O
in	O
;	O
though	O
her	O
head	O
did	O
not	O
be	O
directly	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
bled	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Her	O
throat	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
belly	O
ript	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
place	O
cut	O
in	O
her	O
cheek	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
whether	O
the	O
body	O
was	O
warm	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
warm	O
and	O
her	O
throat	O
and	O
belly	O
were	O
bleeding	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Moore	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
murder	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
senses	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Something	O
disturbed	O
us	O
so	O
for	O
several	O
nights	O
,	O
that	O
neither	O
of	O
us	O
could	O
rest	O
or	O
sleep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
fuddled	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
He	O
appeared	O
sober	O
enough	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
observe	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Vine	O
together	O
upon	O
the	O
alarm	O
of	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sleeves	O
of	O
his	O
shirt	O
were	O
as	O
bloody	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
dipped	O
in	O
blood	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
bloody	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
only	O
his	O
shoes	O
and	O
his	O
shirt	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
he	O
threw	O
his	O
knife	O
into	O
a	O
pond	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
where	O
it	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
[	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
knife	O
with	O
a	O
round	O
pointed	O
blade	O
.	O
]	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
murdered	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
made	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
crazy	O
sometimes	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
crazy	O
sometimes	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
sometimes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
his	O
wife	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
Not	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
glimpse	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sit	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
night	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
disordered	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
talk	O
sensibly	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
but	O
little	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
talked	O
sensibly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
he	O
agree	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
they	O
disagree	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
They	O
used	O
to	O
disagree	O
sometimes	O
-	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
offered	O
any	O
violence	O
to	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
it	O
till	O
just	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
senses	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
half	O
mad	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
said	O
the	O
devil	O
was	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
frightened	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
fighting	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
halfpeny	O
for	O
a	O
halfpeny	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
light	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
innocently	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
316	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Twyford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
upon	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
,	O
wickedly	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
detestable	O
sin	O
of	O
buggery	O
did	O
commit	O
and	O
do	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
named	O
among	O
Christians	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
.	O
Some	O
time	O
in	O
June	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
near	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Market	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
press	O
gang	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
stood	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
:	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
brother	O
soldier	O
,	O
they	O
will	O
not	O
press	O
any	O
Irishmen	O
;	O
yes	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
will	O
press	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
loved	O
a	O
soldier	O
as	O
he	O
loved	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sea	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
good	O
beer	O
.	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Plough	B-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Fleet	I-place
Market	I-place
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
pay	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Talbot	O
Inn	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
to	O
a	O
particular	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
much	O
persuasion	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pressed	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
agreed	O
for	O
a	O
bed	O
for	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
he	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
growing	O
sleepy	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
his	O
tricks	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
ashamed	O
to	O
tell	O
-	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
-	O
into	O
my	O
fundament	O
,	O
and	O
pushing	O
so	O
hard	O
it	O
awaked	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
began	O
to	O
quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
stronger	O
than	O
him	O
turned	O
him	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
o'beating	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
brother	O
soldier	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
make	O
this	O
up	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
much	O
money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
must	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Mullins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
the	O
complaint	O
you	O
had	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
false	O
?	O
Mullins	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
all	O
true	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
declare	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
accord	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
you	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
drunk	O
?	O
Mullins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
;	O
Mullins	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
persuasion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
did	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
:	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
bed	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
Mullins	O
cried	O
out	O
very	O
loud	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
my	O
fundament	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
fell	O
o'fighting	O
:	O
then	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
and	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
Gentlemen	O
who	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
complain	O
to	O
them	O
of	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
?	O
Duck	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
not	O
they	O
fighting	O
before	O
?	O
Duck	O
.	O
No	O
-	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
beat	O
,	O
Mullins	O
was	O
beating	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
when	O
the	O
company	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Duck	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
the	O
drunkest	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
.	O
Oliver	B-pers
Pen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
soldier	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
-	O
that	O
is	O
he	O
.	O
They	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
their	O
lodging	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
complaint	O
made	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
up	O
?	O
Pen	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
the	O
soldier	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wanted	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
fell	O
o'fighting	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
their	O
quarrelling	O
?	O
Pen	O
.	O
Because	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
that	O
to	O
?	O
Pen	O
.	O
To	O
all	O
the	O
whole	O
room	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
maturity	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
be	O
acted	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
a	O
boy	O
)	O
without	O
you	O
was	O
as	O
willing	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
And	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
entered	O
his	O
body	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
assaulted	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
forsworn	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
must	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
be	O
willing	O
alike	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
there	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
done	O
.	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
convict	O
a	O
person	O
upon	O
an	O
indictment	O
for	O
sodomy	O
,	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
parliament	O
requires	O
that	O
the	O
emission	O
should	O
be	O
proved	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
penetration	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
bail	O
for	O
his	O
appearance	O
next	O
sessions	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
trial	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
commit	O
sodomy	O
.	O
317	O
.	O
+	O
Catharine	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
*	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
pounds	O
ten	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
July	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
This	O
Catharine	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
[	O
aged	O
sixty	O
years	O
or	O
upwards	O
]	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
February	O
sessions	O
in	O
the	O
mayoralty	O
of	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Willimott	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
11	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Perthy	I-pers
[	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
]	O
in	O
some	O
private	O
conversation	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
See	O
sessions	O
paper	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Page	O
89	O
,	O
Trial	O
149.	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
Yesterday	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Gracechurch	B-place
Street	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
o'night	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hope	O
a	O
brewer	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
hussled	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
hold	O
by	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
or	O
much	O
about	O
that	O
part	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
missed	O
;	O
missing	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
I	O
thought	O
this	O
woman	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
into	O
Bell	O
Alley	O
,	O
[	O
Petticoat	O
Lane	O
]	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
Bell	O
Alley	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
by	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
housed	O
,	O
mistress	O
,	O
pray	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
more	O
than	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
them	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
denied	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
for	O
it	O
abundance	O
of	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
once	O
more	O
,	O
so	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
for	O
it	O
again	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
six	O
pence	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
afterwards	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
offered	O
them	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
parcels	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
one	O
parcel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
pocket	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
bag	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
8	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
all	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
of	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Of	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
,	O
a	O
bacon	O
man	O
in	O
Goswell	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
seeing	O
this	O
dog	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
pressed	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
pressing	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
[	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cutherson	I-pers
]	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
[	O
the	O
prisoner	O
]	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
see	O
whether	O
you	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
any	O
answer	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
tell	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
see	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
presently	O
began	O
to	O
scramble	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
upon	O
her	O
table	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pounds	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
be	O
at	O
quiet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
do	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
She	O
scrambled	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
meddled	O
with	O
me	O
or	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
knock	O
her	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
curse	O
and	O
swear	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
some	O
by	O
violence	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
had	O
hands	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
money	O
up	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
it	O
afterwards	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
wanted	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
or	O
his	O
money	O
than	O
your	O
Lordship	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
or	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
you	O
set	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
's	O
lap	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
took	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
to	O
take	O
six	O
pence	O
out	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
put	O
your	O
money	O
into	O
your	O
pocket	O
again	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
sure	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
this	O
was	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
sure	O
what	O
you	O
did	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
lay	O
your	O
money	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cutherson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
White	O
in	O
Gracechurch	O
Street	O
;	O
they	O
talked	O
together	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
his	O
consent	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Cutherson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
went	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
too	O
,	O
sometimes	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
behind	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
complained	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
loved	O
justice	O
and	O
honesty	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
Bell	O
Alley	O
in	O
Petticoat	O
Lane	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
there	O
was	O
justice	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
Gracechurch	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
hoped	O
to	O
be	O
saved	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
search	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
three	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
valued	O
it	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
twenty	O
pound	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
as	O
leave	O
have	O
lost	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
more	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
pockets	O
both	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
pushed	O
it	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
but	O
however	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
down	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
gin	O
and	O
small	O
beer	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
any	O
such	O
liquor	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
locked	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bag	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
something	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
bag	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
brazen	O
face	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
?	O
Cutherson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
brazen	O
face	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
again	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
money	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
to	O
tell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
scrambled	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
upon	O
her	O
table	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
scrambled	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
scrambled	O
some	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
money	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
that	O
money	O
he	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
you	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Good	O
Lord	O
forgive	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
his	O
lap	O
.	O
Sure	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
swear	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Cutherson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
sat	O
in	O
his	O
lap	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
never	O
offered	O
to	O
touch	O
me	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
thought	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
have	O
staid	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
his	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
upon	O
my	O
table	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
White	O
there	O
?	O
Cutherson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
what	O
with	O
going	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
disputing	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
hours	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
character	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
her	O
-	O
she	O
winds	O
Bengall	O
silk	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
she	O
comes	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
sometimes	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
very	O
little	O
acquaintance	O
or	O
conversation	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
but	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
family	O
-	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
diamond	O
cutter	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
318.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
dial-plate	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
metal	O
gilt	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
case	O
covered	O
with	O
leather	O
,	O
imitating	O
shagreen	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
edges	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
,	O
May	O
15	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Abchurch	B-place
lane	I-place
,	O
in	O
Lombard	B-place
street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
boy	O
under	O
some	O
concern	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
intimated	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
watch	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
dial	O
plate	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
middle	O
sized	O
man	O
,	O
pitted	O
with	O
the	O
small	O
pox	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
imagined	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
an	O
advertisement	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
out	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
with	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
over	O
all	O
thoughts	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
3	O
weeks	O
a	O
person	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Bride	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
advertised	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
coffee	O
house	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
coffee	O
room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
about	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Lambert	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
face	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
lyes	O
in	O
your	O
power	O
to	O
do	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
at	O
any	O
rate	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
reputation	O
would	O
be	O
spoilt	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
intimated	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
reputation	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
worth	O
much	O
long	O
;	O
meaning	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
live	O
long	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
hanged	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
knows	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Matthew	B-pers
Man	I-pers
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
room	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
first	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
Southamp	O
ton	O
Row	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
find	O
out	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
must	O
stand	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
my	O
boy	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
deny	O
it	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Lambert	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
chairmen	O
,	O
a	O
publick-house	O
near	O
where	O
his	O
master	O
lives	O
.	O
[	O
King	O
's	O
Street	O
Bloomsbury	O
]	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lambert	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
a	O
watch	O
away	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
several	O
questions	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
his	O
watch	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
we	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
one	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
watch	O
lay	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
missed	O
that	O
watch	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
of	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
could	O
come	O
in	O
but	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
directly	O
see	O
which	O
way	O
the	O
person	O
went	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
concern	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
out	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
acquainted	O
my	O
master	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
person	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
dressed	O
in	O
blue	O
grey	O
,	O
turned	O
up	O
with	O
yellow	O
plush	O
,	O
and	O
yellow	O
buttons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
any	O
other	O
description	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
own	O
hair	O
,	O
was	O
middle	O
sized	O
,	O
and	O
pitted	O
with	O
the	O
small-pox	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
or	O
can	O
you	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
circumstances	O
which	O
make	O
me	O
think	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
your	O
going	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Long	O
Room	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
your	O
master	O
then	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
reason	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
his	O
speech	O
was	O
altered	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Long	O
Room	O
he	O
was	O
leaning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Bridge	O
's	O
church	O
yard	O
,	O
in	O
Fleetstreet	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
being	O
recommended	O
by	O
a	O
neighbour	O
to	O
borrow	O
10	O
l.	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
security	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
15	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
this	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
for	O
this	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
all	O
gold	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
who	O
waits	O
on	O
me	O
was	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
looks	O
upon	O
the	O
register	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
register	O
where	O
I	O
enter	O
all	O
the	O
stolen	O
watches	O
in	O
,	O
every	O
day	O
from	O
the	O
advertiser	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
case	O
was	O
not	O
gold	O
,	O
though	O
to	O
some	O
eyes	O
it	O
may	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
gold	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
gold	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
comes	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
?	O
With	O
my	O
Lord	O
Portmore	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
odd	O
your	O
ambition	O
should	O
induce	O
you	O
to	O
wear	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
?	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
satisfy	O
me	O
in	O
that	O
particular	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
press	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
actually	O
very	O
genteely	O
dressed	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
could	O
well	O
be	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
livery	O
?	O
Piercy	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
dress	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
:	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
my	O
Lord	O
Portmore	O
himself	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
Lordship	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
gold	O
,	O
he	O
rapped	O
out	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
am	O
deceived	O
.	O
My	O
young	O
man	O
having	O
looked	O
upon	O
the	O
register	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
nod	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
agreed	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
after	O
this	O
manner	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
.	O
He	O
cursed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
your	O
blood	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
putting	O
my	O
watch	O
into	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
by	O
what	O
authority	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
advertisement	O
to	O
read	O
;	O
he	O
started	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
soon	O
bring	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
release	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
me	O
suffer	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
So	O
as	O
he	O
passed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
b	O
staying	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
crossing	O
from	O
Salisbury	O
court	O
to	O
Shoe	O
lane	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
seek	O
the	O
person	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
still	O
insisted	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
entreaties	O
were	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
back	O
by	O
main	O
force	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
struggling	O
he	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
being	O
stronger	O
than	O
I	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
up	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
to	O
strike	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
how	O
or	O
other	O
I	O
struck	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
decently	O
I	O
would	O
cane	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
to	O
go	O
quietly	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
shown	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Anderson	O
coffee	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
watch	O
cost	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
cost	O
50	O
s.	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
two	O
chairmen	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Lambert	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
the	O
inside	O
metal	O
gilt	O
,	O
and	O
gilt	O
on	O
the	O
edges	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
from	O
422	O
to	O
427	O
,	O
[	O
It	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
numbers	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Lambert	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Gibbon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Bloomsbury	O
square	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
about	O
my	O
size	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
two	O
chairmen	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
About	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
two	O
chairmen	O
-	O
in	O
King	O
's	O
street	O
,	O
by	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
grey	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
blue	O
grey	O
was	O
bargaining	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
3	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
case	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
It	O
looked	O
like	O
black	O
leather	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
who	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
somebody	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
just	O
now	O
two	O
men	O
bargaining	O
about	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
they	O
are	O
gone	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
you	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
bargaining	O
for	O
a	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
two	O
Chairmen	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
men	O
is	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
a	O
tidewaiter	O
in	O
Angel	O
Alley	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
widower	O
,	O
I	O
save	O
him	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
a	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
several	O
families	O
in	O
Gloucestershire	O
,	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
Lady	O
Cholmondley	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Caddy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
as	O
a	O
fellow	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
but	O
last	O
October	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Nicholls	O
of	O
Enfield	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
Lord	O
Castlecomer	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
asked	O
Esquire	O
Nicholls	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
honest	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
.	O
As	O
to	O
what	O
this	O
woman	O
has	O
said	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
manner	O
of	O
buying	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
quite	O
different	O
from	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
private	O
manner	O
,	O
that	O
neither	O
the	O
master	O
nor	O
the	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
could	O
tell	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
319	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Massey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mossey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
company	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
the	O
bedclothes	O
were	O
all	O
stripped	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
robbed	O
a	O
house	O
on	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
Green	I-place
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bye	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Martin	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Boy	O
Alley	O
gang	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Jeffs	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
executed	O
)	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
May	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
robbing	O
.	O
Martin	O
took	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
Jeffs	O
had	O
two	O
bunches	O
of	O
keys	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
Court	O
on	O
Clerkenwell	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
some	O
people	O
talking	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
Jeffs	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
wait	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
we	O
stood	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
Martin	O
went	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
outer	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
opened	O
with	O
a	O
latch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stairs	O
went	O
strait	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
try	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
open	O
the	O
kin	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
nickname	O
we	O
have	O
for	O
a	O
parlour	O
door	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
Jeffs	O
the	O
hanger	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
threw	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
out	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
a	O
quilt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
Jeffs	O
catched	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
(	O
wife	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
executed	O
)	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
notified	O
Hawkins	O
's	O
in	O
Golden	O
Lane	O
,	O
who	O
harbours	O
nothing	O
but	O
thieves	O
from	O
morning	O
till	O
night	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
fast	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
320	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
victualler	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
making	O
,	O
forging	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
false	O
making	O
,	O
forging	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
certain	O
acceptance	O
on	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
signed	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jos	O
.	O
Postweign	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
.	O
Which	O
said	O
bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
'	O
Exchange	O
63	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
'	O
Dublin	O
,	O
May	O
1	O
,	O
1745	O
.	O
'	O
Twenty	O
one	O
days	O
after	O
sight	O
pay	O
this	O
my	O
first	O
'	O
bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
to	O
Messieurs	O
Abraham	O
and	O
John	O
'	O
Duthoit	O
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
sixty	O
three	O
pounds	O
seventeen	O
'	O
shillings	O
.	O
'	O
From	O
your	O
humble	O
servant	O
,	O
'	O
Jos	O
.	O
Postweign	O
.	O
'	O
'	O
To	O
Mr	O
Peter	B-pers
Brozet	I-pers
Linen	I-pers
Draper	O
.	O
'	O
N.	O
564	O
.	O
Accepted	O
to	O
pay	O
in	O
Ports	O
,	O
'	O
May	O
9	O
1745	O
.	O
Indorsement	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Brozett	I-pers
.	O
'	O
Ab	O
.	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Duthoit	I-pers
.	O
'	O
Pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Geo	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
.	O
'	O
Pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
'	O
or	O
Order	O
the	O
Contents	O
.	O
'	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gunn	I-pers
.	O
'	O
Pay	O
the	O
Contents	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
or	O
Order	O
'	O
James	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
.	O
'	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
defraud	O
Peter	B-pers
Brozet	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
.	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Denis	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Whitson	O
Monday	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brozet	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Half	B-place
Moon	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
buying	O
some	O
cambrick	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Brozet	O
if	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Brozet	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
this	O
note	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brozet	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
marked	O
the	O
note	O
)	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
had	O
these	O
endorsements	O
then	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
then	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brozet	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
merchant	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Brozet	O
replied	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
this	O
note	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
note	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
drawer	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
replied	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
saying	O
that	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
directly	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Brozet	O
,	O
jun	O
.	O
This	O
acceptance	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
handwriting	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
far	O
from	O
it	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
to	O
the	O
acceptance	O
is	O
spelt	O
wrong	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
(	O
tt	O
's	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
but	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Suppose	O
you	O
had	O
found	O
this	O
Bill	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
you	O
have	O
tried	O
to	O
have	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Brozet	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
bid	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
?	O
Brozet	O
.	O
Nobody	O
I	O
do	O
assure	O
you	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
bill	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
read	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Kilsey	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
[	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
]	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ford	O
[	O
one	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
with	O
him	O
]	O
on	O
Whitsonday	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
shewed	O
me	O
this	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
bill	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
draught	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
over	O
due	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
by	O
the	O
New	O
Market	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
advertised	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
advertisement	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
go	O
and	O
shew	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brozet	O
,	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
negotiable	O
note	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mar	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
two	O
papers	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
read	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
read	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
read	O
them	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
I.	O
Justinian	O
Ekins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brewer	O
at	O
Westminster	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
he	O
write	O
?	O
Ekins	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
writes	O
a	O
very	O
ordinary	O
hand	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Nutter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
other	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Nutter	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
writes	O
as	O
ordinary	O
an	O
hand	O
as	O
any	O
person	O
I	O
ever	O
knew	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Council	O
.	O
This	O
acceptance	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
hand	O
.	O
It	O
not	O
being	O
proved	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
demand	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
321.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Percivall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
cambrick	O
cape	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
May	O
3	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
stand	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
rain	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
these	O
things	O
