TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
On	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
19th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
C.	O
NUTT	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
.	O
1748	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HOARE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
DENISON	O
,	O
Sir	O
SIMON	B-pers
URLING	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wyld	I-pers
,	O
Mark	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
Durham	O
Sharpe	O
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Crish	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Satchill	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Kettle	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bunny	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Billson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Solby	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Broadhead	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brackett	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Braddock	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Jost	I-pers
,	O
Leonard	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
36.	O
Mary	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
of	O
15	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
David	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
this	O
Woman	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
in	O
King-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
about	O
11	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Manner	O
?	O
Drummond	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
Family	O
I	O
met	O
three	O
Women	O
;	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
stuck	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Drummond	O
.	O
In	O
King-Street	O
,	O
opposite	O
George-Yard	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
you	O
base	O
Woman	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
away	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
perceive	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
.	O
Drummond	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
be	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
Woman	O
about	O
you	O
?	O
Drummond	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
caught	O
this	O
Woman	O
's	O
Hand	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
her	O
along	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
Money	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Drummond	O
.	O
Fifteen	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
your	O
15	O
s.	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
other	O
Women	O
as	O
close	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
put	O
their	O
Hands	O
into	O
your	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Drummond	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
so	O
close	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Woman	O
?	O
Drummond	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
that	O
very	O
Night	O
;	O
she	O
never	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hands	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Can	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
any	O
Questions	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
to	O
your	O
Advantage	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
and	O
hal	B-pers
'd	I-pers
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Drummond	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
hear	O
what	O
she	O
says	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Drummond	O
.	O
Nothing	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
given	O
that	O
Way	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Drummond	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
Woman	O
is	O
on	O
her	O
Trial	O
for	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
positive	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Pocket	O
?	O
Drummond	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
Woman	O
,	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Constable	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
15	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
further	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
;	O
were	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
this	O
Woman	O
before	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
Woman	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
a	O
troublesome	O
Woman	O
,	O
every	O
Body	O
knows	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
when	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
15	O
s.	O
But	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
search	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
15	O
s.	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
happen	O
'd	O
then	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
Money	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
she	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
5	O
s.	O
without	O
being	O
search	O
'd	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
delivering	O
the	O
5	O
s.	O
did	O
you	O
search	O
her	O
and	O
find	O
any	O
more	O
Money	O
upon	O
her	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
No	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
further	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
2	O
d.	O
1/2	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
2	O
d.	O
1/2	O
Moll	O
?	O
But	O
she	O
said	O
neither	O
one	O
Thing	O
nor	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
charge	O
Drummond	O
with	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
For	O
assaulting	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Drummond	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
I	O
pick	O
you	O
up	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
Question	O
has	O
been	O
answer	O
'd	O
already	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
Jury	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
the	O
Money	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
Purse	O
or	O
Bag	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
it	O
loose	O
in	O
your	O
Pocket	O
?	O
Drummond	O
.	O
Loose	O
in	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
Defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37.	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Herman	B-pers
Dock	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
Knife	O
,	O
and	O
wounding	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
desperate	O
and	O
cruel	O
Manner	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
wounding	O
Herman	O
Dock	O
?	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Matter	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
Day	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Webb	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
crying	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
she	O
?	O
Burt	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
own	O
Apartment	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
let	O
me	O
lay	O
with	O
your	O
Daughter	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
would	O
murder	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Murder	O
?	O
Burt	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
between	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
Disturbance	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
Tools	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
Stairs	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
strike	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
by	O
pulling	O
off	O
his	O
Coat	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
Candle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
is	O
this	O
Webb	O
of	O
?	O
Burt	O
.	O
A	O
Shoemaker	O
.	O
Then	O
my	O
Wife	O
and	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
went	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
himself	O
alone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Dock	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
Wife	O
?	O
Burt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
happen	O
'd	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
Burt	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
he	O
made	O
such	O
a	O
Noise	O
as	O
disturb	O
'd	O
the	O
Lodgers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
making	O
that	O
Noise	O
?	O
Burt	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
quite	O
into	O
his	O
Room	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Young	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Candlestick	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
by	O
himself	O
to	O
desire	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
Room	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
up	O
three	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Cry	O
,	O
Murder	O
,	O
Murder	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
lie	O
near	O
the	O
Window	O
of	O
my	O
Room	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
Guts	O
hanging	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
heard	O
the	O
Cry	O
,	O
Murder	O
,	O
after	O
you	O
was	O
got	O
down	O
the	O
Stairs	O
?	O
Burt	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
live	O
after	O
?	O
Burt	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
this	O
Accident	O
happen	O
?	O
Burt	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
did	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
die	O
of	O
the	O
Wound	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
?	O
Burt	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
Condition	O
,	O
how	O
soon	O
after	O
did	O
you	O
secure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Burt	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
above	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
able	O
to	O
speak	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
wounded	O
?	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
any	O
Account	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Burt	O
.	O
He	O
spoke	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Discourse	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
this	O
Matter	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Burt	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
look	O
'd	O
very	O
white	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
Knife	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Questions	O
to	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Frances	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Frances	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
.	O
When	O
my	O
Husband	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
abus	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
But	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
down	O
Stairs	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
of	O
Cursing	O
and	O
Swearing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
pray	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
and	O
pacify	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
the	O
Young	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
above	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Minutes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
God	B-pers
,	I-pers
O	I-pers
God	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
my	O
Shop	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
Mother	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
stabb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
kill	O
'd	O
!	O
He	O
pull	O
'd	O
away	O
his	O
Shirt	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
in	O
my	O
Apron	O
:	O
He	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
Hole	O
and	O
there	O
hung	O
out	O
his	O
Guts	O
.	O
Running	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
leaning	O
with	O
his	O
Head	O
by	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
Murder	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
only	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
without	O
any	O
Provocation	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
stabb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
,	O
being	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
we	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
.	O
Sir	O
Thomas	O
was	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
hear	O
the	O
dying	O
Words	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
the	O
Knife	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
after	O
?	O
Frances	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Knife	O
,	O
the	O
bloody	O
Shirt	O
and	O
Apron	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Frances	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
Knife	O
that	O
was	O
?	O
Frances	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
Knife	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Dennis	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
your	O
examining	O
this	O
Wound	O
?	O
Charles	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
Night	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Bart	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
Sake	O
come	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
below	O
the	O
Navel	O
,	O
the	O
Guts	O
and	O
Caul	O
hanging	O
out	O
at	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Hopes	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
was	O
not	O
mortal	O
;	O
because	O
the	O
Guts	O
seem	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
broke	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
by	O
the	O
great	O
Effusion	O
of	O
Blood	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
other	O
Part	O
wounded	O
within	O
:	O
The	O
Mortification	O
encreas	O
'd	O
every	O
Minute	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
Information	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
to	O
Sir	O
Thomas	O
:	O
At	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Request	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Guts	O
cut	O
thro	O
'	O
and	O
thro	O
'	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
must	O
have	O
reach	O
'd	O
quite	O
to	O
the	O
Back-Bone	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Dennis	O
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
Cause	O
of	O
Dock	O
's	O
Death	O
?	O
Dennis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
convinced	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
persuaded	O
that	O
the	O
Wound	O
would	O
prove	O
mortal	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
very	O
little	O
Hopes	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
what	O
Art	O
could	O
do	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
Upon	O
asking	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
how	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Desire	O
of	O
the	O
People	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
immediately	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
did	O
return	O
the	O
Blow	O
,	O
or	O
struggle	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
to	O
that	O
Purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Knife	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Wound	O
.	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
's	O
Letter	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
ran	O
thus	O
.	O
'	O
That	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
declard	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
'	O
pacify	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
But	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
Sudden	O
turning	O
'	O
a	O
little	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
snatching	O
up	O
a	O
large	O
Shoe-maker	O
's	O
'	O
Knife	O
,	O
he	O
thrust	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Body	O
,	O
'	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
he	O
lies	O
in	O
a	O
dying	O
Condition	O
.	O
'	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
hear	O
the	O
Evidence	O
given	O
against	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
about	O
a	O
little	O
Business	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
Home	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
my	O
Landlord	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
Cards	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
my	O
Landlord	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
Fellow	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
walk	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
going	O
out	O
that	O
Night	O
:	O
My	O
Landlord	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
ready	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
Blows	O
:	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
down	O
Stairs	O
and	O
fastened	O
my	O
Door	O
:	O
What	O
Noise	O
I	O
made	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
breaking	O
my	O
Coals	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Supper	O
,	O
eating	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
in	O
came	O
the	O
Deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
my	O
Door	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
:	O
He	O
ran	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
hurt	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
'till	O
the	O
People	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
Matter	O
.	O
He	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
hurt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
Room	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
any	O
Thing	O
more	O
than	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
Latch	O
of	O
your	O
Door	O
?	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
break	O
it	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
Knees	O
against	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
meant	O
the	O
Noise	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
breaking	O
of	O
Coals	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Chair	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
Way	O
he	O
was	O
hurt	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Knife	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
,	O
eating	O
my	O
Bread	O
and	O
Cheese	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
my	O
Pack	O
when	O
he	O
run	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Q.	O
have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
Child	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
Report	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
But	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
wrong	O
Man	O
,	O
Woman	O
or	O
Child	O
,	O
or	O
come	O
into	O
any	O
Quarrel	O
.	O
-	O
Perriman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
14	O
Years	O
,	O
was	O
born	O
and	O
bred	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
Town	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
any	O
other	O
than	O
a	O
very	O
inoffensive	O
Man	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Burt	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
the	O
Lock	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
broke	O
or	O
strain	O
'd	O
in	O
any	O
Manner	O
?	O
Burt	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Not	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
Crime	O
by	O
the	O
Coronel's-Inquest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
38.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Cust	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
Four	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
My	O
Maid	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Company	O
the	O
Evening	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Six	O
Clerks-Office	O
:	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
knew	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
Things	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
we	O
had	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
Company	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
that	O
Evening	O
but	O
themselves	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
guessing	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
one	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
pledge	O
Things	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
Place	O
we	O
asked	O
for	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
Plates	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
People	O
produced	O
directly	O
,	O
with	O
mine	O
and	O
my	O
Wife	O
's	O
Name	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
they	O
pawned	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Singleton	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Feather-stone	O
Buildings	O
,	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Singleton	O
shew	O
them	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
them	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
Hands	O
.	O
And	O
taking	O
out	O
two	O
Warrants	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
the	O
Goods	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
that	O
Night	O
before	O
Justice	O
Burdus	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
made	O
some	O
Confession	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Singleton	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
bringing	O
me	O
four	O
Plates	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Christopher	B-pers
Cust	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Cust	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
Company	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
's	O
to	O
play	O
a	O
Game	O
at	O
Skittles	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
hard	O
till	O
Night	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
confessing	O
the	O
Plates	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Confession	O
made	O
;	O
the	O
Plates	O
being	O
convey	O
'd	O
into	O
my	O
Pocket	O
without	O
my	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
-	O
Wainwright	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Fellow	O
then	O
behaved	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upwards	O
of	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
Character	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
Business	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Wainwright	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Story	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
Clerk	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
Clerk	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
honest	O
Man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Monkwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
considerable	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
reputed	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39.	O
Hester	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
of	O
a	O
Silver	O
Snuff-Box	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
Seven	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
Cold-bath	O
Fields	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
Mutton-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
staggering	O
and	O
falling	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
lifted	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
else	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
run	O
over	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
come	O
by	O
and	O
saved	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Magpye	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Ale	O
and	O
Gin	O
,	O
I	O
filled	O
my	O
Pipe	O
and	O
smoked	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
my	O
Snuff-Box	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
to	O
my	O
Landlady	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
Welsh-woman	O
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
sat	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
my	O
Box	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
Pinch	O
of	O
Snuff	O
,	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Pocket	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
my	O
Reckoning	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
with	O
me	O
over	O
Clerkenwell-Green	O
towards	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Wall	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
Left	O
Hand	O
about	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
Kiss	O
;	O
while	O
my	O
Left	O
Hand	O
was	O
round	O
her	O
Neck	O
,	O
her	O
Right	O
Hand	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
;	O
I	O
presently	O
missed	O
my	O
Box	O
,	O
but	O
away	O
she	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
Box	O
.	O
She	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
touch	O
me	O
if	O
you	O
dare	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
some	O
Accomplices	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
never	O
leave	O
you	O
till	O
I	O
bring	O
you	O
to	O
Justice	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
St.	O
John's-Street	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
of	O
an	O
Officer	O
.	O
It	O
wanted	O
but	O
a	O
Quarter	O
of	O
an	O
Hour	O
of	O
Nine	O
o'Clock	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
settled	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
charged	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
,	O
she	O
walked	O
out	O
under	O
a	O
Pretence	O
to	O
find	O
my	O
Box	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
a	O
Watchman	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
Landlady	O
;	O
who	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
if	O
she	O
has	O
not	O
picked	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
Box	O
?	O
Rutter	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
her	O
Work	O
very	O
quick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
Hand	O
in	O
your	O
Pocket	O
?	O
Rutter	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Box	O
again	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Rutter	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Rutter	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
Hand	O
upon	O
my	O
Box	O
five	O
Minutes	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
Bottle	O
of	O
Wine	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
And	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Griffith	B-pers
Dowel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Haster	O
Stephens	O
above	O
a	O
Year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Washer	O
of	O
Gentlemen	O
's	O
Linnen	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
found	O
her	O
dishonest	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hog	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
she	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Harm	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
40.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Welsh	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Gibson	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
14th	O
Day	O
of	O
December	O
my	O
Servant	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Thief	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
on	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
Servant	O
said	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Stockings	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
Gibson	O
.	O
Worsted	O
Stockings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
your	O
Servant	O
's	O
Name	O
?	O
Gibson	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Gibson	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
Pardon	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
He	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
Stockings	O
.	O
He	O
looked	O
out	O
two	O
Pair	O
,	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
End	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
slip	O
'd	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
follow	O
him	O
?	O
Gray	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
the	O
Stockings	O
?	O
Gray	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
Stockings	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Gray	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
himself	O
guilty	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
Exeter-Exchange	O
,	O
hearing	O
the	O
Cry	O
,	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
Resistance	O
,	O
but	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Stockings	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hop	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
Forgiveness	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
Fact	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Error	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
Necessity	O
obliged	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
41.	O
Jane	B-pers
Burle	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
great	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
Goods	O
did	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
lose	O
?	O
Mead	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
them	O
?	O
Was	O
this	O
Woman	O
conversant	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
?	O
Mead	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
a	O
Servant	O
with	O
a	O
Woman	O
next	O
Door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Mead	O
.	O
We	O
serv	O
'd	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
next	O
Door	O
with	O
Beer	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
.	O
Some	O
odd	O
Things	O
were	O
left	O
behind	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Mistress	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
moved	O
to	O
another	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
Dinner	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
Steak	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
dress	O
'd	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
drank	O
a	O
Pennyworth	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
her	O
Leave	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
missing	O
the	O
Box	O
with	O
the	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Apparel	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
challeng	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Box	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
Mistress	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
hoped	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
Thing	O
;	O
upon	O
searching	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Things	O
in	O
it	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
Mead	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Publick	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Maid	O
to	O
come	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
Mistress	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Mead	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
your	O
Box	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Mead	O
.	O
My	O
Box	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
at	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
Person	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
your	O
Box	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Mead	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
about	O
Three	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
about	O
Five	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
her	O
Mistress	O
's	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
Box	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Mead	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
Husband	O
did	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
42.	O
Richard	B-pers
Saimon	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
nine	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stockings	O
lost	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
my	O
little	O
Girl	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
take	O
a	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Age	O
is	O
your	O
Girl	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
Thief	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
:	O
With	O
that	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
running	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
pass	O
'd	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
Bundle	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
?	O
where	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
He	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Stockings	O
in	O
the	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
Coatham	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Coatham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
cry	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Bundle	O
and	O
a	O
Stick	O
in	O
his	O
Hand	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
Reason	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Bundle	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
shew	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
he	O
own	O
the	O
Stockings	O
.	O
Coatham	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
He	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
this	O
Time	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
Knees	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
Forgiveness	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Cry	O
of	O
stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
down	O
the	O
Stick	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
down	O
the	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
Manning	O
.	O
He	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
for	O
Mercy	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
Forgiveness	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pardoe	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
James	I-pers
(	O
Daughter	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
on	O
Friday	O
was	O
sen'night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
suspect	O
her	O
taking	O
away	O
the	O
Money	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
My	O
Father	O
was	O
afraid	O
Mary	B-pers
Pardoe	I-pers
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
ill	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
at	O
his	O
Breeches	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
rais	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
look	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
two	O
half	O
Crowns	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
left	O
.	O
He	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
Drawers	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
took	O
nothing	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
what	O
Gold	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
what	O
Silver	O
:	O
Accordingly	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Money	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Black-Boy-Ally	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
Clothes	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
:	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
Fact	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
Knees	O
to	O
implore	O
Mercy	O
:	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
3	O
s.	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Breeches	O
and	O
the	O
6	O
s.	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	O
Lane	O
.	O
)	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
Seventeen	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Foucher	O
's	O
take	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Rag	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Bits	O
of	O
Gold	O
in	O
her	O
Mouth	O
,	O
and	O
hold	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Foucher	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lovage	O
;	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
;	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Pints	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
at	O
her	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
starv	O
'd	O
:	O
But	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
Rag	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Bosom	O
or	O
Pocket	O
,	O
with	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
Gold	O
?	O
Foucher	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
44.	O
Jasper	B-pers
Godby	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Collin	B-pers
Innys	I-pers
.	O
January	O
,	O
10	O
.	O
Collin	B-pers
Innys	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
Back	O
Gate	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Elias	I-pers
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bosom	O
;	O
my	O
own	O
Handkerchief	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
dispute	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
Exchange	O
:	O
We	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
three	O
more	O
Handkerchiefs	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
own	O
Handkerchief	O
worth	O
?	O
Innys	O
.	O
It	O
cost	O
2	O
s.	O
Joseph	O
Threadcall	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
Instant	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
past	O
two	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
Change-Gate	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Innys	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
Tobacco-Box	O
and	O
four	O
Handkerchiefs	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Account	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
of	O
these	O
Handkerchiefs	O
then	O
?	O
Threadcall	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
tristing	O
Excuses	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Elias	I-pers
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
how	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Pocket	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
?	O
Elias	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
Defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
Handkerchief	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45.	O
James	B-pers
Casttelow	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Parcel	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
upon	O
Buttle-Wharf	B-place
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
May	O
.	O
This	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
took	O
upon	O
Buttle-Whars	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
?	O
May	O
.	O
In	O
December	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
steal	O
4	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
;	O
he	O
appear	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
Coal-heaver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
convey	O
'd	O
?	O
May	O
.	O
Some	O
into	O
his	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
some	O
into	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Excuses	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Coopers	O
and	O
the	O
Porters	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
helping	O
them	O
to	O
roll	O
the	O
Hogsheads	O
up	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
any	O
Questions	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
catch	O
me	O
before	O
in	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
?	O
May	O
.	O
Several	O
Times	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Mascle	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
about	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Mascle	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
Poverty	O
was	O
the	O
Occasion	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
Tobacco	O
before	O
?	O
Mascle	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Murgrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
32	O
Years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
Character	O
?	O
Murgrey	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
his	O
Character	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
good	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
Servant	O
to	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Uncle	O
and	O
in	O
other	O
Services	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
-	O
Ascenally	O
.	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Ascenally	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
Father	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
here	O
an	O
London	O
seven	O
Years	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
Dishonesty	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
46.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Read	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
Pocket	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
of	O
six	O
Guineas	O
and	O
a	O
Shilling	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Abroad	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
,	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
Quarters	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
Down	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
all	O
Day	O
till	O
Night	O
:	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Calloe	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
House	O
where	O
I	O
lodg	O
'd	O
:	O
Upon	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
dry	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
And	O
two	O
Women	O
brought	O
the	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Wind	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
shut	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
.	O
Thorn	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
Between	O
Eight	O
and	O
Nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
the	O
Women	O
came	O
in	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
The	O
Woman	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Way	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
receiv	O
'd	O
my	O
Money	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Person	O
's	O
Name	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
bring	O
your	O
Liquor	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
Beer	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
took	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
Drink	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
take	O
my	O
Breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
your	O
Breechees	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Bolster	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
take	O
my	O
Breeches	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
my	O
Money	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
Haste	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Thorn	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
Side	O
of	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
Money	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
to	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
deliver	O
it	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
Breeches	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
Six	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
six	O
Shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
French	O
Crown	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
Woman	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
here	O
but	O
me	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
Woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
you	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Door	O
at	O
the	O
Foot	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
shut	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
came	O
up	O
making	O
a	O
great	O
Noise	O
for	O
my	O
Money	O
,	O
hypocritically	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
become	O
of	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
all	O
this	O
Time	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
had	O
my	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
Woman	O
give	O
Sarah	B-pers
Read	I-pers
the	O
Money	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
Room	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a-bed	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
?	O
Q.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
whether	O
any	O
Woman	O
was	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
none	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
Pot	O
of	O
Beer	O
?	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
where	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
was	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
Beer	O
?	O
You	O
insist	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
was	O
not	O
in	O
Bed	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
Vault	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
sat	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
talk	O
very	O
merrily	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
of	O
the	O
Soldier	O
.	O
My	O
Vault	O
and	O
theirs	O
joined	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
say	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Walter	O
.	O
They	O
wonder	O
'd	O
how	O
the	O
Soldier	O
had	O
got	O
so	O
much	O
Money	O
about	O
him	O
as	O
six	O
Guineas	O
and	O
six	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
?	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Read	I-pers
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
?	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
her	O
Countryman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
her	O
Bosom	O
open	O
;	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
search	O
'd	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
That	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Guineas	O
.	O
So	O
Mary	O
Bell	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
Treat	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
,	O
this	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
gives	O
him	O
the	O
Slip	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
?	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
were	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Calloe	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
was	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
But	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
)	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Lodger	O
there	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Howe	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
conversant	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Howe	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
known	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Person	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
47.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eyres	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
several	O
Sets	O
of	O
Harnesses	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
his	B-pers
Majesty	I-pers
.	O
-	O
Pool	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Collar-maker	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
Harness	O
for	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
Use	O
of	O
the	O
Train	O
of	O
Artillery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
known	O
of	O
these	O
Harnesses	O
?	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Leather	O
Tuggs	O
that	O
are	O
mention	O
'd	O
?	O
Pool	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
's	O
Hands	O
at	O
the	O
Tower	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
the	O
Harness	O
and	O
Leather	O
Tuggs	O
that	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
?	O
Council	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
Pool	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
Harnesses	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
Kind	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
knows	O
this	O
particular	O
Harness	O
?	O
Pool	O
.	O
These	O
were	O
made	O
with	O
an	O
Iron	O
Ring	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
such	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
Shovel	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
House	O
in	O
Paulin-Yard	O
,	O
Tyburn-Road	O
,	O
take	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Harnes	O
s	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
Brewing-Vessel	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
no	O
Questions	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
Harness	O
.	O
Eyres	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Harness	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
upon	O
the	O
Horses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
Eyres	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Paulin-Yard	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
Harness	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Thing	O
more	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Says	O
Eyres	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
Harness	O
of	O
the	O
Horse	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
did	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Brewhouse	O
Yesterday	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
your	O
Horse	O
blind	O
?	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
my	O
Life	O
:	O
But	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Horse	O
with	O
this	O
Harness	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Roberts	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
Harness	O
,	O
you	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
them	O
?	O
Council	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
has	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
run	O
away	O
since	O
this	O
Prosecution	O
?	O
Then	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
Eyres	O
)	O
did	O
not	O
inform	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Harness	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
Harness	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
Horse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
this	O
Harness	O
?	O
Ford	O
.	O
The	O
Harness	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
hear	O
that	O
Smith	O
used	O
to	O
let	O
out	O
Harness	O
?	O
Ford	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Harness	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
]	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Pool	O
.	O
)	O
Were	O
these	O
the	O
Harness	O
you	O
made	O
?	O
Pool	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Roberts	O
.	O
)	O
Were	O
these	O
the	O
Harness	O
you	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Brewing-Vessel	O
of	O
Smith	O
's	O
in	O
Paulin-Yard	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Pool	O
.	O
)	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Harness	O
deliver	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Tower	O
of	O
your	O
making	O
?	O
Pool	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
these	O
Harness	O
in	O
Smith	O
's	O
Brewhouse	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
on	O
Eyres	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
)	O
Pool	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Eyres	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Collar-maker	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
one	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Boy	O
's	O
Defence	O
is	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
industrious	O
Boy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
used	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
Harness	O
of	O
this	O
Smith	O
;	O
that	O
this	O
Hemmings	O
did	O
own	O
he	O
borrow	O
'd	O
these	O
Harness	O
of	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lent	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
Boy	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Gilbert	O
.	O
In	O
Paulin-Yard	O
Paulin-Street	O
near	O
Oxford-Road	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
are	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Eyres	O
?	O
Gilbert	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
both	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
especially	O
Eyres	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
is	O
Hemmings	O
?	O
Gilbert	O
.	O
He	O
stands	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
Discourse	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Gilbert	O
.	O
Never	O
,	O
but	O
once	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Days	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
Trade	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
was	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
let	O
out	O
Horses	O
?	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
let	O
out	O
any	O
Harness	O
?	O
Gilbert	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
Smith	O
abscond	O
?	O
Gilbert	O
.	O
The	O
Day	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gilbert	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
Eyres	O
's	O
Character	O
?	O
How	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
his	O
Livelihood	O
?	O
What	O
his	O
general	O
Character	O
is	O
?	O
Gilbert	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
the	O
Character	O
in	O
the	O
Neighbourhood	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Boy	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
is	O
Eyres	O
's	O
general	O
Character	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
or	O
bad	O
Character	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Beer	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
is	O
Hemmings	O
's	O
Character	O
Beer	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dow	I-pers
.	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Hemmings	O
.	O
Dow	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
both	O
from	O
their	O
Infancy	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Harm	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Millar	I-pers
.	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
Hemmings	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
Character	O
do	O
you	O
give	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Millar	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
Pains-taking	O
working	O
Boy	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
18	O
Years	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Christopher	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
Hemmings	O
's	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
He	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Bouzier	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
Hemmings	O
's	O
Character	O
?	O
Bouzier	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hemmings	O
17	O
or	O
18	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
both	O
?	O
Bouzier	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Hazlewood	I-pers
.	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
Hemmings	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
Character	O
has	O
he	O
?	O
Hazlewood	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
Infancy	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Person	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Roberts	O
.	O
)	O
Has	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
a	O
Stable	O
near	O
to	O
that	O
Place	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Several	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
48.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Zell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Buttons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Munro	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
Ratcliff-Cross	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
Instant	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Munro	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
Rings	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
.	O
Munro	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
Rings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Buttons	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Ear-rings	O
.	O
The	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
broke	O
open	O
my	O
Maid	O
's	O
Chest	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
at	O
Ratcliff-Cross	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
quarter	O
'd	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Munro	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
two	O
Nights	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Maid	O
's	O
Name	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
:	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
her	O
Chest	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
found	O
out	O
?	O
Munro	O
.	O
We	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Soldier	O
with	O
this	O
Robbery	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
behis	O
Serjeant	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Chest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
about	O
the	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
?	O
Munro	O
.	O
The	O
Serjeant	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
whipp	O
'd	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
for	O
stealing	O
.	O
Says	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
yourself	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
two	O
Rings	O
:	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
King's-Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
.	O
The	O
Serjeant	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
Ring	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
's	O
Name	O
?	O
Munro	O
.	O
Robertson	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
Pocket	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
a	O
Silver	O
Seal	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
?	O
Curtis	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Two	O
of	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
I	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
Feet	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
Bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
get	O
your	O
get	O
Seal	O
and	O
Money	O
again	O
?	O
Curtis	O
.	O
The	O
Money	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Seal	O
he	O
flung	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
Robertson	O
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
's	O
when	O
the	O
Lad	O
was	O
accused	O
of	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
young	O
Woman	O
's	O
Chest	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
5	O
s.	O
11	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
Crowns	O
and	O
Sixpence	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Knees	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Rings	O
,	O
missing	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Munro	O
from	O
his	O
Drawer	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
likewise	O
got	O
the	O
Money	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
Ring	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Munro	O
.	O
)	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
Ring	O
?	O
Munro	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
my	O
Ring	O
indeed	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Robertson	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Day	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Maid	O
.	O
)	O
How	O
much	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
Chest	O
?	O
Curtis	O
.	O
Three	O
half	O
Crown	O
Pieces	O
and	O
three	O
single	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
found	O
two	O
half	O
Crowns	O
and	O
Sixpence	O
you	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Knees	O
of	O
his	O
Breeches	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
about	O
the	O
Seal	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
flung	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
Sink	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Ross	O
's	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
of	O
the	O
Girl	O
's	O
Chest	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
Chisel	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
In	O
King's-Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
Ring	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
it	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
Shew	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Munro	O
?	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Munro	O
.	O
)	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
Ring	O
?	O
Munro	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
these	O
Witnesses	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Will	O
you	O
call	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
nor	O
have	O
I	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
to	O
produce	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
49.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
of	O
Clerkenwell-Close	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
Husband	O
's	O
dwelling-House	O
?	O
Osborne	O
.	O
In	O
Clerkenwell-Close	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
?	O
Osborne	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Manner	O
was	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Osborne	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
broke	O
a	O
Pain	O
of	O
Glass	O
of	O
the	O
Closet-Window	O
in	O
the	O
Garden	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Window	O
safe	O
before	O
?	O
Osborne	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
safe	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
open	O
?	O
Osborne	O
.	O
The	O
Window	O
was	O
shut	O
?	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Pain	O
out	O
about	O
Eight	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
lost	O
?	O
Osborne	O
.	O
A	O
Copper-pot	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
three	O
Handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
these	O
Handkerchiefs	O
?	O
Osborne	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Pawn	O
.	O
The	O
Handkerchiefs	O
and	O
Pot	O
at	O
two	O
different	O
Places	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
Means	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
these	O
Things	O
.	O
Osborne	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
own	O
Information	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Osborne	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Osborne	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hole	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
own	O
the	O
Fault	O
in	O
general	O
Terms	O
?	O
Osborne	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
his	O
Parents	O
?	O
Osborne	O
.	O
Silver-Spoon-makers	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Vagabond	O
and	O
has	O
nobody	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50.	O
Roger	B-pers
Galder	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Quantity	O
of	O
Linnen	O
and	O
Wearing	O
Apparel	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
of	O
Spur-Street	B-place
by	I-place
Leicester-Fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
Goods	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
and	O
what	O
Time	O
?	O
Hughes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Hughes	O
.	O
In	O
Spur-Street	O
by	O
Leicester-Fields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Hughes	O
.	O
A	O
flower	O
'd	O
Linnen	O
Gown	O
and	O
another	O
Gown	O
,	O
a	O
Petticoat	O
and	O
a	O
Shift	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
these	O
Goods	O
?	O
Hughes	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
Bed-Chamber	O
up	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Hughes	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Hughes	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hunt	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Goods	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Housekeeper	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Hughes	O
lodges	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
The	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
Hours	O
of	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
cross	O
my	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
(	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
Boy	O
)	O
and	O
being	O
very	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
Business	O
she	O
had	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
having	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Kent	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
under	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
nothing	O
then	O
of	O
Galder	O
(	O
the	O
Boy	O
?	O
)	O
Hunt	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
Evening	O
the	O
Robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
drinking	O
a	O
Dish	O
of	O
Tea	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Hughes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
committed	O
a	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
Kent	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
Boy	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
thrown	O
the	O
Goods	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
to	O
receive	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
farther	O
?	O
Hughes	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
Bundle	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Sister	O
's	O
Goods	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
.	O
)	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
understand	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
false	O
Oath	O
?	O
Suppose	O
you	O
should	O
swear	O
or	O
speak	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
is	O
false	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
burn	O
in	O
Hell-Fire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Galder	I-pers
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
Not	O
before	O
this	O
Time	O
.	O
This	O
Girl	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
Bargain	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
Thieving	O
:	O
At	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
And	O
going	O
along	O
Leicester-Fields	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
Boy	O
,	O
Roger	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
saw	O
the	O
Entry-Door	O
open	O
of	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
the	O
Stocking-Shop	O
:	O
And	O
the	O
Girl	O
and	O
Boy	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
Ladder	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
to	O
see	O
which	O
Way	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
Ladder	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
some	O
Leads	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
both	O
get	O
up	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
get	O
up	O
the	O
Ladder	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
Ladder	O
.	O
They	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Girl	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
Window	O
.	O
And	O
so	O
the	O
Boy	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
Yard	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
they	O
gone	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
Hours	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
About	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
The	O
Boy	O
got	O
the	O
Bundle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Girl	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Boy	O
toss	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
The	O
Girl	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
stay	O
two	O
Hours	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
about	O
that	O
House	O
and	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Boy	O
come	O
down	O
again	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
No	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
have	O
the	O
Bundle	O
?	O
Gough	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Girl	O
have	O
the	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Boy	O
meddle	O
with	O
that	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Gough	O
.	O
No	O
Sir	O
.	O
Boy	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
51.	O
James	B-pers
Solovan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
on	O
the	O
Keys	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Capt	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sutcliff	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
William	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
As	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
Day	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
stripping	O
Tobacco	O
for	O
Capt	O
.	O
Sutcliff	O
,	O
on	O
Buttle-Wharf	B-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
sculking	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
Cooper	O
a	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
the	O
Porters	O
.	O
And	O
every	O
Hogshead	O
he	O
came	O
at	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
Tobacco	O
:	O
And	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Porters	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
Pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
conceal	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
Pockets	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
his	O
leather	O
Apron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
Tobacco	O
?	O
May	O
.	O
About	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Suteliff	O
's	O
Hogsheads	O
?	O
May	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
other	O
Hogsheads	O
on	O
the	O
Keys	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Dark-house-Lane	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
-	O
Maschil	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
deny	O
'd	O
this	O
Charge	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Hazle	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Hazle	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
small	O
Time	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Hazle	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
Time	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
his	O
Bread	O
upon	O
the	O
Keys	O
by	O
helping	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Hazle	O
.	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Hazle	O
.	O
Almost	O
30	O
Years	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
Year	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
his	O
Character	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Hazle	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
Thing	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
May	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
this	O
Man	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
?	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
employ	O
'd	O
above	O
once	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Maschil	O
Constable	O
.	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
frequenting	O
the	O
Keys	O
.	O
Maschil	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
him	O
above	O
two	O
Months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
Porter	O
?	O
Maschil	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
employ	O
'd	O
for	O
an	O
Hour	O
or	O
so	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
52.	O
James	B-pers
Woollard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
Iron	O
Roasting-Jack	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
in	O
Service	O
Time	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
Jack	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
?	O
Nichols	O
.	O
Between	O
Eleven	O
and	O
Twelve	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Body	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
shut	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
This	O
Gentleman	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wealy	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Brother	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
lodges	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Way	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Church	O
.	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Church	O
Door	O
to	O
hear	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Servant	O
read	O
the	O
Gazette	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
this	O
Lad	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
Great	O
Coat	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
a	O
Jack	O
.	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
almost	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Christ	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
Jack	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
Jack	O
?	O
Wealy	O
.	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
one	O
Wilks	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
3	O
d.	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
fetch	O
this	O
Jack	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
'Prentice	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
53.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stanbury	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Shifts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cranford	I-pers
of	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Cranford	I-pers
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Stanbury	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Charewoman	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Bed	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
Pillow	O
upon	O
my	O
Bed	O
more	O
than	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
might	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
Lodging	O
.	O
I	O
reckon	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
coming	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
Boxes	O
of	O
my	O
Grand	O
Mother	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
Care	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
Mother	O
died	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Boxes	O
was	O
like	O
to	O
fall	O
down	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
up	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
Rooms	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Boxes	O
I	O
found	O
uncorded	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
this	O
Anne	B-pers
Stanbury	I-pers
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
early	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
discharged	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
home	O
all	O
Night	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Bunnel-Row	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
the	O
Pillow	O
came	O
upon	O
my	O
Bed	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
My	O
Dear	O
Mistress	O
,	O
she	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
wrong	O
'd	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
asham	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
Boxes	O
:	O
Indeed	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Mistress	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
and	O
I	O
uncorded	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
And	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
give	O
her	O
Trouble	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Kiese	O
's	O
,	O
Pawn-broker	O
in	O
Cheek-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
another	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
two	O
Parcels	O
more	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Sharp	O
's	O
on	O
Saffron-Hill	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
release	O
her	O
'till	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
whether	O
these	O
were	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
Mother	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
was	O
nor	O
half	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sent	O
to	O
Kiese	O
's	O
for	O
a	O
Holland	O
Apron	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
Pawn-broker	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
before	O
.	O
Then	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
Mistress	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
of	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
them	O
out-right	O
to	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
She	O
often	O
used	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
question	O
'd	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
good	O
Things	O
in	O
these	O
Boxes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
got	O
part	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
then	O
?	O
Anne	B-pers
Cranford	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Cranford	I-pers
of	O
Hamstead	O
.	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
these	O
Things	O
that	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Custody	O
of	O
your	O
Grand-Daughter	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Cranford	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
my	O
Grand-Daughter	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
Boxes	O
were	O
there	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Cranford	I-pers
.	O
Three	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Goods	O
I	O
have	O
mention	O
'd	O
were	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
Boxes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
Money	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
under	O
Necessity	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Cranford	I-pers
.	O
)	O
She	O
therefore	O
pawn	O
'd	O
these	O
Things	O
at	O
your	O
Desire	O
?	O
Anne	B-pers
Cranford	I-pers
.	O
No	O
indeed	O
,	O
please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
bidden	O
her	O
break	O
these	O
Boxes	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
lent	O
her	O
Money	O
;	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
Week	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
54.	O
Anne	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Holland	O
Shift	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Bartholina	B-pers
Cromarty	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Bartholina	O
Crom	O
arty	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
these	O
Goods	O
?	O
Cromarty	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
sen'night	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
our	O
Service	O
this	O
Day	O
fortnight	O
about	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
Goods	O
upon	O
her	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Cromarty	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
That	O
Cloak	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
now	O
round	O
her	O
Neck	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
Goods	O
?	O
Cromarty	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
Language	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Goods	O
,	O
a	O
Long-Lawn	O
Apron	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
Women	O
's	O
Pumps	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Buttons	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
these	O
?	O
Cromarty	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
serve	O
me	O
so	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
banish	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
weary	O
of	O
living	O
here	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
.	O
These	O
People	O
are	O
very	O
notorious	O
,	O
they	O
keep	O
a	O
notorious	O
Bawdy-House	O
.	O
Neither	O
did	O
I	O
ever	O
wrong	O
them	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Mistress	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
took	O
two	O
Creatures	O
into	O
your	O
House	O
that	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
your	O
Goods	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
serv	O
'd	O
my	O
Mistress	O
two	O
Years	O
ago	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
making	O
Complaint	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
several	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
Husband	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
Writ	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
chuse	O
to	O
be	O
arrested	O
in	O
a	O
wrong	O
Cause	O
.	O
My	O
Mistress	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
Dear	O
,	O
pray	O
do	O
n't	O
get	O
yourself	O
into	O
a	O
Jail	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
taking	O
these	O
Goods	O
,	O
were	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
Possession	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
the	O
Cloak	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
the	O
Shift	O
upon	O
her	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cap	O
upon	O
her	O
Head	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
got	O
into	O
vile	O
Hands	O
.	O
She	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Pliers	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
swear	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
55.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Sconce	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
of	O
Bridges-Street	B-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
Corner	I-place
of	I-place
Clear's-Passage	I-place
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Howard	O
,	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
e'er	O
a	O
Glass-Sconce	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
Room	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
large	O
Sconce-Glass	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
Sconce	O
?	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
Room	O
next	O
the	O
Street	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
Back-Door	O
up	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
catch	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
Judith	B-pers
Cabino	I-pers
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Cabino	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
the	O
Glass	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
?	O
You	O
saw	O
her	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
with	O
the	O
Sconce	O
in	O
her	O
Hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
Glass	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
meet	O
her	O
coming	O
down	O
Stairs	O
?	O
Cabino	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
who	O
brought	O
her	O
up	O
Stairs	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
Glass	O
and	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
to	O
bring	O
down	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
Glass	O
?	O
Cabino	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Cabino	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Servant	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Gentleman	O
up	O
Stairs	O
?	O
Cabino	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
about	O
that	O
Time	O
?	O
Cabino	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Creature	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Playhouse-Passage	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
took	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
off	O
my	O
Neck	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
Gentlewoman	O
keeps	O
a	O
disorderly	O
House	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
after	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
Steps	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
,	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
coming	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
House	O
near	O
the	O
Playhouse	O
?	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
the	O
Corner	O
House	O
as	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
Bridges-street	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
an	O
Errand	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
Playhouse-Passage	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
then	O
?	O
Gurney	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Back	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
old	O
white	O
Handkerchief	O
:	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
pursuing	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
this	O
Mrs.	O
Howard	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
her	O
Coffee-Room	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Her	O
Maid	O
came	O
down	O
Stairs	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
Coffee-House	O
because	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
assaulted	O
you	O
.	O
You	O
charged	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
with	O
the	O
Handkerchief	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
House	O
indicted	O
.	O
Cabino	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Stairs	O
with	O
my	O
Mistress	O
's	O
Gown	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Glass	O
on	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
you	O
up	O
Stairs	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
went	O
up	O
two	O
Steps	O
of	O
the	O
Stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
brought	O
the	O
Glass	O
down	O
Stairs	O
?	O
Cabino	O
.	O
That	O
Woman	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
the	O
Glass	O
was	O
brought	O
down	O
Stairs	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
had	O
this	O
Glass	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Cabino	O
.	O
)	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Room	O
?	O
she	O
talks	O
of	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
being	O
up	O
Stairs	O
?	O
Cabino	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
Gentleman	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
fixing	O
up	O
Sconces	O
being	O
a	O
Branch	O
of	O
his	O
Business	O
,	O
the	O
Girl	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
have	O
taken	O
down	O
the	O
Sconce	O
by	O
herself	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
56.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Tidmash	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Grates	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Loat	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
several	O
Times	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
late	O
.	O
My	O
Servant	O
told	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Grates	O
.	O
My	O
Servant	O
found	O
the	O
Grates	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Athill	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Servant	O
's	O
Name	O
?	O
Loat	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Servant	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Day	O
for	O
Sale	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Grates	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Athill	O
's	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
her	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
there	O
?	O
Loat	O
.	O
Her	O
Daughter	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
her	O
Mother	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
the	O
Day	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Athill	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
?	O
Athill	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
House	O
on	O
New	O
Year's-Day	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
with	O
the	O
said	O
Grates	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Daughter	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
?	O
Athill	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
Daughter	O
a	O
Shilling	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
Grates	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Susannah	B-pers
Athill	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Daughter	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
buy	O
the	O
Grates	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Tidmash	O
?	O
Susannah	B-pers
Athill	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
Grates	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
Susannah	B-pers
Atbill	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Loat	O
came	O
to	O
demand	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Mr.	O
Loat	O
say	O
?	O
Susannah	B-pers
Athill	I-pers
.	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
Demand	O
of	O
the	O
Grates	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Susannah	B-pers
Athill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
said	O
my	O
Mother	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
deliver	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
Person	O
by	O
her	O
passing	O
often	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
Name	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
her	O
out	O
?	O
Susannah	B-pers
Athill	I-pers
,	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
at	O
her	O
Uncle	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
near	O
our	O
House	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
Grates	O
to	O
our	O
Shop	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Loat	O
.	O
)	O
That	O
Grate	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
demand	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Athill	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
your	O
Grate	O
?	O
Loat	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
us	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
Loat	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Athill	O
's	O
Daughter	O
refused	O
giving	O
me	O
the	O
Grate	O
,	O
not	O
thinking	O
it	O
proper	O
till	O
she	O
had	O
advised	O
with	O
her	O
Mother	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
Time	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Shop	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
Person	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
Woman	O
,	O
remarkable	O
for	O
fore	O
Eyes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
another	O
Woman	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
Grate	O
.	O
But	O
Loat	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Athill	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
the	O
Shilling	O
when	O
she	O
could	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
57.	O
Philip	B-pers
Burne	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Flock	O
Bed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
of	O
Dudley-Court	B-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Freeman	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Dudley-Court	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Room	O
of	O
one	O
Ruth	O
Burne	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
there	O
a	O
Flock	O
Bed	O
,	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bolster	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Sheets	O
,	O
two	O
Quilts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Blankets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
furnish	O
the	O
Room	O
yourself	O
?	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
this	O
Room	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
six	O
Weeks	O
before	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
your	O
Lodgings	O
;	O
how	O
came	O
it	O
that	O
your	O
Bed	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Freeman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
daily	O
Labour	O
,	O
as	O
Washing	O
and	O
Ironing	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
my	O
Bed	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
About	O
Six	O
o'Clock	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Thing	O
else	O
gone	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
Things	O
besides	O
what	O
has	O
been	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
three	O
Days	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
Bed	O
and	O
Bedding	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
Relation	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
your	O
Landlady	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
was	O
you	O
not	O
much	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
to	O
find	O
your	O
Bed	O
gone	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
ask	O
your	O
Landlady	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
pray	O
did	O
not	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
Reason	O
why	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
stripping	O
and	O
robbing	O
of	O
her	O
likewise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
this	O
Burne	O
and	O
your	O
Landlady	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
Man	O
and	O
Wife	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
For	O
they	O
were	O
always	O
jarring	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
Bed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
lay	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Perkin	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
in	O
Relation	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
doing	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
Perkin	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Bed	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Perkin	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Officer	O
came	O
to	O
serve	O
a	O
Warrant	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
?	O
Perkin	O
.	O
In	O
Short's-Gardens	O
Drury-Lane	O
:	O
And	O
I	O
think	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Perkin	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
very	O
Man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
the	O
Bed	O
was	O
he	O
had	O
upon	O
his	O
Back	O
?	O
Perkins	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
ty	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
Quilt	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
believe	O
Anne	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
to	O
be	O
the	O
Owner	O
.	O
Jossiah	O
Morphew	O
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
an	O
Assault	O
.	O
This	O
Anne	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
Bed	O
and	O
Bedding	O
away	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Jane	B-pers
Perkin	I-pers
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Short's-Gardens	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
run	O
,	O
run	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
under	O
the	O
Gateway	O
:	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
Warrant	O
against	O
you	O
Friend	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
Bed	O
down	O
:	O
Then	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
Tussle	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fisher	O
,	O
I	O
charge	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Name	O
to	O
assist	O
;	O
accordingly	O
his	O
Man	O
came	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
Bed	O
and	O
Bedding	O
after	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
would	O
you	O
ask	O
the	O
Witness	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
ask	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
marry	O
'd	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
because	O
that	O
Woman	O
(	O
the	O
Witness	O
)	O
swore	O
3	O
l.	O
3	O
s	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
say	O
this	O
Mary	B-pers
Burne	I-pers
is	O
your	O
Wife	O
,	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
there	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Week	O
,	O
no	O
longer	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
White-Chappel	O
Jail	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
take	O
away	O
that	O
Bed	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
my	O
Wife	O
for	O
a	O
Bed	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
one	O
.	O
This	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Witness	O
,	O
is	O
her	O
Lodger	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
a	O
Groat	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
58.	O
John	B-pers
Glaswell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Watch	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Joan	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
of	O
Lime-House-Hole	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Underwood	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
a	O
Watch	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
?	O
Underwood	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
16th	O
Instant	O
about	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
Watch	O
?	O
Underwood	O
.	O
It	O
hung	O
upon	O
a	O
Nail	O
in	O
the	O
Chimney-Corner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Underwood	O
.	O
At	O
Lime-House-Hole	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Underwood	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
pretty	O
near	O
Four	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
it	O
?	O
Underwood	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Underwood	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
along	O
with	O
one	O
Singleton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
come	O
for	O
?	O
Underwood	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
particularly	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Singleton	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
with	O
this	O
Man	O
to	O
Blackwall	O
.	O
Q.	O
Singleton	O
then	O
you	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Underwood	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
me	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
further	O
of	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
Underwood	O
.	O
Having	O
Occasion	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
Stairs	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Singleton	O
in	O
the	O
lower	O
Room	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Screen	O
that	O
parted	O
the	O
Fire-Place	O
and	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
coming	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
this	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
was	O
talking	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
his	O
Business	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
this	O
other	O
Fellow	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Singleton	O
,	O
why	O
your	O
Friend	O
is	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
took	O
his	O
Leave	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
As	O
we	O
both	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
Fire	O
,	O
I	O
clapp	O
'd	O
my	O
Eyes	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
play	O
'd	O
the	O
Rogue	O
with	O
my	O
Watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
take	O
my	O
Oath	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
Brother	O
to	O
pursue	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eastham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pursue	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Eastham	O
,	O
This	O
poor	O
Man	O
(	O
Singleton	O
)	O
that	O
was	O
charged	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
Pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
Cable-Street	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
House	O
.	O
And	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
Affair	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
no	O
Confession	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
:	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Watch	O
under	O
his	O
left	O
Arm	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
produced	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
Arm-pit	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
then	O
?	O
Eastham	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Liquor	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
