TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
COUNTY	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
Held	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
20th	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Eighth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
OF	O
THE	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Sold	O
by	O
C.	O
NUTT	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
Pamphlet-Shops	O
of	O
London	O
and	O
Westminster	O
.	O
1746	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
HOARE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
FOSTER	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
REYNOLDS	I-pers
,	O
and	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRACEY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Harling	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Grizel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Woodyer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lux	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wetherby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hoddell	I-pers
,	O
Goldsborough	O
Frost	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Thomlinson	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawker	I-pers
,	O
Ed	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Durnas	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Prior	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Walsh	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cullis	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Heasman	I-pers
,	O
331.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mecum	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
about	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
Dwelling-House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
of	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
one	O
Cotton	O
Gown	O
,	O
two	O
Linnen	O
Shirts	O
,	O
two	O
Women	O
's	O
Linnen	O
Caps	O
,	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Worstead	O
Stockings	O
,	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
six	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
one	O
Gun	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
Long	O
Lawn	O
Apron	O
,	O
one	O
Copper	O
Pot	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
certain	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Hillier	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
before	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
House-keeper	O
?	O
Hillier	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
;	O
my	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Manner	O
was	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Hillier	O
.	O
By	O
a	O
Pin	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pain	O
of	O
Glass	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Ground-Floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
up	O
?	O
Hillier	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
at	O
Two	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Things	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Hillier	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
several	O
Things	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
Place	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
two	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
six	O
Plates	O
,	O
one	O
Shirt	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
Things	O
again	O
?	O
Hillier	O
.	O
Only	O
the	O
Gun	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
where	O
were	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Hillier	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Shutter	O
was	O
fastened	O
at	O
Night	O
?	O
Hillier	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
fastened	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
your	O
Gun	O
again	O
?	O
Hillier	O
.	O
A	O
Neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
whose	O
House	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
a	O
Month	O
after	O
mine	O
,	O
was	O
speaking	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Person	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
Robbery	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
Morning	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
any	O
Thing	O
;	O
so	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Collet	O
that	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Gun	O
was	O
in	O
Chancery-Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
Gun	O
brought	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Hillier	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Gun	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
]	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Joshua	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
him	O
with	O
Respect	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
he	O
stands	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
Collet	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Hillier	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
robb	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Hillier	O
's	O
House	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
The	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
Mr.	O
Hillier	O
live	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
In	O
Whitechapel	O
Road	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Oak	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
Between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
this	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Manner	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
The	O
Shutter	O
was	O
shut	O
and	O
key	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Pin	O
round	O
and	O
the	O
Key	O
dropt	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
then	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Lead	O
Work	O
of	O
the	O
Casement	O
was	O
cut	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Glass	O
took	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
a	O
Gun	O
(	O
a	O
Fowling	O
Piece	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
Brass	O
,	O
and	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
and	O
Dishes	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
else	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
A	O
pretty	O
deal	O
of	O
Linnen	O
,	O
Shirts	O
and	O
Aprons	O
.	O
These	O
Things	O
were	O
sold	O
by	O
Matthews	O
at	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
all	O
except	O
the	O
Gun	O
,	O
which	O
Mecum	O
and	O
I	O
disputed	O
who	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
hustled	O
in	O
the	O
Hat	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
won	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
and	O
Mecum	O
to	O
toss	O
up	O
for	O
the	O
Gun	O
when	O
Matthews	O
and	O
Clay	O
were	O
concern	O
'd	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
We	O
allow	O
'd	O
them	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
made	O
the	O
Discovery	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
Discovery	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Hillier	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
by	O
the	O
Gun	O
again	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
to	O
Mecum	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Body	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Body	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
Archer	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
Evidence	O
;	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
Mecum	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
most	O
desperate	O
Resistance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Gun	O
?	O
Body	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
this	O
Gun	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
House	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
cramm	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
Vault	O
;	O
it	O
dawb	O
'd	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
along	O
.	O
Harris	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
Question	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
which	O
of	O
the	O
Persons	O
I	O
made	O
Resistance	O
to	O
;	O
because	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
Gun	O
went	O
to	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Now	O
what	O
is	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
your	O
Defence	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
lay	O
myself	O
at	O
your	O
Mercy	O
:	O
Mr	O
.	O
Body	O
was	O
Evidence	O
against	O
me	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
This	O
Mecum	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
notorious	O
Robber	O
and	O
House-Breaker	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
of	O
two	O
Indictments	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
Sentence	O
for	O
Transportation	O
.	O
332.	O
William	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
Fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
Eyes	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
moved	O
by	O
the	O
Instigation	O
of	O
the	O
Devil	O
,	O
by	O
Force	O
of	O
Arms	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
feloniously	O
and	O
wilfully	O
,	O
with	O
Malice	O
afore-thought	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
charged	O
with	O
Powder	O
and	O
shot	O
,	O
did	O
shoot	O
and	O
wound	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
in	O
his	O
Left	O
Breast	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
Wound	O
two	O
Inches	O
deep	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
Wound	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
died	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Hendley	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
alledge	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Hendley	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
past	O
Seven	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Rope-Walk	O
where	O
we	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
bring	O
a	O
Gun	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
Rope-Walk	O
near	O
Stepney	O
:	O
The	O
Deceased	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Man	O
refused	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
then	O
?	O
Hendley	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
House	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
Hemp	O
to	O
put	O
about	O
me	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
End	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
the	O
dead	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
three	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
Sharp	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
that	O
join	O
'd	O
for	O
two	O
Quarts	O
of	O
Beer	O
;	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Deceased	O
)	O
put	O
the	O
Hemp	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
fired	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
Yards	O
Distance	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
fell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Consequence	O
of	O
letting	O
off	O
the	O
Gun	O
?	O
Heddley	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
;	O
the	O
Man	O
dropt	O
at	O
his	O
Feet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
die	O
immediately	O
?	O
Hendley	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
spoke	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
Quarrel	O
between	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Sharp	O
?	O
Hendley	O
.	O
None	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
quarrelsome	O
Man	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
particular	O
Ill-Will	O
to	O
the	O
Person	O
that	O
is	O
killed	O
?	O
Hendley	O
.	O
Not	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
with	O
Respect	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Rope-Walk	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Stranger	O
bring	O
the	O
Gun	O
in	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
takes	O
the	O
Gun	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Gun	O
that	O
unskrew	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
pulled	O
the	O
Rammer	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Pocket	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Place	O
in	O
the	O
Gun	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
Rammer	O
in	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
folds	O
it	O
together	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
puts	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
I	O
watch	O
'd	O
it	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
turning	O
of	O
it	O
about	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
that	O
owned	O
the	O
Gun	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
Back	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
levelled	O
at	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Deceased	O
had	O
his	O
Face	O
near	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
that	O
bears	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
Character	O
as	O
any	O
Working-Man	O
whatever	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
our	O
Defence	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
this	O
Man	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Walk	O
with	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
accidentally	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
she	O
was	O
loaded	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
Buttons	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
333	O
,	O
334.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bousey	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Ewe	O
Sheep	O
Value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Pope	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
Sheep	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
.	O
Howel	O
.	O
Hearing	O
of	O
a	O
Sheep	O
being	O
found	O
,	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
my	O
Shepherd	O
to	O
tell	O
my	O
Flock	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
Pope	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Skin	O
of	O
a	O
Sheep	O
in	O
a	O
Pond	O
near	O
these	O
People	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
on	O
Uxbridge-Common	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Carcass	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Pluck	O
in	O
his	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
that	O
Sheep	O
missing	O
from	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
from	O
your	O
Flock	O
?	O
Pope	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
Shepherd	O
here	O
?	O
Pope	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Sugg	I-pers
)	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
Shepherd	O
?	O
Sugg	O
.	O
Yes	O
There	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Flock	O
thirteen	O
Score	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
again	O
and	O
there	O
wanted	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
that	O
one	O
Sheep	O
missing	O
?	O
Sugg	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
here	O
's	O
the	O
Skin	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
that	O
Skin	O
.	O
Sugg	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Skin	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
Skin	O
of	O
a	O
Ewe	O
.	O
Sugg	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Sugg	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
we	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
Head	O
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
Body	O
,	O
may	O
tell	O
that	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
Sugg	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
eight	O
Days	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
Skin	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
Michaelmas	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	O
Crouch	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
that	O
Skin	O
before	O
.	O
Crouch	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Pond	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Pond	O
?	O
Crouch	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Pond	O
hard	O
by	O
Powel	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
floating	O
in	O
the	O
Pond	O
?	O
Crouch	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
Bricks	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
sink	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
then	O
.	O
Crouch	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
told	O
of	O
it	O
by	O
some	O
Children	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
this	O
Pond	O
from	O
Powel	O
's	O
House	O
?	O
Crouch	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
Stones	O
throw	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
Husband	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
here	O
?	O
Crouch	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
that	O
Skin	O
?	O
Crouch	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Pond	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
same	O
Skin	O
?	O
Crouch	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Skin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Search	O
made	O
upon	O
this	O
at	O
Powel	O
's	O
House	O
?	O
Crouch	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lyn	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
?	O
Lyn	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
before	O
Michaelmas	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
came	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
is	O
the	O
Time	O
to	O
find	O
your	O
Sheep-Stealers	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
but	O
mine	O
were	O
all	O
Weathers	O
:	O
I	O
goes	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
about	O
Eleven	O
or	O
Twelve	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
I	O
goes	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bousey	I-pers
's	O
House	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Beef	O
for	O
Dinner	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
goes	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Powel	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
looks	O
about	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
Candle	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
sorry	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
an	O
ill	O
Opinion	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
but	O
go	O
to	O
those	O
that	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
about	O
for	O
some	O
Time	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
Door	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Foot	O
over	O
,	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Cupboard	O
Door	O
,	O
low	O
and	O
very	O
narrow	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Way	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Roof	O
of	O
the	O
Parlour	O
;	O
there	O
a	O
Sack	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
whole	O
Carcass	O
,	O
not	O
cut	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
dressed	O
that	O
Morning	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
Philip	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
Fool	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
dressed	O
by	O
a	O
better	O
Hand	O
than	O
yourself	O
:	O
So	O
I	O
goes	O
forthwith	O
and	O
takes	O
up	O
Bousey	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
up	O
your	O
Father-in-Law	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bousey	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
Sheep	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
no	O
otherwise	O
concern	O
'd	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Sheep	O
's	O
Head	O
and	O
Pluck	O
in	O
Philip	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
's	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Your	O
hear	O
what	O
is	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Carcass	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
your	O
House	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
unlikely	O
Place	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
Head	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
Pluck	O
in	O
your	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
(	O
Powel	O
)	O
Please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
making	O
some	O
Skewers	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Drove	O
of	O
Sheep	O
passed	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
Light	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
a	O
Man	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
dress	O
this	O
Sheep	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
If	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
it	O
dressed	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
fetch	O
the	O
Butcher	O
and	O
dress	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
Father-in-Law	O
to	O
dress	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witness	O
of	O
this	O
to	O
call	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
Father-in-Law	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Shillings	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Man	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
335.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Dwyer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bolster	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Bed	O
Curtain	O
Value	O
1	O
s.	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Clark	O
)	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Goods	O
stolen	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
Feather	O
Bolster	O
,	O
a	O
Bed	O
Curtain	O
and	O
other	O
Goods	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Feather	O
Bolster	O
and	O
Bed	O
Curtain	O
only	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
The	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
Ten	O
and	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
have	O
an	O
Opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Lodgers	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
was	O
hired	O
by	O
them	O
to	O
bring	O
off	O
the	O
Goods	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
hear	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
says	O
?	O
[	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
,	O
declar	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
Woman	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
Lodgers	O
that	O
Evening	O
for	O
these	O
Things	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
caught	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
with	O
these	O
Things	O
in	O
her	O
Lap	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
thrust	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Room	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
committed	O
:	O
He	O
also	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Padlock	O
put	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
his	O
Lodgers	O
from	O
carrying	O
off	O
his	O
Goods	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
broken	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
336.	O
John	B-pers
Web	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gilpin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
Gilpin	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Gilpin	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Capacity	O
of	O
a	O
Porter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Gilpin	O
.	O
'Till	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Business	O
?	O
Gilpin	O
.	O
A	O
Grocer	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Till	O
several	O
Times	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Week	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
every	O
Night	O
a	O
Guinea	O
in	O
Silver	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Stairs	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
Night	O
he	O
took	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
next	O
Night	O
nothing	O
,	O
the	O
Night	O
after	O
that	O
4	O
s	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
told	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Journeymen	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
several	O
Times	O
miss	O
'd	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Till	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
mark	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
mark	O
'd	O
Half	O
a	O
Crown	O
and	O
13	O
Shillings	O
and	O
Six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
my	O
Man	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Compting-House	O
to	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
Dark	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
In	O
about	O
five	O
Minutes	O
Time	O
he	O
rung	O
the	O
Bell	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
Porter	O
had	O
taken	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Half-pence	O
:	O
The	O
Porter	O
was	O
there	O
and	O
the	O
Journeyman	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
John	O
,	O
what	O
Money	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
in	O
your	O
Pocket	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
Half-pence	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
Day	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
forgot	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
Half-pence	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
indeed	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Shillings	O
worth	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
5	O
s.	O
mark	O
'd	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
]	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
-	O
Jones	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
Nine	O
and	O
Ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
Compting-House	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Cellar	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
Drawer	O
with	O
some	O
Silver	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
Side	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
presently	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Drawer	O
and	O
hold	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Candle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
.	O
Jones	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
Drawer	O
and	O
hold	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Till	O
he	O
fit	O
the	O
Candle	O
upon	O
the	O
Desk	O
,	O
knelt	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Paper	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Candle	O
.	O
We	O
generally	O
mark	O
what	O
we	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
sometimes	O
5	O
s.	O
worth	O
and	O
sometimes	O
10	O
s	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
this	O
Fact	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Cellar	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Compting-House	O
and	O
rung	O
the	O
Bell	O
for	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
Master	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
your	O
Master	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
Money	O
several	O
Times	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
Money	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
five	O
Shillings	O
that	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gilpin	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
Gilpin	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Hands-full	O
of	O
Half-pence	O
were	O
found	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Transportation	O
.	O
337.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
Silk	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Linnen	O
Sheet	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Tongs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
Chocolate-Pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
12	O
ruffled	O
Shirts	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Joel	B-pers
Fremolt	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Joel	B-pers
Fremolt	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
In	O
Queen's-Court	B-place
,	I-place
Great	I-place
Queen's-Street	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Business	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
An	O
Attorney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
House	O
there	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
Thing	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
to	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
Chamber	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
Copper-Pot	O
and	O
the	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
Corner	O
Cupboard	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
Key	O
in	O
my	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
by	O
herself	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Palmer	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
besides	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
Town	O
.	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
The	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
come	O
then	O
to	O
stay	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
continue	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Town	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Because	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
some	O
'till	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
then	O
miss	O
your	O
Key	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
it	O
where	O
you	O
left	O
it	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
The	O
Key	O
was	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cupboard	O
lock't	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
it	O
rest	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
by	O
that	O
Means	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
Thing	O
below	O
Stairs	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
Thing	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
these	O
Things	O
again	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
Pawnbrokers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
every	O
single	O
Thing	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
every	O
Thing	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
De	I-pers
Veil	I-pers
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Bed-Chamber	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
Chocolate-Pot	O
and	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
those	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
?	O
Fremolt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
Persuasion	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Palmer	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Things	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Business	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
A	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
six	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
,	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
a	O
Saucepan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Chocolate-Pot	O
;	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
were	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
31	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
all	O
together	O
:	O
She	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
say	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
known	O
to	O
deal	O
at	O
our	O
Shop	O
for	O
ten	O
Years	O
past	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
George	B-pers
French	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Business	O
?	O
French	O
.	O
A	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
produce	O
?	O
French	O
.	O
Four	O
Shirts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Any	O
Thing	O
else	O
?	O
French	O
.	O
Nothing	O
else	O
.	O
One	O
Shirt	O
I	O
took	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
one	O
my	O
Master	O
took	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
we	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
borrow	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
French	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
5	O
s.	O
upon	O
one	O
and	O
my	O
Master	O
3	O
s.	O
upon	O
another	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Lankey	I-pers
,	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
speak	O
to	O
?	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
Lankey	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
two	O
Waistcoats	O
,	O
two	O
Shirts	O
,	O
a	O
Table-Cloth	O
,	O
three	O
Silver	O
Tea-Spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Silver	O
Tea-Tongs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
brought	O
all	O
these	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Lankey	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
she	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
Lankey	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
Whole	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
did	O
Mr.	O
Fremolt	O
come	O
to	O
claim	O
them	O
?	O
Lankey	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fremolt	O
came	O
and	O
claim	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
as	O
his	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Gentleman	O
is	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
Town	O
that	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
;	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Fremolt	O
eight	O
Months	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
Pin	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
338.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Maidland	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Coin	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
,	O
of	O
New	B-place
Bond-Court	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Hugh	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Phelps	O
.	O
In	O
New	O
Bond-Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Phelps	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
Pieces	O
of	O
Silver	O
Coin	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Breeches	O
Fob	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Eight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
that	O
weigh	O
?	O
Phelps	O
.	O
Three	O
Shillings	O
.	O
Also	O
a	O
Roman	B-pers
Emperor	I-pers
's	O
Shilling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
might	O
that	O
be	O
worth	O
?	O
Phelps	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
's	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
or	O
the	O
Day	O
was	O
this	O
done	O
?	O
Phelps	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
.	O
This	O
Maid	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
that	O
Month	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
these	O
Pieces	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
off	O
my	O
Breeches	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
Strap	O
set	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Pockets	O
,	O
but	O
forgot	O
that	O
in	O
my	O
Fob	O
.	O
I	O
accus	O
'd	O
the	O
Taylor	O
with	O
having	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
Customers	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
George	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
those	O
Pieces	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
five	O
Weeks	O
afterwards	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
Pieces	O
in	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
her	O
?	O
Phelps	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Maid	O
say	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
'	O
Let	O
us	O
see	O
the	O
Pieces	O
.	O
Phelps	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
Flaw	O
upon	O
King	O
Charles	O
the	O
First	O
's	O
Six-pence	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
Piece	O
is	O
dated	O
the	O
Year	O
15	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
?	O
Phelps	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
nothing	O
:	O
We	O
found	O
them	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
Month	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
had	O
free	O
Access	O
to	O
your	O
Bed-Chamber	O
?	O
Phelps	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
)	O
Where	O
were	O
these	O
Things	O
found	O
?	O
Phelps	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
Pocket	O
,	O
please	O
you	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Pocket	O
myself	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
struggling	O
to	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
struggling	O
,	O
her	O
Pocket	O
came	O
off	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
laid	O
them	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Woodbridge	O
)	O
Was	O
you	O
by	O
when	O
these	O
Things	O
were	O
taken	O
?	O
Woodbridge	O
.	O
Yes	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
an	O
Hundred	O
Times	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Elizabeth	O
Hill	O
)	O
Was	O
you	O
by	O
when	O
these	O
Pieces	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
Yes	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Pocket	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
Things	O
were	O
these	O
three	O
Pieces	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
vile	O
Creature	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
these	O
Pieces	O
the	O
poor	O
Man	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lik	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Bread	O
about	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Francis	O
Evans	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Woman	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Three	O
Years	O
.	O
While	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
she	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
and	O
behav	O
'd	O
very	O
sober	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Maidland	I-pers
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Maidland	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
these	O
20	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
she	O
did	O
any	O
Thing	O
amiss	O
in	O
her	O
Life	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
all	O
her	O
Lifetime	O
;	O
her	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
all	O
Neighbours	O
;	O
she	O
serv	O
'd	O
seven	O
Years	O
as	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
and	O
gave	O
very	O
good	O
Content	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Brunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
two	O
Years	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
all	O
Times	O
and	O
Seasons	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Girl	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
particular	O
Fact	O
?	O
Brunt	O
.	O
No	O
Sir	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
her	O
with	O
my	O
Family	O
at	O
all	O
Times	O
and	O
Seasons	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wingate	I-pers
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
her	O
with	O
my	O
Family	O
many	O
Times	O
,	O
have	O
entrusted	O
her	O
with	O
many	O
good	O
Things	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
wrong	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
Thing	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Comfort	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
know	O
her	O
these	O
two	O
Years	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
many	O
Times	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
entrusted	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Peareth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
in	O
our	O
Neighbourhood	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
339.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
about	O
Twelve	O
or	O
One	O
in	O
the	O
Night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Milson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
one	O
Gun	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Sword	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
five	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
Copper	O
Sauce	O
Pans	O
,	O
Value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
Value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
Duffil	O
Coat	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Japan	O
Looking-Glass	O
,	O
three	O
Guns	O
,	O
Value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Milson	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Loyd	B-pers
.	I-pers
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Francis	B-pers
Milson	I-pers
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Milson	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
your	O
House	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Milson	O
.	O
The	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
your	O
House	O
at	O
Night	O
?	O
Milson	O
.	O
All	O
safe	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
I	O
bolted	O
the	O
Window	O
myself	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
Hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
did	O
you	O
rise	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
?	O
Milson	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
at	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
Five	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
first	O
saw	O
the	O
Window	O
?	O
Milson	O
.	O
My	O
Wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Window	O
?	O
Milson	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
my	O
Wife	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
House	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
Window	O
broke	O
?	O
Milson	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Bolts	O
was	O
wrenched	O
almost	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Goods	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
that	O
Night	O
?	O
Milson	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
is	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
a	O
Gun	O
,	O
a	O
Sword	O
,	O
Bayonet	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
Pewter	O
Dishes	O
?	O
Milson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
twelve	O
Pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
three	O
Copper	O
Sauce-Pans	O
,	O
one	O
Tea-Kettle	O
,	O
one	O
Iron	O
Box	O
,	O
one	O
Duffil	O
Coat	O
,	O
four	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Shoes	O
,	O
two	O
Horse	O
Whips	O
,	O
one	O
Japan	O
Cabinet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Looking	O
Glass	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
your	O
Goods	O
?	O
Milson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Cabinet	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Goods	O
taken	O
besides	O
your	O
own	O
?	O
Milson	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
Guns	O
,	O
three	O
Swords	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
Bayonets	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Chester	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Goods	O
belonging	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
?	O
Milson	O
.	O
A	O
Box	O
Iron	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
and	O
a	O
Horse	O
Whip	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Loyd	O
's	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
The	O
Great	O
Coat	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
lost	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
all	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
again	O
?	O
Milson	O
.	O
Only	O
this	O
trifling	O
Thing	O
the	O
Cabinet	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
produced	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Collet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Thing	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
Knowledge	O
?	O
Milson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Joshua	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
)	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Collet	O
.	O
Lake	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
Clay	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
of	O
Milson	O
's	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
The	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
was	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
Collet	O
.	O
We	O
broke	O
the	O
Shutter	O
with	O
a	O
Chisel	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
Shutter	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
helped	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Goods	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
Four	O
Guns	O
,	O
four	O
Swords	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Goods	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Buckland	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rising	O
Sun	O
in	O
Long	O
Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
divide	O
the	O
Spoil	O
between	O
you	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
divided	O
the	O
Money	O
amongst	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
they	O
sold	O
for	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
Guineas	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
divided	O
between	O
yourself	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Clay	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
further	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
No	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
You	O
have	O
heard	O
what	O
this	O
Witness	O
Joshua	O
Collet	O
has	O
said	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
willing	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
Questions	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
cross-examine	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
enquire	O
into	O
the	O
Witness	O
's	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
Rogue	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Collet	O
)	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
this	O
Robbery	O
committed	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
Between	O
Twelve	O
and	O
Two	O
,	O
near	O
One	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
Not	O
above	O
two	O
Months	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
Box	O
taken	O
out	O
?	O
Collet	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Spice	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Box	O
I	O
kept	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	O
-	O
,	O
Constable	O
)	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
touching	O
this	O
Charge	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
the	O
City	O
Marshal	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Warrant	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
Lake	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
serve	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
(	O
Lake	O
)	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
Wood-Street	O
Compter	O
for	O
a	O
Quarrel	O
in	O
Bartholomew-Fair	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
would	O
discharge	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
discharge	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Coach	O
,	O
he	O
reflected	O
much	O
upon	O
Collet	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Men	O
are	O
easily	O
frightned	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
as	O
soon	O
be	O
D	O
-	O
d	O
as	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Friends	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
have	O
done	O
this	O
six	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
turn	O
Evidence	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
as	O
soon	O
be	O
D	O
-	O
d	O
as	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
,	O
for	O
Men	O
are	O
frightned	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
at	O
their	O
own	O
Shadow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
that	O
Collet	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
well	O
acquainted	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
they	O
first	O
met	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
At	O
Justice	O
Rickards	O
's	O
,	O
Collet	O
spoke	O
to	O
Lake	O
,	O
and	O
Lake	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
advis	O
'd	O
ten	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
do	O
what	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
turn	O
Evidence	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Ask	O
this	O
Witness	O
what	O
Question	O
you	O
please	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
set	O
on	O
by	O
these	O
Thief-catchers	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
Thing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Joseph	O
Lake	O
)	O
What	O
Time	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
come	O
from	O
Sea	O
?	O
(	O
By	O
the	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
Condition	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
then	O
?	O
Lake	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
sick	O
before	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
his	O
Bedfellow	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Disorder	O
had	O
he	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Lake	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
Itch	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
confined	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
his	O
Chamber	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
keep	O
his	O
Bed	O
from	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
to	O
the	O
22d	O
?	O
Did	O
he	O
keep	O
his	O
Bed	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
?	O
Lake	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
Room	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
his	O
Bed-fellow	O
;	O
would	O
you	O
chuse	O
to	O
be	O
Bed-fellow	O
to	O
a	O
Person	O
that	O
has	O
the	O
Itch	O
?	O
Lake	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Room	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
keep	O
the	O
Chamber	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Lake	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
Father	O
's	O
Door	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
Brother	O
lay	O
out	O
of	O
Nights	O
from	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
to	O
the	O
22d	O
?	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
lay	O
out	O
of	O
Nights	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Lake	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Katherine	O
Lake	O
)	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Lake	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
Mother	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
your	O
Son	O
's	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Lake	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Itch	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
8th	O
to	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
say	O
he	O
kept	O
one	O
Room	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
into	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
particular	O
to	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Lake	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Reason	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
this	O
Lad	O
of	O
mine	O
was	O
at	O
Maidstone	O
Fair	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
never	O
lay	O
out	O
of	O
Nights	O
?	O
Lake	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
he	O
never	O
lay	O
out	O
,	O
except	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
Fair	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Maidstone	O
Fair	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Chatham	O
,	O
that	O
holds	O
three	O
Days	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fourth	O
Day	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
general	O
Character	O
?	O
Shaw	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shadpale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stockal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Maddocks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
of	O
an	O
undoubted	O
Character	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Meldin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
worked	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
several	O
Companies	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kilpal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
fifteen	O
Years	O
of	O
Age	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kilpack	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
Ill	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Dibdale	I-pers
.	O
He	O
dwelt	O
almost	O
two	O
Years	O
in	O
my	O
House	O
'till	O
his	O
Wife	O
died	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
340	O
,	O
341	O
,	O
342.	O
,	O
Battholomew	B-pers
Quickly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
,	O
the	O
Wife	O
of	O
John	O
,	O
Pigeon	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Corp	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Lincoln's-Inn	B-place
Wall	I-place
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
all	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
lay	O
to	O
all	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
their	O
Charge	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
;	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Quickley	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Pigeon	I-pers
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
's	O
Shop	O
;	O
they	O
spoke	O
about	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Quickley	I-pers
stole	O
the	O
Shoes	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Corp	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Wall	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
into	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
Shops	O
,	O
which	O
increas	O
'd	O
my	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
go	O
into	O
Corp	O
's	O
Shop	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
smallest	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
Bartholomew	O
,	O
steal	O
the	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
steal	O
them	O
from	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Cutting-Board	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
or	O
Day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
About	O
Seven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
then	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
He	O
conceal	O
'd	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
Coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Shoes	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
A	O
Pair	O
of	O
Mens	O
Shoes	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
Escape	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
into	O
Lincolns-Inn-Fields	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
together	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Quickley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
my	O
Escape	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
a	O
Press-Gang	O
was	O
come	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
He	O
us	O
'd	O
a	O
great	O
Oath	B-pers
,	I-pers
G	I-pers
-	O
d	O
-	O
your	O
Soul	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
.	O
I	O
apprehend	O
they	O
are	O
Confederates	O
by	O
speaking	O
in	O
our	O
Shop	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
familiar	O
Stile	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
In	O
Turnstile	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Housekeeper	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
tall	O
Man	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
for	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
my	O
Servant	O
had	O
shewn	O
two	O
Pair	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
Pair	O
,	O
the	O
little	O
Fellow	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
off	O
together	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Catherine	B-pers
Corp	I-pers
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Corp	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Pigeon	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
House	O
last	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
;	O
she	O
pretended	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stuff	O
Shoes	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
Pair	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
Men	O
came	O
presently	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
try	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
come	O
in	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
Shoes	O
?	O
Corp.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
our	O
Man	O
to	O
fit	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
please	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
Shoes	O
from	O
under	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Quickley	I-pers
's	O
Coat	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
tall	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
my	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
Friend	O
has	O
stole	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no-body	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
his	O
Wife	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Pigeon	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pigeon	I-pers
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
attempt	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
Shoes	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
sworn	O
she	O
suspected	O
you	O
.	O
Pigeon	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
Reason	O
did	O
you	O
suspect	O
me	O
?	O
Corp	O
.	O
Because	O
no-body	O
had	O
any	O
Business	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
that	O
Corner	O
to	O
crowd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Halsey	I-pers
)	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Halsey	O
.	O
With	O
Mr.	O
Corp.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Halsey	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
I	O
try	O
'd	O
a	O
Pair	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
did	O
not	O
fit	O
her	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Halsey	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
try	O
another	O
Pair	O
,	O
the	O
tall	O
Man	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
Tooley	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
that	O
would	O
fit	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
Pair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Candle	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
that	O
Craft	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
what	O
Shoes	O
were	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Sea	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
want	O
half	O
a	O
Dozen	O
Pair	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
use	O
me	O
well	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
trying	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
in	O
comes	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
from	O
the	O
short	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
:	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
tall	O
Man	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Matter	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
you	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Shop	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
has	O
stole	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
body	O
but	O
my	O
Wife	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
Woman	O
,	O
The	O
Man	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
The	O
tall	O
Man	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
detain	O
his	O
Wife	O
over	O
and	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
let	O
you	O
go	O
'till	O
my	O
Master	O
comes	O
.	O
She	O
declar	O
'd	O
afterwards	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
Wife	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Quickley	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
your	O
Defence	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
these	O
People	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
that	O
Night	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
Shoes	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
over	O
and	O
over	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
the	O
Shoes	O
?	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Fool	O
Tooley	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Tooley	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Notion	O
of	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
made	O
my	O
Escape	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
no-body	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
but	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
Gentlewoman	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Pigeon	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Pigeon	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
set	O
Eyes	O
on	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
Halsey	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
swear	O
on	O
Sunday	O
;	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
deliver	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
Wolf	O
if	O
ever	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
All	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
343.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pieces	O
of	O
flower	O
'd	O
Silk	O
,	O
containing	O
one	O
Yard	O
and	O
a	O
Quarter	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
)	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Good	O
stole	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Bradshaw	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Susannah	O
Jones	O
,	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Servant	O
about	O
twelve	O
Months	O
:	O
After	O
she	O
left	O
my	O
Service	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Godwin	O
,	O
who	O
suspecting	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Goods	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
Value	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
Search	O
Warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
Place	O
of	O
Rendezvour	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
Place	O
were	O
several	O
Goods	O
that	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
Goods	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
that	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
she	O
left	O
your	O
Service	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
told	O
you	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Bradshaw	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
two	O
Years	O
afterwards	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Godwin	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
remarkable	O
Silk	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
W	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
Gown	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Godwin	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
upon	O
searching	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Bastard	O
Child	O
at	O
Nurse	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
Child	O
had	O
the	O
Skirt	O
of	O
a	O
Coat	O
of	O
a	O
remarkable	O
fine	O
Silk	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
London	O
;	O
by	O
comparing	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
Silk	O
which	O
had	O
lain	O
by	O
as	O
useless	O
,	O
'till	O
we	O
should	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
Child	O
of	O
our	O
own	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Judith	B-pers
Simson	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
Simson	O
.	O
The	O
Skirt	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
of	O
2	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
Mr.	O
Godwin	O
's	O
Man	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
bring	O
it	O
?	O
Simson	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
while	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
Time	O
;	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
Half	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
Quarters	O
a	O
Year	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Child	O
to	O
wear	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Recollect	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
was	O
ago	O
.	O
Simson	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
last	O
Summer	O
:	O
I	O
nurs	O
'd	O
the	O
Child	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
Child	O
is	O
almost	O
four	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
Silk	O
ever	O
search	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
or	O
demanded	O
by	O
you	O
?	O
Simson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
Inventory	O
of	O
the	O
Child	O
's	O
Things	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
Silk	O
?	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
Manning	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Simson	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Susannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
:	O
Going	O
there	O
the	O
Woman	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
should	O
see	O
her	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
Eight	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Oars	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
Susannah	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
another	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Waterman	O
,	O
keep	O
up	O
close	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
pay	O
you	O
something	O
extraordinary	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Waterman	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
bound	O
for	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
Blackfryers	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
Waterman	O
,	O
You	O
land	O
where	O
the	O
other	O
lands	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Boat	O
,	O
I	O
dogg	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
Blackfryers	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Saracen's-Head	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
my	O
Master	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
set	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
waited	O
some	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
into	O
Newgate-Street	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Harrow	O
in	O
Greyfryers	O
;	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
run	O
down	O
that	O
Place	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Susan	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
no	O
further	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
slip	O
my	O
Hands	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Bradshaw	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
that	O
this	O
Silk	O
was	O
stole	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Bradshaw	O
.	O
This	O
Silk	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Gown	O
for	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
't	O
is	O
very	O
remarkable	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
France	O
.	O
Another	O
Reason	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Breadth	O
is	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
the	O
Breadth	O
cut	O
in	O
two	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
miss	O
'd	O
?	O
Bradshaw	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
miss	O
'd	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
left	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
six	O
Months	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
Wife	O
had	O
no	O
Occasion	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
Silk	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
your	O
Defence	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
behind	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
laced	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
Linnen	O
Shirt	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
and	O
Chattels	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Alexander	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Godwin	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
your	O
House	O
;	O
as	O
a	O
laced	O
Cambrick	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
Knowledge	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
them	O
?	O
Godwin	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
others	O
will	O
speak	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Kendall	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
Goods	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
pawn	O
'd	O
?	O
Kendal	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
Box	O
of	O
Goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Kendal	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Week	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
such	O
Things	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Box	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
Goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Messenger	O
's	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Messenger	O
,	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
Woman	O
?	O
Messenger	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
an	O
Apron	O
,	O
Handkerchief	O
and	O
Ruffles	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
twenty	O
Shillings	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
near	O
three	O
Years	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
Character	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
they	O
continue	O
in	O
your	O
Possession	O
?	O
Messenger	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
'till	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Godwin	O
and	O
his	O
Spouse	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
all	O
down	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Sweet	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Goods	O
?	O
Sweet	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
her	O
Goods	O
were	O
left	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
Box	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
Goods	O
these	O
are	O
?	O
Godwin	O
.	O
The	O
laced	O
Handkerchief	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Ruffles	O
and	O
laced	O
Cap	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
four	O
Yards	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
within	O
half	O
a	O
Quarter	O
,	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Shift	O
and	O
Apron	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
these	O
Things	O
lost	O
?	O
Godwin	O
.	O
In	O
May	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
7th	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
miss	O
'd	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
Things	O
before	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
?	O
Godwin	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
that	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
Lace	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
Witness	O
to	O
call	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
Witness	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
Things	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
Goods	O
at	O
several	O
Times	O
.	O
A	O
Person	O
that	O
quarrell	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
several	O
Things	O
.	O
She	O
serv	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Writ	O
for	O
false	O
Imprisonment	O
;	O
she	O
employ	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
Attorney	O
)	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
Witness	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
344.	O
Robert	B-pers
Radwell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gelding	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
Colour	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
alledge	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
Fact	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
stands	O
charg	O
'd	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
Horse	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Train	O
of	O
Artillery	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Rodwell	I-pers
rode	O
the	O
Horse	O
from	O
Scotland	O
to	O
Kicksend	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Train	O
of	O
Artillery	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
Capacity	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Did	O
he	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Train	O
of	O
Artillery	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
overtook	O
us	O
at	O
Mansell	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
Kicksend	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
furnish	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
Horses	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Artillery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
further	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Kicksend	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
)	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
or	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
Day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
at	O
Kicksend	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Saddle	O
and	O
Bridle	O
upon	O
that	O
Horse	O
he	O
rode	O
;	O
he	O
rode	O
from	O
Kicksend	O
to	O
Barnet	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
on	O
Sunday	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
Brother	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
at	O
Highgate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Horse	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Conductor	O
's	O
Orders	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
Will	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
Witness	O
ask	O
'd	O
any	O
Questions	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
more	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
knows	O
I	O
behav	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Witness	O
)	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
behave	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
He	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
We	O
'll	O
ask	O
the	O
same	O
Question	O
to	O
Morgan	O
;	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
behave	O
all	O
the	O
Time	O
upon	O
the	O
Road	O
.	O
Morgan	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
his	O
Behaviour	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
)	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
At	O
Barnet	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
black	O
Gelding	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
what	O
Day	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
the	O
Horse	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
forty-five	O
Shillings	O
at	O
Whetstone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
offer	O
him	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
Dean	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
at	O
Whetstone	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
Sixpence	O
Earnest	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
's	O
Conductor	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
toll	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
drunken	O
Fellow	O
to	O
vouch	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
buy	O
it	O
at	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
so	O
contrary	O
a	O
Story	O
to	O
what	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
's	O
Conductors	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Would	O
you	O
have	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
asked	O
any	O
Question	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
Question	O
to	O
ask	O
,	O
any	O
further	O
than	O
that	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
Horse	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Train	O
of	O
Artillery	O
three	O
Quarters	O
of	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
great	O
Troubles	O
happened	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
345.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Snuff-Box	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
five	O
Silver	O
Knee-Buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
eight	O
Guineas	O
,	O
between	O
30	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
the	O
Monies	O
and	O
Properties	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
worth	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
Gold	O
Ring	O
worth	O
18	O
s.	O
another	O
worth	O
4	O
s.	O
five	O
Silver	O
Knee-Buckles	O
worth	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
eight	O
Guineas	O
,	O
between	O
30	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
Silver	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
all	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
Drawer	O
in	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
them	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Between	O
the	O
30th	O
and	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
The	O
very	O
Day	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
Hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
Drawer	O
lock	O
'd	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
unlock	O
'd	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Drawer	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
Things	O
again	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
in	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Hand	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
other	O
Things	O
again	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
for	O
something	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
tax	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
Things	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
Words	O
he	O
confessed	O
;	O
did	O
he	O
confess	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
Drawer	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
come	O
from	O
my	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
live	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Shoemaker	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Greensword	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
Snuff-Box	O
?	O
Greensword	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
Publick	O
House	O
near	O
our	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
8	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
a	O
Snuff-Box	O
for	O
?	O
Greensword	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
my	O
Wife	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
accept	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
bought	O
it	O
?	O
Greensword	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Friend	O
of	O
his	O
that	O
wanted	O
Money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
Greensword	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
Morning	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
come	O
with	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
House	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
Man	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
Snuff-Box	O
and	O
Half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
to	O
hold	O
his	O
Tongue	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Cator	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Affair	O
?	O
Cator	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Fisher	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
Note	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
Note	O
,	O
or	O
could	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
the	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
Note	O
sign	O
'd	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cator	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fisher	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
two	O
Gold	O
Rings	O
?	O
He	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
Box	O
,	O
however	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
bebetween	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
but	O
few	O
of	O
them	O
Gold	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Note	O
besides	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
my	O
Note	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
should	O
never	O
come	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
either	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
destroy	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Man	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
as	O
before-mention	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
yourself	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
concerning	O
a	O
Note	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fisher	O
sent	O
Men	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
Men	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
the	O
Liquor	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
drink	O
to	O
Excess	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Roger	B-pers
Berrel	I-pers
.	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Berrel	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
Years	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
my	O
House	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
married	O
Man	O
?	O
Berrel	O
.	O
Married	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Shirison	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Shirison	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
three	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
Misbehaviour	O
in	O
the	O
young	O
Fellow	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Daniel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
four	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
Man	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Cartwright	O
.	O
His	O
Character	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
good	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Alexander	B-pers
Mitchen	I-pers
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Mitchen	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Bliss	I-pers
.	O
)	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Bliss	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
always	O
a	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
Character	O
has	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Simons	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
Character	O
,	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
laborious	O
young	O
Fellow	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
346.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mcasham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Livery	O
Suit	O
of	O
Clothes	O
,	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Sumers	I-pers
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Sumers	I-pers
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Child	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Sumers	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Coachman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
Clothes	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
's	O
Stable	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Great	O
Coat	O
and	O
a	O
Suit	O
of	O
Livery	O
,	O
a	O
Coat	O
and	O
Waistcoat	O
besides	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
them	O
?	O
Sumers	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
four	O
Months	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
lay	O
them	O
as	O
yours	O
?	O
Sumers	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
Master	O
's	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
Livery	O
Clothes	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Stable	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
?	O
Sumers	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
caught	O
that	O
Boy	O
rising	O
a	O
Ladder	O
against	O
the	O
Lost	O
Door	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
Boy	O
rise	O
a	O
Ladder	O
!	O
Sumers	O
.	O
A	O
small	O
Ladder	O
that	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
Coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
,	O
besides	O
your	O
Master	O
's	O
?	O
Sumers	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Cloth	O
Coat	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
28th	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rising	O
the	O
Ladder	O
against	O
the	O
Lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
then	O
?	O
Sumers	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
Business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
Top	O
in	O
the	O
Horse-Pond	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
had	O
that	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
Lost	O
?	O
Sumers	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Lost	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
rose	O
the	O
Ladder	O
;	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
no	O
such	O
Thing	O
as	O
a	O
Top	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
Stable	O
Door	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Thorough-fare	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Bricklayers	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Thorough-fare	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Ladder	O
,	O
he	O
declared	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
before	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
George	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Boy	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
Witness	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
Suspicion	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
Michaelmas	O
Day	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
heard	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Day	O
after	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Pennant	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Norril	I-pers
.	O
)	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
Between	O
13	O
and	O
14	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Nature	O
of	O
an	O
Oath	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
They	O
must	O
not	O
swear	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
Truth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
Notion	O
if	O
a	O
Person	O
takes	O
a	O
false	O
Oath	O
.	O
Norril	O
.	O
Their	O
Souls	O
go	O
to	O
Hell	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
That	O
Boy	O
(	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Any	O
body	O
else	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
None	O
but	O
him	O
and	O
I.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Yard	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
up	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
's	O
Yard	O
in	O
Broad-Street	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
Month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
six	O
Weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
then	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Window	O
,	O
just	O
over	O
the	O
Place	O
where	O
they	O
shoot	O
the	O
Dung	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
a	O
Pane	O
of	O
Glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Sash	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Dunghil	O
,	O
then	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
Between	O
One	O
and	O
Two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
he	O
raise	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Place	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
Where	O
they	O
shoot	O
their	O
Dung	O
,	O
the	O
Casement	O
was	O
just	O
over	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
Dung	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
in	O
as	O
easy	O
as	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
any	O
Thing	O
out	O
.	O
Norril	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
Time	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
afterwards	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
brown	O
Coat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
He	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
:	O
We	O
tied	O
up	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
in	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
they	O
a	O
Child	O
's	O
Coat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
A	O
Man	O
's	O
Coat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Handkerchief	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
A	O
blue	O
Handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
tie	O
them	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Necessary-House	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
tie	O
them	O
up	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Aaron	B-pers
Cordozer	I-pers
,	O
over-against	O
the	O
Gullyhole	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
the	O
Coat	O
,	O
Waistcoat	O
and	O
Breeches	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
white	O
cap	O
'd	O
Coat	O
and	O
brown	O
Waistcoat	O
we	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Stable	O
a	O
second	O
Time	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
made	O
this	O
Confession	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
Week	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
taken	O
up	O
before	O
you	O
made	O
this	O
Confession	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
Witnesses	O
?	O
Norril	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Swanson	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
on	O
the	O
Behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Swanson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
three	O
Years	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
his	O
Friends	O
?	O
Swanson	O
.	O
His	O
Friends	O
are	O
poor	O
working	O
People	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
any	O
Relation	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Swanson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
the	O
Boy	O
go	O
to	O
School	O
any	O
where	O
?	O
Swanson	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
School	O
at	O
a	O
House	O
in	O
Wingfield-Street	O
,	O
Spitalfields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
his	O
Father	O
and	O
Mother	O
here	O
?	O
Swanson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
Father	O
here	O
to	O
Day	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
347.	O
John	B-pers
Jetter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Piece	O
of	O
Gold	O
Coin	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Shop	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
1745	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
was	O
a	O
Twelve-Month	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
Guinea	O
;	O
this	O
Man	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
Shop	O
:	O
My	O
Wife	O
had	O
just	O
receiv	O
'd	O
four	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
towards	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
Till	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
out	O
his	O
Hand	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Guinea	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
withdrew	O
himself	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
soon	O
return	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
whipp	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Guinea	O
away	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
Answer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
ago	O
?	O
You	O
say	O
last	O
April	O
was	O
a	O
Twelve-Month	O
.	O
Morgan	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
was	O
never	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
by	O
me	O
nor	O
others	O
that	O
wanted	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
Person	O
went	O
sometimes	O
as	O
his	O
Servant	O
,	O
his	O
Footman	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
for	O
his	O
Son	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
of	O
the	O
Night	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
About	O
Ten	O
o'Clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Shop	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
A	O
Broker	O
's	O
Shop	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
sell	O
there	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
Not	O
much	O
;	O
sometimes	O
I	O
sell	O
some	O
Things	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
Places	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Fortnight	O
before	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Business	O
did	O
he	O
follow	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
Business	O
,	O
besides	O
taking	O
of	O
Houses	O
and	O
defrauding	O
People	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
other	O
Character	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
You	O
hear	O
what	O
this	O
Man	O
says	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Man	O
is	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
pawn	O
some	O
Things	O
about	O
a	O
Twelve-Month	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lent	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
more	O
upon	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
:	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
Money	O
upon	O
a	O
Wig	O
that	O
cost	O
me	O
three	O
Guineas	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
Guinea	O
more	O
upon	O
the	O
Plate	O
last	O
Easter	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
Twelve-Month	O
;	O
upon	O
two	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
a	O
Silver	O
Salt	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Morgan	O
.	O
)	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
Plate	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
pawn	O
?	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
Money	O
advanced	O
as	O
he	O
speaks	O
of	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
Not	O
one	O
Farthing	O
at	O
that	O
Time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
advance	O
at	O
first	O
upon	O
the	O
Plate	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
exactly	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
this	O
Guinea	O
did	O
you	O
pursue	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Hannah	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
)	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
Matter	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
House	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
behind	O
the	O
Compter	O
in	O
receiving	O
some	O
Money	O
.	O
I	O
shov	O
'd	O
some	O
Guineas	O
towards	O
my	O
Husband	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
Care	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
directly	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
Guinea	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Day	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Morgan	O
.	O
Really	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
justify	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
Twelve-Month	O
ago	O
.	O
My	O
Husband	O
went	O
several	O
Times	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
(	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
Woman	O
says	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
Guinea	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Her	O
Husband	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
my	O
Jetter	O
have	O
a	O
Guinea	O
more	O
upon	O
his	O
Plate	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
cheated	O
me	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
[	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Son	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
for	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
declar	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
present	O
in	O
the	O
Shop	O
when	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
a	O
Sort	O
of	O
a	O
Story	O
that	O
the	O
Guinea	O
was	O
advanced	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
some	O
Writings	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
gain	O
great	O
Advantage	O
by	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
helping	O
his	O
Father	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
Escape	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
clapp	O
'd	O
in	O
Irons	O
;	O
though	O
at	O
the	O
breaking	O
up	O
of	O
the	O
Sessions	O
the	O
Court	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
releas	O
'd	O
.	O
]	O
Guilty	O
Transportation	O
.	O
348.	O
Katherine	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
large	O
Silver	O
Spoons	O
and	O
a	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Eddison	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Chiswell-Street	B-place
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Eddison	I-pers
)	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
Thing	O
?	O
Eddison	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
Spoon	O
and	O
a	O
Tea	O
Spoon	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
these	O
Things	O
?	O
Eddison	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
Buffet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Eddison	O
.	O
In	O
Chiswell-Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
miss	O
them	O
?	O
Eddison	O
.	O
The	O
Maid	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
presently	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Eddison	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
14	O
Years	O
ago	O
,	O
she	O
nurs	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Eddison	O
.	O
About	O
Two	O
or	O
Three	O
o'Clock	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
she	O
stay	O
?	O
Eddison	O
.	O
About	O
an	O
Hour	O
and	O
Half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
Pursuit	O
after	O
her	O
?	O
Eddison	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
down	O
at	O
Tower-Hill	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
that	O
Way	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
about	O
the	O
Street	O
I	O
enquired	O
of	O
Black-shoe	O
Folks	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
Wellclose-Square	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
standing	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
my	O
House	O
yesterday	O
Afternoon	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
accordingly	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Maid	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Person	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Maid	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
Robbery	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
pleaded	O
with	O
her	O
hard	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
Spoons	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
any	O
Thing	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
got	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
Lodgings	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
Farthing	O
in	O
the	O
World	O
to	O
help	O
herself	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
great	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
she	O
threw	O
into	O
the	O
Vault	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
worth	O
?	O
Eddison	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
valued	O
at	O
5	O
s.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
Ratcliffe	O
Highway	O
,	O
so	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
every	O
Silversmith	O
and	O
Pawnbroker	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
this	O
Gentlewoman	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Wiles	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
Spoon	O
there	O
that	O
Katherine	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
had	O
brought	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
brought	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
Marks	O
,	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
Spoon	O
that	O
Katherine	B-pers
Jolly	I-pers
had	O
shewn	O
her	O
:	O
She	O
would	O
have	O
sold	O
it	O
or	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
would	O
not	O
receive	O
it	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
)	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Snow	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Servant	O
Maid	B-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
Mistress	O
's	O
House	O
at	O
any	O
Time	O
?	O
Snow	O
.	O
Yes	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
she	O
stay	O
?	O
Snow	O
.	O
An	O
Hour	O
and	O
Half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
remember	O
when	O
your	O
Mistress	O
brought	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
Day	O
?	O
Snow	O
.	O
Yes	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
?	O
Snow	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
one	O
for	O
a	O
Crown	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
she	O
hurl	O
'd	O
away	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Wiles	I-pers
)	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bring	O
any	O
Spoon	O
to	O
pawn	O
?	O
Wiles	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
would	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
trouble	O
myself	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
it	O
was	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Eddison	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
349.	O
Mary	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
John	O
Manning	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
aledge	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Manning	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
yourself	O
?	O
Manning	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Spoon	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Kitchen	O
?	O
Manning	O
.	O
When	O
Dinner	O
is	O
over	O
the	O
Pewter	O
is	O
wash	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Spoon	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
Servants	O
were	O
examin	O
'd	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
thinking	O
of	O
advertising	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
Time	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Clew	O
,	O
Constable	O
of	O
Westminster	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
Thing	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
Silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
one	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Spoon	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
Fellow	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
she	O
begg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
never	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
Thing	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Woman	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
your	O
House	O
?	O
Manning	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
the	O
Woman	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
she	O
begg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Power	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
as	O
the	O
Law	O
directs	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Manly	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
among	O
some	O
broken	O
Victuals	O
,	O
some	O
stew	O
'd	O
Beef	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
for	O
two	O
Days	O
before	O
.	O
First	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
with	O
broken	O
Victuals	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Clew	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Constable	O
of	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Clew	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pearson	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
this	O
Woman	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
Spoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
?	O
Clew	O
.	O
He	O
stopp	O
'd	O
this	O
Spoon	O
,	O
as	O
stolen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Clew	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
at	O
Justice	O
Manly	O
's	O
?	O
Clew	O
.	O
She	O
deny	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
-	O
Pearson	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
Woman	O
,	O
(	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
)	O
with	O
this	O
Spoon	O
;	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
Silver	O
,	O
