TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
22d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Eighth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1748	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Sixpence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
LADBROKE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourble	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
LEGGE	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRACY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Weeden	I-pers
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
North	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Streames	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Wilde	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wooldridge	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Huggett	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
.	O
479	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
September	O
22	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
off	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
open	O
and	O
upon	O
the	O
jar	O
:	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Herring	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Herring	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
Morris	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
Chatham	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Chatham	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
him	O
any	O
harm	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Herring	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Wapping-wall	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
your	O
Life	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
my	O
lad	O
what	O
trade	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
[	O
here	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
]	O
Mr	O
.	O
Herring	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
[	O
by	O
alderman	O
Parson	O
's	O
brew-house	O
]	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Guinea	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
money	O
to	O
receive	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
must	O
sell	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
gold	O
dust	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
Gold	O
dust	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
3	O
l.	O
at	O
Chatham	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
45	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
about	O
that	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
dirty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
dial-plate	O
was	O
hardly	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
his	O
money	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
more	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
45	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Herring	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dangerous	O
fellow	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
Irish	O
fellows	O
would	O
rescue	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
an	O
Irish	O
man	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
appeared	O
very	O
remarkable	O
with	O
his	O
face	O
scratched	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
watch	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
three	O
tuns	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
that	O
before	O
you	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
Gentleman	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
About	O
12	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
ship	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Monmouth	O
,	O
Captain	O
Harrison	O
,	O
a	O
70	O
gun	O
ship	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
Thursday	O
,	O
last	O
Thursday	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
Thursday	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Tuesday	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
yesterday	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
not	O
lost	O
then	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
lost	O
till	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Follyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
3	O
Tuns	O
in	O
Greenwich	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Tuesday	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
Why	O
this	O
day	O
month	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
mistaken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
this	O
is	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
Follyer	O
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
Lane	O
by	O
the	O
Tower	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
This	O
young	O
woman	O
[	O
Mary	B-pers
Connelly	I-pers
]	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
sailor	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
sailor	O
were	O
arguing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
they	O
arguing	O
about	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sailor	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
3	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
3	O
guineas	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
dear	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
agreed	O
for	O
40	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
company	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
company	O
in	O
the	O
foreroom	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
there	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
money	O
for	O
rabbits	O
,	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
rabbits	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
money	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
40	O
s.	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
was	O
it	O
paid	O
in	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
paid	O
in	O
small	O
silver	O
and	O
large	O
silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
gold	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
notice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
suppose	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
us	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
send	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
send	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
To	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
know	O
your	O
names	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
down	O
our	O
names	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
other	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
down	O
their	O
names	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Greenwich	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
cross	O
the	O
water	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
against	O
Iron	O
Gate	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
we	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
appear	O
ever	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
in	O
your	O
life	O
,	O
speak	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
place	O
is	O
Greenwich	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
churches	O
are	O
there	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Follyer	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
park	O
and	O
an	O
hospital	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
is	O
nearest	O
the	O
water	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
park	O
or	O
the	O
hospital	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
word	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
Name	O
till	O
this	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
it	O
to	O
Greenwich	O
?	O
is	O
it	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
or	O
a	O
mile	O
.	O
Follyer	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
at	O
Greenwich	O
?	O
Follyer	O
.	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
not	O
very	O
often	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Connelly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Follyer	I-pers
at	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
3	O
tuns	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
At	O
Chelsea	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
sailor	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
bargaining	O
about	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
sailor	O
ask	O
3	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
bargained	O
for	O
40	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
then	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
watch	O
paid	O
for	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Money	O
paid	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
this	O
day	O
Month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
paid	O
in	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
paid	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
half	O
crowns	O
and	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
gold	O
.	O
Connelly	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
[	O
the	O
prisoner	O
]	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
company	O
and	O
the	O
seafaring	O
man	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
nor	O
since	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
have	O
not	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
from	O
that	O
day	O
to	O
this	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
Never	O
but	O
once	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
hole	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
Not	O
long	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
hours	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
Not	O
many	O
hours	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
then	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
Connelly	O
.	O
No	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
from	O
Chelsea	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
on	O
foot	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
a	O
boat	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Connelly	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
constant	O
employ	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
Service	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
deal	O
in	O
Rabbits	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
woman	O
any	O
rabbits	O
then	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
to	O
London	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
Connelly	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
think	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
place	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
over	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
Over	O
Battle-bridge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
you	O
your	O
name	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
This	O
day	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
remember	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
so	O
long	O
ago	O
as	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
nor	O
since	O
,	O
till	O
within	O
these	O
2	O
hours	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
remember	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
Greenwich	O
park	O
?	O
Connelly	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
it	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
they	O
are	O
drunk	O
now	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
prisoner	O
of	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
felony	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
committed	O
Follyer	O
and	O
Connelly	O
into	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
their	O
being	O
indicted	O
the	O
next	O
sessions	O
for	O
perjury	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
480.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Poland	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
lost	O
2	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
Putney	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
advertise	O
them	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jacobs	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
advertised	O
the	O
spoon	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jacobs	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
you	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jacobs	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hemming	O
's	O
Row	O
by	O
Leicester	O
fields	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
spoon	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
Afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
buy	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
likely	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Crest	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
spoon	O
again	O
unless	O
he	O
brought	O
some	O
person	O
of	O
credit	O
to	O
prove	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
secure	O
him	O
?	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fraser	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
?	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
his	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
same	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Rose	O
might	O
be	O
asked	O
whether	O
that	O
spoon	O
was	O
not	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
pattern	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
engrave	O
the	O
crest	O
on	O
some	O
pewter	O
.	O
Rose	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
the	O
fellow	O
came	O
to	O
engrave	O
the	O
crest	O
on	O
some	O
pewter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
dirty	O
looking	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
fellow	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
my	O
maid	O
he	O
wanted	O
2	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
going	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
2	O
spoons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
them	O
for	O
any	O
other	O
Purpose	O
than	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
engraving	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
for	O
no	O
other	O
purpose	O
than	O
to	O
engrave	O
the	O
plates	O
.	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
countrymen	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
481	O
.	O
+	O
Isaac	B-pers
Alvarez	I-pers
Decosta	I-pers
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
27	O
yards	O
of	O
superfine	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
warehouse	O
,	O
February	O
11	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
whole	O
piece	O
of	O
superfine	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Warehouse	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
perfectly	O
wet	O
as	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Dyers	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
set	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
us	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
you	O
apprehend	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Winter	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
some	O
rails	O
that	O
are	O
before	O
my	O
yard	O
that	O
are	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
an	O
Area	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
rails	O
was	O
cut	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cloth	O
was	O
drawn	O
through	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
warehouse	O
locked	O
?	O
Winter	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
warehouse	O
is	O
never	O
locked	O
,	O
the	O
wall	O
is	O
almost	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
this	O
cieling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
was	O
there	O
room	O
for	O
one	O
man	O
to	O
come	O
through	O
?	O
Winter	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
possible	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
tried	O
myself	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
thro	O
'	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
got	O
thro	O
'	O
without	O
hurting	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Winter	O
.	O
It	O
must	O
be	O
sadly	O
purpled	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Winter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Whitson	O
monday	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
letter	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
searched	O
Alvarez	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
my	O
cloth	O
or	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
remnants	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
?	O
Winter	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
appear	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
worn	O
?	O
Winter	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
his	O
landlady	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
home	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
was	O
my	O
cloth	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
never	O
was	O
planed	O
nor	O
pressed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
lodging	O
?	O
Winter	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
absconded	O
from	O
thence	O
six	O
Weeks	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
one	O
Johnson	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
cloth	O
?	O
Winter	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Polander	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
whether	O
that	O
is	O
an	O
English	O
manufacture	O
or	O
a	O
foreign	O
manufacture	O
?	O
Winter	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
an	O
English	O
manufacture	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
those	O
stains	O
done	O
by	O
fresh	O
water	O
or	O
salt	O
water	O
?	O
Winter	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
drawing	O
it	O
thro	O
'	O
my	O
rails	O
,	O
for	O
salt	O
water	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
turn	O
quite	O
black	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
importing	O
cloth	O
from	O
Poland	O
?	O
Winter	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Bid	O
him	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
enough	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
bit	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
the	O
breeches	O
.	O
Winter	O
.	O
The	O
waistband	O
of	O
the	O
breeches	O
is	O
quite	O
another	O
thing	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
cloth	O
business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
that	O
waistcoat	O
ever	O
been	O
planed	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
;	O
these	O
stains	O
are	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
crimsoned	O
,	O
which	O
come	O
by	O
dirt	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
by	O
salt	O
water	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
turned	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
close	O
tied	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
edges	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
wet	O
and	O
the	O
inside	O
free	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Winter	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
him	O
night	O
and	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
breeches	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
stains	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Polander	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
those	O
stains	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
salt	O
water	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Buckland	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
better	O
dressed	O
then	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
Portsoken-Ward	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
my	O
rounds	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
an	O
infamous	O
house	O
in	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hoop	O
Yard	O
,	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
turnkey	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Alvarez	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
down	O
the	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Alvarez	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
name	O
is	O
not	O
Alvarez	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
name	O
is	O
Alvarez	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cordosa	I-pers
there	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
receiver	O
of	O
stolen	O
goods	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Barnes	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
absconded	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
shift	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
that	O
a	O
boy	O
had	O
discovered	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
I	O
heard	O
several	O
persons	O
dragging	O
something	O
up	O
stairs	O
that	O
was	O
heavy	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
because	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
tea	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
smuggler	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
.	O
Some	O
time	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
long	O
it	O
was	O
ago	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Shoemaker-Row	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
a	O
stall	O
in	O
Shoemaker-Row	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
fish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Sampson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
or	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
or	O
since	O
in	O
any	O
shape	O
whatsoever	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
an	O
intire	O
stranger	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
that	O
gentleman	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
buying	O
the	O
fish	O
,	O
a	O
Polander	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
with	O
two	O
remnants	O
of	O
cloth	O
over	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
much	O
there	O
was	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Polander	O
?	O
Sampson	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
Polander	O
's	O
dress	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
Polander	O
first	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Polander	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Sampson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
spoke	O
first	O
;	O
the	O
Polander	O
asked	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
18	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
measured	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Polander	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
in	O
Shoemaker-Row	O
?	O
Sampson	O
.	O
Why	O
master	O
we	O
want	O
to	O
buy	O
fish	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
other	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
bargain	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Coveneys	O
,	O
in	O
Shoemaker-Row	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Sampson	O
.	O
A	O
money	O
changer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
Sampson	O
.	O
Buying	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
money	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cloth	O
delivered	O
?	O
Sampson	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cloth	O
delivered	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
asked	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
?	O
Sampson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kay	O
desired	O
to	O
besworn	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Sampson	O
together	O
about	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
acquainted	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
Decosta	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
cloths	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
court	O
committed	O
Sampson	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
him	O
being	O
indicted	O
the	O
next	O
sessions	O
for	O
perjury	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
482.	O
Roger	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bennet	I-place
Gracechurch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
Harrateen	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
15	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Cloathworker	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
man	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cut	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
Harrateen	O
off	O
a	O
piece	O
in	O
my	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Randolph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
deliver	O
some	O
goods	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
Davis	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
Harrateen	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
delivered	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
ride	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
but	O
one	O
leg	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
ride	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Gracechurch	O
Street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
an	O
easier	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Harrateen	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
trousers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
trousers	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
publickly	O
whipped	O
at	O
a	O
whipping	O
post	O
.	O
483.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Masterson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martins	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
castor	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Triquett	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
October	O
5th	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Triquett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
goldsmiths	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
seven	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buttons	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
price	O
was	O
16	O
d.	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
weighing	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
silver	O
castor	O
which	O
I	O
now	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
but	O
rather	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
then	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
turn	O
my	O
eye	O
towards	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
castor	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
overtake	O
him	O
?	O
Triquett	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
castor	O
into	O
the	O
kennel	O
,	O
the	O
castor	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
you	O
had	O
missed	O
the	O
castor	O
?	O
Triquett	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
opportunity	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
:	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Fraser	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
?	O
Triquett	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Sinclair	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
accidentally	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
beyond	O
Mr.	O
Triquett	O
's	O
door	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
call	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
stop	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
so	O
to	O
?	O
Sinclair	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
mob	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
Sinclair	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
first	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Triquett	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
2	O
hours	O
with	O
him	O
afterwards	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Three	O
witnesses	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
had	O
behaved	O
faithfully	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+	O
484.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
*	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
violently	O
and	O
feloniously	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Swaine	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Swaine	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Sept.	O
30th	O
.	O
*	O
This	O
Indictment	O
was	O
founded	O
on	O
the	O
statute	O
of	O
the	O
3d	O
and	O
4th	O
of	O
William	O
and	O
Mary	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
this	O
offence	O
felony	O
without	O
benefit	O
of	O
clergy	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Swaine	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
or	O
before	O
the	O
watch	O
went	O
eleven	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
penny	O
dram	O
of	O
cinnamon	O
water	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
upon	O
the	O
jar	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
drank	O
one	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
six-pence	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
giving	O
him	O
change	O
,	O
he	O
pushed	O
the	O
door	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
compter	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
some	O
company	O
at	O
the	O
tavern	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
discharge	O
his	O
reckoning	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
first	O
)	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
3	O
s.	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
resistance	O
he	O
would	O
destroy	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
unbottoned	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
then	O
?	O
Swaine	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
had	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
he	O
demanded	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
there	O
that	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
me	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
tobacco	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
18	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
that	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
half	O
pence	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
that	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
small	O
beer	O
brewer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
set	O
a	O
candle	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
ever	O
took	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threatened	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
said	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
same	O
clothes	O
on	O
then	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
?	O
Swaine	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Swaine	O
.	O
No	O
never	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
in	O
any	O
house	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Swaine	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
over	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
body	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
some	O
meat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
pepper	O
and	O
salt	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
no	O
knowledge	O
of	O
my	O
face	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
directly	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
lodgers	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Swaine	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
call	O
out	O
to	O
these	O
lodgers	O
?	O
Swaine	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
or	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
this	O
cook	O
's	O
shop	O
open	O
then	O
?	O
Swaine	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
never	O
a	O
shop	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
shut	O
your	O
shop	O
door	O
?	O
Swaine	O
.	O
Because	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
but	O
him	O
and	O
I.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
but	O
the	O
door	O
might	O
shut	O
of	O
itself	O
?	O
Swaine	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sensible	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
your	O
's	O
a	O
glass	O
door	O
?	O
Swaine	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
any	O
body	O
going	O
by	O
might	O
look	O
in	O
?	O
Swaine	O
.	O
It	O
slides	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
?	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
think	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
cried	O
out	O
aloud	O
the	O
watchman	O
would	O
have	O
heard	O
you	O
?	O
Swaine	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
run	O
the	O
risque	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
great	O
mastiff	O
dog	O
there	O
?	O
Swaine	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
chained	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Keyan	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
one	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fraser	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Keyan	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
?	O
what	O
were	O
his	O
words	O
?	O
Keyan	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
borrowed	O
some	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
any	O
sum	O
?	O
Keyan	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dunham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
cook	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
Dunham	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
being	O
a	O
customer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
groat	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
beef	O
(	O
which	O
I	O
served	O
him	O
with	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Swaine	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
body	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sat	O
so	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
well	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Swaine	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Swaine	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
borrowed	O
some	O
money	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bertie	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Richmond	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
do	O
you	O
follow	O
?	O
Bertie	O
.	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
father	O
?	O
Bertie	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Bertie	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
since	O
Christmas	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Bertie	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
sea	O
surgeon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
Bertie	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Kew	O
Lane	O
at	O
Richmond	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
lady	O
lives	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
is	O
very	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
have	O
any	O
business	O
as	O
a	O
surgeon	O
?	O
Bertie	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
here	O
that	O
knows	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
surgeon	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Richmond	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
character	O
does	O
he	O
bear	O
?	O
Monk	O
.	O
He	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
walk	O
with	O
him	O
with	O
100	O
l.	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
mistrusted	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
his	O
lady	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
kept	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
quality	O
company	O
.	O
-	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Marlborough	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
acted	O
as	O
such	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Emerson	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
since	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
been	O
married	O
?	O
Trueman	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
my	O
mistress	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
character	O
has	O
Mr.	O
Emerson	O
?	O
Trueman	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
see	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
,	O
and	O
ply	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
sea	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
officers	O
respected	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kilpin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
sometimes	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
opportunities	O
of	O
taking	O
away	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bell	O
and	O
Castle	O
at	O
Windsor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
very	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
make	O
any	O
inquiry	O
after	O
him	O
in	O
Kew	O
Lane	O
.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
The	O
Duke	O
of	O
St.	O
Alban	O
's	O
park-keeper	O
made	O
a	O
strickt	O
inquiry	O
after	O
him	O
in	O
Kew	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
garret	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Kew	O
Lane	O
?	O
Trueman	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
keep	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
he	O
a	O
lodger	O
?	O
Trueman	O
.	O
He	O
kept	O
a	O
house	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
18	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Swaine	I-pers
,	O
Sep.	O
30th	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
tried	O
.	O
+	O
485.	O
Richard	B-pers
Plaistowe	I-pers
*	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Allhallows	B-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
gent	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
.	O
for	O
feloniously	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
,	O
or	O
causing	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
writing	O
in	O
paper	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
which	O
is	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
*	O
Stat	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
G.	O
II	O
.	O
>	O
June	O
7th	O
,	O
1747	O
.	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Plaistowe	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
five	O
pounds	O
five	O
shillings	O
on	O
demand	O
,	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
by	O
me	O
£5	O
.	O
5s	O
.	O
J.	O
Kynaston	O
Fawkner	O
.	O
By	O
reason	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
note	O
,	O
he	O
(	O
the	O
Defendant	O
)	O
defrauded	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinton	I-pers
of	O
2	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Steel-yard	O
coffee	O
house	O
in	O
Thomas	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
appearance	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
searcher	O
at	O
the	O
port	O
of	O
Lewis	O
in	O
Sussex	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
searcher	O
at	O
the	O
port	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
some	O
body	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
fetch	O
his	O
books	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
seem	O
to	O
want	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
Kinton	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
with	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Lewis	O
in	O
Sussex	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Crockatts	O
in	O
Cloak	O
Lane	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
this	O
note	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Crockatt	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
Did	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
notes	O
but	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
paid	O
next	O
Saturday	O
:	O
the	O
inquest	O
of	O
the	O
ward	O
were	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
strange	O
thing	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
worthy	O
man	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Crockatt	O
should	O
let	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
made	O
payable	O
on	O
demand	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
drawn	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1747	O
,	O
lye	O
to	O
this	O
time	O
unpaid	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
money	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
and	O
demand	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
three	O
guineas	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
leave	O
myself	O
without	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
two	O
guineas	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
any	O
service	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
have	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
indorsed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
indorsed	O
it	O
?	O
Kinton	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
for	O
the	O
remaining	O
3	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
5	O
guineas	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
all	O
upon	O
the	O
credit	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crockatt	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
there	O
that	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
payment	O
:	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
the	O
note	O
and	O
laughed	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
Fawkner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
does	O
this	O
note	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
signed	O
by	O
?	O
Kinton	O
.	O
By	O
J	O
Kynaston	O
Fawkner	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Plaistowe	O
never	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
Money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
since	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
from	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
before	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
had	O
not	O
you	O
frequently	O
seen	O
him	O
?	O
Kinton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
acquainted	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
that	O
use	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
very	O
seldom	O
came	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
time	O
but	O
of	O
an	O
evening	O
.	O
The	O
note	O
was	O
read.	O
``	O
June	O
27th	O
,	O
1747.	O
``	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Plaistowe	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
``	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
on	O
demand	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
five	O
pounds	O
``	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
value	O
received	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
``	O
J.	O
Kynaston	O
Fawkner	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
lend	O
him	O
any	O
other	O
money	O
?	O
Kinton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
once	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
18	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
him	O
these	O
2	O
guineas	O
for	O
?	O
Kinton	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
note	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
lend	O
Mr.	O
Plaistow	O
money	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Kinton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
once	O
?	O
Kinton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
18	O
s.	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
the	O
loan	O
of	O
the	O
18	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
loan	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
guineas	O
?	O
Kinton	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
but	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
18	O
s.	O
piece	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
less	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
than	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Fawkner	O
's	O
hand	O
?	O
Kinton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Crockatt	O
's	O
in	O
Cloak	O
lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Kinton	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
gentleman	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
one	O
Fawkner	O
of	O
South	O
Carolina	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
who	O
came	O
from	O
South	O
Carolina	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
note	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
for	O
30	O
l.	O
which	O
was	O
accepted	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Plaistowe	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
defrauded	O
him	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
election	O
at	O
Southampton	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
advertised	O
him	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
initial	O
letters	O
of	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
J.	O
K.	O
F.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
July	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
Last	O
July	O
was	O
12	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
you	O
then	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
Kynaston	O
had	O
defrauded	O
him	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
in	O
passing	O
away	O
notes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
since	O
that	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
Never	O
since	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
court	O
to	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
shew	O
him	O
Mr.	O
Fawkners	O
's	O
acceptance	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Baccus	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Attorney	O
]	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
centry	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
centry	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
they	O
prosecuted	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
ruin	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
twice	O
.	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Baccus	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
of	O
any	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Consider	O
the	O
prisoner	O
now	O
stands	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
crime	O
which	O
affects	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
lieutenant	O
in	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
service	O
?	O
Baccus	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
you	O
what	O
was	O
contained	O
in	O
the	O
warrant	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
warrant	O
for	O
?	O
Baccus	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
defrauding	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinton	I-pers
and	O
others	O
,	O
under	O
false	O
tokens	O
and	O
pretences	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
both	O
indictments	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
detainer	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
another	O
fact	O
.	O
486.	O
William	B-pers
Tally	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Pancras	I-place
Soper	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
iron	O
japan	O
'd	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Chiswell	I-pers
,	O
October	O
8	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Chiswell	I-pers
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
eight	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
?	O
Chiswell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
across	O
the	O
Kennel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
dropped	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
?	O
Chiswell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
what	O
induced	O
me	O
to	O
prosecute	O
him	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
frightened	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
honest	O
lad	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
487.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
nutmegs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
chocolate	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
hyson	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
September	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sharpe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	B-place
of	I-place
Mark	I-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pound	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
hyson	O
tea	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
but	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
challenged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
he	O
knew	O
something	O
of	O
the	O
tea	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
chocolate	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
pretty	O
early	O
,	O
and	O
slipped	O
into	O
the	O
compting	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
;	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
six	O
nutmegs	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
Mr.	O
Wardley	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
our	O
gate	O
keeper	O
at	O
Algate	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
better	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
than	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Wardley	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
nutmegs	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
where	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
lodge	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
chocolate	O
and	O
some	O
tea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
be	O
certain	O
that	O
that	O
tea	O
was	O
yours	O
?	O
Sharpe	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
hyson	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
chocolate	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
easy	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
carrying	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
in	O
Seething	O
Lane	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
time	O
:	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
my	O
laying	O
those	O
goods	O
so	O
low	O
was	O
because	O
his	O
parents	O
are	O
very	O
honest	O
people	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
court	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
publickly	O
whipped	O
in	O
Fenchurch	O
Street	O
.	O
+	O
488	O
James	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
cambrick	O
bonnet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woollen	O
petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
cock	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
;	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
dimitty	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
trousers	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lemmon	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
11th	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
entrusted	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
bed	O
side	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
wak	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
mistress	O
,	O
your	O
house	O
is	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
fasten	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
fastened	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
imagine	O
that	O
the	O
thief	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
fore	O
door	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
backwards	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
skittle	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
garden	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
watchman	O
pushed	O
back	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
fore	O
door	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
my	O
drawers	O
were	O
all	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
cock	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lemon	I-pers
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
man	O
we	O
let	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	O
Cobham	O
's	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
confess	O
the	O
fact	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Whitton	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
such	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
in	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
find	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
house	O
open	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
drawers	O
with	O
a	O
wire	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
ordered	O
Mr.	O
Ind	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Ind	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Ind	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
turnkey	O
of	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Cook	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
live	O
over	O
against	O
you	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
only	O
by	O
his	O
coming	O
and	O
mending	O
the	O
locks	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
asking	O
you	O
how	O
intimate	O
you	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
how	O
long	O
you	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
come	O
often	O
to	O
Daniel	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
almost	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
spend	O
an	O
evening	O
there	O
sometimes	O
Cook	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
The	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
in	O
Middle-row	O
,	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
lived	O
over	O
against	O
you	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
A	O
lock-smith	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
Saturday	O
night	O
?	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
sailor	O
there	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
upon	O
a	O
party	O
of	O
pleasure	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	O
's	O
sister	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
find	O
a	O
trick	O
to	O
prevent	O
you	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
I	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
turn	O
out	O
so	O
;	O
take	O
your	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
consider	O
whether	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
spoke	O
in	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Cook	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
hearing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
By	O
means	O
of	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
watchman	O
said	O
,	O
peggy	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
has	O
your	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
watchman	O
said	O
,	O
Peggy	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
your	O
things	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
them	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Peggy	O
,	O
I	O
hear	O
you	O
are	O
robbed	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
fasten	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
drawers	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Cook	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
fastened	O
but	O
one	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
had	O
no	O
lock	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
sailor	O
sober	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
The	O
sailor	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lemmon	I-pers
[	O
the	O
sailor	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
Daniel	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
and	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
robbed	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Fox	O
(	O
the	O
watchman	O
)	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
smile	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
I	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
:	O
and	O
Fox	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
small	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
willing	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
small	O
satisfaction	O
?	O
Lemmon	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
Daniel	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
another	O
half	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
who	O
had	O
them	O
?	O
Lemmon	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
Weston	O
go	O
along	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
Weston	O
lived	O
?	O
Lemmon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Lemmon	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jemmy	O
the	O
smith	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
called	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jemmy	O
the	O
smith	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Things	O
belonging	O
to	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Lemmon	I-pers
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
]	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
says	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
twelve	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Lemmon	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
or	O
to	O
see	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
just	O
by	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ind	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
house-keeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
in	O
Middle-row	O
,	O
Holborn	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
was	O
talking	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
down	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Ind	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
Lord	O
Cobham	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
And	O
Justice	O
Hole	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
own	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
directions	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
in	O
Chancery	O
Lane	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
White	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
into	O
this	O
empty	O
house	O
?	O
Ind	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
borrowed	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
a	O
screw	O
driver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gimblet	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
another	O
screw	O
driver	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
charge	O
any	O
body	O
wrongfully	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Ind	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
that	O
appeared	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
induced	O
me	O
to	O
neglect	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
do	O
other	O
things	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dolley	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
years	O
as	O
working	O
with	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
complaint	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
jobbing	O
smith	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
employed	O
promiscuously	O
at	O
other	O
people	O
's	O
houses	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
wronged	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
notorious	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
people	O
are	O
afraid	O
to	O
live	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Woman	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
?	O
Dolley	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
word	O
for	O
a	O
pin	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
the	O
ruin	O
of	O
half	O
the	O
young	O
men	O
in	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
John	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
master	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
near	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
work	O
with	O
you	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
apprehend	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
wrong	O
you	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
boy	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
'till	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
company	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
boy	O
of	O
fifteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
can	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
without	O
being	O
pulled	O
in	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Gunter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
his	O
master	O
works	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
an	O
hundred	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
mistrust	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Gunter	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
so	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
opportunities	O
enough	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
have	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
Gunter	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
verily	O
believe	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
represented	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
infamous	O
house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Middle	O
row	O
,	O
Holborn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
three	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
hardworking-man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
,	O
and	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
489.	O
Joseph	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
6th	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cornish	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lad	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
wedding	O
ring	O
off	O
my	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
ring	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
till	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Febr	O
.	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
ring	O
was	O
pawned	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
redeem	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
redeem	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Febr	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
;	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
that	O
for	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Febr	O
.	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
same	O
ring	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
redeemed	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
ring	O
off	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
rogue	O
,	O
what	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
again	O
?	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
three	O
days	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
(	O
one	O
Bull	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Dyer	O
's	O
street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
cup	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
abuse	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
no	O
husband	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
lives	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
after	O
March	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
see	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
up	O
twenty	O
times	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Co.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cornish	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
obliged	O
to	O
say	O
a	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
against	O
yourself	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
work	O
for	O
a	O
tenant	O
of	O
yours	O
,	O
one	O
Hookham	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
there	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
;	O
where	O
was	O
your	O
husband	O
then	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lie	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
Guy	B-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	O
Warwick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
all	O
that	O
six	O
weeks	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
never	O
lay	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
lie	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
children	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
nobody	O
take	O
somebody	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
from	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
children	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
Yo	O
u	O
was	O
very	O
intimate	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
you	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
We	O
used	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
six	O
weeks	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
ring	O
off	O
your	O
finger	O
,	O
or	O
after	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
ring	O
off	O
your	O
finger	O
in	O
Febr	O
.	O
was	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
visiting	O
you	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
or	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
visited	O
you	O
for	O
six	O
weeks	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
the	O
ring	O
in	O
a	O
jocose	O
manner	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
my	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
with	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
ring	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
because	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
ring	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
this	O
ring	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
ring	O
pawn	O
'd	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
At	O
one	O
Dawson	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Bell	O
yard	O
,	O
Whitechappel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
ring	O
,	O
what	O
time	O
was	O
that	O
taken	O
away	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
were	O
they	O
two	O
different	O
rings	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
same	O
ring	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
ring	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
how	O
often	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
after	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ignorant	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
third	O
ring	O
taken	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
At	O
Mrs.	O
Bull	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
had	O
you	O
no	O
bedfellow	O
there	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bull	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
child	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
now	O
did	O
not	O
Mr.	O
King	O
lay	O
with	O
you	O
one	O
night	O
there	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
your	O
father-in-law	O
beat	O
you	O
for	O
?	O
Cornish	O
.	O
For	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Estber	O
Lander	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
recompence	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
let	O
it	O
alone	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
his	O
remedy	O
at	O
law	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barret	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
in	O
Mount	O
Street	O
,	O
by	O
Grosvenor	O
Square	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
work	O
was	O
scarce	O
,	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
believing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
where-ever	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
Woman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
redeem	O
a	O
ring	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
whether	O
you	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
this	O
woman	O
was	O
his	O
wife	O
?	O
Dawson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
in	O
her	O
hearing	O
?	O
Dawson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
near	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
490.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
26	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Compton	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
keeps	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Peynon	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Peynon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
but	O
not	O
giving	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
mug	O
and	O
her	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Mrs.	O
Compton	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
mug	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
Compton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
consider	O
how	O
poor	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
compassion	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
491.	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
West	I-place
,	I-place
minster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
July	O
2d	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
wanted	O
some	O
Allopeans	O
and	O
Grograms	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silk	O
stockings	O
;	O
and	O
accordingly	O
I	O
took	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
Allopeans	O
and	O
Grograms	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
desirous	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
carry	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
carry	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
one	O
piece	O
and	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
looked	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
tradesman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
let	O
him	O
carry	O
one	O
piece	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
resist	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
Mall	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
by	O
Buckingham-house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
kitchin	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
Allo	O
peans	O
and	O
Grograms	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
stockings	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
place	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
says	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
stockings	O
from	O
him	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
kitchin	O
door	O
,	O
says	O
wrong	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
stockings	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
gentleman	O
is	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
some	O
grograms	O
and	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
knew	O
some	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
I	O
believed	O
wanted	O
some	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
kitchin	O
door	O
I	O
agreed	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
for	O
the	O
white	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
gone	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
before	O
I	O
returned	O
.	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
three	O
hours	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
any	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
in	O
that	O
narrow	O
place	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
called	O
or	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
finger	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
a	O
centry	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
lightish	O
coloured	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
light	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
run	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
ready	O
to	O
break	O
his	O
neck	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
up	O
my	O
allopeans	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
492.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wisby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
quilted	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
crape	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
damask	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
hood	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
linnen	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
my	O
cloaths	O
and	O
my	O
linnen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
them	O
?	O
Sibley	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Sibley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
age	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
Sibley	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
at	O
least	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Sibley	O
.	O
Because	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
charged	O
some	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
partaker	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Sibley	O
.	O
Her	O
going	O
away	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
returning	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
vestry-clark	O
of	O
Cheshunt	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
from	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
workhouse	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
warrant	O
down	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
fell	O
asleep	O
under	O
a	O
hedge	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
under	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Sibley	O
.	O
Only	O
a	O
cap	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
serve	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
girl	O
from	O
Cheshunt	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
apprentice	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
detained	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
workhouse	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
vestry-clark	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
up	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
her	O
mother	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
field	O
?	O
Broom	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
beyond	O
Wood	O
's	O
Close	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Islington	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wanted	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
mother	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
cleared	O
herself	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
what	O
her	O
daughter	O
accused	O
her	O
of	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
493.	O
Peter	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
unknown	O
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
September	O
14	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dutton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
follow	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
that	O
gentleman	O
?	O
Dutton	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
acquaint	O
the	O
gentleman	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Dutton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
?	O
Dutton	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
it	O
hang	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
the	O
gentleman	O
out	O
?	O
Dutton	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
's	O
Advertiser	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
once	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
came	O
again	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
by	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Dutton	O
pursuing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
step	O
their	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
either	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
Mr.	O
Dutton	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
then	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
mistress	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
difference	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
away	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
his	O
master	O
and	O
another	O
gentleman	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
belived	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Collins	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
apprentice	O
with	O
him	O
now	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
me	O
well	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
494.	O
Peter	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
the	I-pers
elder	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
the	I-pers
younger	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
September	O
5	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
wharfingers	O
company	O
,	O
at	O
Ralph	O
's	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
Young	O
's	O
Key	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
a	B-place
warehouse	I-place
,	I-place
under	I-place
Young	I-place
's	I-place
Key	I-place
gateway	I-place
,	O
with	O
sugar	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
Austin	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Thames	O
Street	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
a	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
us	O
the	O
hogshead	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
which	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Coleman	O
and	O
son	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
Otley	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
the	O
Cask	O
was	O
14	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
mark	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
?	O
Austin	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
marked	O
with	O
an	O
O	O
for	O
the	O
ship	O
Otley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
weigh	O
it	O
?	O
Austin	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Beale	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
grocer	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
weighed	O
nine	O
pound	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
Tower	O
Ward	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
with	O
this	O
sugar	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
breeches	O
upon	O
Young	O
's	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
charged	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Austin	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
sugar	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
showed	O
me	O
the	O
hogshead	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
O.	B-pers
N	I-pers
.	I-pers
14	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Box	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
in	O
King	O
Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
to	O
open	O
his	O
shop	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
York	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
entrusted	O
with	O
some	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
him	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
my	O
father	O
died	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Box	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
grocer	O
and	O
druggist	O
,	O
in	O
King	O
Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bliss	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Bell	O
Alley	O
,	O
by	O
King	O
Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
oftentimes	O
I	O
am	O
intrusted	O
with	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
intrusted	O
with	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
wronged	O
any	O
body	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Bliss	O
.	O
That	O
which	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
was	O
not	O
he	O
a	O
little	O
liquorish	O
?	O
Bliss	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
he	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
third	O
regiment	O
of	O
guards	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
General	O
Post	O
Office	O
,	O
not	O
as	O
a	O
letter	O
carrier	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
from	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
what	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
carrying	O
my	O
heavy	O
bags	O
to	O
the	O
Post	O
Office	O
,	O
one	O
hundred	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
half	O
weight	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
character	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
To	O
be	O
publickly	O
whipped	O
on	O
the	O
keys	O
.	O
495.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
gown	O
eyes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
,	O
September	O
8	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
,	O
a	B-place
hardware	I-place
shop	I-place
,	I-place
opposite	I-place
to	I-place
St.	I-place
Michaell	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
that	O
woman	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
eighth	O
or	O
ninth	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
snuffers	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
scissars	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
snuffers	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
good	O
enough	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
gown	O
eyes	O
about	O
a	O
gross	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
opening	O
the	O
snuffers	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
snuffers	O
were	O
not	O
worth	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
a	O
paper	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
stood	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
the	O
snuffers	O
under	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gross	O
of	O
gown	O
eyes	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
throw	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
:	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
to	O
Guild	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
innocent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
paper	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
took	O
up	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
say	O
she	O
threw	O
down	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
paper	O
which	O
she	O
threw	O
be	O
hind	O
the	O
computer	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
496	O
,	O
497.	O
Jane	B-pers
Swanson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
How	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
velvet	O
pillorean	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tuston	I-pers
,	O
October	O
5	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tuston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
velvet	O
pillorean	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
off	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
woman	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Tuston	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
have	O
it	O
?	O
Tuston	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Swanson	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
used	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Tuston	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
close	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
handed	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lad	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tuston	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
pilloreen	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
How	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Tuston	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
as	O
plain	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
Swanson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
How	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
Swanson	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
498.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linnen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
,	O
Sept	O
17	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
linnen	O
waistcoat	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
pinned	O
to	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
peep	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
unpin	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
officer	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
,	O
over-against	O
Mr.	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
concealed	O
?	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
waistcoat	O
?	O
Bagnall	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
+499	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kennigem	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mawhood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bedell	I-pers
,	O
September	O
22	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mawhood	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
27	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Mawhood	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
or	O
a	O
lodger	O
?	O
Mawhood	O
.	O
He	O
lodges	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Bedell	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
in	O
William	B-pers
Bedell	I-pers
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
locked	O
?	O
Mawhood	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
that	O
very	O
morning	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
little	O
prize	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Mawhood	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
then	O
?	O
Mawhood	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
prize	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
more	O
money	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
in	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
open	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
back	O
?	O
Mawhood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
recovered	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
money	O
again	O
?	O
Mawhood	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
returned	O
me	O
14	O
guineas	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Mawhood	O
.	O
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
elaven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
Goodmans	O
Fields	O
Wells	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
c	O
oming	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Mawhood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodge	O
there	O
?	O
Mawhood	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
