TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
22d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1748	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Public	O
may	O
be	O
assured	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
during	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CALVERT	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
)	O
the	O
Sessions-Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
Four-pence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
Sessions	O
shall	O
be	O
carefully	O
compriz	O
'd	O
in	O
One	O
such	O
Four-penny	O
Book	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
farther	O
Burthen	O
on	O
the	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CALVERT	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DENISON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ABNEY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr	O
Baron	B-pers
CLIVE	I-pers
,	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRACEY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Moulson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Baron	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Naldor	I-pers
,	O
Josiah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Twells	I-pers
,	O
St.	B-pers
John	I-pers
Burrough	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lasoffe	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hornblower	I-pers
,	O
Solomon	B-pers
Pelitior	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bridge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Langworthy	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chishohn	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jaumard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickett	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Deschampus	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hoben	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sarsfield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lowry	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
John	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Falsey	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
The	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
tobacco	O
;	O
I	O
weigh	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
30	O
lb	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
,	O
Wapping	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
honestly	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
vessel	O
outward	O
bound	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Manwaring	O
,	O
before	O
whom	O
he	O
confest	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
vessel	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Holly	O
,	O
the	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
Burling	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr	O
William	B-pers
Falsey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
tobacco	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
Holly	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Falsey	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
on	O
board	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
theirs	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Bowson	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Holly	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Captain	O
of	O
this	O
person	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
tobacco	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Casks	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Captain	O
we	O
found	O
three	O
more	O
opened	O
;	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
casks	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
tobacco	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
either	O
drunk	O
or	O
bewitch	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
John	B-pers
Bowley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cart-whip	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Enips	I-pers
,	O
November	O
14	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Enips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hammersmith	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
this	O
cart-whip	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
stable	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
which	O
way	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
selling	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
value	O
it	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Henry	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
whip	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
by	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
whip	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
James	B-pers
Gailey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
l.	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr	O
Joseph	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Loe	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
till	O
last	O
Sunday	O
,	O
to	O
wait	O
at	O
table	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
?	O
Loe	O
.	O
With	O
taking	O
20	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawer	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
away	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
he	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
to	O
?	O
Loe	O
.	O
To	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
;	O
my	O
apprentice	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
Loe	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
had	O
been	O
here	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
:	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
gone	O
to	O
his	O
guardian	O
at	O
Camberwell	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
drawer	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
cloaths	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
supper	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
maid	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
took	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
his	O
linen	O
;	O
at	O
length	O
my	O
apprentice	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
36	O
shilling	O
piece	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
:	O
Richard	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
better	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
than	O
to	O
think	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
the	O
Pyde-horse	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
;	O
thus	O
he	O
persisted	O
till	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
strip	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
17	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
with	O
the	O
half-guinea	O
and	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
was	O
14	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
is	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Loe	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
minded	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
size	O
and	O
the	O
crack	O
in	O
the	O
glass	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
pistol	O
?	O
Loe	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
loaded	O
?	O
Loe	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Herbert	B-pers
Reader	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Loe	O
's	O
house	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Excise	O
Office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Reader	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr	O
Loe	O
to	O
the	O
Spotted	O
Horse	O
in	O
Shore-ditch	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
those	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
pockets	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
this	O
watch	O
before	O
?	O
Reader	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
in	O
Mr	O
Loe	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
size	O
and	O
crack	O
in	O
the	O
glass	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Loe	O
's	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
this	O
particular	O
pistol	O
before	O
?	O
Reader	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
oftimes	O
put	O
in	O
and	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
compter	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4.	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
serge	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Hethcote	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
5.	O
Charles	B-pers
Culley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
china	O
punch	O
bowl	O
and	O
two	O
glasses	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hinkley	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
19	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hinkley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Virginia	B-place
street	I-place
No	I-place
24	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
and	O
stole	O
a	O
china	O
punch	O
bowl	O
and	O
two	O
glass	O
tumblers	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
call	O
me	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
knock	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
man	O
?	O
Hinkley	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
up	O
a	O
turning	O
about	O
six	O
doors	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
no	O
thorough	O
fare	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
neighbours	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
assistance	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Hannah	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
caught	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
buset	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
skirt	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
recovered	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
kept	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
till	O
others	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
broke	O
into	O
pieces	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
three	O
sheets	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
29	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
7.	O
Richard	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robing	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
of	O
a	O
hat	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
8.	O
Ann	B-pers
Towning	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Towning	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
capuchin	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lomux	B-pers
Ryder	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
15	O
.	O
Lomux	O
Ryder	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
at	O
five	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
my	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
was	O
shewing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
some	O
capuchins	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
compter	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
stooping	O
down	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
hang	O
down	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
capuchin	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
David	B-pers
Macklane	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
Oct.	O
11	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
10.	O
George	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
pounds	O
of	O
sugar	O
.	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
,	O
widow	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
12.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
rabbits	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Olney	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
But	O
recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
.	O
13.	O
Jane	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
34	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Steven	B-pers
Gilley	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
15	O
.	O
Steven	B-pers
Gilley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
of	O
small	O
ware	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
street	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Gilley	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
pretending	O
to	O
look	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
candle	O
to	O
the	O
colour	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
conveyed	O
two	O
half	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
wanted	O
two	O
ounces	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
my	O
apprentice	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
two	O
half	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
her	O
apron	O
aside	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
under	O
that	O
a	O
pocket	O
apron	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
hand	O
two	O
half	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Sweeting	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gilley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Richards	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
to	O
buy	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
served	O
her	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
half	O
piece	O
in	O
each	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
conveyed	O
them	O
by	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
whispered	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
compter	O
and	O
stayed	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
served	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
those	O
half	O
pieces	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
apron	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mosman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Hymore	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3600	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
shells	O
and	O
shot	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Eade	I-pers
.	O
Nov.	O
2	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Eade	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ship	O
chandler	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
King	B-place
Edward	I-place
's	I-place
stairs	I-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
buying	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
iron	O
shot	O
and	O
boomshels	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
they	O
were	O
bought	O
,	O
shipped	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
,	O
the	O
ship	O
anchored	O
against	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
shells	O
and	O
shot	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
two	O
lighters	O
,	O
one	O
went	O
through	O
bridge	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
my	O
hous	O
Says	O
the	O
clerk	O
that	O
bought	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
shot	O
in	O
that	O
lighter	O
which	O
we	O
put	O
in	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
weighed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
deficient	O
3	O
hundred	O
weight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
weight	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
?	O
Eade	O
.	O
We	O
bought	O
about	O
50	O
tun	O
of	O
shot	O
and	O
shells	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
French	O
prize	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
this	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
iron	O
shot	O
,	O
I	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
four	O
shillings	O
a	O
hundred	O
for	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
This	O
person	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
man	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
very	O
shot	O
that	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
weighed	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
26	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
prove	O
they	O
were	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Eade	O
.	O
We	O
prove	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
another	O
evidence	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
Then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
those	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
into	O
Surry	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
bought	O
.	O
Welch	O
told	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Larrance	O
,	O
whom	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Hammond	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
prison	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
him	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
in	O
his	O
evidence	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Larrance	I-pers
.	O
Welch	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
who	O
carries	O
on	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
keeps	O
an	O
old	O
rope	O
shop	O
in	O
Rotherheath	O
in	O
Surry	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Isaac	B-pers
Larrance	I-pers
,	O
Welch	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
there	O
?	O
Larrance	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
us	O
the	O
time	O
your	O
brother	O
bought	O
those	O
things	O
.	O
Larrance	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
?	O
Larrance	O
.	O
Some	O
iron	O
shot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
those	O
mens	O
name	O
that	O
came	O
?	O
Larrance	O
.	O
One	O
John	B-pers
Mossman	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
house	O
about	O
three	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
shot	O
and	O
boom	O
shells	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
an	O
hundred	O
?	O
Larrance	O
.	O
Two	O
shillings	O
an	O
hundred	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
Welch	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
an	O
hundred	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
persons	O
that	O
brought	O
and	O
sold	O
those	O
shot	O
and	O
shells	O
to	O
your	O
brother	O
?	O
Larrance	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Churchouse	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Brisingham	I-pers
,	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
that	O
is	O
gone	O
off	O
,	O
linked	O
me	O
in	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
about	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Eade	O
was	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
of	O
the	O
lighter	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
together	O
in	O
taking	O
some	O
of	O
this	O
iron	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
lighter	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Nov.	O
We	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Hymore	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
watchman	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
the	O
lighters	O
lay	O
along	O
side	O
the	O
ship	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
agreed	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
this	O
iron	O
?	O
Churchouse	O
.	O
Brisingham	O
,	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
Mossman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
Bentley	O
there	O
?	O
Churchouse	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
please	O
you	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
nine	O
booms	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
skiff	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
shore	O
at	O
new	O
crane	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Larrance	O
's	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Brisingham	O
and	O
Mossman	O
made	O
three	O
freights	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Bentley	O
with	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Churchouse	O
.	O
Bentley	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
another	O
box	O
seeing	O
some	O
men	O
play	O
at	O
cards	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
nine	O
shillings	O
and	O
seven	O
pence	O
half	O
penny	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
receive	O
it	O
.	O
Mossman	O
,	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
Hymore	O
had	O
each	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Churchouse	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Patts	O
's	O
alehouse	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
master	O
of	O
this	O
ship	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
the	O
vessel	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
the	O
Portsmouth	O
tender	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
goods	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
London	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
goods	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
Shells	O
and	O
booms	O
for	O
messrs.	O
Eades	O
and	O
Boulton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
hundred	O
tun	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
bring	O
the	O
ship	O
to	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
To	O
Wapping	O
dock	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
two	O
lighters	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Nov.	O
And	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Eades	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
clerk	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
clerk	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
part	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Eades	O
's	O
goods	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
very	O
remarkable	O
;	O
we	O
broke	O
them	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
save	O
the	O
duty	O
,	O
by	O
an	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
commissioners	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
satisfied	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
shot	O
and	O
shells	O
I	O
brought	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Eades	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
cross	O
board	O
shot	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
Captain	O
Rose	B-pers
to	O
take	O
them	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
ship	O
;	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
ship	O
's	O
arrival	O
,	O
we	O
sent	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
goods	O
out	O
;	O
one	O
went	O
through	O
bridge	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
those	O
that	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
imagined	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
shot	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
and	O
weighed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
deficiency	O
of	O
26	O
hundred	O
weight	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
Welch	O
brought	O
in	O
about	O
this	O
quantity	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
Larrance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
Larrance	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
four	O
shillings	O
an	O
hundred	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
to	O
compare	O
those	O
with	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
reason	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Bently	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Mossman	I-pers
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Hymore	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Mary	B-pers
Upman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
china	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
china	O
mug	O
,	O
two	O
napkins	O
,	O
one	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Perkinton	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
.	O
Perkinton	O
Tomkins	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Shakespear	B-place
's	I-place
head	I-place
in	I-place
Covent	I-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
interim	O
I	O
lost	O
several	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
things	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Tompkins	O
.	O
Three	O
china	O
plates	O
,	O
two	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
things	O
?	O
Tompkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
on	O
this	O
Mary	B-pers
Upman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
there	O
?	O
Tompkins	O
.	O
By	O
instructions	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
Bowers	O
immediately	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
:	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Green	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
Upman	O
to	O
the	O
gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
Bowers	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
.	O
Bowers	O
confessed	O
there	O
were	O
14	O
china	O
plates	O
this	O
Upman	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
Thomas	O
Morris	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
china	O
mug	O
,	O
two	O
napkins	O
,	O
one	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
some	O
jelly	O
glasses	O
,	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
wash	O
some	O
things	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
three	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
two	O
china	O
ones	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
broken	O
one	O
,	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
soap	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
only	O
those	O
dozen	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
plates	O
against	O
she	O
married	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
boys	O
saw	O
her	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
discover	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Bowers	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
box	O
for	O
seven	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Tompkins	O
.	O
Did	O
this	O
woman	O
make	O
any	O
confession	O
before	O
Justice	O
Green	O
of	O
those	O
plates	O
?	O
Tompkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Upman	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
of	O
carrying	O
those	O
few	O
plates	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
at	O
Morris	O
's	O
.	O
Bowers	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
dozen	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
plates	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Brown	O
's	O
gardens	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
she	O
lodged	O
there	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
.	O
Morris	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
did	O
lodge	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tompkins	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
live	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
ever	O
come	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Her	O
box	O
was	O
brought	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
knowledge	O
of	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
desired	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
till	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
16.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
,	O
Oct.	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
17.	O
Richard	B-pers
Prat	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Clinch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Clinch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
butter	O
,	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
All	O
acquitted	O
.	O
18.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jolley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shard	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
1	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Morefields	B-place
,	O
am	O
an	O
upholsterer	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
took	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
from	O
my	O
door	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Cart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Shard	O
,	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Shard	O
's	O
maid	O
bring	O
out	O
an	O
old	O
pail	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
set	O
the	O
saucepan	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Cart	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
stooping	O
down	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
saucepan	O
with	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
left	O
arm	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shard	O
's	O
maid	O
servant	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I.	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Shard	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shard	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
saucepan	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Shard	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Ann	B-pers
Harison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Shamburg	I-pers
,	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jinks	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
17	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Shamburg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
shirts	O
off	O
the	O
line	O
the	O
17	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
,	O
three	O
were	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
his	O
kinsman	O
's	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Jinks	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
f	O
in	O
?	O
Shamburg	O
.	O
I	O
se	O
re	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
out	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
marked	O
J	O
J	O
the	O
John	B-pers
Jinks	I-pers
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
in	O
g	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
;	O
she	O
g	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
herself	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chitwin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
of	O
November	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
stept	O
into	O
rton	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
by	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
Crown-court	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
pawn	O
this	O
very	O
shirt	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
desired	O
9	O
s.	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
that	O
too	O
much	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
7	O
s.	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
secure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
questions	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Chitwin	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
cloath-woman	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20.	O
Henry	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
pewter-plates	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
knife	O
and	O
fork	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Addington	I-pers
,	O
November	O
9	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Addington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
le	I-place
Bone	I-place
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
purl	O
,	O
he	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
sleep	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
leave	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
immediately	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
some	O
plates	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
fore	O
door	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
going	O
cross	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
person	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
he	O
dropt	O
nine	O
plates	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
one	O
knife	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
fork	O
we	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
before	O
Justice	O
Green	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cheese	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Scull	I-pers
,	O
December	O
1	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Scull	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
near	O
Temple-Bar	B-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
hock	O
of	O
bacon	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
as	O
though	O
she	O
would	O
consult	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
crying	O
John	O
!	O
John	O
!	O
still	O
she	O
kept	O
going	O
farther	O
from	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
my	O
stacks	O
of	O
cheeses	O
that	O
had	O
an	O
equal	O
number	O
on	O
each	O
stack	O
,	O
I	O
presently	O
miss	O
'd	O
one	O
Gloucestershire	O
cheese	O
:	O
I	O
stept	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
still	O
she	O
went	O
forward	O
crying	O
John	O
!	O
John	O
!	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
tax	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
a	O
cheese	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
about	O
her	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
perceive	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
when	O
I	O
oblig	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
move	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cheese	O
between	O
her	O
legs	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
red	O
bays	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
October	O
14	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
on	O
October	O
14	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
red	O
bays	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
saw	O
some	O
body	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
young	O
men	O
pursued	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Cockpit	O
,	O
White-hall	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
told	O
a	O
centinel	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
see	O
a	O
person	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hallocks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
centinel	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
White-hall	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
October	O
4.	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
Hallocks	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Hallocks	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
him	O
six-pence	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
abuseful	O
:	O
So	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
my	O
bayonet	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
relief	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23.	O
John	B-pers
Frimley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
November	O
19	O
.	O
Nath	O
.	O
Neal	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
drawer	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
Red-lyon	O
in	O
Hownslow	O
;	O
on	O
Nov.	O
19.	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
on	O
horse-back	O
to	O
town	O
about	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
between	O
Brentford	B-place
and	O
Hounslow	B-place
,	O
on	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Smallberry-green	B-place
,	O
three	O
men	O
on	O
horse-back	O
stop	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
pistols	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
searing	O
they	O
should	O
lay-wait	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
towards	O
Hounslow	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
stay	O
'd	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
at	O
this	O
alehouse	O
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
man	O
got	O
up	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
over	O
the	O
green	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
highwayman	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
tall	O
thin	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
sailor	O
's	O
jacket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Describe	O
him	O
.	O
Neal	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
is	O
one	O
that	O
clap	O
'd	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
moon	O
light	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
so	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
White-bear	O
in	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
?	O
Neal	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Bulstrode	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Gloucester	O
waggoner	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
Smallberry-green	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
having	O
some	O
disbanded	O
marines	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
on	O
horse-back	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
having	O
heard	O
there	O
were	O
thieves	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
marines	O
lent	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
long	O
hanger	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
great	O
house	O
on	O
Smallberry-green	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
robbery	O
committed	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
lain	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
coming	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
hanger	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
riding	O
along	O
,	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
riding	O
by	O
me	O
a	O
full	O
speed	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
Green	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
flash	O
'd	O
a	O
pistol	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
short	O
about	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
following	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
chop	O
at	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
the	O
mark	O
is	O
visible	O
enough	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
feeding	O
my	O
horses	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
some	O
water	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White-bear	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
hollowing	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
why	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
them	O
?	O
I	O
having	O
nothing	O
bu	O
t	O
my	O
whip	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
could	O
not	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
before	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
got	O
in	O
between	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
horse	O
's	O
bridle	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
master	O
had	O
cut	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
loose	O
his	O
horse	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
,	O
and	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
how	O
could	O
I	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
left	O
arm	O
was	O
cut	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
?	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
24.	O
James	B-pers
Wrangham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
ravishment	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
a	O
child	O
ten	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
25.	O
William	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dollar	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
14	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
parish	O
,	O
Fleet-street	B-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
two	O
sailors	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
introduced	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
with	O
these	O
words	O
,	O
you	O
want	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
this	O
gentleman	O
will	O
sell	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
pair	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
my	O
shop	O
is	O
but	O
narrow	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
place	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
little	O
work	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
lay	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
great	O
silver	O
buckles	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sailors	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
lets	O
lock	O
at	O
these	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
;	O
says	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
gentleman	O
sell	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
stout	O
pair	O
,	O
then	O
you	O
will	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
buy	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
these	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
reach	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
glass	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
of	O
my	O
doorway	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
round	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
buckles	O
I	O
wanted	O
;	O
upon	O
turning	O
myself	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
show	O
glass	O
to	O
show	O
them	O
the	O
new	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
soldier	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
indeed	O
,	O
say	O
they	O
,	O
we	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
our	O
eyes	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
but	O
three	O
buckles	O
instead	O
of	O
four	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
sailors	O
,	O
the	O
soldier	O
had	O
stole	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
no	O
says	O
they	O
,	O
God	O
forbid	O
!	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
24	O
s.	O
for	O
that	O
pair	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
20	O
s.	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
big	O
enough	O
;	O
said	O
put	O
one	O
on	O
;	O
still	O
I	O
kept	O
harping	O
about	O
my	O
buckle	O
;	O
say	O
they	O
,	O
make	O
your	O
self	O
easy	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
certainly	O
find	O
it	O
if	O
you	O
look	O
about	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
another	O
buckle	O
was	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
show-glass	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
this	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
22	O
s.	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
no	O
accomplices	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
detected	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
will	O
make	O
appear	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
beedle	O
of	O
Goldsmith's-hall	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Goldsmith's-hall	O
,	O
Oct.	O
14.	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
maker	O
of	O
two	O
odd	O
buckles	O
he	O
brought	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
made	O
by	O
two	O
different	O
persons	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
one	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
work	O
of	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Swan-alley	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
large	O
buckle	O
by	O
two	O
sailors	O
and	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
:	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
glass	O
did	O
you	O
show	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
the	O
buckle	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
?	O
so	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
buckle	O
that	O
match	O
'd	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
brought	O
from	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
says	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
admit	O
this	O
sailor	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
shall	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
;	O
accordingly	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
at	O
Holborn-bridge	O
,	O
i.e	O
.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
sailors	O
,	O
and	O
concluded	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
robbing	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
David	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Duke's-place	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
an	O
ale-house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
taylor	O
's	O
arms	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
,	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
urgent	O
business	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
forward	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
a	O
room	O
with	O
boxes	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
he	O
directly	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
these	O
buckles	O
and	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
flatted	O
silver	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
ask	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
David	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
meant	O
5	O
s.	O
an	O
ounce	O
,	O
or	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
nothing	O
else	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
wrong	O
person	O
;	O
you	O
must	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
account	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
shall	O
stop	O
these	O
things	O
and	O
you	O
too	O
directly	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
sat	O
down	O
next	O
him	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
this	O
sailor	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
the	O
sailor	O
shall	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
shall	O
detain	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
sailor	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
three	O
sailors	O
which	O
were	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
too	O
many	O
in	O
company	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
take	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
sailor	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry-counter	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
all	O
over	O
Leaden-hall-street	O
and	O
without	O
Algate	O
,	O
to	O
inquire	O
what	O
Goldsmith	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
hall	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
the	O
beadle	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
one	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
another	O
name	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
person	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
fellows	O
to	O
the	O
buckles	O
before	O
ever	O
he	O
saw	O
these	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
and	O
two	O
sailors	O
at	O
his	O
shop	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
brought	O
them	O
before	O
alderman	O
Davies	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
many	O
excuses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26	O
,	O
27.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
M'Daniel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ansley	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
Oct.	O
27	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
27	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
28.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Cable	I-pers
,	O
chocolate-maker	O
,	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	B-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
and	O
grossly	O
insulting	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
procession	O
of	O
the	O
lord	O
mayor	O
and	O
alderman	O
,	O
in	O
their	O
return	O
from	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
court	B-place
of	I-place
Exchequer	I-place
to	O
Guild-hall	B-place
,	O
October	O
29	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
beg	O
'd	O
pardon	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
particularly	O
of	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
advertise	O
the	O
same	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
papers	O
,	O
which	O
accordingly	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
fine	O
of	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
8	O
d.	O
29.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
,	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
ticket	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Badgot	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
him	O
of	O
13	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Ann	B-pers
Galley	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
31	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
30.	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lisle	I-pers
.	I-pers
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31.	O
William	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
bed-curtains	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
2	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
William	B-pers
Downing	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
covering	O
of	O
an	O
easy-chair	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stollen	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33	O
,	O
34.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bockcomb	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
,	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35.	O
Henry	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
Oct.	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36	O
,	O
37.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
coles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Powers	B-pers
Fitzer	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
24	O
.	O
Wm	O
Jones	O
,	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Wm	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
guilty	O
.	O
38.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Rostrom	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pounds	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Clement's-lane	B-place
:	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
pounds	O
,	O
a	O
canvass	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
money	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
and	O
she	O
were	O
gone	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
maid	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
took	O
coach	O
for	O
Bath	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
purse	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
miss	O
'd	O
that	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
her	O
way	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
should	O
both	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
:	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
bag	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
than	O
five	O
pounds	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
above	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
maid	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
cousin	O
;	O
she	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
our	O
maid	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
three	O
times	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
approved	O
of	O
her	O
work	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
d	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
on	O
with	O
her	O
work	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
candle	O
burning	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
fire	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
;	O
my	O
maid	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
washing	O
dishes	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
Catherine	O
?	O
Madam	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
above	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
drawers	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
purse	O
and	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
,	O
although	O
it	O
lay	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
?	O
M.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
10	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
she	O
staid	O
and	O
done	O
her	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39.	O
William	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
,	O
October	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
40.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
stew-pan	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Greencase	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Priscella	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
two	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
Not	O
guilty	O
.	O
42.	O
George	B-pers
Hutcherson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
flannel	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jeffery	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
And	O
43.	O
John	B-pers
Chillingworth	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hutcherson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warne	I-pers
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
44.	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
window	O
curtain	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hallet	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45	O
,	O
46.	O
Mary	B-pers
Royan	I-pers
,	O
(	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Royan	I-pers
)	O
and	O
Locklen	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
Kentish	B-place
town	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
into	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Alien	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
nine	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
;	O
likewise	O
some	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Alien	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Alien	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kentish	B-place
town	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Highgate	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
up	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
pin	O
'd	O
the	O
windows	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
pin	O
'd	O
the	O
window	O
down	O
fast	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
entirely	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
back	O
window	O
.	O
One	O
pane	O
of	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
blood	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
This	O
pane	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
unpin	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
windows	O
and	O
doors	O
I	O
found	O
open	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
three	O
houses	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
row	O
,	O
mine	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
had	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
all	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
lost	O
upwards	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
shop	O
.	O
Some	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
drawers	O
above	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
goods	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Alien	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
caps	O
,	O
three	O
cambrick	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
ones	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
bacon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Alien	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
nine	O
shilling	O
piece	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
was	O
silver	O
and	O
brass	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
green	O
purse	O
.	O
Two	O
men	O
pursued	O
those	O
prisoners	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
at	O
Bushey	O
in	O
Hertfordshire	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
there	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
we	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Holt	O
;	O
Royan	O
discovered	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
this	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
dinner	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
some	O
bacon	O
.	O
Kelley	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
might	O
get	O
some	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
she	O
went	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
pane	O
in	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
linen	O
and	O
bacon	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
Kelley	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
go	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Kelley	O
ever	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Alien	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
ever	O
since	O
harvest	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
several	O
times	O
for	O
bread	O
,	O
cheese	O
,	O
bear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
When	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
open	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
suspected	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
27	O
shillings	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Cooper	O
at	O
Bushey	O
:	O
and	O
before	O
Justice	O
Holt	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Kelley	O
denied	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kenney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
Kentish	O
town	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
widow	O
Alien	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Royan	I-pers
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
day	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
fore	O
door	O
.	O
Her	O
husband	O
and	O
Kelley	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
she	O
stood	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
elbow	O
bloody	O
.	O
Kelley	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Kelley	O
or	O
she	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
?	O
Kenney	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
twice	O
.	O
Next	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
discovered	O
,	O
widow	O
Alien	O
said	O
her	O
table	O
near	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
bloody	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Royan	I-pers
's	O
elbow	O
was	O
bloody	O
last	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
green	O
purse	O
flourishing	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
woman	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
between	O
Bushey	O
and	O
Watford	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
green	O
purse	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Pasford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
Kentish	O
town	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
Mrs.	O
Alien	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
persons	O
,	O
we	O
suspected	O
,	O
had	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Ireland	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
took	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Royan	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
between	O
Bushey	O
and	O
Watford	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
.	O
Then	O
upon	O
her	O
confession	O
,	O
Kelley	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
together	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Holt	O
,	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
which	O
the	O
widow	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
Kelley	O
would	O
not	O
acknowledge	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
her	O
own	O
confession	O
she	O
made	O
before	O
Justice	O
Cooper	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
sign	O
it	O
Nov.	O
15.	O
at	O
Bushey	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
delivered	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
piece	O
.	O
Kenney	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Royan	I-pers
,	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
47.	O
George	B-pers
Alien	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
pattens	O
,	O
val	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
48.	O
John	B-pers
Chillingworth	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
50.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
51.	O
John	B-pers
Overy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
Nov.	O
26	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
52.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Debee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bradey	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
53.	O
William	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
54.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bray	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cask	O
of	O
white	O
lead	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholson	B-pers
Nudich	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
55.	O
Richard	B-pers
Carden	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
2	O
d.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
56.	O
William	B-pers
Denny	I-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
assembled	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
armed	O
with	O
fire	O
arms	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
running	O
of	O
uncustomed	O
goods	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
19th	O
and	O
20th	O
years	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
57	O
,	O
58.	O
John	B-pers
Hubord	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Rawlings	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
concerned	O
with	O
three	O
others	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Woodford	O
stage	O
coach	O
,	O
Sep.	O
15	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
59.	O
Lancelot	B-pers
Barrot	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jasper	B-pers
Fetchen	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
30	O
.	O
Jasper	B-pers
Fetchen	I-pers
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
dined	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
crowd	O
about	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
answered	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
seeing	O
some	O
rooms	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
let	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jarret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Fetchen	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
at	O
our	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seeing	O
a	O
bill	O
put	O
up	O
(	O
lodgings	O
to	O
let	O
)	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
first	O
and	O
second	O
floor	O
unfurnished	O
,	O
all	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
together	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
rooms	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
lik	O
'd	O
the	O
apartment	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
He	O
cheapened	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
master	O
could	O
let	O
them	O
for	O
25	O
l	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
person	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
would	O
not	O
grudge	O
that	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
lock	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
fore	O
parlour	O
door	O
.	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
who	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
silversmith	O
trade	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
disturbing	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
pen	O
,	O
ink	O
,	O
and	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
master	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
a	O
pencil	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
one	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
about	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
small	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
He	O
begged	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
for	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
water	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
move	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
fore	O
parlour	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
flew	O
up	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
water	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
thrust	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
left	O
side	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
water	O
?	O
Jerrat	O
:	O
But	O
just	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
water	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
hurt	O
you	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Jerrat	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
hurt	O
me	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
head	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
fore	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
my	O
head	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
side	O
way	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
Then	O
I	O
bolted	O
the	O
parlour-door	O
,	O
left	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
person	O
,	O
his	O
face	O
is	O
remarkable	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Munk	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
street	O
when	O
this	O
thing	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Fetchen	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
nobody	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
he	O
ran	O
?	O
Munk	O
.	O
I	O
once	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
soon	O
got	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
often	O
as	O
he	O
run	O
put	O
it	O
farther	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
sometimes	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
something	O
like	O
pewter	O
or	O
silver	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
Nov.	O
30	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Fetchen	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
where	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
in	O
?	O
Munk	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
better	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hockley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
smoaking	O
a	O
pipe	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
on	O
Nov.	O
30.	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
hastily	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Pearoe	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Peares	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
12	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
coming	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Barret	O
,	O
what	O
makes	O
you	O
come	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
hurry	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
business	O
this	O
way	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
ask	O
you	O
how	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
?	O
Peares	O
.	O
I	O
perceived	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
bundle	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
pint-pot	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
60.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
stands	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
having	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
a	O
certain	O
paper	O
written	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
inland	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
signed	O
by	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Edgerton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
to	O
bear	O
date	O
at	O
Broxton	O
,	O
Aug.	O
15	O
,	O
1748.	O
and	O
directed	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Cholmondeley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
James's-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
300	O
pounds	O
to	O
Sir	O
Watkin	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Wynn	O
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
or	O
his	O
order	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
month	O
after	O
date	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
which	O
said	O
paper	O
,	O
the	O
words	O
and	O
letters	O
following	O
were	O
subscribed	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
accept	O
to	O
pay	O
when	O
due	O
C.	O
Cholmondeley	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
write	O
acceptance	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Cholomondeley	I-pers
,	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
day	O
of	O
Sept.	O
with	O
force	O
and	O
arms	O
,	O
feloniously	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
an	O
indorsment	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
as	O
aforesasd	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sir	O
Watkin	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Wynn	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
Sir	O
Watkin	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Wynn	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
in	O
such	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
peace	O
,	O
crown	O
and	O
dignity	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
likewise	O
stands	O
indicted	O
for	O
knowingly	O
and	O
feloniously	O
uttering	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
endorsement	O
of	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Sir	O
Watkin	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
Wynn	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
for	O
forging	O
the	O
said	O
endorsement	O
and	O
for	O
uttering	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Edward	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
,	I-pers
Esq	I-pers
;	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Co.	O
bankers	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Alderman	O
Ironside	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
papers	O
,	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
inclosed	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Belcher	O
and	O
Co.	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
woman	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Belcher	O
's	O
the	O
banker	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
town	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gauler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
witness	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
.	O
Upon	O
reading	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
a	O
true	O
bill	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
read	O
the	O
contents	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
woman	O
were	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
from	O
'Squire	O
Jones	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Pomeroy	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
check	O
at	O
Deptford	O
:	O
immediately	O
I	O
called	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
servants	O
,	O
and	O
whispered	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
coming	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
some	O
terror	O
,	O
and	O
confest	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
them	O
from	O
Deptford	O
,	O
but	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
prison	O
for	O
debt	O
;	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry-counter	O
,	O
and	O
detain	O
her	O
there	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
suffer	O
no	O
person	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
over	O
to	O
Southwark	O
,	O
before	O
justice	O
Hammond	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
a	O
proper	O
officer	O
to	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
prison	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
upon	O
examining	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
woman	O
there	O
charged	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
having	O
those	O
papers	O
she	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
of	O
him	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
himself	O
confest	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
deliver	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
some	O
papers	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
into	O
Goodman's-fields	O
;	O
Justice	O
Hammond	O
thought	O
fit	O
to	O
commit	O
her	O
:	O
we	O
have	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Sir	O
Watkin	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
answered	O
this	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
returns	O
back	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
letter	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
from	O
Sir	O
Watkin	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
manner	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
like	O
his	O
.	O
Here	O
the	O
letters	O
were	O
read	O
.	O
Letter	O
I.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
``	O
The	O
inclosed	O
is	O
my	O
uncle	O
's	O
letter	O
and	O
bill	O
,	O
if	O
``	O
you	O
chuse	O
to	O
comply	O
with	O
his	O
request	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
``	O
indorse	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
bearer	O
and	O
``	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
bill	O
excepted	O
,	O
``	O
but	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
Windsor	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
``	O
see	O
per	O
the	O
inclosed	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
chuse	O
to	O
discount	O
``	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
inclose	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
``	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
bearer	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
may	O
apply	O
``	O
elsewhere	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
uncle	O
's	O
direction	O
to	O
``	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
business	O
accomplished	O
in	O
``	O
time	O
for	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
night	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
,	O
I	O
``	O
am	O
so	O
much	O
indisposed	O
with	O
sickness	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
``	O
possibly	O
wait	O
of	O
you	O
myself	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
the	O
``	O
same	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
inclose	O
the	O
note	O
by	O
bearer	O
,	O
shall	O
``	O
have	O
it	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Cheque	O
at	O
``	O
Deptford	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
Your	O
most	O
obedient	O
servant	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Dated	O
Sept.	O
6	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
To	O
mess	O
.	O
Belcher	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
these	O
.	O
Letter	O
II	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
``	O
At	O
one	O
month	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
pay	O
Sir	O
Wat.	O
``	O
Will	O
.	O
Wynn	O
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
or	O
his	O
order	O
,	O
in	O
cash	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
``	O
of	O
300	O
pounds	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
,	O
as	O
per	O
advice	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
place	O
it	O
to	O
account	O
of	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
most	O
obedient	O
servant	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Edgerton	I-pers
.	O
Broxton	O
,	O
Aug.	O
15	O
,	O
1748	O
.	O
To	O
Charles	B-pers
Cholmondeley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
,	O
Except	O
to	O
pay	O
when	O
due	O
C.	O
Cholmondeley	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
Wat	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Wynn	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Letter	O
III	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
``	O
As	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
assured	O
you	O
do	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
``	O
business	O
,	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
discounting	O
of	O
bills	O
,	O
I	O
make	O
``	O
so	O
free	O
as	O
to	O
direct	O
my	O
nephew	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
``	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
300	O
l.	O
discounted	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
``	O
pay	O
a	O
large	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
next	O
week	O
,	O
for	O
an	O
estate	O
``	O
bought	O
of	O
my	O
lord	O
Warrington	O
,	O
am	O
indeavouring	O
``	O
to	O
raise	O
the	O
cash	O
against	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
be	O
``	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
bearer	O
,	O
my	O
nephew	O
,	O
a	O
bank	O
``	O
note	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
may	O
send	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
``	O
certain	O
whether	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
wait	O
of	O
you	O
``	O
himself	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
indisposed	O
``	O
with	O
sickness	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
secretary	O
to	O
lord	O
``	O
Anson	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
not	O
done	O
any	O
business	O
this	O
some	O
``	O
time	O
,	O
having	O
had	O
very	O
bad	O
health	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
``	O
not	O
wait	O
of	O
you	O
himself	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
send	O
some	O
person	O
``	O
down	O
to	O
Deptford	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
except	O
he	O
send	O
``	O
a	O
message	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
he	O
can	O
confide	O
in	O
,	O
``	O
pray	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
herein	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
``	O
favour	O
shall	O
be	O
always	O
acknowledged	O
:	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
``	O
in	O
London	O
in	O
less	O
till	O
a	O
three	O
weeks	O
time	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
``	O
time	O
I	O
shall	O
wait	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
most	O
obedient	O
servant	O
,	O
Wat	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Wynn	O
.	O
Bath	O
,	O
Aug.	O
29	O
,	O
1748	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
backside	O
,	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Belcher	O
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
Bankers	O
in	O
Lombard	O
street	O
,	O
present	O
.	O
Letter	O
IV	O
.	O
Dear	O
Nephew	O
,	O
``	O
Yours	O
I	O
received	O
,	O
and	O
inclosed	O
7000	O
l.	O
in	O
bank	O
``	O
notes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
inclosed	O
to	O
you	O
five	O
bills	O
for	O
9000	O
l.	O
``	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
due	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
comes	O
to	O
hand	O
,	O
``	O
which	O
desire	O
you	O
either	O
go	O
or	O
send	O
to	O
receive	O
``	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
you	O
received	O
the	O
``	O
money	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
indorse	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
immediately	O
;	O
you	O
'll	O
find	O
likewise	O
``	O
another	O
bill	O
inclosed	O
for	O
300	O
l.	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
``	O
due	O
these	O
several	O
days	O
,	O
upon	O
'Squire	O
Cholmondeley	O
``	O
in	O
James's-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
get	O
it	O
``	O
accepted	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
apply	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
``	O
bankers	O
,	O
in	O
or	O
about	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
to	O
``	O
get	O
it	O
discounted	O
;	O
get	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
``	O
send	O
it	O
me	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
pay	O
``	O
for	O
the	O
estate	O
I	O
purchased	O
of	O
my	O
lord	O
Warrington	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
week	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
fail	O
sending	O
``	O
down	O
the	O
notes	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
lord	O
is	O
now	O
here	O
;	O
``	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
wont	O
be	O
so	O
well	O
recovered	O
as	O
to	O
``	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
yourself	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
would	O
``	O
have	O
you	O
prejudice	O
yourself	O
by	O
too	O
soon	O
going	O
``	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
'd	O
rather	O
advise	O
you	O
to	O
get	O
somebody	O
``	O
and	O
they	O
to	O
transact	O
the	O
business	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
a	O
``	O
person	O
whom	O
you	O
can	O
conside	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
``	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
Bath	O
,	O
I	O
've	O
an	O
opinion	O
the	O
water	O
``	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
obliged	O
``	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
London	O
in	O
less	O
till	O
one	O
three	O
weeks	O
time	O
,	O
``	O
I	O
will	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
you	O
down	O
along	O
with	O
``	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
going	O
again	O
soon	O
afterwards	O
:	O
``	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mostyn	I-pers
and	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Glynn	I-pers
presents	O
``	O
their	O
respects	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
my	O
compliments	O
to	O
lord	O
``	O
Anson	O
and	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Grosvenor	I-pers
when	O
you	O
see	O
``	O
or	O
write	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
acquaint	O
them	O
of	O
my	O
coming	O
``	O
to	O
town	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
week	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
``	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
find	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
better	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
,	O
``	O
than	O
you	O
were	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
you	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
``	O
sincere	O
desire	O
of	O
,	O
dear	O
nephew	O
,	O
Your	O
very	O
affectionate	O
and	O
loving	O
uncle	O
,	O
Wat	O
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Wynn	O
.	O
P.	B-pers
S	I-pers
.	I-pers
``	O
Deliver	O
the	O
inclosed	O
letter	O
to	O
Mess.	O
``	O
Belcher	O
and	O
Co.	O
with	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
``	O
they	O
'll	O
discount	O
it	O
without	O
any	O
farther	O
trouble	O
,	O
``	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
they	O
are	O
as	O
likely	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
``	O
apply	O
too	O
as	O
any	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
do	O
n't	O
chuse	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
``	O
go	O
to	O
lord	O
Anson	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
``	O
get	O
you	O
bank	O
notes	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
backside	O
;	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Pomeroy	O
's	O
,	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
cheque	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
-	O
Sir	O
Wat	O
.	O
Wm	O
Wynn.	O
``	O
The	O
paper	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
inclosed	O
,	O
directed	O
``	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Pomeroy	O
's	O
``	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
cheque	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
near	O
London	O
.	O
Fra	O
.	O
C.	O
Cholmondeley	O
.	O
The	O
inclosed	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
``	O
Yours	O
I	O
received	O
with	O
a	O
bill	O
inclosed	O
for	O
acceptance	O
,	O
``	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
accept	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
town	O
``	O
in	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
night	O
's	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
when	O
due	O
,	O
``	O
shall	O
be	O
punctually	O
paid	O
.	O
My	O
service	O
to	O
Sir	O
Watkin	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
am	O
,	O
your	O
humble	O
servant	O
.	O
C.	O
Cholmondeley	O
.	O
Windor	O
Sept.	O
2	O
,	O
1748	O
.	O
These	O
letters	O
,	O
I	O
apprehend	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
to	O
strengthen	O
the	O
credit	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
domestick	O
of	O
Sir	O
Watkins	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
his	O
clerk	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
Sir	O
Watkins	O
write	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
often	O
.	O
A	O
letter	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
somewhat	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
Watkin	O
in	O
resemblance	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
(	O
Another	O
was	O
shewed	O
him	O
.	O
)	O
That	O
is	O
not	O
Sir	O
Watkins	O
's	O
writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
servant	O
to	O
Sir	O
Watkins	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
he	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
Litchfield	O
races	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Wales	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Litchfield	O
races	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
set	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
servants	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
returning	O
,	O
the	O
servants	O
all	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
hunted	O
two	O
days	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
other	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
Sir	O
Watkin	O
was	O
at	O
Bath	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
Bath	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Alderman	O
Ironside	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
on	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
examination	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
money	O
for	O
going	O
of	O
this	O
message	O
,	O
She	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
bring	O
money	O
back	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
would	O
pay	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gauler	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
going	O
of	O
errands	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
those	O
letters	O
,	O
all	O
enclosed	O
in	O
a	O
parcel	O
to	O
Alderman	O
Ironside	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Gauler	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
carry	O
that	O
letter	O
to	O
Alderman	O
Ironside	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
back	O
any	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
letter	O
was	O
sealed	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
come	O
immediately	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Gauler	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
once	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
errands	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
would	O
go	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
letter	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
At	O
first	O
it	O
was	O
long	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
it	O
up	O
less	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
told	O
Justice	O
Hammond	O
.	O
Ald	O
.	O
Ironside	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
this	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Gauler	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
prison	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
asked	O
any	O
questions	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
say	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Deptford	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Gauler	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
a	O
prisoner	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
letter	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
plight	O
when	O
you	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
as	O
when	O
you	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
Jones	O
?	O
Gauler	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hands	O
.	O
Every	O
thing	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
when	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ironside	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
declare	O
upon	O
oath	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
business	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
followed	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
gaol	O
?	O
Gauler	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Gauler	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
no	O
more	O
letters	O
besides	O
mine	O
that	O
morning	O
to	O
deliver	O
?	O
Gauler	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
begged	O
and	O
prayed	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
his	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
other	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
but	O
his	O
letter	O
when	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
forgery	O
,	O
but	O
guilty	O
for	O
uttering	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
61.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bracket	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
62	O
,	O
63	O
,	O
64.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Raductin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Mildred	I-pers
*	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
They	O
were	O
tried	O
by	O
half	O
the	O
London	O
jury	O
and	O
half	O
foreigners	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Irish	O
factor	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Milkstreet	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
about	O
100	O
yards	O
.	O
These	O
three	O
women	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
one	O
Solomon	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
with	O
them	O
for	O
their	O
interpreter	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
by	O
their	O
interpreter	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
linen	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
one	O
word	O
of	O
English	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
Irish	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
from	O
two	O
shillings	O
a	O
yard	O
to	O
five	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
interpreter	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
women	O
I	O
could	O
serve	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
accordingly	O
brought	O
down	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
send	O
my	O
clerk	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
just	O
upon	O
their	O
coming	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
remained	O
none	O
but	O
my	O
porter	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
(	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
reaching	O
the	O
linen	O
from	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
long	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
considerable	O
distance	O
from	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
linen	O
)	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
porter	O
to	O
a	O
grocer	O
's	O
for	O
a	O
sample	O
of	O
coffee	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
to	O
themselves	O
.	O
The	O
grocer	O
came	O
over	O
with	O
the	O
coffee	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
bargain	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
coffee	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
apprehend	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
very	O
morning	O
sold	O
some	O
linen	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
draper	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
carried	O
them	O
returned	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
piece	O
wanting	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
carefully	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
pile	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
more	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
them	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
gentleman	O
at	O
breakfast	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
telling	O
the	O
case	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
in	O
shewing	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
linen	O
on	O
the	O
board	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
an	O
opportunity	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
take	O
what	O
they	O
pleased	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
perhaps	O
an	O
100	O
or	O
200	O
pieces	O
on	O
the	O
shop	O
board	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Heavingham	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
clerk	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
pieces	O
gone	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
three	O
pieces	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
am	O
trying	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
fact	O
on	O
the	O
15	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
each	O
a	O
load	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
took	O
one	O
piece	O
she	O
had	O
concealed	O
and	O
lays	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
another	O
drops	O
another	O
piece	O
down	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
;	O
the	O
third	O
had	O
hers	O
about	O
her	O
for	O
near	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
taxed	O
them	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
four	O
pieces	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
They	O
ordered	O
the	O
Jew	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
willing	O
to	O
leave	O
me	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
those	O
pieces	O
until	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
searched	O
them	O
they	O
had	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
petticoats	O
,	O
each	O
had	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
pockets	O
in	O
every	O
petticoat	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
place	O
by	O
the	O
persuasion	O
of	O
the	O
husband	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
women	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
merchants	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
their	O
interpreter	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
bought	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
found	O
an	O
opportunity	O
they	O
would	O
steal	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
cloth	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
sent	O
out	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
man	O
for	O
some	O
coffee	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
they	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Irish	O
cloth	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
pieces	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
pockets	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
.	O
Three	O
of	O
them	O
the	O
husband	O
to	O
Hannah	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
bought	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
them	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
guineas	O
for	O
them	O
and	O
some	O
stockings	O
:	O
the	O
fourth	O
piece	O
they	O
cut	O
in	O
pieces	O
to	O
make	O
shirts	O
of	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
the	O
women	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
found	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
four	O
pieces	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
missed	O
among	O
so	O
large	O
a	O
quantity	O
.	O
They	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
:	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
next	O
day	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
same	O
cloth	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
bill	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
was	O
writing	O
a	O
bill	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
begin	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
out	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
you	O
have	O
under	O
your	O
petticoat	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
talked	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
language	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
said	O
?	O
Levi	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
in	O
Dutch	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
to	O
have	O
let	O
me	O
kept	O
my	O
place	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
steal	O
things	O
.	O
They	O
gave	O
me	O
for	O
answer	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
interpreter	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
cloth	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
say	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
tell	O
we	O
shall	O
all	O
be	O
hanged	O
;	O
this	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
said	O
.	O
They	O
bid	O
me	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
they	O
would	O
lay	O
down	O
as	O
much	O
money	O
as	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
was	O
worth	O
,	O
until	O
he	O
should	O
find	O
the	O
linen	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
should	O
pay	O
them	O
the	O
money	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Heavingham	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
that	O
the	O
15th	O
he	O
lost	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
looking	O
at	O
some	O
linen	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
as	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Presently	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
this	O
Jew	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
and	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
making	O
motions	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
compting	O
house	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
