TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
22d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1748	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Sixpence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
LADBROKE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRACEY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sallis	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Corp	I-pers
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Stagg	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Simpton	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Cullis	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Crundon	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Crumpton	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hawker	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
.	O
381	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chestney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Stepney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
mare	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Coxhead	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
July	O
2	O
.	O
N.B	O
.	O
Those	O
Trials	O
with	O
this	O
mark	O
+	O
shew	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Capital	O
Offences	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Jury	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
town	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
Mr.	O
Coxhead	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
mare	O
and	O
a	O
gelding	O
at	O
the	O
globe	O
at	O
Mile	O
end	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
Mr.	O
Coxhead	O
had	O
word	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
mare	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
grounds	O
at	O
Thetford	B-place
in	I-place
Norfolk	I-place
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
globe	O
at	O
Mile-end	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
pasture-grounds	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
mare	O
,	O
and	O
challeng	O
'd	O
her	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
orders	O
not	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
indemnify	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
for	O
detaining	O
the	O
mare	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Potter	O
.	O
A	O
dark	O
brown	O
mare	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
Mr.	O
Coxhead	O
had	O
the	O
mare	O
?	O
Potter	O
.	O
Several	O
years	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
globe	O
at	O
Mile-end	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
mare	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
)	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
cage	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
,	O
then	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
himself	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
mare	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
brown	O
mare	O
,	O
about	O
fourteen	O
hands	O
high	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
work	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
claim	O
this	O
mare	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Coxhead	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Potter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
Mr.	O
Coxhead	O
's	O
servant	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
claim	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
word	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Potter	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
mare	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
park	O
in	O
Norfolk	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Still	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
horse	O
into	O
a	O
pasture	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Coxhead	O
's	O
at	O
Thetford	O
,	O
where	O
this	O
mare	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
mare	O
in	O
the	O
grounds	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
reported	O
that	O
the	O
mare	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
mare	O
upon	O
an	O
exchange	O
at	O
Stebbing	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
miles	O
from	O
Chelmsford	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
exchanged	O
a	O
grey	O
poney	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
for	O
the	O
mare	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
prove	O
this	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
all	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
quite	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
poney	O
but	O
two	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
him	O
at	O
Rumford-fair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
[	O
Mr.	O
Potter	O
produced	O
a	O
Letter	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Coxhead	O
,	O
petitioning	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
recommended	O
for	O
mercy	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
recommended	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
.	O
]	O
382	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Bew	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
the	I-place
Evangelist	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dimity	O
gown	O
,	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
sustian	O
frock	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
passing	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
:	O
about	O
200	O
yards	O
from	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
house	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
came	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
threw	O
down	O
this	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
(	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
claimed	O
)	O
were	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
this	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
coat	O
?	O
Bromley	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
Servant	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
five	O
I	O
had	O
almost	O
cleaned	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
clap	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
running	O
along	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Thieves	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Bromley	O
to	O
drop	O
them	O
.	O
Bright	O
Wilmott	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Wilmott	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
there	O
was	O
no-body	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
Wilmott	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
second	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Westway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
nor	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
London	O
privateer	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
3	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
barrow	O
in	O
Deans-yard	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
cherries	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
cherries	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
run	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
bundle	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
383	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
June	O
22	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
which	O
cost	O
me	O
36	O
s.	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
them	O
?	O
Harwood	O
.	O
At	O
Mary	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Rag-fair	B-place
,	O
about	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
them	O
?	O
Harwood	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Harwood	O
.	O
About	O
12	O
o'clock	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday-night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
there	O
for	O
?	O
Harwood	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
by	O
chance	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
chamber	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
great	O
plain	O
ring	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Sutton	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Lyon	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
another	O
young	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Harwood	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
sober	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
384	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
385	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
leaden	O
dial-weight	O
of	O
25	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
,	O
August	O
1	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
leaden	O
dial-weight	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
weight	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Clements	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
the	O
son	O
,	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
father	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blackburn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
owned	O
he	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
weight	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clements	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
they	O
owing	O
him	O
a	O
penny	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clements	O
stopped	O
the	O
penny	O
.	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
My	O
son	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Long-alley	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
386	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christchurch	B-place
Spittle-fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
19	O
yards	O
of	O
velvet	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
William	O
Austin	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
being	O
moon-light	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
slept	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
chamber-window	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
knife	O
lying	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
shutters	O
to	O
this	O
window	O
?	O
Austin	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
there	O
was	O
19	O
yards	O
of	O
velvet	O
missing	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
19	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
does	O
it	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
Austin	O
.	O
To	O
my	O
master	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Austin	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
some	O
months	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
character	O
,	O
I	O
discharged	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
did	O
this	O
?	O
Austin	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no-body	O
,	O
but	O
him	O
,	O
could	O
do	O
it	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Relph	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Austin	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
window	O
close	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
ashcolour	O
'd	O
velvet	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
velvet	O
into	O
my	O
box	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
cut	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
,	O
about	O
1	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Austin	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Vine-court	O
Spittle	O
Fields	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
a	O
man	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
pay	O
himself	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
without	O
a	O
ladder	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
helped	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
knife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
stay	O
there	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
bundle	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
rolled	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
velvet	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
jumped	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
and	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
we	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Life	O
Chitty	O
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
it	O
there	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
yard	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Jew	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
asked	O
too	O
much	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
velvet	O
before	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
brought	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
this	O
Jew	O
live	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
whether	O
John	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
was	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
denied	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
want	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
John	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Doyle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
velvet-weaver	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
work	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
loom	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
John	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
we	O
heard	O
that	O
Lancaster	O
was	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
and	O
Lewis	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dorman	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pratt	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King's-arms	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
(	O
't	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
house	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
landlady	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
not	O
John	O
Lancaster	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
John	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
not	O
John	O
Lancaster	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
want	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
a	O
coach	O
.	O
Lewis	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
not	O
squeak	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
387	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jackwest	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
shifts	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
.	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
388.	O
Jazachex	B-pers
Corfoni	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
August	O
31	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
fellows	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
2	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
made	O
you	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
prison	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
pretended	O
they	O
could	O
speak	O
no	O
English	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
shew	O
them	O
in	O
Portugal	O
money	O
what	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
worth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
buy	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
for	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
12	O
guineas	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
put	O
their	O
hands	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
mixed	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
man	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Tripoli	O
ambassador	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
ambassador	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
2	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
2	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
Justice	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
produced	O
12	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
mixed	O
their	O
hands	O
among	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
but	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
was	O
the	O
nearest	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
finger	O
'd	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
other	O
touch	O
it	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brugar	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
said	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
12	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
many	O
guineas	O
there	O
were	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
asked	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Brugar	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
money	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
that	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
finger	O
'd	O
?	O
Brugar	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
word	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
389.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
laun	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Oseland	I-pers
;	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linen-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
390	O
Alberto	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
391	O
Mary	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
392	O
Mary	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
,	O
August	O
17	O
.	O
Alberto	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
Acquitted	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
393	O
John	B-pers
Mawden	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Mowden	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
building	O
belonging	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Withers	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
August	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
394	O
Roger	B-pers
Durant	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
rice	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Crockatt	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
395	O
Rice	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
hogs	O
bristles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pickle	I-pers
,	O
July	O
13	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pickle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
In	O
July	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
4	O
pounds	O
of	O
hogs	O
bristles	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
1	O
pound	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
pounds	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
lewd	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
who	O
had	O
seduced	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
rob	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Courtman	O
.	O
In	O
July	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
pound	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
hair	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Courtman	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
full	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
made	O
up	O
brushes	O
for	O
himself	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
prove	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
their	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Lyon	O
,	O
in	O
Crooked-lane	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Pickle	O
.	O
William	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
master	O
Mr.	O
Pickle	O
's	O
hairs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
396	O
William	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
pounds	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
397	O
+	O
Peter	B-pers
Dayley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
Portugal	O
gold	O
coin	O
,	O
36	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
one	O
moidore	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
moidore	O
,	O
8	O
guineas	O
,	O
12	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
;	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
August	O
23	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Marlborough-street	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
cobler	O
and	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
money	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
moidore	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
guineas	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
guineas	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
to	O
8	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Counc	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offer	O
your	O
wife	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
think	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
being	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
it	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
persuaded	O
to	O
get	O
more	O
money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
obstinate	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
any	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
seeing	O
him	O
have	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
the	O
cobler	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
rude	O
and	O
faucy	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
he	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
's	O
the	O
letter	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
And	O
the	O
constable	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
letter	O
or	O
paper	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
again	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
earn	O
'd	O
it	O
?	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
day	O
in	O
my	O
stall	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
rogue	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
your	O
way	O
as	O
you	O
went	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
before	O
saw	O
him	O
master	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
say	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
thus	O
[	O
making	O
a	O
motion	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
]	O
and	O
his	O
sister	O
brought	O
my	O
wife	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
kept	O
this	O
money	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
we	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
lock	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
mark	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
mark	O
any	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
a	O
moidore	O
to	O
your	O
wife	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
rent	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
not	O
he	O
bear	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
His	O
neighbours	O
will	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
to	O
your	O
knowledge	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
He	O
will	O
stick	O
to	O
his	O
work	O
sometimes	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
will	O
run	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
lie	O
out	O
o'nights	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
two	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
money	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
purse	O
;	O
the	O
whole	O
was	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
guinea	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
14	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
halfpenny	O
remaining	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
27	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
forgot	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
the	O
moidore	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
purse	O
and	O
all	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
the	O
cobler	O
has	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
;	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
flush	O
of	O
money	O
then	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
forbid	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
,	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
a	O
staymaker	O
brought	O
his	O
sister	O
12	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
more	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
before	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
afterwards	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
earn	O
'd	O
it	O
?	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
more	O
shame	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
pay	O
your	O
debts	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lyne	O
(	O
Constable	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Pearce	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
1	O
guinea	O
,	O
3	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
his	O
thighs	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
a	O
bunch	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
knees	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
a	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
money	O
out	O
which	O
was	O
sewed	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
cut	O
open	O
another	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
set	O
down	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
person	O
could	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
letter	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
would	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
sister	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
letter	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
sister	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
about	O
12	O
l.	O
or	O
12	O
guineas	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
given	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
already	O
,	O
with	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
paid	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
here	O
[	O
making	O
a	O
motion	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
sooner	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
]	O
and	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
days	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
for	O
my	O
servant	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
pretty	O
girl	O
by	O
the	O
foot	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
5	O
s.	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
worth	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
she	O
paid	O
him	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
lucky	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
good	O
luck	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Chissell	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dove	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Connell	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Finglass	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Ingoldsby	I-pers
,	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
character	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
3	O
,	O
4	O
,	O
or	O
5	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
398	O
John	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	O
and	O
399	O
John	B-pers
Joffrane	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
eight	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
linnen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
;	O
July	O
7	O
.	O
Flemming	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Bird-in-hand	B-place
in	I-place
King-street	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
John	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
five	O
days	O
before	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Landlord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
used	O
you	O
grosly	O
ill	O
,	O
in	O
taking	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
8	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
at	O
Cock-hill	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Trounson	I-pers
.	O
Joffrane	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Roach	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
400	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Swanney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Burrass	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
August	O
24	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Burrass	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
Bartholomew-fair	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Burrass	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Swanney	I-pers
took	O
it	O
;	O
because	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
down	O
Chick-lane	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
an	O
alehouse-door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fish	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
an	O
impudent	O
dog	O
.	O
He	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
7	O
d.	O
half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Burrass	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
by	O
me	O
but	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
your	O
hand	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Burrass	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
fair	O
,	O
eating	O
some	O
curds	O
and	O
whey	O
,	O
and	O
Swanney	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Burrass	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Fish	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
an	O
alehouse-door	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
an	O
impudent	O
dog	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
punch	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
me	O
a-bleeding	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
7	O
d.	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
where	O
;	O
and	O
offered	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
the	O
7	O
d.	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
who	O
has	O
serv	O
'd	O
the	O
office	O
of	O
constable	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
old	O
offender	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
401	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Kates	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Ben	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
under	O
Newgate	B-place
,	O
(	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
made	O
me	O
the	O
more	O
cautious	O
)	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
bobbing	O
against	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
bosom	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
402	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Messenger	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ramsay	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
twelve	O
silver	O
buttons	O
for	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
a	O
tea-strainer	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
hose	O
,	O
a	O
mask	O
,	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
cambrick	O
,	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
linnen	O
,	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
callico	O
,	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
a	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
crystal	O
buttons	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
flowered	O
silk	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
;	O
July	O
21	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
Service	O
in	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
and	O
some	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
trunk	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cooley	I-pers
Constable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
those	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
trunk	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
damask	O
shoes	O
,	O
this	O
printed	O
linnen	O
,	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
[	O
these	O
were	O
proved	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Clarke	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Lord	O
my	O
God	O
liveth	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
403	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Jacob	B-pers
Salvador	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
silver	O
watchchain	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
seal	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jacob	B-pers
Salvador	I-pers
,	O
August	O
22d	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Salvador	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
lane	O
near	O
Islington	O
the	O
prisoner	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
you	O
coming	O
from	O
?	O
Salvador	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Highgate	B-place
to	O
London	B-place
,	O
in	O
Mr	O
Decosta	O
's	O
chariot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
meet	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Salvador	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
after	O
us	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
to	O
plead	O
,	O
guilty	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
the	O
court	O
any	O
farther	O
trouble	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Salvador	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
rob	O
you	O
of	O
?	O
Salvador	O
.	O
A	O
Silver	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
chain	O
,	O
a	O
seal	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
rob	O
Mr.	O
Decosta	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Salvador	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
behave	O
?	O
Salvador	O
.	O
He	O
behaved	O
civilly	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
us	O
his	O
pistols	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
immediately	O
?	O
Salvador	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
,	O
going	O
up	O
Highgate	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
of	O
very	O
honest	O
parents	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Mendez	I-pers
Decosta	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Highgate	O
in	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
chariot	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Salvador	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Decosta	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
when	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
Lane	O
when	O
he	O
demanded	O
our	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
His	O
hand	O
trembled	O
exceedingly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
fact	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
?	O
Decosta	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
enquired	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
ever	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
before	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
Man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
but	O
19	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
for	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
also	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Moses	B-pers
Mendez	I-pers
Decosta	I-pers
on	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
August	O
22d	O
.	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
this	O
indictment	O
.	O
404	O
,	O
405.	O
Francis	B-pers
Otter	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
shirts	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mandineau	I-pers
,	O
August	O
15th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mandineau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
shirts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
them	O
from	O
?	O
Mandineau	O
.	O
From	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
at	O
Bethnal-Green	B-place
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Garden	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
drying	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
were	O
the	O
prisoners	O
taken	O
?	O
Mandineau	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nutbrown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Bethnal-Green	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
a	O
bank	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
rogues	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
upon	O
the	O
bank	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
bank	O
and	O
they	O
made	O
them	O
into	O
two	O
bundles	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
separated	O
,	O
one	O
went	O
over	O
one	O
field	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
over	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
their	O
names	O
?	O
Nutbrown	O
.	O
One	O
is	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
Francis	B-pers
Otter	I-pers
;	O
one	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
one	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
by	O
another	O
.	O
Otter	O
drew	O
a	O
knife	O
twice	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Norris	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
secured	O
the	O
linnen	O
?	O
Nutbrown	O
.	O
We	O
left	O
the	O
linnen	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
little	O
boy	O
my	O
brother	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
linnen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
appeared	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
to	O
accuse	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Nutbrown	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
upon	O
Bethnal	O
Green	O
had	O
the	O
linnen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
was	O
the	O
linnen	O
?	O
Nutbrown	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
John	O
Mandineau	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
garden	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
linnen	O
.	O
M	B-pers
.	I-pers
-	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
up	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
if	O
we	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
just	O
by	O
to	O
get	O
more	O
help	O
;	O
and	O
Otter	O
got	O
his	O
basket	O
off	O
his	O
head	O
and	O
pulled	O
down	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Witness	O
.	O
A	O
baker	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
both	O
baker	O
s	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
;	O
Otter	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
rolled	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
pursued	O
they	O
dropped	O
the	O
linnen	O
and	O
parted	O
,	O
one	O
took	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
another	O
.	O
And	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Hackney-town	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
406.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
deal	O
boards	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bosworth	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
407	O
Mary	B-pers
Beshar	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bezar	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Sisum	I-pers
,	O
June	O
21	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
408.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
August	O
13th	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
buckle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoe	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
drop	O
out	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
it	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
In	O
Wapping	B-place
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
out	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
o'Night	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
settle	O
and	O
both	O
of	O
us	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
catched	O
this	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
taking	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoe	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
for	O
the	O
buckle	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
buckle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
one	O
of	O
your	O
companions	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
actually	O
take	O
one	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
secure	O
hi	O
m	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
Watchman	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
opportunity	O
of	O
getting	O
rid	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
many	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
throwing	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
giving	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
fell	O
asleep	O
and	O
he	O
lost	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
a	O
long	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
hold	O
him	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
for	O
the	O
buckle	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
buckle	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
search	O
'd	O
'till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
throwing	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
that	O
night	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cooper	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
15	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
serv	O
'd	O
me	O
faithfully	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
409	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bawkum	I-pers
,	O
and	O
410.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bawkum	I-pers
.	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
periwig	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Mackcormick	I-pers
,	O
February	O
2d	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
411.	O
Ann	B-pers
Winfield	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
a	O
velvet	O
hood	O
,	O
2	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
July	O
19th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
412	O
,	O
+	O
Edmund	B-pers
Thorpe	I-pers
and	O
413	O
.	O
+	O
Charles	B-pers
Cluer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Skales	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
his	O
wife	O
Catherine	B-pers
Skales	I-pers
.	O
August	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
Cath	O
.	O
Skales	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Broad	B-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
night	O
they	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
light	O
them	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
they	O
got	O
to	O
my	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
picked	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Skales	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cluer	I-pers
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
all	O
in	O
half-pence	O
?	O
Skales	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sixpence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
catch	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Skales	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
?	O
Skales	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
great	O
fellow	O
[	O
Thorpe	O
]	O
that	O
stands	O
by	O
the	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
get	O
your	O
money	O
again	O
?	O
Skales	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
and	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
and	O
Thorpe	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
gaol	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Cluer	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Denn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
:	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
searched	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Noake	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
Church	O
lane	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
let	O
in	O
.	O
They	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
did	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
this	O
Church-lane	O
?	O
Noake	O
.	O
Near	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
very	O
disorderly	O
people	O
live	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
?	O
Noake	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
nor	O
Mrs.	O
Skales	O
never	O
desired	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
never	O
refused	O
it	O
.	O
If	O
she	O
had	O
desir	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
search	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
414.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
415	O
Samuel	B-pers
Linton	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Matthew	I-place
Bethnal-green	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shuttlewood	I-pers
,	O
gent	O
.	O
August	O
3	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shuttlewood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
shirts	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
garden	O
at	O
Bethnal-green	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Shuttlewood	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
accuse	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Shuttlewood	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
days	O
afterwards	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
persons	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
Whitechapel	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
maid	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
could	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
the	O
best	O
judges	O
of	O
the	O
linnen	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
both	O
positive	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
shirts	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
Bethnal-green	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
,	O
one	O
Sheppard	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
line	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Martifaa	O
(	O
the	O
Constable	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
about	O
140	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
3	O
shirts	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Shuttlewood	O
.	O
Are	O
these	O
shirts	O
your	O
husband	O
's	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shuttlewood	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
2	O
o'clock	O
and	O
8	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
8	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
your	O
husband	O
's	O
shirts	O
?	O
Shuttlewood	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Martisaa	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
them	O
?	O
Martisaa	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
one	O
Cooper	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
barber	O
,	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
takes	O
in	O
pawns	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
Sheppard	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
:	O
and	O
Sheppard	O
said	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
that	O
Thompson	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Linton	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
.	O
And	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
were	O
taking	O
a	O
walk	O
round	O
Bethnal-green	O
one	O
Friday	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
?	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
going	O
there	O
for	O
?	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
To	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
these	O
3	O
shirts	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
line	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Linton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
in	O
Stoney-lane	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
yard-door	O
ready	O
to	O
receive	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dark	O
,	O
or	O
light	O
?	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
this	O
Rawlins	O
?	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
.	O
Thompson	O
,	O
to	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
shirts	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Thompson	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
as	O
false	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
true	O
.	O
Linton	O
to	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Thompson	O
deliver	O
the	O
shirts	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Walpole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Samuel	B-pers
Linton	I-pers
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
hanging-sleeve-coats	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Walpole	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
Goodman's-yard	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
as	O
honest	O
parents	O
as	O
any	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
his	O
?	O
Walpole	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
about	O
a	O
third	O
cousin	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
trusted	O
with	O
hundreds	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
careful	O
,	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
youth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Sheppard	O
?	O
Walpole	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
these	O
people	O
?	O
Sheppard	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
while	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Jury	O
recommended	O
Linton	O
for	O
corporal	O
punishment	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Thompson	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Linton	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
416	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
(	O
together	O
with	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
quart	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Punch-bowl	B-place
in	O
Halfmoon-alley	B-place
in	O
Little	B-place
Moor-fields	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
off	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
which	O
cost	O
me	O
9	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
it	O
was	O
28	O
ounces	O
and	O
5	O
pennyweights	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
partner	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
his	O
partner	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Elliot	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
partner	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
think	O
of	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
melted	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Elliot	O
.	O
Yes	O
he	O
did	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Elliot	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
it	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
?	O
Elliot	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
being	O
there	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
Const	I-pers
.	O
I	O
think	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
fellows	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
who	O
had	O
stole	O
his	O
tankard	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
their	O
names	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
Son	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
should	O
I	O
suffer	O
for	O
my	O
son	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
new	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
says	O
you	O
have	O
stole	O
his	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rubbed	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
own	O
nothing	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
Mr.	O
Elliot	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Aldermanbury	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Castle	O
by	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
,	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
James	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
off	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
they	O
met	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Goose-alley	O
by	O
the	O
Ditch-side	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
melted	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
[	O
This	O
witness	O
proved	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
it	O
was	O
melted	O
]	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
wooden	O
bottom	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
from	O
bruising	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
engraved	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
melted	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Walter	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
in	O
Long-lane	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
get	O
this	O
plate	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
silver	O
bars	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
one	O
Taylor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
these	O
two	O
Bars	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
bit	O
of	O
silver	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
pennyweight	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
try	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
silver	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
these	O
two	O
bars	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
they	O
were	O
weighed	O
at	O
a	O
silver-smiths	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Elliot	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
engraved	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
your	O
tankard	O
?	O
Elliot	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
stop	O
thief	O
engraved	O
on	O
the	O
bottom	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
an	O
inscription	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
wooden	O
bottoms	O
to	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
417	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
mare	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
July	O
26th	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
deserted	O
from	O
his	O
regiment	O
of	O
Marine	O
s	O
lying	O
in	O
Chichester	B-place
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
own	O
clothes	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
and	O
robbed	O
nine	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mare	O
was	O
missing	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
marine	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
the	O
night	O
he	O
deserted	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
my	O
mare	O
in	O
Smithfield-market	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Barker	O
,	O
the	O
hostler	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
in	O
Basinghall-street	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
mare	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
good	O
market	O
of	O
the	O
mare	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
shillings	O
more	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
in	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
beg	O
for	O
transportation	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
sworn	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
mare	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
mare	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Prince	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
that	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
mare	O
into	O
the	O
Field	O
at	O
Chichester	O
in	O
Sussex	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
the	O
mare	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
mare	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
The	O
Wednesday-night	O
following	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
mare	O
in	O
Yorkshire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
in	O
Basinghall-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
the	O
mare	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
25	O
s.	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
He	O
gave	O
but	O
25	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
mare	O
,	O
bridle	O
and	O
saddle	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Barker	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
toll	O
her	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
Smithfield-market	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
blind	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
Palmer	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
not	O
true	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
bridle	O
and	O
saddle	O
to	O
market	O
too	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
mare	O
was	O
not	O
sold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
mare	O
delivered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Palmer	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
mare	O
you	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Barker	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
mare	O
at	O
a	O
fair	O
at	O
Chichester	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
three	O
guineas	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
418.	O
Mary	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gyles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
Aug.	O
10	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gyles	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
silver	O
spoons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
who	O
had	O
them	O
?	O
Gyles	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
two	O
different	O
persons	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gyles	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
these	O
two	O
spoons	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q.	O
had	O
you	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
No	O
more	O
than	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gyles	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
she	O
confess	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
?	O
Gyles	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Elizabeth	O
Green	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
confess	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
spoons	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
quarrel	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Churchman	I-pers
(	O
Constable	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
found	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Fore-street	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
leather	O
breeches	O
I	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
Leadenhall	O
market	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
yearly	O
servant	O
?	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
She	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
by	O
the	O
week	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
on	O
nights	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Warner	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
6	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
fetched	O
away	O
the	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
four	O
shillings	O
on	O
the	O
leather	O
ones	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
419.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
of	O
Hendon	B-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linnen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
80	O
pounds	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
420.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Downey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Marley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
22d	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Marley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
shillings	O
at	O
Peter	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
's	O
house	O
in	O
Wapping	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
Marley	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
whole	O
story	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Marley	O
.	O
We	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
pumps	O
with	O
the	O
buckles	O
in	O
them	O
were	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
lye	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Marley	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
one	O
Anthony	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
lay	O
together	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
all	O
three	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
?	O
Marley	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Marley	O
.	O
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
awake	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
?	O
Marley	O
.	O
Between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
buckles	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
my	O
comrade	O
Mumford	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
long-side	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
Downing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
along-side	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
advertise	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
you	O
?	O
Marley	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
piece	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Marley	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
found	O
between	O
his	O
stocking	O
and	O
his	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
was	O
changed	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
shoes	O
upon	O
his	O
feet	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
buckles	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
was	O
he	O
a	O
brother	O
sailor	O
?	O
Marley	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
ship	O
with	O
me	O
5	O
months	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
express	O
myself	O
in	O
English	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
Marley	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
piece	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Marley	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Marley	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
says	O
he	O
saw	O
his	O
shoes	O
upon	O
my	O
feet	O
;	O
why	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
challenge	O
them	O
?	O
Marley	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
buckles	O
?	O
Marley	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
brass	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
fashion	O
as	O
your	O
own	O
.	O
Marley	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
a	O
quarter	O
so	O
large	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Mumford	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
lay	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
at	O
Peter	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Mumford	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
any	O
silver	O
buckles	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Mumford	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
had	O
he	O
?	O
Mumford	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
buckles	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Mumford	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
either	O
copper	O
,	O
or	O
brass	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
buckles	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
;	O
there	O
's	O
W	O
M	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
long-side	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
to	O
piss	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
window-shutters	O
and	O
the	O
casement	O
open	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
bear	O
a	O
hand	O
,	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
piece	O
between	O
his	O
stocking	O
and	O
his	O
foot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
?	O
Mumford	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
was	O
changed	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Haynes	O
's	O
in	O
Darkhouse-lane	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Memorandum	O
.	O
It	O
does	O
not	O
appear	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
421	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
saddle	O
,	O
a	O
bridle	O
,	O
a	O
girt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
circingle	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
;	O
and	O
two	O
bridles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Peake	I-pers
;	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
stable	O
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Peake	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
stable	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Peake	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
where	O
the	O
girt	O
and	O
the	O
circingle	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
Durham-yard	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
them	O
you	O
from	O
?	O
Peake	O
.	O
Give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
first	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
story	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
shall	O
never	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bullhead	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
parcel	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
my	O
two	O
snaffle-bridles	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
pulled	O
two	O
girts	O
and	O
a	O
circingle	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
hop	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
good-natur	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
all	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
kind	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
a	O
coachman	O
,	O
to	O
drive	O
me	O
to	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
his	O
chamber	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
saddle	O
and	O
saddle-cloth	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
tell	O
you	O
all	O
along	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
?	O
Peake	O
.	O
You	O
told	O
me	O
you	O
bought	O
them	O
all	O
for	O
16	O
shillings	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Two	O
months	O
ago	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Tyburn-road	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
by	O
then	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Ryley	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Spratt	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
26	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Peake	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
but	O
16	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
in	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
other	O
10	O
s.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Peake	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
they	O
worth	O
second-hand	O
?	O
Peake	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
4	O
l.	O
now	O
second-hand	O
,	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hopley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
horses	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
20	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
'squire	O
Broughton	O
16	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
in	O
several	O
gentlemen	O
's	O
services	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
service	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
About	O
9	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
5	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
countryman	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Ryley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Irishman	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
hostler	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-boar	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
buying	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Ryley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
a	O
bridle	O
,	O
saddle	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
rugs	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
16	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Ryley	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
Ryley	O
.	O
I	O
write	O
for	O
my	O
livelihood	O
.	O
I	O
write	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Brett	O
,	O
an	O
attorney	O
at	O
law	O
,	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Spratt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
buy	O
a	O
saddle	O
,	O
some	O
bridles	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
rugs	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
rugs	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Tyburn-road	O
?	O
Spratt	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
for	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Spratt	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
positively	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
paid	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
something	O
more	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
422	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Armson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
,	O
and	O
lost	O
12	O
pounds	O
,	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Five	O
weeks	O
last	O
Friday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
drawers	O
lock	O
'd	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
it	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
missed	O
this	O
money	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday-morning	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
drawers	O
lock	O
'd	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
lock	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
.	I-pers
Lambert	I-pers
Constable	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
after	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
hid	O
it	O
?	O
Lambert	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Love	O
lane	O
near	O
Kensington	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
lantern	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
mo	O
ney	O
as	O
plain	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
stood	O
upright	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Lambert	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
9	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
all	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
confess	O
only	O
that	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
more	O
?	O
Lambert	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
?	O
Lambert	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
?	O
Lambert	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
this	O
particular	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wood	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Almost	O
all	O
queen	O
Anne	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
entered	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
bed-chamber	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
bag	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
in	O
Love-lane	O
by	O
Kensington	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
how	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
drawers	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
drawer	O
with	O
a	O
spring	O
:	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
clapped	O
it	O
too	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
fast	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
423	O
Thomas	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Bromley	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
penny	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kilby	I-pers
;	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Tho	O
.	O
Kilby	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
key	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
it	O
?	O
Kilby	O
.	O
At	O
Bromley	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
made	O
you	O
mistrust	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Kilby	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
:	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
people	O
said	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
8	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
playing	O
with	O
some	O
boys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Kilby	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Bazil	O
Denn	O
on	O
London-bridge	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Denn	O
's	O
on	O
London-bridge	O
.	O
Bazil	O
Denn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
Denn	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
that	O
is	O
produced	O
?	O
Denn	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Denn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
master	O
's	O
son	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
424	O
Arthur	B-pers
Peccival	I-pers
,	O
and	O
425	O
Henry	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
28	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
rice	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Crockatt	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
July	O
31	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
coming	O
upon	O
Hammond	B-place
's	I-place
key	I-place
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
got	O
upon	O
some	O
barrels	O
of	O
rice	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
barrels	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eades	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Vintners-alley	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
Peirson	O
lying	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
barrels	O
on	O
his	O
belly	O
,	O
handing	O
the	O
rice	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cask	O
into	O
Henry	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
's	O
apron	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
saw	O
Haynes	O
lying	O
upon	O
his	O
belly	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rubbed	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
rice	O
drop	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
apron	O
between	O
the	O
barrels	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
cask	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
of	O
rice	O
do	O
you	O
reckon	O
was	O
dropped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
apron	O
of	O
this	O
Haynes	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
About	O
7	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
One	O
is	O
a	O
lighterman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
ticket	O
porter	O
.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
constable	O
in	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
rice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
?	O
Hartley	O
.	O
About	O
21	O
pounds	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Currey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
distiller	O
's	O
shop	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
leave	O
this	O
rice	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Currey	O
.	O
Between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
brought	O
into	O
any	O
premunire	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
rice	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Currey	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
20	O
pounds	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
a	O
friend	O
gave	O
it	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
belived	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
some	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
spoke	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Currey	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
hearing	O
?	O
Currey	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
it	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
these	O
people	O
?	O
Currey	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
rice	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
friend	O
Eades	O
,	O
and	O
placed	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
resolved	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
five	O
hours	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
secure	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
them	O
?	O
Currey	O
.	O
A	O
watchman	O
came	O
and	O
acquainted	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
barrels	O
of	O
rice	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
rice	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
persons	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
I	O
believed	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
John	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Arthur	O
Percival	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
youth	O
.	O
James	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Haynes	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
426	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
precinct	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Savoy	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch-chain	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
August	O
22	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
and	O
chain	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
them	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
In	O
Somerset-yard	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
time	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
At	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Mary	O
Mills	O
.	O
She	O
followed	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
boat	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
chain	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
off	O
my	O
neck	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
these	O
things	O
taken	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
watch	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
feel	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
taken	O
off	O
your	O
neck	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
tied	O
but	O
with	O
one	O
knot	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
dunghill	O
in	O
Somerset-yard	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
at	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
secure	O
her	O
then	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
several	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
losing	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
meet	O
with	O
her	O
another	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
you	O
saw	O
her	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
Catherine-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
you	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sensible	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
my	O
legs	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
since	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
sold	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wished	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
my	O
buckles	O
had	O
been	O
silver	O
;	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
speak	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
somebody	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Raybold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
garret	O
in	O
Swan-alley	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Cowley	O
's	O
to	O
lodge	O
yesterday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
came	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
petticoat	O
she	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
before	O
.	O
Raybold	O
.	O
And	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
a	O
dosing	O
upon	O
a	O
dunghill	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
that	O
cost	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
that	O
cost	O
2	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
before	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
great	O
God	O
in	O
heaven	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
427	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
*	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Cullingham	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
late	O
of	O
Wingfield	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
county	I-place
of	I-place
Suffolk	I-place
,	O
labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
malefactors	O
,	O
disturbers	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
the	O
kingdom	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
40	O
persons	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
,	O
(	O
whose	O
names	O
are	O
unknown	O
)	O
after	O
the	O
24th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
19th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
day	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
the	O
20th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
at	O
Horsey	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Norfolk	B-place
,	O
with	O
fire-arms	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
offensive	O
weapons	O
,	O
riotously	O
,	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
,	O
assemble	O
themselves	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
running	O
,	O
landing	O
,	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
uncustomed	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
goods	O
liable	O
to	O
pay	O
duties	O
which	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
paid	O
or	O
secured	O
;	O
in	O
defiance	O
and	O
contempt	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
and	O
his	O
laws	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
evil	O
example	O
of	O
all	O
others	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
his	O
crown	O
and	O
dignity	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
*	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
Sessions	O
for	O
not	O
surrendering	O
himself	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
Act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
counsel	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
charge	O
is	O
,	O
being	O
assembled	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
40	O
,	O
at	O
Horsey	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Norfolk	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
running	O
and	O
landing	O
uncustomed	O
goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1746.	O
one	O
Bailey	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
a	O
coffee-house	O
in	O
Yarmouth	O
,	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Horsey	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
smuglers	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
expected	O
their	O
cutter	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
came	O
as	O
a	O
spy	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Manning	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
this	O
Bailey	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
whipp	O
'd	O
Bailey	O
in	O
a	O
cruel	O
manner	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Manning	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
church-yard	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
caseknife	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
would	O
cut	O
his	O
throat	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
all	O
the	O
questions	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
acquaintance	O
Manning	O
:	O
and	O
they	O
tied	O
a	O
rope	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
strangled	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
an	O
arm	O
of	O
a	O
tree	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
almost	O
dead	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
next	O
step	O
they	O
took	O
to	O
get	O
this	O
man	O
to	O
shew	O
his	O
great	O
thanks	O
to	O
them	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
made	O
him	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
thank	O
them	O
for	O
not	O
hanging	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
swear	O
damnation	O
to	O
his	O
soul	O
if	O
he	O
revealed	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
And	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
treat	O
him	O
so	O
ill	O
as	O
they	O
did	O
before	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
consider	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
very	O
great	O
terror	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
having	O
been	O
treated	O
as	O
a	O
spy	O
without	O
foundation	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
treated	O
so	O
ill	O
,	O
now	O
I	O
will	O
see	O
what	O
these	O
people	O
are	O
about	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
very	O
cunningly	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
going	O
another	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
so	O
close	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
going	O
forward	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
gang	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
40	O
or	O
50	O
,	O
running	O
and	O
landing	O
of	O
goods	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
says	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
prove	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
persons	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
do	O
your	O
duty	O
in	O
bringing	O
this	O
person	O
to	O
condign	O
punishment	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
we	O
prove	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
guilty	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Co.	O
for	O
the	O
Crown	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
March	O
1746	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
At	O
Yarmouth	O
in	O
Norfolk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
Horsey	O
that	O
Month	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
Horsey	O
beach	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
William	O
or	O
Robert	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Horsey-beach	O
on	O
the	O
eleventh	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Manning	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
used	O
so	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
smugglers	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
on	O
the	O
beach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
forty	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
armed	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
all	O
armed	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
three	O
armed	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
cutter	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
goods	O
landed	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
goods	O
were	O
landed	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
oil-skin	O
bags	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
had	O
tea	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
casks	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
commonly	O
run	O
brandy	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
these	O
bags	O
the	O
usual	O
package	O
for	O
tea	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
always	O
saw	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
custom-house	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
of	O
tea	O
do	O
those	O
bags	O
hold	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
About	O
25	O
pounds	O
weight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
do	O
these	O
casks	O
hold	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
gallons	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
or	O
five	O
gallons	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
loaded	O
their	O
horses	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
his	O
pistols	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
