TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
and	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
21st	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
Cooper	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1748	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief-	O
Baron	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
FOSTER	O
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRACEY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rivington	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Parkes	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Sterrop	I-pers
,	O
Philips	B-pers
Garden	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collyer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hollamby	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barkham	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Beake	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Babb	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Solby	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Heritage	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brackett	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Braddock	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Broadhead	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
71	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
yards	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
broad	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
December	O
31	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
hired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
weekly	O
boy	O
to	O
run	O
of	O
errands	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Dec.	O
31	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
nine	O
yards	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
broad	O
cloth	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
made	O
you	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
idle	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
given	O
to	O
gaming	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
yards	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Granger	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
on	O
Puddle-Dock	O
Hill	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
nine	O
yards	O
three	O
quarters	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
middle	O
room	O
in	O
my	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
's	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
a	O
hair	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
made	O
him	O
any	O
promise	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
threatened	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Murfin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
boy	O
before	O
?	O
Murfin	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
cloth	O
?	O
Murfin	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Granger	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
?	O
Murfin	O
.	O
For	O
six	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
?	O
Murfin	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
boy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
you	O
have	O
produced	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
three	O
yards	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
at	O
7	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
bring	O
her	O
some	O
cloth	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
+	O
George	O
Knight	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
broad	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
thirty	O
yards	O
of	O
stuff	O
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
long	O
ells	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taverner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
-	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taverner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cloth-worker	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
about	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
broad	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
yards	O
of	O
long	O
ells	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
?	O
Taverner	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
these	O
four	O
yards	O
three	O
quarters	O
I	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
that	O
cloth	O
?	O
Taverner	O
.	O
At	O
Ward	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
Murfin	O
lodges	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
cloth	O
?	O
Taverner	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
farrel	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
head	O
end	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Taverner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
white	O
spots	O
upon	O
it	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
There	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
pieces	O
that	O
may	O
have	O
white	O
spots	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Taverner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
cloth	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
cloth	O
out	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Wood	O
's	O
room	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Taverner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
key	O
?	O
Hodges	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Murfin	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ward	O
's	O
wife	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
this	O
cloth	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Taverner	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
owned	O
he	O
carried	O
these	O
goods	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Ward	O
himself	O
by	O
?	O
Taverner	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
said	O
sometimes	O
he	O
was	O
and	O
sometimes	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
sometimes	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
penny	O
and	O
sometimes	O
two	O
pence	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
Constable	O
.	O
This	O
cloth	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
condition	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Murfin	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
drawers	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hodges	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
72.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Walsh	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
28	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
matters	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
an	O
action	O
,	O
and	O
confined	O
me	O
for	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
matters	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Cecilia	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
six	O
spoons	O
lost	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
next	O
the	O
street	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
makes	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Cecilia	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
Because	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
handle	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
pretty	O
clean	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
short	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
afterwards	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
,	O
saving	O
your	O
favour	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
so	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
one	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Brice	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Cecilia	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
?	O
Cecilia	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Emelia	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
with	O
this	O
old	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Brice	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
for	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
answer	O
did	O
he	O
return	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
Brice	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Brice	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
mention	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
three	O
alehouses	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
vault	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
brought	O
us	O
into	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
pretence	O
of	O
making	O
water	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
run	O
off	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
us	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
two	O
watchmen	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afterwards	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
?	O
Brice	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
Brice	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
Brice	O
.	O
Half	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
spoons	O
?	O
Brice	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
on	O
suspicion	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
your	O
husband	O
commit	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
beating	O
him	O
?	O
Brice	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
felony	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
committed	O
for	O
beating	O
him	O
?	O
Brice	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Count	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
spoke	O
to	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
a	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
Count	O
.	O
Nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
called	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
you	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
when	O
the	O
spoons	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
upon	O
this	O
?	O
Brice	O
.	O
I	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
night	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
to	O
detain	O
him	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
Justice	O
Frazer	O
's	O
order	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
people	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
broke	O
from	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
commitment	O
*	O
by	O
Justice	O
Frazer	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
day	O
of	O
commitment	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
commitment	O
was	O
for	O
assaulting	O
,	O
beating	O
and	O
bruising	O
William	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
detained	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
oath	O
of	O
Emelia	O
Brice	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Count	I-pers
,	O
(	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Brice	O
say	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
,	O
You	O
old	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
me	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
this	O
was	O
.	O
Count	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
tell	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
words	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Brice	O
used	O
.	O
Count	O
.	O
She	O
damned	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
sunk	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
old	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
who	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
upon	O
his	O
trial	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
character	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
any	O
person	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
said	O
?	O
Count	O
.	O
In	O
Task-Court	O
,	O
Purpool-Lane	O
.	O
Emelia	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
shew	O
how	O
long	O
this	O
woman	O
(	O
who	O
now	O
appears	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
company	O
together	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
73	O
.	O
+	O
74	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Macklin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Bryant	B-pers
Ivery	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Christ	B-place
Church	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
January	O
6	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
the	O
linen	O
drapery	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
half	O
doors	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
these	O
two	O
boys	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
doors	O
were	O
shut	O
;	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
one	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
who	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
;	O
though	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
great	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
frightened	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
pieces	O
off	O
a	O
shelf	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
was	O
hovering	O
about	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
)	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
goods	O
?	O
Paine	O
.	O
Yes	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
goods	O
.	O
Bryant	B-pers
Ivery	I-pers
.	O
Pray	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Paine	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
make	O
room	O
for	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
to	O
pass	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
Ivery	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scarlet	O
garters	O
?	O
Paine	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
my	O
neighbours	O
asked	O
for	O
garters	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
asked	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Delafort	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
somebody	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
a	O
boy	O
with	O
these	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
boy	O
?	O
Delafort	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Ivery	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scarlet	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
steal	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Macklin	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Macklin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
ten	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
place	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
?	O
Macklin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
-	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
75	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Hackney	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
moved	O
and	O
seduced	O
by	O
the	O
instigation	O
of	O
the	O
devil	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
21st	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
in	O
and	O
upon	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Upington	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
an	O
infant	O
of	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
twelve	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
,	O
did	O
carnally	O
know	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
produced	O
.	O
And	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
Page	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
said	O
rape	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Upington	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
age	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
above	O
twelve	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
William	B-pers
Page	I-pers
at	O
any	O
time	O
do	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
two	O
shillings	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
gown	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Moody	O
had	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
gown	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
holiday	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
must	O
wait	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
*	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Crew	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Crew	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
*	O
This	O
does	O
not	O
agree	O
with	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
Monday	O
fortnight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
happened	O
then	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
shillings	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
tea	O
and	O
sugar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
bring	O
the	O
tea	O
and	O
sugar	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
pushed	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
chamber	O
with	O
a	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
his	O
will	O
of	O
me	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
finger	O
up	O
my	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
boy	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
One	O
Dick	O
that	O
lives	O
at	O
Kingsland	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Page	I-pers
asked	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Crew	O
said	O
stay	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
did	O
Page	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
She	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
me	O
down	O
while	O
William	B-pers
Page	I-pers
did	O
.	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
upon	O
any	O
bed	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
upon	O
some	O
straw	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
consent	O
or	O
resist	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
consent	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
with	O
your	O
will	O
or	O
against	O
your	O
will	O
that	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Against	O
my	O
will	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Crew	O
do	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
She	O
clapped	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
knees	O
against	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
upon	O
my	O
mouth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
complain	O
of	O
this	O
matter	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
The	O
very	O
same	O
week	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
in	O
Crew	O
's	O
house	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
immediately	O
go	O
home	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Crew	O
's	O
to	O
ask	O
about	O
the	O
coals	O
that	O
were	O
given	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
away	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
home	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
your	O
mother	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
then	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
No	O
body	O
but	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
your	O
mother	O
come	O
home	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
your	O
mother	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
acquaint	O
your	O
mother	O
with	O
it	O
then	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
my	O
mother	O
would	O
beat	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
complaint	O
to	O
your	O
mother	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
complaint	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
mother	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
that	O
you	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Friday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
mother	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
occasion	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
examine	O
your	O
body	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
there	O
besides	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
One	O
Ann	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
examine	O
your	O
body	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Pris	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
questions	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
?	O
Pris	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Upington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
mother	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
that	O
you	O
sent	O
your	O
daughter	O
on	O
Monday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
on	O
any	O
errand	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Moody	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
mantua-maker	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
shillings	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
daughter	O
above	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
lives	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Moody	O
's	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
They	O
face	O
one	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
go	O
a	O
milking	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
your	O
daughter	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
'till	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
did	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
gown	O
or	O
money	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
gown	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Moody	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
wait	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
holiday	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
further	O
discourse	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
that	O
the	O
child	O
walked	O
oddly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
ailed	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
chafed	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
where	O
she	O
made	O
water	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
ago	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Monday	O
sevennight	O
.	O
Upington	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
Christmas-day	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Upington	I-pers
called	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
when	O
Christmas	O
day	O
was	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
Friday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
Christmas	O
day	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
last	O
Monday	O
but	O
one	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Upington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
mother	O
,	O
called	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
further	O
about	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
I	O
inquired	O
after	O
the	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
brought	O
all	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
then	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
had	O
discovered	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
neighbours	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
midwife	O
to	O
examine	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
midwife	O
here	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
condition	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
her	O
in	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
entered	O
about	O
half	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
my	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
she	O
may	O
have	O
the	O
foul	O
distemper	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
did	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
says	O
,	O
up	O
her	O
coats	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
too	O
many	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Crew	O
held	O
her	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
wad	O
of	O
straw	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
have	O
nothing	O
but	O
straw	O
to	O
lie	O
upon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
consenting	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
.	O
Upington	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Crew	O
stopped	O
her	O
mouth	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
said	O
so	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
to	O
the	O
ending	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Friday	O
that	O
you	O
examined	O
her	O
body	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
last	O
Friday	O
past	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
Christmas-day	O
you	O
sent	O
your	O
daughter	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
examined	O
her	O
body	O
was	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
also	O
a	O
fortnight	O
's	O
difference	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
your	O
daughter	O
's	O
linen	O
that	O
gave	O
you	O
any	O
suspicion	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
?	O
Upington	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
this	O
girl	O
's	O
mother	O
upon	O
any	O
occasion	O
?	O
Scott	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
by	O
a	O
midwife	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
another	O
neighbour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
girl	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
Scott	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
her	O
body	O
?	O
Scott	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sore	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
upon	O
examining	O
her	O
body	O
,	O
think	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
by	O
any	O
man	O
?	O
Scott	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
our	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
midwife	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
this	O
girl	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
account	O
did	O
she	O
give	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
Nothing	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sore	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
so	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Crew	O
's	O
had	O
made	O
her	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Crew	O
did	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Crew	O
held	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
give	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
then	O
as	O
she	O
does	O
now	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
that	O
apprehended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
else	O
of	O
the	O
Affair	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
exchanged	O
a	O
word	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
all	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
a	O
thousand	O
times	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Moffat	O
,	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
give	O
his	O
opinion	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Moffat	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
above	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
says	O
no	O
blood	O
was	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
entered	O
,	O
as	O
her	O
mother	O
says	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
her	O
finger	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
your	O
opinion	O
.	O
Moffat	O
.	O
Suppose	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
be	O
extremely	O
small	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
a	O
man	O
is	O
full	O
made	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
without	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
blood	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
76	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dyall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Lestrand	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
foreign	O
silver	O
coin	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
French	O
crown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
,	O
clerk	O
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Dec.	O
18	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
,	I-place
and	I-place
went	I-place
into	I-place
Eagle-Court	I-place
to	O
make	O
water	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
run	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
breeches	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
postures	O
I	O
pleased	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
wrong	O
person	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
directly	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
in	O
particular	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
got	O
in	O
between	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
needs	O
say	O
I	O
run	O
a	O
great	O
risque	O
in	O
so	O
doing	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
watchmen	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
pretended	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
watchmen	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
she	O
pulled	O
down	O
her	O
stocking	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
stocking	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
piece	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
this	O
piece	O
before	O
you	O
pursued	O
her	O
?	O
Acton	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
can	O
you	O
swear	O
this	O
piece	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Acton	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
you	O
had	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
Acton	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
twenty	O
thousand	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Raynoe	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eleven	O
there	O
was	O
watch	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
another	O
watchman	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
French	O
piece	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
more	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
that	O
again	O
,	O
what	O
other	O
money	O
she	O
had	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
welcome	O
to	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
her	O
stocking	O
which	O
was	O
upon	O
her	O
right	O
leg	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Acton	B-pers
She	I-pers
picked	O
more	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
indict	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
my	O
oisters	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
gentleman	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
some	O
four	O
and	O
some	O
five	O
a	O
penny	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
eat	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
broad	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Eagle-Court	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
watchmen	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
.	O
Acton	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
oisters	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Oh	O
!	O
fye	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Lord	O
have	O
mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
so	O
?	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
77	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
nine	O
moidores	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
value	O
31	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Guyther	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
December	O
10	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Guyther	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barber	O
and	O
peruke-maker	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
,	O
(	O
James	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
)	O
met	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
looking	O
for	O
a	O
brush	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
:	O
Bell	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
bureau	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
my	O
bureau	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
nine	O
moidores	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
there	O
that	O
afternoon	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Bell	O
tell	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
Simpson	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
?	O
Guyther	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
dining-room	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
him	O
?	O
Guyther	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
forgiveness	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
me	O
nine	O
moidores	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
side-breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
marks	O
upon	O
the	O
moidores	O
?	O
Guyther	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
marks	O
upon	O
the	O
moidores	O
,	O
the	O
rings	O
I	O
can	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
lost	O
eight	O
rings	O
;	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Guyther	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
them	O
?	O
Guyther	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
of	O
rings	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
gold	O
rings	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
served	O
my	O
time	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Guyther	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
journeyman	O
then	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Guyther	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
formerly	O
lived	O
there	O
?	O
Bell	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
conversation	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
to	O
the	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
not	O
seeing	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
fellow-servant	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
?	O
And	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
I.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
brush	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
the	O
bureau	O
quite	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
confused	O
manner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
brush	O
?	O
Bell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
afterwards	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
thought	O
Mr.	O
Guyther	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
Simpson	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
satisfy	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
I	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
bureau	O
open	O
then	O
?	O
Bell	O
.	O
The	O
flap	O
was	O
put	O
up	O
again	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
that	O
?	O
Bell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
down	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
looking	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Guyther	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Guyther	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Guyther	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
slid	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Guyther	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
from	O
him	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
Bell	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
Bell	O
.	O
Rings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
gold	O
rings	O
?	O
Bell	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
gold	O
rings	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
rings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
a	O
fellow-servant	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Guyther	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
being	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
(	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cutler	O
in	O
Eastsmithfield	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
very	O
much	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
in	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
night	O
he	O
was	O
fuddled	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
fuddled	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
swear	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
he	O
do	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
He	O
goes	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
can	O
get	O
any	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
journeyman	O
barber	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
mother-in-law	O
has	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
always	O
counted	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
lad	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
his	O
poor	O
father	O
will	O
break	O
his	O
heart	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
ever	O
lived	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barber	O
and	O
peruke-maker	O
in	O
Mincing-lane	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
Daniel	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
upon	O
any	O
dislike	O
that	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
farther	O
occasion	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bartlett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
lad	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Guyther	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
behaved	O
exceeding	O
well	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
,	O
honest	O
a	O
fellow	O
,	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
account	O
I	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
recommended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Court	O
would	O
be	O
merciful	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
evidence	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
in	O
conscience	O
help	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
78	O
.	O
+	O
Isaac	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Hannah	B-pers
Maund	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
alley	O
,	O
called	O
Bowl-alley	B-place
,	O
in	O
or	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
;	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
four	O
pence	O
.	O
Dec.	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Couch	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Hog	O
lane	O
,	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Maund	I-pers
,	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
us	O
into	O
Bowl-court	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
blew	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
spoke	O
to	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
money	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
my	O
sister	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
surprize	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
what	O
money	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
four	O
pence	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
a	O
necklace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
noise	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
rip	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
razors	O
,	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cutlass	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
frighten	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
watchmen	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
the	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
that	O
fellow	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
us	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
watchmen	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
us	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
watchmen	O
and	O
you	O
discourse	O
some	O
small	O
time	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
secured	O
?	O
Couch	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
razors	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
were	O
any	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Couch	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
her	O
whether	O
the	O
watchmen	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
?	O
Couch	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
deliver	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
?	O
Couch	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Maund	I-pers
.	O
As	O
my	O
sister	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hog-lane	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stood	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
some	O
words	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
Bowl-court	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
blew	O
it	O
out	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
groat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
to	O
your	O
sister	O
?	O
Maund	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
a	O
necklace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
frighten	O
my	O
sister	O
:	O
he	O
D	O
-	O
d	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
B	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
stab	O
me	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
two	O
razors	O
,	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cutlass	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
talking	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
watchmen	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
them	O
beat	O
the	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
upon	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
upon	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
it	O
pretty	O
tight	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wished	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
halter	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
tighter	O
than	O
that	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
that	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
calls	O
herself	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
blow	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
herself	O
?	O
Couch	O
.	O
He	O
blew	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
blew	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
,	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
near	O
?	O
Couch	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
keys	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Couch	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
see	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
Davis	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
find	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
were	O
the	O
keys	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
my	O
rounds	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
women	O
were	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
watch	O
,	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
of	O
a	O
groat	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
consider	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
they	O
charged	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
we	O
are	O
drunk	O
or	O
mad	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
mind	O
them	O
,	O
watchman	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
are	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
B	O
-	O
s	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
them	O
both	O
:	O
they	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
papers	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
gutter	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
gutter	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
Near	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
Only	O
four	O
keys	O
.	O
William	O
Rooke	O
produced	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
sealed	O
up	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
:	O
which	O
Davis	O
proved	O
was	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
keys	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rooke	O
likewise	O
produced	O
a	O
necklace	O
and	O
a	O
thimble	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
penyworth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
headborough	O
that	O
night	O
the	O
watchmen	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
women	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
women	O
say	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
necklace	O
and	O
thimble	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
Davis	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
them	O
say	O
so	O
?	O
Rooke	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Couch	O
called	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
necklace	O
and	O
thimble	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Couch	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
them	O
again	O
:	O
for	O
they	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
service	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
(	O
who	O
lives	O
by	O
Shoreditch	O
church	O
)	O
as	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
me	O
my	O
wages	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hob	O
in	O
the	O
well	O
to	O
meet	O
some	O
acquaintance	O
:	O
my	O
father	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
late	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
dish	O
of	O
stakes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
staid	O
later	O
than	O
ordinary	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
till	O
one	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Hog-lane	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
;	O
says	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
women	O
,	O
hark	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
Bowl-court	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
made	O
an	O
agreement	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
groat	O
;	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
calls	O
herself	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
groat	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
:	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
charge	O
you	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
your	O
Lordship	O
saw	O
just	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
carnal	O
knowledge	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
for	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
watchmen	O
coming	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
charged	O
the	O
watchmen	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
watchmen	O
charge	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
spoke	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
discoursing	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
:	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
And	O
as	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
dropped	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
watchman	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
witnesses	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
keys	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stiff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
above	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
his	O
father	O
too	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
ever	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ogden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
:	O
and	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
is	O
such	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutors	O
offered	O
me	O
four	O
shillings	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
up	O
.	O
Bernard	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Fletcher	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
called	O
again	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
offer	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
four	O
shillings	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
of	O
four	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
What	O
characters	O
do	O
Couch	O
and	O
Maund	O
bear	O
?	O
Hopkins	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
bad	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
credited	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
.	O
They	O
are	O
both	O
persons	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
minded	O
.	O
Joanna	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Couch	O
and	O
Maund	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
they	O
bear	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
credited	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
keep	O
late	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
in	O
at	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinchen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Couch	O
and	O
Maund	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
them	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
their	O
general	O
character	O
among	O
their	O
neighbours	O
?	O
Kinchen	O
.	O
Their	O
characters	O
are	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
keep	O
late	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
are	O
drunkards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
persons	O
to	O
be	O
credited	O
?	O
Kinchen	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Racket	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
their	O
characters	O
among	O
their	O
neighbours	O
is	O
but	O
very	O
indifferent	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
+	O
Isaac	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
James	I-pers
Couch	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
alley	O
,	O
in	O
or	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
called	O
Bowl-Alley	B-place
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
one	O
shilling	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
a	O
necklace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
,	O
December	O
13	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Couch	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Shoreditch	O
with	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Hog-Lane	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Bowl-Alley	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
blew	O
our	O
candle	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
a	O
necklace	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
further	O
circumstances	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
,	O
than	O
you	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
trial	O
?	O
Couch	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Maund	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
further	O
evidence	O
to	O
give	O
,	O
than	O
what	O
I	O
gave	O
upon	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Couch	I-pers
.	O
desired	O
some	O
witnesses	O
might	O
be	O
called	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wangow	I-pers
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Maund	I-pers
came	O
to	O
nurse	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
fever	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
her	O
sister	O
came	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
staid	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
till	O
past	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
characters	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
goes	O
out	O
a	O
charing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
winds	O
silk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
near	O
them	O
?	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
have	O
lived	O
twenty-five	O
or	O
twenty	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
79.	O
James	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
shilling	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
14	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
partner	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Foster	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
marked	O
six	O
shillings	O
;	O
yesterday	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
marked	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
shilling	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
of	O
a	O
customer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
marked	O
shillings	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
mark	O
them	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
C.	O
W.	O
1747.	O
upon	O
five	O
of	O
the	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
cross	O
;	O
the	O
shilling	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
he	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
desk	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
C.	O
W.	O
1747	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
besides	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
Nothing	O
but	O
a	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
six	O
marked	O
shillings	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
shilling	O
he	O
took	O
of	O
a	O
customer	O
.	O
Septimus	B-pers
Harling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Foster	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wilkins	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Olive-Tree	O
in	O
Tower-Street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
compting-house	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
marked	O
six	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
mark	O
did	O
he	O
put	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
Harling	O
.	O
He	O
marked	O
five	O
with	O
C.	B-pers
W	I-pers
.	I-pers
1747.	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
another	O
mark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
marking	O
these	O
?	O
Harling	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
had	O
missed	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
bespoke	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
that	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
and	O
take	O
another	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
master	O
challenge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
?	O
Harling	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
compting-house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
pulled	O
out	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
desk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
?	O
Harling	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
marked	O
C.	O
W.	O
1747.	O
was	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
then	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
80.	O
William	B-pers
Haddock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
West	I-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
12	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
pretty	O
near	B-place
Black-Fryer	I-place
's	I-place
gate	I-place
,	O
and	O
observing	O
a	O
twitch	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
unbuttoned	O
,	O
that	O
drew	O
the	O
skirt	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
persons	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
taxed	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
apprehend	O
was	O
his	O
companion	O
,	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
dragged	O
him	O
to	O
Grocers-Hall	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
constable	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
,	O
neither	O
could	O
I	O
get	O
one	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
myself	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
examined	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
belonging	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
at	O
Cow-Cross	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
but	O
carried	O
coals	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
for	O
a	O
livelihood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
twitch	O
at	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
A	O
Juryman	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dirty	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
But	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
place	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
paved	O
stones	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
dirty	O
weather	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
The	O
stones	O
were	O
slappy	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
81.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
ounces	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
worsted	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
82.	O
David	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
November	O
20	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
frame-work	O
knitter	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
twentieth	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
twelve	O
ounces	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
frame-work	O
knitting	O
worsted	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
(	O
Adams	O
)	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
people	O
that	O
kept	O
frames	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
my	O
oath	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
worsted	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
one	O
Wagg	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
seven	O
ounces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
Lloyd	O
owned	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
Adams	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Lloyd	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
He	O
keeps	O
a	O
stocking	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
sells	O
buttons	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
laid	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
groat	O
an	O
ounce	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
gave	O
three	O
halfpence	O
or	O
seven	O
farthings	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
give	O
five	O
pence	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
gave	O
but	O
three	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
this	O
worsted	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
One	O
William	B-pers
Meads	I-pers
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
worth	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
a	O
groat	O
an	O
ounce	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
would	O
you	O
buy	O
it	O
at	O
three	O
pence	O
an	O
ounce	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
you	O
buy	O
it	O
at	O
two	O
pence	O
an	O
ounce	O
.	O
if	O
any	O
was	O
offered	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
difficult	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
)	O
Consider	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
matter	O
that	O
may	O
affect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
worsted	O
you	O
have	O
produced	O
is	O
the	O
worsted	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
tied	O
it	O
round	O
with	O
some	O
yarn	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
trade	O
can	O
do	O
so	O
as	O
myself	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Meads	I-pers
.	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
into	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wagg	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
Wagg	O
directly	O
?	O
Meads	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
you	O
has	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
Wagg	O
was	O
there	O
any	O
inquiry	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Meads	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
?	O
Meads	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
twelve	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
?	O
Meads	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
he	O
understand	O
these	O
goods	O
?	O
Meads	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
brought	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
trade	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
difference	O
between	O
the	O
weaving	O
yarn	O
and	O
the	O
knitting	O
yarn	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
is	O
dearest	O
and	O
which	O
is	O
cheapest	O
.	O
Meads	O
.	O
One	O
is	O
hard	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
soft	O
,	O
the	O
hard	O
is	O
the	O
dearest	O
and	O
the	O
soft	O
is	O
the	O
cheapest	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
knitting	O
yarn	O
is	O
not	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
the	O
weaving	O
yarn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
that	O
worsted	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
?	O
Meads	O
.	O
Three	O
pence	O
half	O
penny	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
groat	O
an	O
ounce	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Suppose	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
this	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Meads	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
what	O
I	O
pleased	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
you	O
?	O
Meads	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
do	O
as	O
they	O
pleased	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Suppose	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
to	O
offer	O
you	O
that	O
at	O
three	O
halfpence	O
an	O
ounce	O
,	O
what	O
should	O
you	O
think	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Meads	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
must	O
cost	O
more	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
some	O
white	O
and	O
blue	O
worsted	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
groat	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
grey	O
worsted	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Lloyd	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
He	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
you	O
the	O
groat	O
for	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
ounces	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
mother	O
was	O
starving	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
.	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
Coun	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
told	O
him	O
you	O
wanted	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
family	O
from	O
starving	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
you	O
have	O
some	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
?	O
Court	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
aggravation	O
of	O
the	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
squeezing	O
the	O
poor	O
prodigiously	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Adams	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
worsted	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
paper	O
in	O
Tothill	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
worsted	O
I	O
spun	O
myself	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
odds	O
and	O
ends	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
has	O
kept	O
the	O
girl	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
apprentice	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
evidence	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
judged	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
King	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
worsted	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
insist	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
fair	O
market	O
price	O
?	O
Lloyd	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
seven	O
farthings	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
at	O
times	O
;	O
this	O
worsted	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
much	O
there	O
was	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
question	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
given	O
very	O
near	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
understand	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
worsted	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
thirty	O
years	O
a	O
stocking-maker	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
worth	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
a	O
groat	O
an	O
ounce	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
given	O
for	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
near	O
sighted	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
five	O
pence	O
an	O
ounce	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
fine	O
frame	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
fine	O
frame	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
worth	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
worth	O
three	O
pence	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
three	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
worth	O
seven	O
farthings	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
chance	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
given	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
understand	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
Coun	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
receive	O
stolen	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
given	O
seven	O
farthings	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
what	O
made	O
you	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
three	O
pence	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
It	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
worth	O
so	O
much	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
take	O
me	O
up	O
more	O
time	O
to	O
fit	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
work	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
afford	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bascomb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Legrand	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
stocking	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Lloyd	O
above	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
?	O
Bascomb	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
man	O
of	O
any	O
character	O
that	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
judge	O
of	O
worsted	O
?	O
Bascomb	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
only	O
deals	O
in	O
two	O
penny	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
and	O
low	O
sorts	O
of	O
worsted	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
and	O
honest	O
character	O
?	O
Bascomb	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
as	O
fair	O
and	O
honest	O
a	O
character	O
as	O
any	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
would	O
you	O
give	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Bascomb	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
four	O
pence	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
you	O
give	O
seven	O
farthings	O
?	O
Bascomb	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
tumbled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
above	O
three	O
pence	O
for	O
this	O
worsted	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
worth	O
more	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Lloyd	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
an	O
honester	O
juster	O
dealer	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
than	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Hales	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
worsted	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
worth	O
?	O
Hale	O
.	O
As	O
it	O
is	O
tumbled	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
(	O
though	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
better	O
than	O
it	O
appears	O
to	O
be	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
good	O
for	O
three	O
pence	O
an	O
ounce	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
as	O
good	O
for	O
something	O
less	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
judge	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
himself	O
?	O
Hales	O
.	O
Unless	O
he	O
deals	O
in	O
it	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
deal	O
much	O
in	O
this	O
article	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
judge	O
of	O
the	O
goodness	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Lloyd	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
ever	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ashmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Lloyd	O
these	O
sixteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
,	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Lloyd	O
these	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
character	O
has	O
he	O
born	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Collyer	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nor	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
roguery	O
?	O
Collyer	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
or	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
candid	O
honest	O
man	O
:	O
his	O
business	O
does	O
not	O
lie	O
among	O
chance	O
customers	O
,	O
but	O
amongst	O
those	O
that	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
receive	O
stolen	O
goods	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
them	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
83	O
.	O
84.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Maybank	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
knives	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
hammer	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
24	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
a	O
hammer	O
and	O
two	O
knives	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
stall	O
in	O
Piccadilly	B-place
,	O
for	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
stall	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
gone	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Skate	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
past	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
time	O
for	O
all	O
honest	O
people	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
bed	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
stall	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Skate	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
two	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
?	O
Skate	O
.	O
Upon	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Maybank	I-pers
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Maybank	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
some	O
things	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
of	O
her	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lowry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
almost	O
these	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
sells	O
fruit	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
in	O
summer	O
,	O
her	O
mother	O
keeps	O
a	O
green-stall	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
her	O
bread	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
a	O
stone	O
's	O
throw	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shank	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
about	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
living	O
by	O
selling	O
fruit	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Questen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
money	O
lent	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
buy	O
the	O
goods	O
she	O
carried	O
the	O
money	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
her	O
as	O
readily	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
before	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Maybank	I-pers
guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
85.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mackdonald	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
28	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
cap	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Mrs.	O
to	O
beg	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
a	O
message	O
to	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
who	O
owed	O
her	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mrs.	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
breakfast	O
;	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
elbow	O
chair	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
into	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
my	O
Mrs.	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
great	O
chair	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Nanny	O
has	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Mrs.	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Nanny	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
again	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
bureau	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
drawers	O
except	O
one	O
were	O
locked	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
my	O
cap	O
;	O
the	O
cap	O
lay	O
uppermost	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
cap	O
was	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Nanny	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
we	O
talked	O
of	O
searching	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
dirty	O
cap	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
or	O
sold	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
cap	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
wondered	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
so	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
cap	O
upon	O
her	O
?	O
Bennett	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Loveday	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
message	O
for	O
her	O
in	O
Spring	O
Garden	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
and	O
my	O
maid	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
Peggy	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
strange	O
thing	O
you	O
should	O
see	O
a	O
person	O
take	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
stop	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
cap	O
?	O
Loveday	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
saw	O
the	O
cap	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
it	O
lay	O
uppermost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
cap	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
86	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Smallwood	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
Peruke	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
oak	O
stick	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
,	O
December	O
5	O
.	O
Laurence	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
two	O
blue	O
posts	O
in	O
Russel-Street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
Bridges	B-place
Street	I-place
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stepped	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
myself	O
a	O
jerk	O
and	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Watch	O
!	O
but	O
the	O
man	O
replied	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
two	O
Paddies	O
,	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
two	O
Irishmen	O
)	O
met	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
again	O
after	O
the	O
chairman	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
fight	O
you	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
fighting	O
man	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
fight	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
replied	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
fight	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
collared	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
on	O
my	O
body	O
,	O
the	O
effects	O
of	O
which	O
blows	O
I	O
now	O
feel	O
;	O
then	O
a	O
little	O
fellow	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
accomplices	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
tripped	O
up	O
my	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
fell	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
me	O
down	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
your	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
stunned	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
bruised	O
;	O
then	O
Smallwood	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
chairman	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
inquired	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
able	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
,	O
Sir	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Legrand	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
account	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
robbery	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
swear	O
a	O
point	O
blank	O
robbery	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
only	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
?	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
suppose	O
a	O
man	O
should	O
assault	O
me	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
stole	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
?	O
P.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
stopped	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
me	O
an	O
answer	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
did	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
charge	O
him	O
for	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
For	O
being	O
stopped	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
by	O
his	O
companions	O
of	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
relate	O
the	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
as	O
you	O
say	O
now	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
's	O
warrant	O
for	O
a	O
common	O
assault	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
what	O
you	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
assaulted	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
Smallwood	O
before	O
he	O
struck	O
you	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
Nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
attempt	O
to	O
knock	O
you	O
down	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
struck	O
first	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ask	O
you	O
for	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
order	O
you	O
to	O
deliver	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
-	O
Burton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Bridges-Street	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smallwood	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
stood	O
over	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
came	O
singly	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
:	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
say	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
assault	O
me	O
for	O
?	O
Ca	O
n't	O
a	O
man	O
go	O
along	O
quietly	O
?	O
and	O
Smallwood	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
fight	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
fighting	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
fight	O
you	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
stepped	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
steps	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
fellow	O
came	O
and	O
tripped	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
was	O
almost	O
smothered	O
in	O
the	O
dirt	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
Smallwood	O
off	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
both	O
kept	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
all	O
night	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Coun	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wanted	O
to	O
fight	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
fight	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Smallwood	O
charge	O
him	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Smallwood	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
words	O
did	O
Potts	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
stick	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coun	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
examined	O
Potts	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
stick	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
glover	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Vinegar-yard	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
four	O
men	O
together	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
blows	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
gentleman	O
and	O
Smallwood	O
engaged	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
fellow	O
came	O
and	O
tripped	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
up	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
Smallwood	O
lay	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Smallwood	O
gave	O
the	O
first	O
charge	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
man	O
who	O
tripped	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
up	O
,	O
gathered	O
up	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
Coun	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
offered	O
you	O
to	O
prevent	O
you	O
from	O
coming	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
to	O
day	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
offered	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Potts	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
brother	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
night	O
afterwards	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
stick	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
had	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Coun	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
perfectly	O
sober	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
an	O
ale-house	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
you	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
reeling	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
Burton	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
against	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
:	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
several	O
blows	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
.	O
Burton	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
wig	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Tamar	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Smallwood	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
where	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
drunk	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
as	O
fuddled	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
by	O
it	O
till	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
unbuttoned	O
the	O
knees	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
garters	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Stock	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Stock	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
fellow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
robbing	O
this	O
man	O
upon	O
the	O
highway	O
.	O
Stock	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
publick-house	O
?	O
Stock	O
.	O
The	O
Crooked	O
Billet	O
in	O
Bridges-Street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
squabble	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
near	O
Vinegar-Yard	O
,	O
how	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Stock	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
stones	O
throw	O
.	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Smallwood	O
at	O
the	O
Crooked	O
Billet	O
in	O
Bridges-Street	O
on	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
away	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
twelve	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
come	O
in	O
with	O
any	O
company	O
,	O
or	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
any	O
company	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
staggered	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
his	O
head	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
87.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Featherstone	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Peter	I-place
Cheap	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
truss	O
,	O
containing	O
ten	O
dozen	O
,	O
of	O
woollen	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
,	O
December	O
19	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
to	O
carriers	O
at	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
Inn	O
in	O
Wood-Street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
intrusted	O
with	O
these	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
are	O
you	O
answerable	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
lose	O
any	O
hose	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
the	O
Kidderminster	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
truss	O
of	O
hose	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
inn-yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
quantity	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
truss	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
twenty	O
dozen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
dozen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
my	O
brother	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
into	O
the	O
Old-Jewry	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
delivered	O
any	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
Inn	O
gate	O
in	O
Wood-Street	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
up	O
into	O
Gold-Street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
stockings	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
or	O
shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
Gold-Street	O
into	O
Gutter-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
among	O
the	O
coachmen	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
clothes	O
had	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
with	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
stockings	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
all	O
the	O
same	O
clothes	O
on	O
then	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
dussled	O
coat	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
or	O
your	O
brother	O
take	O
the	O
stockings	O
up	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
brother	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
stay	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
did	O
any	O
discourse	O
pass	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
him	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
too	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
sure	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
something	O
of	O
Christian	O
knowledge	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
falsely	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
never	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
they	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
inn-yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
these	O
stockings	O
to	O
be	O
delivered	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
find	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
at	O
Holbourn-Bridge	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
other	O
carrier	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
brother	O
your	O
servant	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you-take	O
all	O
the	O
stockings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
out	O
six	O
trusses	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
butter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Jury	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cross	O
Keys	O
in	O
Wood-Street	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turning	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
inn	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
stockings	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
or	O
shoulder	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
till	O
my	O
brother	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
double-breasted	O
lapel	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
inn	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
stockings	O
at	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
just	O
turning	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
inn-gate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Stroud	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
