TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
21st	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1748	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Sixpence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
LADBROKE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
DENISON	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLIVE	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRACEY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lasingby	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Thorpe	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hucks	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stavely	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Money	I-pers
.	O
Humphry	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Patience	I-pers
.	O
Cambulanus	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Sam	B-pers
Leightonhouse	I-pers
.	O
Nath	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
George	B-pers
Fettiplace	I-pers
.	O
Duncan	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Staton	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wickstead	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
.	O
262	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Matfellon	I-place
,	I-place
otherwise	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
parish	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
In	O
Whitechapel	O
parish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
losing	O
of	O
a	O
Watch	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
abroad	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
it	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
message	O
from	O
one	O
Capt	O
.	O
Johnson	O
in	O
Soho-square	O
,	O
about	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
smallbeer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
great	O
chair	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
seize	O
him	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
lay	O
the	O
watch	O
down	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
false	O
message	O
from	O
Capt	O
.	O
Johnson	O
:	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Capt	O
.	O
Johnson	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
nor	O
he	O
neither	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
watch	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
it	O
hung	O
up	O
over	O
the	O
chimney-piece	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
frivolous	O
message	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
hang	O
over	O
the	O
chimney-piece	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
lay	O
the	O
watch	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
great	O
chair	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
great	O
chair	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Shaw	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fellowship-porter	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Shaw	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
taken	O
my	O
till	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Shaw	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
lady	O
in	O
New	O
Bond-street	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
servant	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
he	O
of	O
now	O
?	O
Trueman	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
now	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
263.	O
George	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Stead	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Farm	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
Rose	O
Stead	O
,	O
Wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Stead	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Stead	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
lost	O
it	O
?	O
Stead	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
room	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
sick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Stead	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Stead	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
wife	O
lived	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
forgot	O
her	O
name	O
?	O
The	O
nurse	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Stead	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Capt	O
.	O
Johnson	O
in	O
Soho-square	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
the	O
West-Indies	O
from	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Stead	O
.	O
If	O
your	O
lordship	O
pleases	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
letter	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
bring	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
Capt	O
.	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
easy	O
till	O
he	O
sees	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
ill	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
somebody	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
nurse	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Stead	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
hanging	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
sidled	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
chimney-piece	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
one	O
hand	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
to	O
hide	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
put	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
bundle	O
in	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
your	O
servant	O
madam	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
Stead	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
he	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Stead	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Stead	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
out	O
among	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
disguise	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
concerning	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
I	O
the	O
same	O
cloaths	O
on	O
then	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
?	O
Stead	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
duffle	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
check	O
'd	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
colour	O
'd	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Mary	O
Blundell	O
(	O
the	O
nurse	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Stead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mistress	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Blundell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
all	O
over	O
Soho-square	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
chairmen	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
where	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
as	O
Capt	O
.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stead	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
stop	O
me	O
if	O
you	O
saw	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Stead	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
you	O
had	O
pistols	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
threaten	O
you	O
?	O
Stead	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
threaten	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
run	O
away	O
directly	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
threatned	O
her	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Because	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
which	O
she	O
thought	O
was	O
pistols	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Indictment	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
264.	O
John	B-pers
Kearney	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Michael	I-place
,	I-place
Cornhill	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
copper	O
,	O
being	O
forty	O
mathematical	O
plates	O
engrav	O
'd	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
6th	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bookseller	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
late	O
fire	O
in	O
Cornhill	B-place
I	O
lost	O
forty	O
mathematical	O
copper	O
plates	O
,	O
engraved	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
(	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
)	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
these	O
plates	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
mine	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
plates	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Meadows	O
swore	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
]	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
This	O
fellow	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
as	O
a	O
labourer	O
,	O
in	O
clearing	O
the	O
ruins	O
after	O
the	O
late	O
fire	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
these	O
plates	O
on	O
his	O
shoulders	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
The	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
old	O
iron	O
and	O
old	O
lead	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
they	O
must	O
belong	O
either	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Meadows	O
or	O
Mr.	O
Brotherton	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
spot	O
where	O
their	O
houses	O
stood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
these	O
the	O
plates	O
you	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
all	O
this	O
while	O
in	O
my	O
possession	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
what	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
six-pence	O
?	O
Reynolds	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Meadows	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
direction	O
given	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
when	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
any	O
particular	O
place	O
?	O
Meadows	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ruins	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Murray	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
sailor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
family	O
has	O
he	O
?	O
Murray	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
has	O
three	O
children	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
enquire	O
into	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Fulbrook	I-pers
.	O
The	O
man	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
buy	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Fulbrook	O
.	O
Gingerbread	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
fells	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
day	O
labour	O
.	O
Fulbrook	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
sometimes	O
;	O
and	O
sometimes	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
a	O
brewhouse	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Curning	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
brewers	O
and	O
other	O
people	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
the	O
sea	O
?	O
Curning	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
sea	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
left	O
that	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
off	O
?	O
Curning	O
.	O
About	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Ring	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
long	O
enough	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
how	O
long	O
you	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Ring	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
265.	O
Jane	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Caleb	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
2d	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
any	O
relation	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Caleb	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
He	O
married	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
plates	O
and	O
sheet	O
were	O
produced	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
these	O
goods	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
sheet	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Caleb	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
plates	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
this	O
plate	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
plates	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
have	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
mark	O
now	O
;	O
we	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
sale	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
keep	O
the	O
n	O
Coffee-house	O
by	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
our	O
servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
come	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
after	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
she	O
live	O
with	O
your	O
father	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
Till	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
go	O
then	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
Because	O
we	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
honest	O
:	O
we	O
turned	O
her	O
away	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Worral	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
of	O
being	O
dishonest	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
plates	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Worral	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Worral	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
plates	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Worral	I-pers
.	O
These	O
plates	O
and	O
sheet	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
by	O
Jane	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Worral	O
.	O
In	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
things	O
in	O
of	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
ever	O
a	O
house-keeper	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Worral	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
all	O
together	O
?	O
Worral	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
plates	O
and	O
sheet	O
in	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
these	O
plates	O
down	O
without	O
being	O
asked	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Glover	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
because	O
Mr.	O
Worral	O
was	O
so	O
very	O
civil	O
as	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
down	O
without	O
their	O
being	O
asked	O
for	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
Miss	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
my	O
mistress	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
all	O
her	O
plates	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
266.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
,	I-place
Lombard-street	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fossey	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
some	O
plain	O
ones	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
wrought	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
buckler	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
missing	O
?	O
Newman	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
eighteen	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
seventeen	O
when	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
Newman	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
round	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
it	O
between	O
the	O
lining	O
and	O
the	O
outside	O
covering	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
ripped	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
buckle	O
.	O
Newman	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
buckle	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
267.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Dillow	I-pers
.	O
of	O
Christ-Church	B-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Apleford	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
25th	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Apleford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
them	O
?	O
Apleford	O
.	O
The	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
made	O
you	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Apleford	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
honesty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Apleford	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
days	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
errands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Apleford	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
them	O
?	O
Apleford	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hewitt	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
.	O
I	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
tax	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
?	O
Apleford	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
they	O
pawned	O
for	O
?	O
Apleford	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
's	O
?	O
Apleford	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
there	O
?	O
Apleford	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
for	O
two	O
gowns	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Dillow	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
money	O
paid	O
to	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Apleford	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
her	O
any	O
promises	O
of	O
being	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
told	O
you	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
Apleford	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
crime	O
was	O
capital	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
mention	O
made	O
by	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Apleford	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
's	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hewitt	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
honest	O
creature	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
looked	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
things	O
to	O
pledge	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
brought	O
these	O
gowns	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
these	O
gowns	O
are	O
not	O
yours	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
of	O
your	O
size	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
do	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
them	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
known	O
her	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
quiet	O
,	O
sober	O
a	O
girl	O
,	O
as	O
ever	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
drinking	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
ill.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
she	O
any	O
parents	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
Her	O
mother	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
her	O
father	O
is	O
very	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
now	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
spoke	O
last	O
:	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
sober	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Dillow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
she	O
behaved	O
?	O
Dillow	O
.	O
Very	O
prettily	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
sober	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
went	O
into	O
any	O
men	O
's	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
was	O
never	O
guilty	O
of	O
swearing	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
this	O
unhappy	O
thing	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
her	O
father	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
268.	O
Martha	B-pers
Ryson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
camblet	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Maidley	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Maidley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
scarlet	O
camblet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Maidley	O
.	O
In	O
Angel-Alley	B-place
,	I-place
Little	I-place
Moorfields	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Maidley	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
silk	O
gown	O
under	O
her	O
petticoat	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
scarlet	O
gown	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lend	O
it	O
her	O
?	O
Maidley	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
any	O
cloak	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
?	O
Maidley	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Maidley	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
silk	O
gown	O
under	O
her	O
petticoat	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
camblet	O
gown	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
Maidley	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
pulled	O
it	O
off	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
directly	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Maidley	I-pers
.	O
My	O
sister	O
lost	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
heartily	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
her	O
?	O
Maidley	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
a	O
sober	O
woman	O
?	O
Maidley	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
apt	O
to	O
drink	O
much	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
Maidley	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
millenery	O
business	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
can	O
not	O
get	O
employment	O
in	O
the	O
milliners	O
shops	O
till	O
she	O
can	O
get	O
her	O
cloaths	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
my	O
sister	O
when	O
the	O
scarlet	O
gown	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
mother	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Maidley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
my	O
son	O
and	O
daughter	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
drawers	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
robbed	O
them	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
as	O
true	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
heaven	O
and	O
a	O
God	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
creature	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
liquor	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
269.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
Winifred	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Harp-Alley	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
broker	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
were	O
brought	O
down	O
to	O
be	O
brushed	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
laid	O
upon	O
a	O
bedstead	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
man	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
come	O
into	O
your	O
shop	O
for	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
man	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
hands	O
off	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
She	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
and	O
asked	O
pardon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crab	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
William	O
Atkinson	O
I	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
stooping	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
tying	O
her	O
garter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
And	O
seeing	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
only	O
picked	O
up	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
rags	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
she	O
then	O
?	O
Crab	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
further	O
?	O
Crab	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
brush	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
laid	O
them	O
upon	O
a	O
bedstead	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
things	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Atkinson	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
like	O
a	O
mad	O
dog	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Holdsworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
Holdsworth	O
.	O
About	O
twenty	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
she	O
do	O
for	O
her	O
living	O
?	O
Holdsworth	O
.	O
She	O
goes	O
a	O
nursing	O
,	O
or	O
one	O
thing	O
or	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
she	O
live	O
?	O
Holdsworth	O
.	O
In	O
Tooly-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Holdsworth	O
.	O
In	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
some	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
buy	O
any	O
cloaths	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
Holdsworth	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
bought	O
any	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Girtley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Girtley	O
.	O
In	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lived	O
there	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
character	O
?	O
Girtley	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
270.	O
Edward	B-pers
Clowden	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clement	I-place
Danes	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
perriwig	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Jenns	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Jenns	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
perriwig-maker	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
perriwig	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Jenns	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Clowden	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Jenns	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
fictitious	O
name	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
chair	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
for	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
minutes	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
passed	O
his	O
compliments	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Sir	O
,	O
your	O
humble	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
shook	O
hands	O
with	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
wig	O
off	O
a	O
block	O
.	O
I	O
presently	O
missed	O
the	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
wig	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
:	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
wig	O
:	O
I	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
:	O
a	O
constable	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brabsey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Matthews	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Granger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
upright	O
man	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
bread	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
271.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Stead	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
pieces	O
of	O
leather	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
272.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bedell	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
distiller	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Market	O
.	O
The	O
beginning	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
whence	O
?	O
Birch	O
.	O
Out	O
of	O
my	O
kitchen	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
can	O
inform	O
your	O
lordship	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Birch	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
spoon	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
this	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
soon	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
full	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
she	O
do	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
She	O
pretends	O
to	O
black	O
shoes	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
High-Holborn	O
,	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
silver	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
these	O
spoons	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
other	O
five	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
this	O
where	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
pretty	O
closely	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
tub	O
of	O
hogwash	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
Tavern	O
in	O
Pall-Mall	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
there	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
a	O
spoon	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
a	O
headborough	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Broadhead	O
,	O
and	O
whilst	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
writing	O
the	O
Commitment	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
(	O
constable	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
shew	O
us	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Birch	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
delivered	O
the	O
spoon	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
spoon	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
Birch	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
spoon	O
.	O
Newton	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
spoon	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
spoon	O
among	O
some	O
broken	O
victuals	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Birch	O
's	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
373	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Quick	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Hendon	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
lamb	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
May	O
22	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
lamb	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
lamb	O
?	O
Parsons	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
we	O
found	O
was	O
a	O
lamb	O
pye	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
live	O
?	O
Parsons	O
.	O
At	O
Hendon	O
.	O
The	O
pye	O
was	O
covered	O
with	O
a	O
wet	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pulled	O
a	O
leg	O
of	O
lamb	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
pulled	O
out	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
pulled	O
out	O
?	O
Parsons	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Parsons	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
lamb	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
we	O
found	O
was	O
this	O
lamb	O
pye	O
,	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
wet	O
gown	O
;	O
we	O
turned	O
the	O
bed	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
came	O
some	O
feathers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pulled	O
a	O
leg	O
out	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
present	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
served	O
the	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lamb	O
pye	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Nothing	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Found	O
what	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
The	O
lamb	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
speak	O
a	O
good	O
word	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
,	O
only	O
what	O
they	O
say	O
now	O
:	O
This	O
lamb	O
lay	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Lambert	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
274.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
gallon	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
May	O
15	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pewter	O
gallon	O
pot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
it	O
from	O
?	O
Gray	O
.	O
From	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Long-Acre	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
lost	O
?	O
Gray	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Macguire	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden	O
Hart	O
in	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
publick-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Macguire	O
's	O
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
there	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Macguire	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
this	O
pot	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
my	O
wife	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
Macguire	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
pot	O
down	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
blade	O
six	O
inches	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
rip	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
name	O
is	O
there	O
upon	O
the	O
pot	O
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Coalheavers	O
Arms	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
this	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
dead	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Trevor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
going	O
along	O
Drury-Lane	O
with	O
a	O
gallon	O
pot	O
under	O
the	O
left	O
slap	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
blade	O
of	O
the	O
knife	O
was	O
six	O
inches	O
long	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
rip	O
me	O
up	O
if	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
curs	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
dangerous	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Gray	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
pot	O
found	O
?	O
Trevor	O
.	O
The	O
pot	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Macguire	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
275	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
capuchin	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Allen	B-pers
Rutlidge	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
May	O
14	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Champion	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Allen	B-pers
Rutlidge	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silk	O
capuchin	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
ruffled	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
taking	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Maltus	O
Paine	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
silver	O
hilted	O
sword	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
sword	O
was	O
advertised	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Champion	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
him	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
confusion	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
little	O
girls	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
rely	O
upon	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
hilted	O
sword	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
8	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
this	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
276	O
,	O
277	O
,	O
278.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
>	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Sharpless	I-pers
``	I-pers
/	I-pers
>	I-pers
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Dicker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Luke	O
's	O
,	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
340	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
linen	O
yarn	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Irish	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bolus	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
April	O
29	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bolus	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sailmaker	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Irish	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
carry	O
on	O
your	O
trade	O
?	O
Bolus	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Bolus	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
missed	O
yarn	O
frequently	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
these	O
goods	O
?	O
Bolus	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Bolus	O
.	O
Forty-one	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
linen	O
yarn	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
Dicker	O
and	O
Palmer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
yarn	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
Bolus	O
.	O
Out	O
of	O
our	O
factory	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
employ	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
in	O
weaving	O
,	O
spinning	O
,	O
and	O
sailcloth	O
making	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
yarn	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
yarn	O
?	O
Bolus	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
is	O
a	O
better	O
judge	O
of	O
that	O
than	O
I.	O
Robert	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Irish	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bolus	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
yarn	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Street	O
to	O
Charter-house	O
Square	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Catharine	B-pers
Dicker	I-pers
and	O
Palmer	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
Dicker	O
pass	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
bag	O
upon	O
her	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
go	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
bag	O
upon	O
her	O
head	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
had	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
looked	O
like	O
yarn	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
packing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Palmer	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
it	O
seems	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
yarn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
shew	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
our	O
yarn	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
work	O
for	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
?	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
very	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
seized	O
Palmer	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
off	O
her	O
head	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
our	O
yarn	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
bag	O
from	O
Palmer	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
should	O
make	O
her	O
escape	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
would	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pursue	O
Dicker	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
charge	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
factory	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
carry	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
factory	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Palmer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
Brooks	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
in	O
stealing	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
you	O
with	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
her	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
daughter	O
have	O
left	O
it	O
off	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
ago	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
her	O
daughter	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Dicker	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Harlow	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Catharine	B-pers
Dicker	I-pers
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
constable	O
?	O
Harlow	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
factory	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Dicker	I-pers
did	O
declare	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
steal	O
goods	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Irish	O
and	O
company	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
-	O
Dennis	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Lively	I-pers
,	O
some	O
at	O
three	O
halfpence	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
a	O
penny	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
From	O
ten	O
pence	O
to	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
best	O
sort	O
of	O
yarn	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Lively	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
bring	O
her	O
some	O
more	O
of	O
that	O
yarn	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
into	O
sheets	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Dennis	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
an	O
hostler	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
ropemaker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
hear	O
that	O
Dicker	O
says	O
she	O
sold	O
some	O
yarn	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Dennis	O
.	O
She	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
?	O
Dennis	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
sold	O
any	O
yarn	O
to	O
your	O
mother	O
?	O
Dennis	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
woman	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
bring	O
any	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Palmer	O
ever	O
bring	O
any	O
?	O
Dennis	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
times	O
might	O
Brooks	O
bring	O
yarn	O
?	O
Dennis	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
yarn	O
found	O
at	O
your	O
mother	O
's	O
?	O
Dennis	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
brought	O
the	O
yarn	O
to	O
your	O
mother	O
?	O
Dennis	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
woman	O
always	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Brooks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
she	O
bring	O
the	O
last	O
?	O
Dennis	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
28th	O
or	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Price	O
.	O
)	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
yarn	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
has	O
undergone	O
an	O
operation	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
operation	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
cut	O
a	O
length	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
to	O
fit	O
it	O
for	O
their	O
use	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lively	I-pers
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
brought	O
ten	O
pounds	O
of	O
yarn	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
honestly	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
bought	O
it	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Lively	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
enough	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bolus	I-pers
.	O
I	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
say	O
one	O
word	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Brooks	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
,	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
hundred	O
weight	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Dicker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saved	O
a	O
little	O
out	O
of	O
every	O
parcel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
?	O
Dicker	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
persuaded	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
this	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Bolus	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
deliver	O
your	O
yarn	O
to	O
them	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
their	O
own	O
habitations	O
?	O
Bolus	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
of	O
our	O
yarn	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
worked	O
in	O
our	O
factory	O
;	O
and	O
Dicker	O
said	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
factory	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Palmer	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
your	O
advising	O
Dicker	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Palmer	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Dicker	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
poor	O
person	O
may	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sometimes	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
pence	O
for	O
carrying	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
?	O
Palmer	O
.	O
To	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hosier-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
Dicker	O
and	O
Sharpless	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Bolus	O
.	O
)	O
What	O
quantity	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
bags	O
?	O
Bolus	O
.	O
About	O
forty	O
pounds	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
.	O
All	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
279	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Reynart	B-pers
Pieterz	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
Reynart	O
Pieterz	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
it	O
?	O
Pieterz	O
.	O
Just	O
by	O
the	O
Exchange	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
Pieterz	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
where	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
?	O
Pieterz	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
feet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Pieterz	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
was	O
it	O
only	O
because	O
you	O
saw	O
it	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
feet	O
?	O
Pieterz	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Totton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Pieterz	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
drop	O
it	O
immediately	O
?	O
Totton	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
it	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
confused	O
,	O
being	O
so	O
suddenly	O
seized	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
force	O
himself	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
troubled	O
with	O
fits	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
A	O
victualler	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
One-Ton	O
,	O
on	O
Holborn-Hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
Twelve	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
he	O
do	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
poor	O
fellow	O
that	O
goes	O
of	O
errands	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
run	O
of	O
errands	O
for	O
gentlemen	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
troubled	O
with	O
fits	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
half	O
an	O
ideot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
him	O
?	O
Kitchen	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
nor	O
never	O
mistrusted	O
him	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Mallet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Magpy	O
at	O
Holborn-Bridge	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
,	O
or	O
heard	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
wronged	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
of	O
a	O
penny	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
brother	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
maintained	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
except	O
what	O
little	O
matters	O
he	O
got	O
by	O
running	O
of	O
errands	O
for	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
under	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
doctors	O
hands	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ever	O
challenged	O
with	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
280.	O
Mary	B-pers
Adlam	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pillow	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Silvester	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
let	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	B-pers
Silvester	I-pers
,	O
April	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Silvester	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bell-yard	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
King-street	I-place
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
she	O
left	O
her	O
lodging	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Silvester	O
.	O
About	O
twelve	O
weeks	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
chamber	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
.	O
Silvester	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
these	O
things	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
?	O
Silvester	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
all	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
challenged	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
be	O
forthcoming	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
the	O
glass	O
to	O
be	O
mended	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
pawned	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
accordingly	O
sent	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
but	O
who	O
sent	O
them	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
porter	O
?	O
Silvester	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
apron	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
they	O
brought	O
?	O
Silvester	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Silvester	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
passed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
?	O
Acton	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
very	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
forthcoming	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Silvester	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
very	O
soon	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
tale	O
there	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Silvester	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
letter	O
come	O
before	O
the	O
goods	O
or	O
after	O
them	O
?	O
Silvester	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
?	O
Silvester	O
.	O
About	O
an	O
hour	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
letter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Silvester	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
write	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Letter	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
]	O
''	O
Mrs.	O
Silvester	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
have	O
received	O
your	O
``	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
no	O
small	O
concern	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
``	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
warning	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
``	O
there	O
are	O
any	O
more	O
things	O
missing	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
``	O
them	O
all	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
person	O
I	O
would	O
sooner	O
``	O
trust	O
my	O
life	O
with	O
,	O
than	O
Mrs.	O
Silvester	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
``	O
beg	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
find	O
a	O
bill	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
ignoramus	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
``	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
appear	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
``	O
shall	O
have	O
some	O
punishment	O
which	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
``	O
desire	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
much	O
``	O
your	O
humble	O
servant	O
,	O
M	O
.	O
Adlam	O
.	O
''	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
worth	O
200	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
coming	O
now	O
from	O
Jamaica	O
in	O
General	O
Dalziel	B-pers
's	O
regiment	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Silvester	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
her	O
things	O
again	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
cost	O
me	O
never	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
are	O
but	O
things	O
of	O
a	O
trifling	O
value	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
hundred	O
people	O
that	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
a	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
bail	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
281	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Garlick-Hith	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
quart	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Cardmaker	B-place
's	I-place
Arms	I-place
on	I-place
Garlick-Hith	I-place
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
about	O
the	O
silver	O
tankard	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Honey-lane	O
market	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
my	O
tankard	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
advertised	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
it	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
when	O
you	O
missed	O
it	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
housekeeper	O
where	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
your	O
tankard	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
please	O
your	O
lordship	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
your	O
tankard	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
house-keeper	O
,	O
if	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
?	O
My	O
house-keeper	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
boy	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
My	O
house-keeper	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
cloak	O
:	O
What	O
!	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
steal	O
my	O
tankard	O
!	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
words	O
when	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
pawned	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
not	O
shewn	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
house	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
say	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
here	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
's	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coachman	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
Mrs.	O
Humphrys	O
lives	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Humphrys	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
:	O
She	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
Mrs.	O
Humphrys	O
would	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Humphrys	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
tankard	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
pawn	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
owned	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
outright	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
4	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
ounce	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
us	O
the	O
tankard	O
without	O
we	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
justice	O
Rickards	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
and	O
demand	O
the	O
tankard	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
warrant	O
was	O
served	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
tankard	O
forthcoming	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
Charles	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
's	O
,	O
the	O
headborough	O
's	O
hands	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
called	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
?	O
Heath	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
tankard	O
of	O
.	O
[	O
Mr.	O
Barber	O
,	O
the	O
headborough	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
Heath	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Heath	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
5	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Am	O
I	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
sold	O
it	O
you	O
?	O
Heath	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
that	O
sold	O
it	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Heath	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Heath	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
plausible	O
story	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
debts	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
been	O
reported	O
in	O
my	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
forty	O
shillings	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
sold	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
washing	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
my	O
mistress	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
money	O
did	O
your	O
mistress	O
give	O
her	O
?	O
Gibbons	O
.	O
Five	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
.	O
Am	O
I	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Heath	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Heath	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
sold	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
[	O
Mrs.	O
Humphrys	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Slater	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Snow-Hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Slater	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
parents	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
industrious	O
person	O
for	O
working	O
;	O
and	O
her	O
parents	O
are	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
people	O
;	O
her	O
mother	O
goes	O
a	O
chairing	O
to	O
gentlemens	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
father	O
is	O
at	O
sea	O
now	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
with	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
character	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
her	O
mother	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
brought	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
honesty	O
and	O
industry	O
;	O
she	O
never	O
lay	O
a	O
night	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
do	O
any	O
harm	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
thing	O
happened	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
promise	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
thing	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
acknowledge	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
282.	O
Henry	B-pers
Rooke	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
21st	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
offensive	O
weapon	O
,	O
called	O
an	O
iron	O
poker	O
,	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
and	O
maliciously	O
,	O
did	O
demand	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
feloniously	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
our	O
said	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
or	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
A	O
married	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Tod	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
In	O
Queen's-head	O
Alley	O
,	O
Wapping	O
,	O
at	O
number	O
four	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
enquired	O
for	O
my	O
eldest	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
your	O
servant	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
you	O
these	O
fifteen	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
good	O
morrow	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
sending	O
for	O
some	O
fine	O
tea	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
child	O
two	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
poker	O
from	O
the	O
fireplace	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
toast	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
poker	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
fire	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
chimney-side	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
cursed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
decayed	O
gentleman	O
,	O
deliver	O
to	O
me	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
this	O
minute	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
make	O
no	O
words	O
,	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
this	O
minute	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
sum	O
as	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blood	O
run	O
down	O
very	O
fast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
knock	O
you	O
down	O
before	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
demand	O
,	O
or	O
after	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
He	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
spot	O
,	O
just	O
after	O
he	O
demanded	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
the	O
poker	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
cut	O
down	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
places	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
he	O
stamped	O
upon	O
me	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dragged	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
hair	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
to	O
the	O
staircase	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
mark	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
day	O
light	O
you	O
might	O
see	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
entirely	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
gore	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
poker	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
cut	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
the	O
wounds	O
are	O
not	O
quite	O
well	O
yet	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
exceeding	O
good	O
flesh	O
to	O
heal	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
twelve	O
wounds	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
neck	O
.	O
[	O
Mrs.	O
Tod	O
produced	O
some	O
linen	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
.	O
]	O
And	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
make	O
any	O
noise	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
knock	O
you	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
murder	O
you	O
afterwards	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
poker	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
closet	O
;	O
he	O
kneeled	O
upon	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
me	O
down	O
for	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
from	O
under	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
jumped	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
taken	O
immediately	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
indict	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
indicted	O
him	O
both	O
for	O
the	O
robbery	O
*	O
and	O
the	O
assault	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
had	O
preferred	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
found	O
it	O
Ignoramus	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
him	O
every	O
day	O
from	O
Jamaica	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
gone	O
for	O
a	O
ship	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
master	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
poker	O
.	O
Court	O
(	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Tod	O
.	O
)	O
Did	O
you	O
strike	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
poker	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
lawyer	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
all	O
as	O
false	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
struck	O
her	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Justice	O
Mainwairing	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
would	O
swear	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
any	O
money	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Hardy	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Hardy	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Hardy	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
about	O
two	O
doors	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Tod	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
a	O
strange	O
man	O
was	O
beating	O
Mrs.	O
Tod	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
rumour	O
of	O
it	O
carried	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
all	O
in	O
her	O
gore	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
before	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
Hardy	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
blood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
prodigiously	O
bloody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
able	O
to	O
speak	O
?	O
Hardy	O
.	O
Very	O
little	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
almost	O
murdered	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
afterwards	O
,	O
news	O
was	O
brought	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
run	O
down	O
Queen's-head	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
waterside	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
a	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
wet	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
ruffles	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
neck	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
shirt	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
to	O
herself	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
six	O
cuts	O
in	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
least	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
an	O
inch	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
long	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Hardy	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
cage	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
wet	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
tumbled	O
into	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
cage	O
?	O
Hardy	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Hardy	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
not	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
drunk	O
then	O
?	O
Hardy	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
vile	O
scandalous	O
women	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
gin	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
crazy	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
Just	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Tod	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Wapping	O
Chapel	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
come	O
,	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Tod	O
is	O
almost	O
murdered	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Tod	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
here	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Rooke	O
the	O
lawyer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
six	O
places	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
Dr.	O
Scot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
barber	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
barber	O
came	O
and	O
shaved	O
those	O
places	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
that	O
were	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
walk	O
after	O
her	O
wounds	O
were	O
dressed	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
hands	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
I	O
done	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
!	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
York	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
devil	O
was	O
in	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Tod	O
sent	O
her	O
girl	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Rooke	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
come	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
come	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rooke	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
eat	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
dined	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
any	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
treat	O
you	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
treated	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
some	O
falmon	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
swear	O
nothing	O
but	O
falsities	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Tod	O
.	O
)	O
Was	O
he	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
April	O
?	O
Tod	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
falmon	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Collingwood	I-pers
(	O
Sister	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Collingwood	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
after	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
fifteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rooke	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
little	O
bumbo	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
us	O
in	O
a	O
way	O
of	O
getting	O
an	O
estate	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
agreeable	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
much	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
upon	O
my	O
sister	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
fact	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
your	O
sister	O
in	O
this	O
condition	O
?	O
Collingwood	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
drunk	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
I	O
searched	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Collingwood	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
threw	O
himself	O
into	O
the	O
river	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Tod	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
head	O
against	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
poker	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
shew	O
the	O
malice	O
of	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
raised	O
up	O
two	O
boys	O
to	O
swear	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
threw	O
this	O
money	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
.	O
She	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
solicitor	O
at	O
Hick	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
thrown	O
into	O
the	O
Thames	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
persons	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
transport	O
me	O
or	O
hang	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
money	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
house	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mortgagee	O
's	O
hands	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
honour	O
twice	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
attorney	O
,	O
once	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Justice	O
Price	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Denton	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
an	O
artful	O
laid	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
and	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
a	O
week	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
sister	O
went	O
through	O
my	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
quarrel	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
intention	O
to	O
commit	O
a	O
robbery	O
or	O
any	O
act	O
of	O
violence	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
youngest	O
sister	O
,	O
Polly	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
dare	O
not	O
let	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
she	O
is	O
catched	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
be	O
hanged	O
[	O
for	O
her	O
mother	O
and	O
she	O
were	O
transported	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
I	O
hurt	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
struck	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
poker	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
poker	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
bent	O
so	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
any	O
anvil	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
at	O
their	O
house	O
,	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
guineas	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
these	O
persons	O
were	O
of	O
that	O
character	O
,	O
what	O
made	O
you	O
go	O
there	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Tod	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
child	O
when	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
We	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
Mrs.	O
Collingwood	O
's	O
husband	O
is	O
?	O
Collingwood	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
master	O
of	O
a	O
Guinea-man	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Collingwood	O
.	O
In	O
Queen's-Square	O
,	O
Ratcliff-Highway	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Why	O
was	O
it	O
improper	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Collingwood	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
improper	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
reason	O
.	O
Collingwood	O
.	O
Why	O
then	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
these	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
trading	O
on	O
the	O
coast	O
of	O
Guinea	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
gone	O
so	O
long	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
in	O
plain	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
ironing	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
creditable	O
manner	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
assure	O
you	O
.	O
Guilty	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
This	O
offence	O
was	O
made	O
transportation	O
by	O
an	O
Act	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1734	O
;	O
whereby	O
it	O
is	O
enacted	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
any	O
person	O
or	O
persons	O
after	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1734	O
,	O
shall	O
with	O
any	O
unlawful	O
instrument	O
or	O
weapon	O
assault	O
,	O
or	O
with	O
any	O
menances	O
demand	O
any	O
goods	O
,	O
chattels	O
or	O
money	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
intent	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
,	O
every	O
person	O
lawfully	O
convicted	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
shall	O
be	O
adjudged	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
283	O
.	O
+	O
Frances	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
28	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
April	O
the	O
17th	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
do	O
you	O
follow	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
this	O
woman	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
two	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
In	O
Drum-Ally	B-place
in	I-place
Drury-Lane	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
besides	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
28	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
breeches-pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
room	O
was	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
breeches	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
,	O
though	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
so	O
careful	O
as	O
to	O
lay	O
your	O
breeches	O
under	O
your	O
head	O
.	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
go	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
her	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
did	O
she	O
take	O
your	O
breeches	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
that	O
again	O
by	O
a	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
chairmen	O
use	O
to	O
carry	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
about	O
you	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
we	O
do	O
.	O
Three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
stay	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
a	O
lawyer	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
again	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
then	O
?	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
your	O
money	O
again	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dicey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Macguire	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
Dicey	O
.	O
She	O
waked	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
Dicey	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
small-beer	O
brought	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
punch-bowl	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
pull	O
off	O
all	O
her	O
things	O
but	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
into	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
whom	O
did	O
she	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Dicey	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
chairman	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
money	O
chink	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
tossed	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Dicey	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
she	O
take	O
.	O
Dicey	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
some	O
gold	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Sykes	I-pers
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
Sykes	O
whether	O
she	O
should	O
take	O
it	O
all	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Macguire	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
proper	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
the	O
chairman	O
?	O
Dicey	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Macguire	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Macguire	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Macguire	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
live	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
this	O
Jones	O
?	O
Macguire	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
drank	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
she	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Macguire	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
off	O
all	O
her	O
things	O
but	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
up	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Macguire	O
.	O
She	O
tossed	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
you	O
for	O
?	O
Macguire	O
.	O
Asking	O
your	O
pardon	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
my	O
backside	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
gentlemen	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
284.	O
Jane	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
camblet	O
skirt	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
stripped	O
my	O
child	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
it	O
had	O
on	O
almost	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
only	O
an	O
apron	O
pinned	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Hughes	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
King	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
parliament	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
child	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
?	O
Hughes	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
by	O
himself	O
into	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
King	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
Huges	O
.	O
Three	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
child	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mammy	O
,	O
Mammy	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
the	O
child	O
come	O
home	O
?	O
Hughes	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Cooke	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
child	O
's	O
stays	O
hanging	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
a	O
green	O
camblet	O
skirt	O
and	O
a	O
frock	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
King	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
deal	O
in	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Cooke	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Cooke	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
frock	O
,	O
a	O
skirt	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
poor	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
brother	O
's	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
put	O
out	O
to	O
nurse	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
almost	O
starved	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
mother	O
must	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
bread	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Mrs.	O
Hughes	O
's	O
child	O
has	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
now	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
seeing	O
the	O
stay	O
hang	O
up	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
along	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
a	O
skirt	O
and	O
a	O
frock	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
person	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
know	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
gown	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
buy	O
a	O
frock	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
:	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
stript	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hughes	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
285	O
.	O
+	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
30th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
17	O
48	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tufnell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
3	O
l.	O
212	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
coin	O
of	O
the	O
proper	O
coin	O
of	O
this	O
realm	O
,	O
called	O
guineas	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
222	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
coin	O
of	O
the	O
proper	O
coin	O
of	O
this	O
realm	O
,	O
called	O
an	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
did	O
feloniously	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
account	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
30th	O
day	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
212	O
guineas	O
,	O
value	O
222	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tufnell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
feloniously	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
our	O
sovereign	O
lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tufnell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
been	O
?	O
Tufnell	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
between	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
did	O
he	O
break	O
into	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Tufnell	O
.	O
He	O
broke	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
unscrew	O
'd	O
the	O
pin	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
unbolted	O
a	O
back	O
door	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
parlour	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
two	O
locks	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
bureau	O
took	O
212	O
guineas	O
