TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
21st	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1748	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
LADBROKE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WRIGHT	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BIRCH	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
LEGGE	I-pers
,	O
JOHN	B-pers
STRACEY	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Reyner	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Farel	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Gutridge	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hanson	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Restall	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Vultjohn	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Joel	B-pers
Alderton	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Curson	I-pers
.	O
118.	O
Mary	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
six	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
castors	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
18	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
coach	O
on	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
January	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Dulwich	B-place
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
six	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
castors	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
February	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
information	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Langley	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
plate	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
which	O
contained	O
the	O
plate	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Johnson	O
's	O
in	O
Russel-Court	O
,	O
Bridges-Street	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
spoons	O
,	O
two	O
salts	O
,	O
a	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
castor	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
the	O
castor	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
castor	O
;	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
one	O
Stringer	O
's	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
(	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
)	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Dulwich	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
plate	O
out	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
(	O
hearing	O
a	O
report	O
of	O
several	O
robberies	O
)	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
plate	O
behind	O
me	O
under	O
the	O
seat	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
our	O
being	O
robbed	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
for	O
the	O
plate	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
duskish	O
;	O
we	O
enquired	O
after	O
it	O
and	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
at	O
Johnson	O
's	O
and	O
Stringer	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
[	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
]	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
Those	O
Trials	O
with	O
this	O
mark	O
+	O
shew	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Capital	O
Offences	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
have	O
received	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
if	O
the	O
Jury	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Douglas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
one	O
Catharine	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
found	O
some	O
plate	O
in	O
the	O
borough	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
Douglas	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
spoons	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
found	O
at	O
Langley	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
Johnson	O
's	O
?	O
Douglas	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
Stringer	O
's	O
?	O
Douglas	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
I	O
served	O
a	O
warrant	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
into	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
presently	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
trunk	O
behind	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
trunk	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
then	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
place	O
where	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Herbert	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
(	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Cox	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
two	O
spoons	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
trunk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
?	O
Frost	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
respect	O
to	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
?	O
Frost	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
another	O
woman	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
plate	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
one	O
Gordon	O
keeps	O
,	O
who	O
goes	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
came	O
with	O
this	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
woman	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
She	O
goes	O
by	O
three	O
names	O
,	O
Douglas	O
,	O
Hughes	O
,	O
and	O
Keys	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
things	O
in	O
several	O
times	O
which	O
she	O
brought	O
that	O
were	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
Cath	O
.	O
Keys	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
it	O
you	O
?	O
Keys	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Langley	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
Court	O
upon	O
a	O
trial	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
Subpoena	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
women	O
of	O
us	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
the	O
plate	O
dropped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
pawned	O
it	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
I	O
might	O
very	O
well	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
any	O
Damage	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
declaration	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
your	O
character	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
twenty	O
as	O
substantial	O
people	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
desired	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
might	O
be	O
asked	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
people	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
expect	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
those	O
women	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
Vinegar-Yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
subpoena	O
them	O
here	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
my	O
trial	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
told	O
my	O
Lord	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
119	O
.	O
+	O
Peter	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
plush	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
duffle	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
dimithy	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rymer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
January	O
26	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ryner	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
at	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
that	O
were	O
pledged	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Rymer	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
In	O
December	O
last	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
honest	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
first	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
plush	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
short	O
cloak	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
afterwards	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
with	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
?	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
My	O
man	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
Peter	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
came	O
with	O
goods	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
another	O
person	O
's	O
.	O
My	O
man	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
whose	O
shop	O
that	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Rymer	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Rymer	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
journeyman	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Moss	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
goods	O
had	O
you	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
and	O
a	O
short	O
cloak	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Rymer	O
come	O
and	O
own	O
these	O
goods	O
?	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
will	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
ask	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
to	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Rymer	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
discovered	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rymer	O
the	O
transactions	O
Mr.	O
Moss	O
had	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rymer	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
convinced	O
we	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
affair	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rymer	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
tears	O
in	O
his	O
eyes	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
wronged	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
masters	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Foot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
street	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jacobs	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
goods	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Moss	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
twelvemonths	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Rymer	O
said	O
were	O
his	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Malpas	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
pledge	O
a	O
duffle	O
coat	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Rymer	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
32	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
16	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
lend	O
him	O
above	O
8	O
s.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
120.	O
John	B-pers
Lathey	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
Lothbury	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
perriwigs	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
St.	I-pers
Andre	I-pers
,	O
January	O
23	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
St	I-pers
.	O
Andre	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
lost	O
ten	O
perriwigs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
St.	O
Andre	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barber	O
and	O
perriwig	O
maker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
were	O
these	O
perriwigs	O
?	O
St.	O
Andre	O
.	O
They	O
belonged	O
to	O
several	O
customers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
answerable	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
St.	O
Andre	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
already	O
for	O
my	O
customers	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
?	O
St.	O
Andre	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
boy	O
upon	O
trial	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suspected	O
my	O
Journeymen	O
and	O
apprentices	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
this	O
boy	O
,	O
just	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
perriwigs	O
in	O
the	O
Advertiser	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
boy	O
out	O
by	O
this	O
means	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
Mr.	O
Winter	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
seven	O
of	O
my	O
wigs	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
to	O
another	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
writing	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
wrote	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
so	O
?	O
St.	O
Andre	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
?	O
St.	O
Andre	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
some	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
some	O
for	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
sold	O
for	O
seven	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
they	O
worth	O
?	O
St.	O
Andre	O
.	O
At	O
least	O
twenty-five	O
pounds	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
worth	O
four	O
pounds	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Piddington	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
twenty	O
seventh	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
his	O
master	O
of	O
ten	O
wigs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
old	O
clothes	O
folks	O
;	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
for	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
and	O
wrote	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
frequently	O
coming	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
St.	O
Andre	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
twenty-third	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Austin-friars	O
,	O
under	O
a	O
gateway	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
selling	O
a	O
wig	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
sixpence	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
another	O
boy	O
for	O
three	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
old	O
clothes	O
man	O
give	O
him	O
six	O
pence	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
shewed	O
that	O
wig	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
people	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
what	O
signified	O
shewing	O
such	O
an	O
old	O
wig	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
old	O
clothes	O
man	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
bring	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
as	O
one	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
121	O
.	O
+	O
122	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
in	O
the	O
night	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
six	O
gallons	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
gallon	O
of	O
usquebaugh	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
27	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Burnell	O
.	O
Very	O
well	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
them	O
?	O
Burnell	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
of	O
the	O
losing	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
gallons	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
one	O
gallon	O
of	O
usquebaugh	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
tobacco	O
.	O
They	O
broke	O
open	O
my	O
cellar	O
on	O
the	O
twenty-seventh	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
after	O
Christmas	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
confess	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
cellar	O
?	O
Burnell	O
.	O
The	O
accomplice	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
confess	O
this	O
?	O
Burnell	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
did	O
,	O
at	O
Covent-Garden	O
Round-house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
assisted	O
the	O
others	O
in	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
done	O
?	O
Burnell	O
.	O
Between	O
two	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
this	O
cellar	O
belong	O
to	O
your	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
Burnell	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
two	O
doors	O
;	O
one	O
comes	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Burnell	O
.	O
That	O
which	O
comes	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
The	O
cellar	O
door	O
is	O
made	O
of	O
inch	O
and	O
half	O
deal	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
condition	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
your	O
cellar	O
door	O
?	O
Burnell	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
boards	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
it	O
on	O
top	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
top	O
staple	O
drawn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
fastened	O
?	O
Burnell	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
very	O
well	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
fastened	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
fastened	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
observe	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Burnell	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
suspected	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
Burnell	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
suspect	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
impeached	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Robert	O
Wilson	O
,	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
Stevens	O
got	O
a	O
knife	O
from	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
.	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
groove	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
knife	O
in	O
three	O
pieces	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
board	O
off	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
,	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
up	O
two	O
gallons	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
usquebaugh	O
,	O
and	O
sixteen	O
papers	O
of	O
tobacco	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Stevens	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
there	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Hill	O
and	O
Stevens	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Not	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
done	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
We	O
began	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
discover	O
this	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
discovered	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
night	O
was	O
fortnight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
was	O
fortnight	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
as	O
false	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
true	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Ind	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
witness	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
who	O
bought	O
the	O
brandy	O
.	O
Paul	O
Gossett	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Hill	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
one	O
night	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
busy	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
little	O
brandy	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hill	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
customer	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
well	O
)	O
he	O
came	O
within	O
doors	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
importuned	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
6s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
a	O
gallon	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gallon	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
6s	O
.	O
9d	O
.	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
He	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
since	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
found	O
Hill	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
thought	O
that	O
he	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
bread	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Hill	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
my	O
bread	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Richard	O
Mascall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
all	O
three	O
,	O
two	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
Stevens	O
and	O
Wilson	O
confessed	O
the	O
breaking	O
open	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Burnell	O
's	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
the	O
brandy	O
and	O
usquebaugh	O
.	O
William	O
Smith	O
.	O
This	O
Robert	O
Wilson	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
conjunction	O
with	O
Stevens	O
and	O
Hill	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
cellar	O
of	O
Burnell	O
's	O
and	O
company	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Newtoner's-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
about	O
five	O
gallons	O
of	O
brandy	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
drew	O
it	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
pipe	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
two	O
little	O
casks	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
sixteen	O
papers	O
of	O
tobacco	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Stevens	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
have	O
confessed	O
other	O
robberies	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Hill	O
.	O
Wilson	O
brought	O
the	O
brandy	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
gallon	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
pint	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
promised	O
me	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
selling	O
it	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
more	O
indictments	O
against	O
Stevens	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
.	O
123.	O
John	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Nicholas	I-place
Acons	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Barnston	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
Robert	O
Partridge	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
morning	O
I	O
lost	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
two	O
sixpences	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
under	O
my	O
counter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Partridge	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
thief	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
a	O
trap	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
this	O
Money	O
?	O
Partridge	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Partridge	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
particular	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Partridge	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
are	O
they	O
marked	O
?	O
Partridge	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
marked	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
them	O
?	O
Partridge	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
he	O
ever	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
robbing	O
us	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
master	O
knows	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
servant	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
your	O
servant	O
?	O
Partridge	O
.	O
Near	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
an	O
honest	O
servant	O
?	O
Partridge	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Turvill	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Partridge	O
(	O
partner	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Barnston	O
)	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
thief	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
consult	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
their	O
journeyman	O
had	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
missed	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pressed	O
him	O
to	O
tell	O
who	O
he	O
imagined	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
their	O
porter	O
:	O
They	O
contrived	O
to	O
mark	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
marked	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
two	O
sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
journeyman	O
to	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
they	O
marked	O
?	O
Turvill	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
marked	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
stroke	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
one	O
under	O
that	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
mark	O
under	O
the	O
chin	O
;	O
these	O
three	O
pieces	O
I	O
marked	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Neave	I-pers
(	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Partridge	O
and	O
Barnston	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
particularly	O
sure	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
person	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
four	O
sixpences	O
marked	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
drawer	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
one	O
shilling	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
tha	O
t	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
purl	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
this	O
to	O
try	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
all	O
the	O
liberty	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
sixpences	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
pulled	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
wronged	O
his	O
master	O
but	O
once	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
of	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
124	O
,	O
125.	O
Charles	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Leadley	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
(	O
after	O
June	O
24	O
,	O
1731	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
)	O
for	O
stealing	O
eighty-one	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Bingham	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
being	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
shop	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Bingham	O
Davis	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
persons	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
believed	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
beset	O
with	O
thieves	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
premises	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Budge	I-pers
seized	O
Watts	O
upon	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
leg	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
into	O
an	O
area	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
before	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
thrown	O
down	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Watts	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
take	O
any	O
lead	O
off	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Budge	I-pers
(	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
.	O
)	O
On	O
the	O
twentieth	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
hovering	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
pork	O
stakes	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
?	O
Budge	O
.	O
Two	O
.	O
Leadley	O
was	O
taken	O
behind	O
a	O
door	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Chisholm	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Watts	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
no	O
harm	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
lead	O
come	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Budge	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Watts	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
with	O
us	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Leadley	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
meddle	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
or	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
?	O
Budge	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
come	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
Watts	O
and	O
Leadley	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Randall	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Little	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
)	O
and	O
Leadley	O
helped	O
Watts	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
place	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Watts	O
do	O
?	O
Ball	O
.	O
He	O
cut	O
the	O
lead	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Ball	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
so	O
near	O
as	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
?	O
Ball	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Watts	O
cut	O
the	O
lead	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
hand	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
Leadley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Leadley	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
?	O
Ball	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sheers	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
Leadley	O
came	O
out	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
passage	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
then	O
.	O
Leadley	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
help	O
Watts	O
up	O
?	O
Ball	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
for	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
Watts	O
was	O
brought	O
a	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Ball	O
.	O
Watts	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
desire	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
club	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
fudling	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
club	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
persuaded	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
club	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
together	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
.	O
Leadley	O
.	O
Watts	O
put	O
his	O
foot	O
upon	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
knew	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
I	O
suppose	O
?	O
Leadley	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
till	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
lead	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bagley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Robert	B-pers
Leadley	I-pers
for	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
manner	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
works	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
dealings	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
his	O
character	O
stained	O
,	O
upon	O
any	O
account	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
126	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
*	O
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
She	O
was	O
tried	O
in	O
September	O
Sessions	O
,	O
in	O
Heathcote	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
dressing	O
glass	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Vide	O
pag	O
.	O
31	O
.	O
Trial	O
77	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
also	O
tried	O
in	O
December	O
Sessions	O
,	O
in	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
Willimott	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
Moidore	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Vide	O
pag	O
.	O
24	O
.	O
Trial	O
38.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
She	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
done	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
In	O
Windsor	B-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Drury-Lane	I-place
,	O
the	O
twenty-sixth	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
The	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
has	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
's	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
down	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
run	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
shop	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sell	O
liquors	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
into	O
her	O
company	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
five	O
minutes	O
time	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Fob	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
offered	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
[	O
meaning	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
]	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
were	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
beadle	O
said	O
they	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
stocking	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
thought	O
they	O
saw	O
something	O
stick	O
out	O
:	O
The	O
constable	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
afterwards	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
constable	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
's	O
man	O
produced	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Tickler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Tickler	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
her	O
stocking	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
stocking	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
,	O
between	O
her	O
stocking	O
and	O
her	O
heel	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
constable	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
thumb	O
screw	O
her	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bromley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
of	O
that	O
beat	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
Jones	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
charged	O
her	O
they	O
must	O
both	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
surrendered	O
my	O
charge	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
she	O
went	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Bromley	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Falkener	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
beadle	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
)	O
this	O
woman	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
charged	O
by	O
this	O
chairman	O
Jones	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
pretended	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
the	O
chairman	O
insisted	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchmen	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
hold	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
observed	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
bump	O
just	O
by	O
her	O
ankle	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
her	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
struggle	O
before	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
Tickler	O
the	O
turnkey	O
got	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
properest	O
person	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
watch	O
:	O
she	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
her	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
prosecute	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
being	O
timorous	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
she	O
was	O
thumb	O
screwed	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Perkinson	I-pers
.	O
She	O
refused	O
to	O
deliver	O
up	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
forced	O
to	O
thumb	O
screw	O
her	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
where	O
we	O
judged	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
landlady	O
to	O
borrow	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
short	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
five	O
shillings	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
her	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
her	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
127	O
,	O
128	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Cuthbert	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty-two	O
yards	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
February	O
12	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
twelfth	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
with	O
four	O
customers	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Cuthbert	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
servant	O
maid	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
too	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Bell	O
.	O
Because	O
my	O
girl	O
knew	O
her	O
afterwards	O
;	O
Cuthbert	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
(	O
it	O
put	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
damp	O
upon	O
my	O
spirits	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
steal	O
something	O
)	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
of	O
thirty-two	O
yards	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
with	O
Cuthbert	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
cloth	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
lived	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
her	O
yesterday	O
(	O
King	O
;	O
)	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
New	O
Hermitage-street	O
with	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Cuthbert	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
boy	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
find	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Cuthbert	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
this	O
printed	O
cotton	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
tied	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
,	O
after	O
struggling	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
my	O
cotton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
your	O
long	O
lawn	O
again	O
?	O
Bell	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
yards	O
cut	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
through	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
Mary	O
King	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
where	O
the	O
long	O
lawn	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
denied	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
farthing	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
the	O
long	O
lawn	O
was	O
pawned	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Calmer	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
which	O
cost	O
me	O
4	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
perhaps	O
you	O
have	O
mislaid	O
it	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
behind	O
these	O
dowlas	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
maid	O
that	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Cuthbert	O
came	O
to	O
change	O
the	O
goods	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
lived	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
yesterday	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Cuthbert	O
in	O
New	O
Hermitage-street	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cuthbert	O
's	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
home	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
for	O
what	O
they	O
knew	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
King	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
signify	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
Mrs.	O
Cuthbert	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Cuthbert	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
might	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
wait	O
upon	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
somebody	O
else	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
seeing	O
a	O
bulk	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
fancy	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
's	O
goods	O
under	O
your	O
petticoats	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
forced	O
her	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
under	O
her	O
first	O
petticoat	O
:	O
I	O
felt	O
under	O
her	O
second	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
this	O
in	O
her	O
bosom	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
cut	O
this	O
off	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
frock	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
four	O
men	O
,	O
which	O
cost	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
her	O
to	O
Justice	O
Duckenfield	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
cotton	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
gown	O
at	O
a	O
shop	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
;	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
buy	O
nine	O
yards	O
,	O
when	O
six	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
pattern	O
?	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
cotton	O
is	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
shelf	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
Justice	O
Manwaring	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
long	O
lawn	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Green	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
pawned	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
by	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
for	O
Cuthbert	O
's	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Cuthbert	O
put	O
the	O
long	O
lawn	O
into	O
her	O
[	O
King	O
's	O
]	O
apron	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
King	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
I	O
stole	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
?	O
Calmer	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
helped	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Manwaring	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
long	O
lawn	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Christie	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
every	O
thing	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Mittimus	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
headborough	O
of	O
St.	O
John	O
,	O
Wapping	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
King	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Manwaring	O
.	O
King	O
said	O
the	O
long	O
lawn	O
was	O
at	O
Christie	O
's	O
.	O
Green	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
married	O
now	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
twenty-six	O
yards	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
.	O
Q	B-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
to	O
Bell	O
.	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
long	O
lawn	O
?	O
Bell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Green	O
called	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
is	O
called	O
Christie	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Cuthbert	O
brought	O
this	O
long	O
lawn	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
brother	O
,	O
a	O
headborough	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
goal	O
.	O
[	O
Green	O
asked	O
King	O
whether	O
Cuthbert	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
King	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
.	O
Both	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
Cuthbert	O
and	O
King	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
fine	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
cut	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
off	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
to	O
my	O
servant	O
maid	O
's	O
mother	O
's	O
child	O
;	O
Cuthbert	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
printed	O
cotton	O
found	O
under	O
her	O
gown	O
:	O
King	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
lodges	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
Cuthbert	O
pawned	O
the	O
long	O
lawn	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Christie	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
King	O
.	O
This	O
good	O
woman	O
,	O
Cuthbert	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
cloth	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
's	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Cuthbert	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
long	O
lawn	O
to	O
Christie	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Cuthbert	O
.	O
This	O
same	O
Mary	B-pers
King	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
King	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
lurch	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witness	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
body	O
knows	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
129.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
White-chapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Evett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
shop-maid	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dennis	O
in	O
Houndsditch	B-place
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
one	O
night	O
,	O
towards	O
dusk	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
a	O
shift	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
kept	O
us	O
in	O
discourse	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
check	O
off	O
the	O
shelf	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Rag-Fair	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
woman	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
each	O
with	O
an	O
apron	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
check	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
it	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
there	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Evett	O
.	O
Thirteen	O
yards	O
of	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
wide	O
cotton	O
check	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
with	O
these	O
aprons	O
on	O
?	O
Evett	O
.	O
I	O
seized	O
them	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
many	O
tones	O
;	O
first	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
;	O
and	O
several	O
tales	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
?	O
Evett	O
.	O
Next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Crooked	O
Billet	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
Gentlewoman	O
who	O
bought	O
it	O
to	O
make	O
shirts	O
of	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Linstead	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Crooked	O
Billet	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
person	O
she	O
called	O
her	O
mistress	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
my	O
maid	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
two	O
women	O
wanted	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
check	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
better	O
than	O
eight	O
yards	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
eight	O
shillings	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
for	O
nine	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
afford	O
any	O
more	O
:	O
They	O
went	O
away	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
eight	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
the	O
eight	O
shillings	O
?	O
Linstead	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Jonas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
whole	O
twelvemonth	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sober	O
and	O
industrious	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
any	O
opportunity	O
of	O
wronging	O
you	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
by	O
herself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
130.	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
likewise	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
East	B-pers
India	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
Sep.	O
14	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
husband	O
to	O
the	O
East	O
India	O
Company	O
.	O
In	O
August	O
last	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
tea	O
landed	O
from	O
Holland	O
by	O
licences	O
from	O
the	O
Treasury	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
one	O
Roberts	O
a	O
carman	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
East	O
India	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
Roberts	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
injuries	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
tea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
charged	O
with	O
?	O
Day	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
tea	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
at	O
Botolph	O
wharf	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
tea	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chests	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
He	O
drives	O
a	O
cart	O
very	O
often	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
drive	O
any	O
cart	O
with	O
tea	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
chests	O
were	O
generally	O
pretty	O
much	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tea	O
run	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
often	O
broke	O
when	O
they	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
carts	O
by	O
rubbing	O
against	O
the	O
ships	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
occasioned	O
the	O
tea	O
to	O
run	O
out	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Because	O
the	O
corners	O
of	O
the	O
chests	O
were	O
broke	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
tea	O
out	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
tea	O
out	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
by	O
making	O
little	O
holes	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
chests	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
shook	O
the	O
tea	O
out	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
or	O
into	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
away	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
As	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
well	O
carry	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
A	O
pound	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
sometimes	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
August	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chests	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
in	O
a	O
cart	O
to	O
load	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
August	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
some	O
several	O
times	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
tea	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
He	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
sold	O
one	O
parcel	O
to	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Animan	I-pers
for	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
this	O
tea	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
East	O
India	O
Company	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
this	O
tea	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Some	O
into	O
Lime-street	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
ticket-man	O
Robert	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Mascall	I-pers
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
carmen	O
had	O
committed	O
a	O
fault	O
in	O
striking	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
taken	O
out	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Roberts	O
came	O
and	O
surrendered	O
himself	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
thinking	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
tea	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
East	O
India	O
Company	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Day	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
were	O
concerned	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
absconded	O
himself	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
tackle	O
porters	O
alehouse	O
:	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
shake	O
the	O
chests	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
tea	O
into	O
their	O
bosom	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
growing	O
evil	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
necessary	O
to	O
endeavour	O
to	O
prevent	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
made	O
their	O
brags	O
that	O
they	O
have	O
got	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
shillings	O
a	O
day	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
quantity	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
some	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Animan	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ticket	O
writer	O
to	O
the	O
East	O
India	O
Company	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
down	O
what	O
they	O
take	O
into	O
their	O
carts	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
they	O
receive	O
for	O
cartage	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
any	O
teas	O
being	O
lost	O
.	O
Sutton	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
ships	O
were	O
unloaded	O
in	O
August	O
?	O
Sutton	O
.	O
The	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
and	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
any	O
tea	O
?	O
Sutton	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
the	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
any	O
tea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
?	O
Sutton	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
sometimes	O
a	O
scuffle	O
hunter	O
,	O
sometimes	O
one	O
thing	O
,	O
sometimes	O
another	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
work	O
for	O
any	O
particular	O
person	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
131.	O
George	B-pers
Skarrett	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
31	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Broome	I-pers
,	O
January	O
26	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Broome	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
mug	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
detected	O
presently	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty-sixth	O
instant	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
that	O
George	B-pers
Skarrett	I-pers
was	O
just	O
gone	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
mug	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
silver	O
,	O
so	O
drunk	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
stand	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
entry	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
mug	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
to	O
do	O
something	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
fault	O
but	O
a	O
bruise	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
hit	O
it	O
against	O
something	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
Castle	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Broome	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Castle	B-place
at	I-place
Cow-Cross	I-place
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
identical	O
mug	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Broome	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
mug	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
(	O
Constable	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
mug	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
called	O
for	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hit	O
it	O
against	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
bruise	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
run	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
and	O
bruised	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
or	O
pewter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
mug	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Pris	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
132.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
coral	O
with	O
eight	O
silver	O
bells	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
coral	O
necklace	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
locket	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
thirtieth	O
of	O
January	O
my	O
chimney	O
was	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
help	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
time	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
coral	O
and	O
necklace	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
:	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
necklace	O
and	O
locket	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
yours	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
fetched	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
so	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
mother	O
the	O
coral	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
for	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
and	O
nine	O
pence	O
.	O
She	O
paid	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
necklace	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Sanders	O
pawned	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
one	O
at	O
Greenbank	O
for	O
fifteen	O
pence	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
delivered	O
me	O
the	O
coral	O
necklace	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sanders	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
occasion	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
these	O
goods	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
thirtieth	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
chimney	O
was	O
on	O
fire	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
mother	O
the	O
coral	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
coral	O
hang	O
up	O
at	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
's	O
in	O
West-Smithfield	O
with	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
gentleman	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
comely	O
lusty	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
a	O
child	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
that	O
the	O
child	O
might	O
not	O
lie	O
above	O
ground	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
the	O
silver-smith	O
here	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
fetch	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
silver-smith	O
for	O
the	O
coral	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
market	O
price	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
(	O
she	O
is	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
a	O
few	O
doors	O
off	O
;	O
)	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
necklace	O
and	O
locket	O
pawned	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Paine	O
's	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
coral	O
and	O
necklace	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
fault	O
more	O
than	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
Court	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
would	O
be	O
merciful	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
Court	O
will	O
not	O
hurt	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
that	O
ever	O
she	O
committed	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
133.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Rumbow	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Paddington	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hendey	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
28	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
this	O
coat	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hendey	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
upon	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hendey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
two	O
nights	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
dispatched	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
I	O
missed	O
linen	O
and	O
this	O
coat	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
this	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
would	O
content	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
carry	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hendey	O
happened	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
coat	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
on	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
coat	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
18	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
bargain	O
was	O
made	O
for	O
11	O
s.	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
French	O
Horn	O
in	O
Holborn	O
who	O
sitted	O
the	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Hendey	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
any	O
satisfaction	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
man	O
out	O
in	O
ten	O
days	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
prison	O
my	O
name	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
newspapers	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Hendey	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
rheumatism	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
not	O
being	O
there	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
134	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Corp	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
January	O
27	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Corp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
people	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
shoplifter	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hang	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hang	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
laws	O
might	O
hang	O
her	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
took	O
the	O
cotton	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
merciful	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
purple	O
and	O
white	O
cotton	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
liked	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
pointed	O
to	O
this	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
more	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
remnant	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
to	O
call	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
instead	O
of	O
waiting	O
for	O
my	O
mistress	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
hanging	O
down	O
behind	O
under	O
her	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
mistress	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
goods	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
heard	O
my	O
mistress	O
a	O
coming	O
,	O
she	O
let	O
the	O
cotton	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
cotton	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
the	O
cotton	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Pray	O
miss	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
step	O
one	O
step	O
from	O
the	O
counter	O
?	O
Ryley	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Corp	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
cotton	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Corp	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
when	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
called	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cotton	O
lie	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
cotton	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
lady	O
who	O
allows	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
income	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cook	O
gave	O
me	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
cotton	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
short	O
gown	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ryley	I-pers
for	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
cotton	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
some	O
cottons	O
off	O
the	O
shelf	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
fit	O
of	O
coughing	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
pulling	O
and	O
hauling	O
of	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
wits	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
rope	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
rope	O
should	O
be	O
my	O
executioner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
135.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pounds	O
eight	O
ounces	O
of	O
Turkey	O
raw	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sharrer	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
19	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Alderson	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
William	B-pers
Alderson	I-pers
(	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
,	O
son	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
hope	O
is	O
alive	O
)	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
He	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
very	O
good	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
supposed	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
throwster	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
weaver	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
any	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
drink	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
liquor	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
work	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
surprize	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
work	O
all	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
before	O
Justice	O
Tall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
these	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Alderson	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
them	O
?	O
Alderson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
headborough	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shewed	O
him	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Alderson	O
.	O
Are	O
these	O
the	O
bobbins	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Alderson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sharrer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
throwster	O
.	O
I	O
employ	O
about	O
three	O
hundred	O
people	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty-fourth	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Tall	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
examination	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
four	O
ounces	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kent	O
,	O
at	O
St.	O
Agnes	O
le	O
Clear	O
:	O
Kent	O
absconded	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
headborough	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
information	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
,	O
otherwise	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
bobbins	O
,	O
we	O
mark	O
all	O
our	O
bobbins	O
with	O
this	O
mark	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
136.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Audrey	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Pepper	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Fortman	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
27	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fortman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
Justice	O
Broadhead	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
you	O
have	O
your	O
spoon	O
again	O
(	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
spoon	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
fairly	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Princes-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Hanover-Square	I-place
,	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Fortman	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
rung	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
four	O
bunches	O
of	O
sallary	O
upon	O
her	O
head	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
lusty	O
fat	O
gentleman	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
six	O
pence	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
stay	O
till	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
:	O
She	O
desired	O
a	O
little	O
small	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
spoon	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
China	O
plate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
Because	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
but	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
spoon	O
till	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
drawn	O
the	O
beer	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
spoon	O
till	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
spoon	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
and	O
then	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
would	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
four	O
bunches	O
of	O
sallary	O
upon	O
her	O
head	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
And	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
.	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wyrett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
sallary	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
told	O
you	O
this	O
?	O
Wyrett	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
brandy	O
shop	O
in	O
Tyburn-Road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
spoon	O
sold	O
there	O
?	O
Wyrett	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
by	O
Holborn-Bars	O
for	O
ten	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
spoon	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
fairly	O
.	O
Fortman	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
for	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
finding	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
returned	O
it	O
again	O
without	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
indeed	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
spoon	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
street	O
by	O
Grosvenor-Square	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
137	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
hyson	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
6l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
Feb.	O
22	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gifford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
missed	O
this	O
tea	O
last	O
Monday	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
compting-house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
large	O
canisters	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
or	O
both	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Gifford	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
at	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
my	O
man	O
was	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
lock	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
neglected	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
tells	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
cellar	O
about	O
three	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
that	O
tea	O
:	O
She	O
confessed	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
tea	O
before	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
that	O
my	O
servant	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
accused	O
my	O
servant	O
of	O
carrying	O
tea	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
there	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
half	O
pound	O
canisters	O
produced	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Gifford	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
tea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Gifford	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
washed	O
for	O
me	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
lived	O
t	O
here	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
hard	O
thing	O
upon	O
a	O
young	O
beginner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
fifteenth	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
to	O
wash	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
lock	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
heavy	O
with	O
sleep	O
,	O
I	O
neglected	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
going	O
in	O
there	O
till	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
taking	O
it	O
?	O
How	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
lie	O
near	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
How	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Jury	O
(	O
to	O
Gifford	O
)	O
How	O
far	O
did	O
these	O
canisters	O
stand	O
off	O
his	O
bed	O
?	O
Gifford	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
off	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sleep	O
a	O
person	O
might	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Trovell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
headborough	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
tea	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Gifford	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
tea	O
:	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Gifford	O
's	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
How	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
:	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
son	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
India	O
gave	O
her	O
one	O
canister	O
of	O
tea	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
tea	O
I	O
bought	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
son	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
canister	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
John	B-pers
How	I-pers
at	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fright	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
staymaker	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
last	O
two	O
years	O
?	O
Parsons	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
not	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
since	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Levidge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fourteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
laid	O
to	O
her	O
charge	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
chaired	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
?	O
Levidge	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
138.	O
Edward	B-pers
Bredway	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Woodfall	I-pers
,	O
January	O
27	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Woodfall	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
just	O
by	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
make	O
a	O
motion	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
papers	O
and	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
in	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
missed	O
:	O
I	O
walked	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Corbet	O
's	O
Lottery-Office	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
pushed	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
?	O
Woodfall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Maylin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
Mr.	O
Woodfall	O
pushed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
shuffle	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
somebody	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
throw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Maylin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
139.	O
Ann	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
Cripplegate	I-place
,	I-place
London	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thompson	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
,	O
January	O
9	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
this	O
linen	O
to	O
Catherine	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
to	O
wash	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Stanton	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
kinswoman	O
of	O
hers	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
linen	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Packer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
all	O
this	O
shirt	O
was	O
pawned	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
all	O
that	O
is	O
found	O
:	O
she	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Packer	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
some	O
were	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
sold	O
.	O
Thompson	B-pers
Packer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
this	O
shirt	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Olliman	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
an	O
apron	O
and	O
a	O
laced	O
cap	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
lawn	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
140.	O
James	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
in	O
Tower-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
for	O
thirteen	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
dishonesty	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
marked	O
ten	O
shillings	O
with	O
a	O
cross	O
with	O
a	O
penknife	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
nose	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
of	O
those	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
are	O
three	O
of	O
those	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
because	O
of	O
the	O
marks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
mark	O
them	O
?	O
Keys	O
.	O
The	O
fourth	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
of	O
those	O
shillings	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
shillings	O
among	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
side	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
that	O
money	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Holbert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
till	O
twice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
sugar	O
hogshead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
Mr.	O
Key	O
's	O
servant	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
there	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
hogshead	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
hogshead	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
to	O
watch	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
watch	O
for	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
any	O
particular	O
person	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
this	O
hogshead	O
stand	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
Just	O
before	O
the	O
till	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
any	O
candle	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
this	O
money	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
till	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hogshead	O
twice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
time	O
you	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
hogshead	O
to	O
watch	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
was	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
does	O
not	O
agree	O
.	O
Keys	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
twice	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
there	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
From	O
seven	O
till	O
ten	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
till	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
Twice	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
money	O
both	O
times	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Keys	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
pull	O
his	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pulled	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
marked	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
Some	O
were	O
marked	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
were	O
not	O
marked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
mark	O
?	O
Holbert	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
mark	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
marked	O
.	O
Keys	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
persons	O
more	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
them	O
here	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
son	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
his	O
behaviour	O
been	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
That	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
lad	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
his	O
relations	O
will	O
say	O
so	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
High	O
Wycomb	O
,	O
signed	O
by	O
the	O
Mayor	O
and	O
Aldermen	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
allowed	O
to	O
be	O
evidence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
141.	O
Ann	B-pers
Calabar	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Alhallows	B-place
Barking	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
January	O
20	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
on	O
the	O
twentieth	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wine	O
merchant	O
in	O
Mincing-Lane	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
ours	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
's	O
a	O
silversmith	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
's	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
Because	O
Ann	O
Milner	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
February	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Mussell	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
clothes	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
spoon	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
Because	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
crest	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
produced	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
spoon	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
upon	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
spoon	O
she	O
gave	O
you	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
her	O
?	O
Milner	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
you	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
?	O
Milner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
stopped	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
did	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
acted	O
like	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
honour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
immediately	O
where	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
Milner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
Mr.	O
Stephens	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
this	O
Ann	B-pers
Calabar	I-pers
?	O
Milner	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
her	O
again	O
?	O
Milner	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
spoon	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
spoon	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
clothes	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
's	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
Ann	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
my	O
son	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
Milner	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
spoon	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
son	O
seeing	O
a	O
crest	O
on	O
the	O
spoon	O
called	O
me	O
(	O
he	O
had	O
weighed	O
it	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
gave	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
:	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
girl	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
imposed	O
upon	O
,	O
it	O
weighs	O
but	O
two	O
ounces	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
at	O
six	O
shillings	O
an	O
ounce	O
,	O
comes	O
but	O
to	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
her	O
righted	O
:	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Somerset	O
Street	O
[	O
by	O
Whitechappel-bars	O
]	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
tugged	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
sleeve	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
This	O
spoon	O
is	O
not	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
's	O
who	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
told	O
me	O
such	O
a	O
falsity	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
neighbour	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
taken	O
out	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
it	O
)	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
name	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
enquired	O
what	O
the	O
person	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
Calabar	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
christian	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
must	O
look	O
after	O
Mrs.	O
Calaber	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
own	O
security	O
and	O
character	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
Milner	O
's	O
mother	O
went	O
to	O
inform	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
.	O
My	O
daughter	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
,	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
Ann	O
Calabar	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Blakesley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
friends	O
these	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
honest	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
did	O
any	O
harm	O
in	O
her	O
life	O
.	O
Her	O
friends	O
live	O
at	O
Mile	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
helps	O
her	O
mother	O
to	O
wash.	O
Elizabeth	O
Stephenson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
seventeen	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
she	O
has	O
nobody	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
142.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
19.	O
Ann	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
washer-woman	O
;	O
I	O
directed	O
her	O
to	O
one	O
.	O
This	O
linnen	O
was	O
ready	O
ironed	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
whipped	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
these	O
shirts	O
?	O
Griffith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
neckcloths	O
:	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
a	O
presser	O
in	O
Coleman-Street	B-place
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
drop	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
to	O
her	O
heels	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
made	O
me	O
suspect	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
thief	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
six	O
shirts	O
and	O
three	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
which	O
she	O
dropped	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Griffith	O
swore	O
to	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Charity	B-pers
Nutting	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	O
Ball	O
said	O
that	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
dropped	O
something	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
six	O
shirts	O
and	O
three	O
neckcloths	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
owned	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
linnen	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
143	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Finchley	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
(	O
her	O
servant	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
beating	O
and	O
striking	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
back	O
,	O
belly	O
,	O
breasts	O
and	O
sides	O
,	O
and	O
thereby	O
giving	O
her	O
several	O
mortal	O
wounds	O
and	O
bruises	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
languished	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
25th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
to	O
the	O
22d	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
mortal	O
wounds	O
and	O
bruises	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
Indictment	O
further	O
faith	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
being	O
void	O
of	O
all	O
christian	O
charity	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
1st	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
continually	O
afterwards	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
22d	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
allow	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
(	O
an	O
infant	O
of	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
sixteen	O
years	O
)	O
sufficient	O
victuals	O
,	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
necessaries	O
,	O
to	O
preserve	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
,	O
