TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
22d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Ladbroke	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1748	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Sixpence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
ROBERT	B-pers
LADBROKE	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BURNET	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
FOSTER	O
,	O
JOHN	O
STRACEY	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Scarr	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
Caleb	B-pers
Toulman	I-pers
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Ilive	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Bonner	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
.	O
Newton	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Egremon	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Waugh	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Tipp	I-pers
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Merriweather	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Deschamps	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
Willian	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Boozshire	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Harrop	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Moran	I-pers
.	O
316	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lodge	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
ward	O
of	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
,	O
London	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
forty	O
yards	O
of	O
broad	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
Those	O
Trials	O
with	O
this	O
mark	O
+	O
shew	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
Capital	O
Offences	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
Sentence	O
of	O
Death	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
Jury	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
Indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Skelton	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
with	O
relation	O
to	O
this	O
charge	O
?	O
Skelton	O
.	O
The	O
beginning	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
piece	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
broad	O
cloth	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lodge	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
of	O
yards	O
were	O
there	O
?	O
Skelton	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
quantities	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
twenty-five	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
about	O
eighteen	O
yards	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
cloth	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
cloth	O
?	O
Skelton	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
stole	O
it	O
?	O
Skelton	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
farther	O
than	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
stealing	O
this	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
cloth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
?	O
Skelton	O
.	O
No	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
cloth	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
?	O
Skelton	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
superfine	O
cloth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
this	O
cloth	O
again	O
?	O
Skelton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sent	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cam	O
's	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Lodge	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
work	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
worked	O
there	O
since	O
this	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
taking	O
in	O
of	O
that	O
cloth	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lodge	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
cloth	O
[	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
]	O
On	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
these	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lodge	O
's	O
,	O
safe	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
these	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Lodge	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
work	O
there	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
worked	O
there	O
for	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
months	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lodge	O
's	O
again	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
concerning	O
the	O
cloth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
gate	O
there	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
gate	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
lock	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bolt	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
staple	O
four	O
inches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
this	O
warehouse	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
Little	O
St.	O
Hellen	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
it	O
join	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
They	O
join	O
wall	O
to	O
wall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
passage	O
,	O
or	O
communication	O
,	O
between	O
this	O
place	O
and	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
None	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
going	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
.	O
The	O
house	O
and	O
warehouse	O
is	O
all	O
within	O
the	O
gate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Lodge	O
's	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
for	O
to	O
receive	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
this	O
warehouse	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
any	O
door	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
is	O
there	O
no	O
way	O
of	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
into	O
this	O
warehouse	O
,	O
without	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
cloth	O
was	O
found	O
again	O
?	O
White	O
.	O
Only	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cam	O
's	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
sixteenth	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
something	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
wrapper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
post	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
an	O
inn	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
inn	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Catharine-Street	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
wrapper	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
dark	O
coloured	O
cloth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
wrapper	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
cloth	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
the	O
cloth	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
table	O
below	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
lighted	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
occasion	O
had	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
candle	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
Because	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
inn	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Your	O
servant	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
sixteenth	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
seeing	O
that	O
young	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
into	O
my	O
aunt	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
something	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
was	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
bring	O
?	O
was	O
it	O
a	O
portmanteau	O
?	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
like	O
a	O
portmanteau	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
portmanteau	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
cloth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
cloth	O
?	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
leave	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
away	O
?	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
My	O
uncle	O
sent	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
upon	O
seeing	O
an	O
advertisement	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
uncle	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
it	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
sent	O
home	O
?	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
The	O
Saturday	O
following	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
?	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
cloth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
come	O
to	O
demand	O
it	O
?	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
before	O
,	O
or	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
?	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
your	O
uncle	O
say	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
angry	O
at	O
my	O
taking	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
tea	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Longbottom	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Longbottom	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
your	O
house	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
?	O
Longbottom	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
or	O
nineteenth	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
they	O
come	O
?	O
Longbottom	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
about	O
cloth	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
about	O
this	O
cloth	O
to	O
Scot	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
believed	O
the	O
cloth	O
was	O
damned	O
,	O
but	O
sooner	O
than	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
owner	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
said	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
?	O
Longbottom	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
another	O
person	O
said	O
so	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
send	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Scot	O
's	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
advertise	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
Longbottom	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Scot	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
presently	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
advised	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Scot	O
's	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
would	O
blow	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
to	O
Scot	O
's	O
?	O
Longbottom	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Scot	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
return	O
again	O
?	O
Longbottom	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
stay	O
?	O
Longbottom	O
.	O
About	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
woman	O
stay	O
?	O
Longbottom	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
staid	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
?	O
Longbottom	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
offer	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
could	O
be	O
done	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
conversation	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
him	O
?	O
Longbottom	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
tell	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
money	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
cloth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
cloth	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Longbottom	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
superfine	O
cloth	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
White	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
work	O
upon	O
that	O
account	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
it	O
very	O
nearly	O
concern	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
sufferer	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Longbottom	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
clear	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
uncle	O
's	O
name	O
Scot	O
?	O
Goldsmith	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
demand	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
asleep	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
several	O
times	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
one	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
a	O
cloak	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
threatened	O
my	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
her	O
eye	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
cane	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
cloth	O
was	O
worth	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
very	O
good	O
sense	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
keep	O
it	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
it	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
advertised	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
advertised	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
ordered	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
no	O
money	O
taken	O
for	O
the	O
carrying	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
cloth	O
?	O
Scot	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
angry	O
with	O
my	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
for	O
taking	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
upon	O
that	O
account	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
317.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Portore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
bever	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
five	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
towel	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Bridget	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
A	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Honnor	B-pers
Obrian	I-pers
;	O
and	O
four	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
a	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
aunt	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
hand	O
at	O
washing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
set	O
in	O
scorn	O
by	O
her	O
friends	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
a	O
sweetheart	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
or	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
she	O
lay	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
maid	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
some	O
victuals	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
talked	O
to	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
very	O
simpathizing	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
a	O
fault	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
my	O
maid	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
maid	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
an	O
impediment	O
in	O
her	O
speech	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
in	O
a	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
take	O
of	O
yours	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
my	O
new	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
do	O
this	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
with	O
your	O
good	O
order	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
are	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Noakes	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
hands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
very	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
up	O
so	O
soon	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
enquired	O
after	O
the	O
chairwoman	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
maid	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Temple-Mews	B-place
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
coach-yard	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
maid	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
bear	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
?	O
And	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
left	O
quite	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
At	O
a	O
publick-house	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Noakes	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
.	O
Honner	O
Obrian	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Murphy	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Obrian	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
them	O
?	O
Obrian	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
my	O
gown	O
and	O
stays	O
on	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
whether	O
Mrs.	O
Obrian	O
did	O
not	O
lend	O
me	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Obrian	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
gown	O
and	O
stays	O
on	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lend	O
her	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Noakes	I-pers
.	O
A	O
woman	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
bundle	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
into	O
St.	O
Thomas's-Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Broadhead	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Murphy	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
318	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Sepulchre	B-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
monies	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
June	O
22	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
do	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
In	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
stables	O
at	O
the	O
Swan-Inn	B-place
at	O
Holborn-Bridge	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
canvas	O
purse	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
asleep	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
manger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
hours	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
any	O
company	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
horses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
coachman	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
in	O
Barnet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
punctually	O
say	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
particular	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
your	O
money	O
again	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
is	O
gone	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
by	O
when	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
a	O
helper	O
to	O
the	O
hostlers	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
civility	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
true	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
kneel	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
warder	O
in	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
Parish	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
before	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
promise	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
confession	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
offer	O
made	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fulbrook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
for	O
taking	O
the	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
things	O
easy	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
said	O
so	O
?	O
Fulbrook	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
say	O
so	O
?	O
Fulbrook	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
signed	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
could	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
returned	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
again	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Bickerton	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
affair	O
?	O
Bickerton	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
sixteen	O
or	O
seventeen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
first	O
upon	O
liking	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Bickerton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
turner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
differed	O
about	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
brass	O
turner	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
he	O
serve	O
his	O
time	O
out	O
?	O
Bickerton	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
?	O
Bickerton	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
justly	O
,	O
is	O
may	O
be	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
he	O
done	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
since	O
?	O
Bickerton	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
time	O
a	O
year	O
last	O
September	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
319	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Levally	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
,	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Exchange	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
June	O
25	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty-fifth	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Swithin's-Alley	B-place
,	O
about	O
four	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
alarm	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Moxum	O
,	O
that	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Slade	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
accomplice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
it	O
appear	O
?	O
did	O
it	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Slade	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
,	O
not	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
from	O
other	O
people	O
.	O
Slade	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Moxum	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Moxum	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hamlin	O
's	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
in	O
Swithin-Alley	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
conveyed	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
then	O
?	O
Moxum	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
boy	O
close	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Moxum	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
,	O
before	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
320.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
June	O
13	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
thirteenth	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
Poultry	B-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Bodker	O
came	O
running	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Old	O
Jury	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
man	O
pick	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Bodker	O
had	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
person	O
ever	O
took	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Bodker	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
follow	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
?	O
Bodker	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Goodwin	O
's	O
pocket	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
?	O
Bodker	O
.	O
He	O
run	O
under	O
the	O
coaches	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
not	O
thinking	O
to	O
be	O
pursued	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
Little	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
to	O
an	O
uncle	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
fellowship-porter	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
wrong	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
brought	O
here	O
for	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
witnesses	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
here	O
till	O
to-morrow	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
321.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ethelburg	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
pestel	O
and	O
mortar	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
a	O
tin	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Vernon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
duty	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Ethelburg	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
a	O
constable	O
?	O
Vernon	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
what	O
parish	O
?	O
Vernon	B-pers
Of	I-pers
St.	O
Martin	O
Outwich	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
breaking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
celler	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
celler	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
celler	O
?	O
Vernon	O
.	O
The	O
celler	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Ethelburg	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
between	O
his	O
shirt	O
and	O
his	O
skin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
things	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Vernon	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
sorts	O
of	O
things	O
.	O
[	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
saucepan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
kitchen	O
furniture	O
produced	O
.	O
]	O
Margaret	B-pers
Harman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
matron	O
of	O
the	O
workhouse	O
of	O
St.	O
Ethelburg	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
upon	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
workhouse	O
of	O
St.	O
Ethelburg	O
.	O
Harman	O
.	O
They	O
do	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
workhouse	O
;	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
between	O
his	O
shirt	O
and	O
his	O
skin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
saucepan	O
found	O
between	O
his	O
shirt	O
and	O
his	O
skin	O
?	O
Harman	O
.	O
The	O
saucepan	O
he	O
had	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
celler	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
warning-pan	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
celler	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Harman	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
passed	O
in	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
a	O
door	O
and	O
a	O
holt	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
killed	O
me	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
at	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
appeared	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
since	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
had	O
some	O
signs	O
of	O
deliriousness	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
like	O
a	O
crazy	O
man	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
to	O
Harman	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
deliriousness	O
?	O
Harman	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
but	O
one	O
day	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
322	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Haymour	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
Shoe	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
house	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
missed	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
chest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
Upwards	O
of	O
seven	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
Upwards	O
of	O
forty	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
chest	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
Because	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
chest	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
June	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
lodged	O
with	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
taken	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
make	O
any	O
confession	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shape	O
of	O
a	O
chissel	O
,	O
made	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
nail	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
and	O
married	O
her	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
forty	O
shillings	O
taken	O
away	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
Queen	O
Anne	O
's	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
upwards	O
of	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
silver	O
left	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
gold	O
left	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
more	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
moidores	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
these	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
quartern	O
pot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
?	O
Lacey	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
your	O
servant	O
?	O
Gray	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
month	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
Man	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Gray	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
broke	O
the	O
chest	O
open	O
,	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
and	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thrift	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
attempted	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Casson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
attempt	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
man	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
Felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
323	O
.	O
+	O
Joseph	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
June	O
25	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
Sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
?	O
Watts	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
tankard	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
kitchen	O
on	O
Saturday	O
was	O
sev'nnight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Watts	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Castle	B-place
,	O
just	O
by	O
Great-Moorgate	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
tankard	O
worth	O
?	O
Watts	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
valued	O
it	O
at	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
11	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
last	O
September	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Watts	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
lid	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
to	O
Watts	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
lid	O
yours	O
?	O
Watts	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
solder	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
lid	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
that	O
lid	O
?	O
Watts	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Scriven	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
you	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
was	O
sev'nnight	O
?	O
Watts	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Gibbon	O
Scriven	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
see	O
that	O
lid	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
hear	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
claims	O
it	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Scriven	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
was	O
sev'nnight	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
mistres	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
noon	O
or	O
night	O
?	O
Scriven	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
night	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
your	O
mistress	O
?	O
Scriven	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Harvey	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pretty	O
many	O
customers	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
a	O
question	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
bought	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
unless	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
this	O
lid	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
ten	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
make	O
words	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
advertise	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
doubt	O
but	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
an	O
owner	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
an	O
d	O
place	O
of	O
abode	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
return	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
owned	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
's	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
his	O
tankard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
right	O
place	O
of	O
his	O
abode	O
?	O
Scriven	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
pretty	O
near	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
silversmith	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
he	O
sold	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Scriven	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lid	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
by	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
by	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rylance	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Rylance	O
.	O
I	O
draw	O
beer	O
for	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
at	O
Moorgate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
draw	O
any	O
in	O
this	O
tankard	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
night	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
?	O
Rylance	O
.	O
I	O
drew	O
two	O
tankards	O
for	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
in	O
this	O
tankard	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
missing	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Rylance	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
lid	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
shewing	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hands	O
loose	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
fields	O
were	O
these	O
?	O
Rylance	O
.	O
Islington-Fields	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
ditches	O
upon	O
a	O
dunghill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
own	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
Rylance	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
never	O
own	O
what	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
kicked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
they	O
promised	O
me	O
money	O
,	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
them	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
accept	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
poor	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pretended	O
to	O
tell	O
them	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
this	O
tankard	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
?	O
Wilks	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
Wilks	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
might	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
be	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
sold	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Wilks	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
eleven	O
pounds	O
seven	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
us	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
so	O
.	O
Wilks	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
tell	O
us	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
further	O
yet	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
may	O
go	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
you	O
please	O
.	O
Wilks	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
go	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
yet	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
backside	O
of	O
Islington	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
one	O
place	O
,	O
then	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
tried	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Justice	O
?	O
Wilks	O
.	O
Justice	O
Hole	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
letter	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
White	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
yesterday	O
,	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
can	O
call	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
master	O
of	O
my	O
business	O
nineteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
a	O
Judge	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sometimes	O
mad	O
and	O
lunatick	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Reuben	O
Harding	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
this	O
affair	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
deemed	O
a	O
lunatick	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
he	O
deemed	O
so	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
year	O
1745	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
served	O
the	O
office	O
of	O
churchwarden	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
Parish	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
then	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
confined	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
mad-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
lunatick	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
stole	O
this	O
tankard	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
that	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
they	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
abroad	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
him	O
so	O
then	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
better	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
confined	O
again	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
confined	O
in	O
Bethlem	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
informed	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
before	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fearnly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
served	O
me	O
with	O
pipes	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
pipemaker	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
Senses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Fearnly	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
last	O
June	O
?	O
Fearnly	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
table	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
look	O
wild	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
that	O
ago	O
?	O
Fearnly	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
fortnight	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Rylance	I-pers
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
drew	O
the	O
beer	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
?	O
Rylance	O
.	O
An	O
please	O
you	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
well	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
called	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
on	O
this	O
affair	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
accused	O
with	O
wronging	O
any	O
person	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
Rylance	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
tankard	O
at	O
Aldersgate	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
324	O
.	O
+	O
Catharine	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
mantua	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
shop	O
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
that	O
gentlewoman	O
stole	O
thirty	O
yards	O
of	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
silk	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
found	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
Tucker's-Alley	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
mother	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
one	O
Catharine	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
gave	O
that	O
silk	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
again	O
.	O
Grace	O
Baxter	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
's	O
mother	O
;	O
she	O
keeps	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
the	O
silk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
pretence	O
did	O
she	O
come	O
under	O
?	O
Baxter	O
.	O
No	O
pretence	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
silk	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
paper	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
frightened	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
wits	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
she	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
a	O
baker	O
's	O
cellar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
the	O
cellar	O
?	O
Baxter	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
this	O
girl	O
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
fight	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
Baxter	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
looking	O
about	O
Mrs.	O
Cox	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
in	O
Cranbourn-Alley	B-place
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
child	O
a	O
half-penny	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
from	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
silk	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
a	O
baker	O
's	O
cellar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
to	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
fever	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
in	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
's	O
nursery	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Hospital	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
six	O
weeks	O
there	O
under	O
the	O
physicians	O
hands	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
that	O
day	O
to	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
this	O
street	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
white	O
cloak	O
on	O
,	O
slipped	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Baxter	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
slap	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
why	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
another	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
325	O
.	O
+	O
326	O
+	O
327	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Fergus	B-pers
Crone	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
July	O
2	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
struck	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Crone	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haymaker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Crone	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
by	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
Collins	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
take	O
all	O
you	O
had	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
strip	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
so	O
to	O
them	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
clothes	O
,	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
my	O
breeches	O
and	O
stockings	O
,	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
they	O
threw	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
murder	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
threw	O
you	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
pitch	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
,	O
for	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
money	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
justly	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
all	O
but	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
slippers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
overtake	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
three	O
men	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
overtook	O
Frost	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
my	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pitied	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
helped	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
those	O
two	O
men	O
again	O
,	O
Collins	O
and	O
Crone	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Frost	O
afterwards	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White-Swan	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Frost	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
concern	O
himself	O
in	O
any	O
one	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Rouchead	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
night	O
last	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
came	O
into	O
the	O
White-Swan	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
scuffle	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Frost	O
and	O
Hudson	O
fighting	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
(	O
Hudson	O
is	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
Frost	O
into	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
Hudson	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Frost	O
:	O
Now	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
shift	O
for	O
yourself	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
impeach	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
never	O
touched	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
Hudson	O
his	O
clothes	O
on	O
?	O
Rouchead	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
shoes	O
or	O
stockings	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Frost	O
say	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
never	O
touched	O
him	O
?	O
Rouchead	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
one	O
was	O
Fergus	B-pers
Crone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
William	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
set	O
their	O
names	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
Frost	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
?	O
Rouchead	O
.	O
Not	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Frost	O
before	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Justice	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
guard-room	O
with	O
Hudson	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Hudson	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
shake	O
hands	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
see	O
Collins	O
,	O
and	O
shook	O
hands	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Hudson	O
shook	O
hands	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
upon	O
duty	O
then	O
?	O
Rouchead	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Frost	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
upon	O
duty	O
,	O
and	O
Crone	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
guard-room	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
:	O
The	O
colonel	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
affronted	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
guard	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
deliver	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
guard	O
was	O
relieved	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Rouchead	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
frivolous	O
excuses	O
,	O
and	O
Hudson	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
skittle-ground	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
play	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
Kilburn-Turnpike	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Did	O
Justice	O
Poulson	O
admit	O
Frost	O
as	O
an	O
evidence	O
?	O
Rouchead	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
admitted	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
evidence	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
Frost	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
touched	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
Frost	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Justice	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
spoke	O
sooner	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Collins	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
help	O
you	O
to	O
money	O
for	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
sixpence	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
afterwards	O
he	O
was	O
stripped	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
fight	O
my	O
comrade	O
,	O
Crone	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stripped	O
himself	O
stark	O
naked	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
thought	O
you	O
had	O
inlisted	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
sixpence	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
world	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
stripping	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
fight	O
with	O
my	O
comrade	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
pull	O
his	O
clothes	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
took	O
his	O
clothes	O
away	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
clothes	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Crone	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
challenged	O
to	O
fight	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
fight	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Frost	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
haymaking	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
fork	O
in	O
pawn	O
for	O
a	O
penny	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
stark	O
naked	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
challenged	O
me	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
paymaster-sergeant	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
that	O
Collins	O
and	O
Crone	O
belong	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
men	O
have	O
behaved	O
better	O
than	O
they	O
have	O
done	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
Matthews	O
.	O
Never	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
always	O
men	O
that	O
came	O
as	O
clean	O
to	O
their	O
duty	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
my	O
colonel	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
is	O
abroad	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
here	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
the	O
same	O
character	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hannibel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
paymaster-sergeant	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
that	O
Frost	O
belongs	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
incomparably	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
?	O
Hannibel	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
upon	O
duty	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hanover	I-pers
.	O
Frost	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
first	O
entered	O
for	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
.	O
Frost	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Jury	O
desired	O
that	O
John	O
Hudson	O
might	O
be	O
called	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
they	O
might	O
ask	O
him	O
the	O
following	O
questions	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
to	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
playing	O
with	O
these	O
people	O
at	O
skittles	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
games	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
call	O
one	O
another	O
by	O
their	O
names	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
comrade	O
,	O
and	O
comrade	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
drink	O
after	O
you	O
played	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
every	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
a	O
penny	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
pitchfork	O
for	O
the	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
talk	O
of	O
putting	O
sixpence	O
into	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
such	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
wish	O
God	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
judge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
inlisting	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
as	O
God	O
is	O
my	O
judge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
if	O
you	O
paid	O
a	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
your	O
pitchfork	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
That	O
shilling	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
my	O
lodging	O
and	O
washing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
you	O
receive	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
twopence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
paid	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
it	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
owing	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
those	O
breeches	O
,	O
which	O
Rouchead	O
says	O
you	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
was	O
stripped	O
of	O
all	O
your	O
clothes	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Jones	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
along	O
with	O
Frost	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
that	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Frost	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Jury	O
found	O
Collins	O
and	O
Crone	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
328.	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Collings	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1731	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Ann	O
,	O
Black-Friars	O
,	O
did	O
marry	O
Alice	B-pers
Vintyman	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
afterwards	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1748	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Botolph	I-place
,	I-place
Bishopgate	I-place
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
,	O
and	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
marry	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
wife	O
take	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
his	O
said	O
wife	O
,	O
Alice	O
being	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
full	O
life	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
Statute	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
Council	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
council	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
,	O
the	O
poor	O
unfortunate	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
married	O
him	O
,	O
thinking	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
sole	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
living	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Charter-House	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
body	O
can	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
Charter-House	O
without	O
being	O
single	O
*	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
proof	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
married	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
turned	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
afterwards	O
got	O
into	O
company	O
with	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
thought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
consented	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
call	O
our	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
second	O
marriages	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
we	O
do	O
,	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
you	O
will	O
find	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
guilty	O
;	O
for	O
this	O
is	O
gross	O
adultery	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
person	O
must	O
make	O
an	O
affidavit	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
single	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
can	O
be	O
admitted	O
.	O
Rev	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Grainger	O
,	O
rector	O
of	O
Black-Friars	O
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
marriage	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Vintyman	I-pers
?	O
Grainger	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
the	O
register	O
here	O
?	O
Grainger	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
register	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
]	O
This	O
is	O
seventeen	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1721	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Vintyman	I-pers
were	O
married	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
entered	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Vintyman	I-pers
,	O
of	O
All-Saints	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
widow	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Collins	O
?	O
Hayward	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
seventeen	O
years	O
ago	O
?	O
Hayward	O
.	O
About	O
seventeen	O
years	O
ago	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
married	O
Alice	O
Vintyman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
freedom	O
,	O
by	O
marrying	O
a	O
foreigner	O
;	O
she	O
kept	O
a	O
publick-house	O
in	O
All-Hallows	O
,	O
Thames-Street	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
lived	O
in	O
Distaff-Lane	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
live	O
together	O
as	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
?	O
Hayward	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
owned	O
him	O
as	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Collins	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Collins	O
's	O
owning	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
wife	O
?	O
Hayward	O
.	O
Her	O
son	O
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Vintyman	I-pers
,	O
died	O
in	O
Collins	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Distaff-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
buried	O
the	O
deceased	O
person	O
from	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
general	O
report	O
of	O
people	O
.	O
Hayward	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
son	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
displeased	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
Mrs.	O
Collins	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Vintyman	O
?	O
Hayward	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
these	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
Alice	B-pers
Vintyman	I-pers
?	O
Warner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
lived	O
over	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
being	O
married	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
passed	O
as	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
behave	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
?	O
Warner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
acknowledged	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
wife	O
?	O
Warner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
my	O
books	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Warner	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Trigg-Stairs	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
knew	O
this	O
Vintyman	O
;	O
when	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
last	O
?	O
Warner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
well	O
then	O
?	O
Warner	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
plain	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
lost	O
her	O
freedom	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
fifty	O
witnesses	O
were	O
called	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
only	O
losing	O
time	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
six	O
weeks	O
yesterday	O
)	O
at	O
St.	O
Botolph	O
,	O
Bishopsgate	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
discover	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
My	O
maid-servant	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
married	O
by	O
a	O
clergyman	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
you	O
married	O
by	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Warren	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
council	O
produced	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
into	O
Court	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
upon	O
that	O
letter	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
seen	O
this	O
before	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
own	O
daughter	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
his	O
own	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
his	O
own	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
swear	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
not	O
directed	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
question	O
whether	O
they	O
can	O
read	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Watkins	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
letter	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
as	O
follows	O
.	O
]	O
''	O
My	O
dearest	O
wife	O
,	O
``	O
As	O
I	O
always	O
shall	O
term	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
``	O
is	O
,	O
by	O
agreement	O
,	O
to	O
me	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
than	O
one	O
that	O
``	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
;	O
and	O
might	O
I	O
have	O
10,000	O
l.	O
shall	O
``	O
never	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
being	O
more	O
than	O
divorced	O
``	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
Almighty	O
;	O
and	O
``	O
therefore	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
the	O
vile	O
character	O
``	O
that	O
miscreant	O
may	O
have	O
given	O
you	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
``	O
I	O
shall	O
ever	O
remain	O
your	O
sincere	O
friend	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
``	O
I	O
would	O
wrong	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
your	O
children	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
``	O
penny	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
first	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
burn	O
,	O
having	O
nothing	O
more	O
at	O
heart	O
,	O
of	O
``	O
all	O
worldly	O
things	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
secure	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
``	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
ever	O
be	O
devoted	O
to	O
your	O
``	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
``	O
Your	O
most	O
affectionate	O
husband	O
,	O
``	O
whilst	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
``	O
JOHN	B-pers
COLLINGS	I-pers
.	O
''	O
26	O
June	O
,	O
1743	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Watkins	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
discovered	O
this	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
against	O
the	O
laws	O
of	O
the	O
land	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
against	O
the	O
law	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
come	O
and	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
after	O
marriage	O
,	O
as	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mrs.	O
Watkins	O
?	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
married	O
to	O
Collings	O
?	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
church	O
?	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
At	O
St.	O
Botolph	O
,	O
Bishopsgate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
put	O
this	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
married	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
marry	O
her	O
soon	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
me	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
sixteen	O
years	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
marriage	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
people	O
are	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
dallied	O
with	O
for	O
ever	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
329.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Skarrett	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Skarrett	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
ribband	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
Ferrit	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Maria	B-pers
Burgland	I-pers
,	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
Burgland	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clowder	I-pers
being	O
bound	O
in	O
recognizances	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
against	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
ordered	O
their	O
recognizances	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
330	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Garland	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
Martyr	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
July	O
3	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
maid	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
afterwards	O
I	O
heard	O
another	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
these	O
shoes	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
ladder	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
there	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
repairing	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
worked	O
for	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
does	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
worked	O
there	O
ever	O
since	O
Easter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
shut	O
at	O
night	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
left	O
open	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
beat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
houses	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
into	O
is	O
let	O
to	O
two	O
gentlewomen	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
myself	O
,	O
in	O
Fisher's-Street	O
,	O
Red-lion-Square	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
maid-servants	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
kitchen	O
,	O
lying	O
upon	O
two	O
chairs	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drunk	O
that	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
plumber	O
's	O
men	O
was	O
as	O
drunk	O
as	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
ladies	O
live	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
rightly	O
tell	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
331	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
,	I-place
Limehouse	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
value	O
forty-two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooker	I-pers
,	O
June	O
18	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
girl	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
of	O
two	O
guineas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Hewitt	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
before	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Brooker	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
custody	O
were	O
these	O
two	O
guineas	O
?	O
Hewitt	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brooker	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
my	O
brother	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
this	O
money	O
?	O
Brooker	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
locked	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
?	O
Brooker	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
,	O
to	O
play	O
with	O
the	O
children	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
victuals	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
this	O
?	O
Brooker	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
as	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
pulled	O
the	O
drawers	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
.	O
[	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
grandmother	O
,	O
was	O
asked	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
age	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
under	O
or	O
over	O
fourteen	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
away	O
.	O
]	O
Hewitt	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
prosecuted	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
friends	O
threatened	O
to	O
prosecute	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
332	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
peruke	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
April	O
18	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Ratcliff	B-place
Highway	I-place
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
much	O
ado	O
to	O
recover	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
Some	O
time	O
last	O
April	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
Leach	O
's	O
house	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
served	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
presently	O
afterwards	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
this	O
gentleman	O
a	O
drive	O
at	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
snatched	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
off	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
Chambers-Street	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
years	O
.	O
Bridgman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
was	O
served	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Jury	O
to	O
Bridgman	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
gin-shop	O
?	O
Bridgman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
house	O
near	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
run	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
run	O
in	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
stood	O
upon	O
my	O
legs	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
lost	O
that	O
.	O
Jury	O
.	O
Is	O
Mary	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
a	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Matthews	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
as	O
a	O
voluntary	O
evidence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lives	O
?	O
Matthews	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
Back-Lane	O
,	O
Ratcliff-Highway	O
,	O
by	O
Chamber's-Street	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
where	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Tennant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
nursed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
it	O
was	O
reported	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
frying	O
liver	O
and	O
bacon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Tennant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
neither	O
read	O
nor	O
write	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
afterwards	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
lay	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
the	O
room	O
he	O
lies	O
in	O
from	O
the	O
room	O
you	O
lay	O
in	O
?	O
Tennant	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
close	O
together	O
;	O
one	O
is	O
a	O
fore	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
possible	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
?	O
Tennant	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
sleep	O
so	O
heavy	O
as	O
that	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Stannett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
these	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Eyres	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
rope-yard	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
ropemaker	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
sometimes	O
at	O
jobbing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
?	O
Webb	O
.	O
Middling	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
333.	O
Peter	B-pers
Herba	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
nine	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ironmonger	I-pers
;	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
334.	O
Henry	B-pers
Grafton	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Taylor	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
June	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
335.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tolly	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Bride	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
hose	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broomwich	I-pers
,	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Broomwich	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
leather-gilder	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
till	O
this	O
thing	O
happened	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Several	O
people	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
336.	O
Phebe	B-pers
Hayne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Sepulchre	B-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
two	O
petticoats	O
,	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
dimitty	O
,	O
a	O
commonprayer	O
book	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Gunn	I-pers
,	O
June	O
15	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
nursed	O
Mrs.	O
Gunn	O
in	O
a	O
miscarriage	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
these	O
things	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
337.	O
William	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
brass	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
June	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
workman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
ingenious	O
boy	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
begged	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
338.	O
William	B-pers
Clarenbolt	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Thomas	B-pers
Milward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
feloniously	O
demanding	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
Tho	B-pers
Milward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
taking	O
leave	O
of	O
some	O
captains	O
at	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
sugar	O
houses	O
,	O
by	O
Well-Close-Square	B-place
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
suspicious	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
in	O
the	O
highway	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
have	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
to	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
much	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
watch	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Neptune-Street	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
watchmen	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
want	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
just	O
by	O
a	O
warehouse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
rent	O
of	O
Alderman	O
Parsons	O
,	O
we	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
in	O
Well	O
Close-Square	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
Twenty	O
years	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
been	O
evidence	O
in	O
any	O
cause	O
in	O
which	O
you	O
was	O
concerned	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
I	O
owe	O
no	O
body	O
any	O
ill	O
will	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
whether	O
he	O
has	O
,	O
or	O
has	O
not	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
may	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
run	O
back	O
towards	O
you	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
watch	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
a	O
ropemaker	O
hanged	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
hang	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
only	O
charged	O
him	O
wit	O
h	O
an	O
assault	O
.	O
Pros	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
weapon	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
demand	O
your	O
money	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
like	O
lightening	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stopped	O
to	O
tie	O
her	O
garter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
shall	O
I	O
tie	O
it	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Milward	O
called	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
rogue	O
,	O
have	O
I	O
got	O
you	O
?	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
shall	O
I	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
abused	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
assaulted	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
(	O
a	O
watchman	O
)	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
watch	O
called	O
in	O
Neptune-Street	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Milward	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
women	O
to	O
charge	O
us	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Milward	O
charged	O
us	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
He	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
assault	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
call	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Milward	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
(	O
a	O
watchman	O
)	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Milward	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
have	O
charged	O
us	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Milward	O
was	O
running	O
after	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Watch	O
!	O
Watch	O
!	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
need	O
not	O
call	O
watch	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
will	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
directly	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
(	O
the	O
constable	O
)	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Milward	O
charged	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
threatening	O
to	O
blow	O
out	O
his	O
brains	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
pistol	O
about	O
him	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
none	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
women	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
women	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
here	O
standing	O
,	O
before	O
God	O
and	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
though	O
these	O
two	O
rogues	O
of	O
watchmen	O
swear	O
so	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
And	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
desire	O
any	O
women	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Milward	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Milward	O
's	O
spite	O
will	O
appear	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Touchfield	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Milward	O
?	O
Touchfield	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Touchfield	O
.	O
Nothing	O
.	O
Pris	O
Coun	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Touchfield	O
.	O
Nothing	O
bad	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Does	O
he	O
bear	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
and	O
industrious	O
man	O
?	O
Touchfield	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
tricking	O
in	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
follows	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
does	O
as	O
other	O
men	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Eyres	O
(	O
a	O
ropemaker	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
ropemaker	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
employ	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
spleen	O
in	O
the	O
case	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
his	O
son	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
has	O
drove	O
him	O
away	O
from	O
his	O
work	O
by	O
a	O
press-gang	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
send	O
him	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
this	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
spite	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
served	O
me	O
seven	O
years	O
honestly	O
and	O
truly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Stannard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
twenty-seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Coun	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
a	O
bad	O
thing	O
?	O
Stannard	O
.	O
No	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
would	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
339.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
340.	O
Francis	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
jacket	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
quadrant	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
341	O
.	O
342	O
.	O
343.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
lawn	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Sands	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
June	O
17	O
.	O
Eleanor	O
Sands	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
whose	O
house	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
owned	O
all	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
.	O
The	O
buckles	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
the	O
ring	O
upon	O
my	O
finger	O
,	O
the	O
cap	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
apron	O
was	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
done	O
?	O
Sands	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
;	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
publick-house	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
.	O
Pris	O
.	O
Hutchinson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
night-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
this	O
done	O
in	O
?	O
Sands	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
there	O
to	O
drink	O
?	O
Sands	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
pass	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
went	O
there	O
?	O
Sands	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
disordered	O
in	O
liquor	O
then	O
?	O
Sands	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
as	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
;	O
and	O
these	O
good	O
women	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
property	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
walked	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
they	O
quarrelled	O
about	O
sharing	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
thing	O
was	O
discovered	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
Peg	O
took	O
the	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Jane	O
sold	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
ring	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Sands	O
owns	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
ring	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
melt	O
to	O
eighteen-pence	O
.	O
Sands	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
ring	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
ring	O
you	O
had	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
Welch	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Sands	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
silver	O
buckles	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
Susannah	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
was	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
three	O
halfpence	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Sands	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
buckles	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Steele	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Jane	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
to	O
sell	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Steele	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
only	O
as	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
her	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Eleanor	O
Sands	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
that	O
night	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
by	O
herself	O
,	O
because	O
no	O
other	O
persons	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
for	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
people	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
then	O
?	O
Welch	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
Eleanor	O
Sands	O
?	O
Welch	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
acquainted	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Eleanor	O
Sands	O
complain	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
awaked	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Welch	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
awaked	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cap	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
in	O
my	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
days	O
afterwards	O
they	O
quarrelled	O
about	O
dividing	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
then	O
?	O
Welch	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
This	O
little	O
girl	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
,	O
came	O
and	O
discovered	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
gold	O
ring	O
off	O
her	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
brass	O
one	O
on	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
they	O
got	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
apron	O
was	O
sold	O
in	O
Westminster	O
for	O
fifteen	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cap	O
upon	O
Sutherland	O
's	O
head	O
.	O
Sands	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
mark	O
that	O
was	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Hutchinson	O
also	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
keep	O
Morris	O
out	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
she	O
got	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
five	O
pence	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
all	O
along	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lavers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
regulator	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
walking	O
through	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Hutchinson	I-pers
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
Margaret	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
was	O
going	O
to	O
swear	O
her	O
life	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
confessed	O
the	O
robbery	O
that	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Morris	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Hutchinson	O
and	O
Sutherland	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
344.	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
a	O
stew-pan	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
345	O
,	O
346.	O
Honner	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Fling	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Garrick	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
June	O
16	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
347.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carne	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
precinct	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Catherine	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Clas	B-pers
Fanaltena	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
June	O
11	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
