TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
and	O
TUESDAY	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
23d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pennant	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
1749	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Public	O
may	O
be	O
assured	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
during	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PINNANT	I-pers
,	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
)	O
the	O
Sessions	O
Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
Four-pence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
Sessions	O
shall	O
be	O
carefully	O
compriz	O
'd	O
in	O
One	O
such	O
Four-penny	O
Book	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
farther	O
Burthes	O
on	O
the	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PENNANT	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DENNISON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ABNEY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLIVE	I-pers
,	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Green	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Woodyere	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holbrook	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Lake	O
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tony	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Kitcher	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Curson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pyke	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hayne	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Vuljam	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Proffer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pow	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Benbrick	I-pers
.	O
1.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Merryman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
Dwelling	O
House	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
Occupation	O
of	O
the	O
Lady	O
Frances	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
.	O
Oct.	O
16	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
16	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hambleton	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
next	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Glasses	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Hambleton	O
's	O
Servant	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
fall	O
in	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
hard	O
by	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
the	O
lead	O
fall	O
by	O
the	O
Wind	O
blowing	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Waters	O
.	O
The	O
lead	O
was	O
rolled	O
up	O
close	O
together	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
laid	O
down	O
but	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
the	O
place	O
had	O
been	O
stripped	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
in	O
six	O
weeks	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
high	O
is	O
this	O
House	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
But	O
two	O
story	O
high	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hambleton	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Waters	O
might	O
see	O
him	O
from	O
below	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
my	O
Candle	O
:	O
he	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
had	O
cut	O
up	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
masters	O
lead	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
carried	O
away	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
easy	O
to	O
get	O
from	O
one	O
House	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
here	O
,	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hardy	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
old	O
house	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
yard	O
where	O
the	O
lead	O
fell	O
,	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
kitchen	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
concealed	O
under	O
an	O
old	O
dresser	O
,	O
on	O
seeing	O
his	O
legs	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
.	O
Deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
a	O
little	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
in	O
this	O
old	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
fast	O
asleep	O
when	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
Hardy	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
a	O
wall	O
of	O
four	O
foot	O
high	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
that	O
place	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Mahone	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
twezer	O
case	O
,	O
one	O
knife	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
handle	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
fork	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
spoon	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
bodkin	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
chain	O
,	O
laid	O
at	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Diana	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Delaware	O
,	O
Sept.	O
18	O
Josiah	B-pers
Dugdel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
painter	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	O
Delaware	O
's	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
,	O
in	O
Grovesnor	B-place
Square	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Robertson	O
's	O
a	O
silver	O
smith	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
eldest	O
son	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
his	O
Lordship	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
could	O
take	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
letter	O
being	O
answered	O
,	O
it	O
proved	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
lordship	O
's	O
daughter	O
's	O
lady	O
Diana	O
West	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
letter	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
agreed	O
with	O
the	O
particulars	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Robertson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
Michaelmas	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
exactly	O
tell	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
brought	O
this	O
twezer	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
the	O
fork	O
,	O
spoon	O
,	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
bodkin	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
gold	O
chain	O
to	O
my	O
man	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
then	O
melted	O
down	O
with	O
other	O
gold	O
for	O
use	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
found	O
this	O
twezer	O
in	O
Hide-Park	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
lord	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Lord	O
Delaware	O
.	O
This	O
said	O
twezer	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
my	O
late	O
Wife	O
,	O
after	O
whose	O
death	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
youngest	O
daughter	O
,	O
who	O
constantly	O
wore	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
:	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Graston	O
's	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
another	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Dogdel	O
,	O
giving	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
fashioned	O
golden	O
twezer	O
stopped	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Robertson	O
,	O
offered	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
employed	O
in	O
painting	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
twezer	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
imagined	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
this	O
same	O
twezer	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
daughter	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
dressing	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cabinet	O
locked	O
:	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dogdel	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
;	O
describing	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
gold	O
fork	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
very	O
seldom	O
put	O
into	O
twezers	O
now	O
a-days	O
,	O
a	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
swivel	O
was	O
torn	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
she	O
wore	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
twezer	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
reading	O
my	O
letter	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
satisfied	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
daughters	O
twezer	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Pray	O
my	O
Lord	O
Delaware	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
far	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
be	O
transported	O
Lord	O
Delaware	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
objection	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3.	O
James	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
Henry	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
.	O
)	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Piercer	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
;	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
number	O
'd	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
against	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
peace	O
,	O
crown	O
and	O
dignity	O
,	O
September	O
26	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Piercer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kentish	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
curate	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
St.	O
Pancrass	O
to	O
Kentish	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
duty	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Piercer	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
General	O
Fleming	B-pers
's	O
regiment	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
in	O
Brabant	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
,	O
how	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Piercer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
Field	O
in	O
the	O
foot	O
path	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
cutlass	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
sword	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
habit	O
?	O
Piercer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
:	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
they	O
proceeded	O
to	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
hands	O
in	O
my	O
two	O
pockets	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
an	O
india	O
silk	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
linnen	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
exact	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
and	O
received	O
money	O
that	O
day	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
old	O
coin	O
,	O
silver	O
and	O
copper	O
;	O
two	O
Roman	O
coins	O
,	O
an	O
Edward	O
's	O
sixpence	O
,	O
an	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
a	O
Jacobus	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
wash-leather	O
gloves	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
quite	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saved	O
my	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
them	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
confessed	O
all	O
the	O
particulars	O
before	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
justice	O
Manwaring	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
writing	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
almost	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
both	O
soldiers	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
third	O
regiment	O
of	O
Guards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
before	O
this	O
robbery	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
Yes	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
Audheagon	O
in	O
Brabant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
happened	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
at	O
Pancrass	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
We	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
face	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
we	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Aldridge	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
and	O
my	O
self	O
:	O
Henry	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
is	O
not	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
did	O
you	O
stop	O
him	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
between	O
Pancrass	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
Kentish	O
Town	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
us	O
had	O
sticks	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
a	O
sword	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
sticks	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
Green	O
sticks	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hedge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
his	O
silver	O
buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Alridge	I-pers
took	O
his	O
money	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
currant	O
coin	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
old	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
sold	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
a	O
silver	O
smith	O
in	O
King-street	O
Westminster	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
Name	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
an	O
india	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
linnen	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
wash-leather	O
gloves	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
when	O
you	O
had	O
committed	O
this	O
robbery	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
strait	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
sold	O
the	O
old	O
money	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
my	O
Lord	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
buckles	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
They	O
we	O
pawned	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
Long	O
Ditch	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
pieces	O
of	O
old	O
coin	O
were	O
there	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
tell	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
piece	O
of	O
brass	O
with	O
a	O
Turks	O
head	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
together	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
We	O
divided	O
it	O
amongst	O
us	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
this	O
Barret	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
4.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Good	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
Robert	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckle	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkercheief	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
foreign	O
gold	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
ten	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
Oct.	O
15	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
late	O
in	O
receiving	O
money	O
behind	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
towards	O
morning	O
before	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
thinking	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
safe	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
swords	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
knee	O
buckle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
which	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
26	O
l.	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
but	O
4	O
d.	O
1/2	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
confession	O
of	O
himself	O
and	O
Harrison	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
first	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
first	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
Good	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
advertised	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
maker	O
Anthony	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
who	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
justice	O
Mainwaring	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
read	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
sign	O
it	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
get	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
No	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
where	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
silver	O
and	O
gold	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
much	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Good	I-pers
took	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
knee	O
buckle	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
36	O
s.	O
Pieces	O
,	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Holborn	O
to	O
a	O
night	O
house	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
that	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Harrison	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
on	O
monday	O
night	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
night	O
house	O
somewhere	O
near	O
the	O
mansion	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
the	O
robbery	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ember	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
New	O
Crane	O
about	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
soldiers	O
at	O
this	O
Ship	O
alehouse	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Harrison	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
Good	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
quarter	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cleghorne	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
soldiers	O
which	O
he	O
suspected	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
quarrelling	O
about	O
dividing	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
watch	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
quiet	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Cleghorne	O
I	O
'd	O
call	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
quarrelled	O
about	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
called	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
landlord	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
765	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
of	O
your	O
watch	O
you	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Ember	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
Justice	O
Manwaring	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
related	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
reason	O
in	O
life	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
advising	O
me	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
advertise	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Harrison	O
not	O
being	O
there	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
no	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
Harrison	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
he	O
wants	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
comes	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
may	O
be	O
admitted	O
for	O
ought	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
Harrison	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
such	O
words	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
some	O
hot	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
hot	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
drinking	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
Harrison	O
was	O
?	O
we	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
where	O
Harrison	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
secur	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Justice	O
Manwaring	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
about	O
20	O
robberies	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Cleghorne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
near	O
Ratcliff-Cross	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
billited	O
on	O
me	O
about	O
twenty	O
days	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
church	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
four	O
more	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
been	O
constant	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
o'nights	O
?	O
Cleghorne	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
then	O
been	O
out	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
upon	O
duty	O
;	O
these	O
soldiers	O
had	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
bowl	O
of	O
punch	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
,	O
fearing	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
are	O
you	O
afraid	O
of	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
come	O
give	O
me	O
change	O
for	O
this	O
moidore	O
?	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
no	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
;	O
from	O
this	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
robbing	O
somebody	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
constable	O
directly	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
a	O
little	O
quiet	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
let	O
them	O
drink	O
on	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
see	O
more	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
flip	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
servant	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Harrison	O
give	O
Good	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
gold	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
renew	O
the	O
discourse	O
about	O
the	O
thing	O
again	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
before	O
:	O
Harrison	O
said	O
to	O
Good	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
thing	O
I	O
'll	O
draw	O
my	O
sword	O
upon	O
you	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
either	O
give	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
or	O
the	O
thing	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
thing	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
words	O
said	O
Harrison	O
,	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
your	O
delivering	O
the	O
man	O
the	O
watch	O
or	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
Harrison	O
gave	O
him	O
half-a-crown	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
o'clock	O
is	O
it	O
by	O
yours	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
it	O
is	O
down	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
wind	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
as	O
before-mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
it	O
to	O
Harrison	O
again	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
fearing	O
I	O
should	O
mistake	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
set	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
;	O
Harrison	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
constable	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watchmaker	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
inform	O
me	O
who	O
bought	O
that	O
watch	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
proposed	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Manwaring	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
admit	O
me	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
I	O
impeached	O
Aldridge	O
,	O
Harrison	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hickson	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
5.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hickson	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Good	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
2	O
d	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Elick	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
half-pence	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Oct.	O
8	O
.	O
Elick	O
Bull	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
upon	O
Blackheath	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
miller	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	B-place
the	I-place
fields	I-place
near	I-place
Bow-common	I-place
Oct.	O
8.	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
from	O
Bromley	O
to	O
Limehouse	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
three	O
soldiers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
We	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
we	O
?	O
Bull	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Belsham	I-pers
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Bull	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
confest	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
the	O
court	O
how	O
you	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
?	O
Bull	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
both	O
he	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Good	I-pers
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
sold	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
in	O
Shoemaker-Row	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
schoolmaster	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
him	O
Rabby	O
,	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
15	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Belsham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
Elick	O
Bull	O
and	O
I	O
.	O
They	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
dressed	O
in	O
soldier	O
's	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
arm	O
'd	O
?	O
Belsham	O
.	O
With	O
long	O
swords	O
;	O
they	O
put	O
their	O
hands	O
to	O
our	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
our	O
watches	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
?	O
Belsham	O
.	O
Light	O
enough	O
to	O
discern	O
their	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
them	O
rob	O
us	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
eight	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Sunday	O
,	O
since	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
near	O
Bow	O
Common	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
there	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
We	O
stopp	O
'd	O
these	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
to	O
Elick	O
Bull	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
watch	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
and	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Good	I-pers
he	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
watch	O
that	O
Good	O
took	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
;	O
we	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
watch	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
together	O
that	O
night	O
through	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Shoemaker-Row	O
,	O
the	O
Black-Boy	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
taken	O
from	O
Elick	O
Bull	O
,	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
oad	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
share	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
about	O
18	O
s.	O
each	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
6.	O
William	B-pers
Meadall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
3	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
taking	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
and	O
cannisters	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
pound	O
of	O
hyson	O
tea	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
hand	O
bell	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Timothy	O
,	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
spurs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Totenham	B-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
White-Hart	O
inn	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
till	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Oct	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
2	O
and	O
4	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
fast	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
always	O
do	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
o'clock	O
my	O
maids	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
the	O
glass	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
fashioned	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
doors	O
were	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
loose	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
a	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
3	O
cannisters	O
,	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
tea	O
in	O
a	O
cannister	O
,	O
one	O
napkin	O
,	O
a	O
velvet	O
pillareen	O
,	O
a	O
hand-bell	O
,	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
some	O
papers	O
,	O
notes	O
of	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
spurs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
these	O
things	O
before	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
hand-bell	O
behind	O
the	O
bar	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
wore	O
my	O
hat	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
bell	O
and	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
intelligence	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Maiden-Lane	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
we	O
asked	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
about	O
nine	O
pocket-books	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bell	O
was	O
hid	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
hat	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
inform	O
'd	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
pawn	O
things	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jennings	O
,	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
lining	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
All	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
lost	O
was	O
valued	O
at	O
about	O
3	O
l.	O
exclusive	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
spurs	O
and	O
hat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
taking	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
Maiden-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
pocket-books	O
and	O
hand-bell	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
them	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
landlady	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
sometimes	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
gold	O
lac	O
'd	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
in	O
a	O
mean	O
dress	O
,	O
crying	O
hot	O
pyes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
pack	O
of	O
cards	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
's	O
bills	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
confirm	O
'd	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
may	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
has	O
ever	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
several	O
robberies	O
committed	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
since	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Maiden-Lane	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
fifteen	O
times	O
,	O
bringing	O
things	O
and	O
fetching	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
gold	O
laced	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
ruffles	O
?	O
Jennings	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
hare	O
dresser	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
hat	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
has	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
that	O
hat	O
?	O
Walker	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
when	O
new	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
gold	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
you	O
have	O
it	O
now	O
in	O
your	O
possession	O
.	O
Jennings	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
right	O
gold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
right	O
gold	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
tinsel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
him	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
6	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Field	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
tin	O
cannister	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
one	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
tablecloth	O
,	O
one	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Three	B-place
jolly	I-place
Butchers	I-place
at	I-place
Newington	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
this	O
pocket-book	O
and	O
some	O
notes	O
of	O
hand	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
apartment	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
goal	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
charge	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
breaking	O
and	O
robbing	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
asleep	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Pitcher	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
taking	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
bohea	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Pitcher	I-pers
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Pitcher	I-pers
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
hat	O
and	O
this	O
wig	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
pocket-books	O
there	O
.	O
Neither	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
found	O
were	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
therefore	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
7.	O
Earret	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
Dec.	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Stewards	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
thence	O
one	O
pistol	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
pistol	O
mounted	O
with	O
brass	O
,	O
2	O
hangers	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
hilted	O
sword	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
brussels	O
head	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
velvet	O
cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
7	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
cream-pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Adam	B-pers
Stewards	I-pers
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Stewards	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	B-place
Holborn	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Ship	I-place
and	I-place
Sheers	I-place
;	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'clock	O
to	O
sup	O
with	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
again	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
11	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
flew	O
in	O
a	O
hundred	O
pieces	O
,	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
for	O
the	O
lodgers	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
entry	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
opening	O
into	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
double	O
locked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
goods	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
Stewards	O
.	O
Some	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
coats	O
and	O
a	O
laced	O
waistcoat	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
glass	O
case	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
mounted	O
pistol	O
,	O
2	O
silver	O
mounted	O
hangers	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
mounted	O
sword	O
,	O
these	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
shelf	O
where	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
fustians	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
one	O
piece	O
measured	O
20	O
yards	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
24	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
,	O
shirts	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
number	O
,	O
one	O
brussels	O
head	O
,	O
lappets	O
,	O
caul	O
and	O
ruffles	O
,	O
one	O
velvet	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
scarlet	O
cloak	O
not	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
7	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
cream	O
pot	O
.	O
In	O
July	O
,	O
some	O
people	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
confessing	O
what	O
robbery	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
,	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
accomplice	O
in	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Clark	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
justice	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
confession	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
person	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
the	O
next	O
witness	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
pistols	O
are	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
since	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hughs	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
Supple	O
and	O
Mackey	O
in	O
Surry	O
,	O
who	O
on	O
searching	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
at	O
Dicks	O
shore	O
,	O
where	O
Moll	O
Blare	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
he	O
of	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
Picking	O
of	O
pockets	O
and	O
house-breaking	O
,	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
Drury-Lane	O
on	O
purpose	O
of	O
lift	O
up	O
latches	O
and	O
sash-windows	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
steal	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
With	O
this	O
intent	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
towards	O
Holborn	O
,	O
a	O
pretty	O
way	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
the	O
evening	O
sneak	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
open	O
'd	O
a	O
street	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
Garret	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
went	O
in	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
watch	O
word	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
door	O
to	O
an	O
inward	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
the	O
lock	O
fly	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
lik	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
broke	O
the	O
partition	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
upo	O
n	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
higher	O
up	O
,	O
Carter	O
lifted	O
up	O
a	O
latch	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
Garret	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
passed	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
watch	O
word	O
;	O
Lawler	O
presently	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
no	O
light	O
,	O
nor	O
heard	O
any	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
a	O
door	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
passage	O
that	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
shoulder	O
and	O
hands	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
forc	O
'd	O
the	O
pannel	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
a	O
hole	O
through	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
9	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
advertisement	O
in	O
the	O
news	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
made	O
the	O
pannel	O
fly	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
listened	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
one	O
heard	O
us	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
stood	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
upon	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
shut	O
too	O
the	O
outward	O
door	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Carter	O
went	O
in	O
through	O
the	O
hole	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
they	O
drew	O
away	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
splinters	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
through	O
the	O
hole	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
opened	O
,	O
Carter	O
goes	O
to	O
a	O
corner	O
cupboard	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
several	O
ruffles	O
,	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
men	O
's	O
shirts	O
,	O
borders	O
for	O
caps	O
,	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
stone	O
buttons	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
silver	O
stud	O
,	O
a	O
tortoiseshell	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
Says	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
see	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
sink	O
upon	O
you	O
,	O
then	O
Carter	O
was	O
fumbling	O
about	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
hand	O
it	O
through	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
handed	O
me	O
a	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tea	O
chest	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
upon	O
the	O
left-hand	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
brings	O
me	O
2	O
hangers	O
,	O
2	O
small	O
swords	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
pistols	O
.	O
one	O
had	O
either	O
a	O
dog	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
lyon	O
's	O
head	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
pistol	O
,	O
taking	O
up	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
that	O
lay	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
had	O
swore	O
too	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
3	O
pistols	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brings	O
me	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
fustian	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
velvet	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
remnant	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pattern	O
for	O
a	O
cloak	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
goes	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brings	O
me	O
6	O
men	O
's	O
coats	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
through	O
the	O
hole	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
scarlet	O
waistcoat	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
lay	O
without	O
sleeves	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hole	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
strove	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
street-door	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
being	O
fastened	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
somebody	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
trick	O
upon	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
round	O
and	O
open	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
then	O
George	O
Carter	O
came	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Jemmy	O
Field	O
's	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
nor	O
Carter	O
would	O
not	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
Lawler	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
another	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
a	O
shirt	O
too	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
drew	O
lots	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
sell	O
to	O
my	O
lot	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
first	O
choice	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
chusing	O
my	O
shirt	O
,	O
Carter	O
tries	O
on	O
the	O
gold	O
laced	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
thing	O
that	O
we	O
get	O
which	O
you	O
like	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
;	O
the	O
pistols	O
,	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
and	O
the	O
swords	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
at	O
last	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
sell	O
them	O
:	O
Margaret	B-pers
Field	I-pers
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
3	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
bid	O
us	O
4	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
go	O
try	O
elsewhere	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
5	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
cloaths	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
exclusive	O
of	O
the	O
pistols	O
.	O
Q	O
What	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
transported	O
her	O
upon	O
my	O
information	O
;	O
then	O
her	O
husband	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
2	O
pistols	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
we	O
lost	O
one	O
pistol	O
in	O
going	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
whole	O
was	O
7	O
guineas	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
divided	O
amongst	O
us	O
three	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
51	O
shillings	O
a-piece	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
odd	O
shilling	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
our	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
had	O
another	O
bottle	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
.	O
Bowen	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
discover	O
this	O
sooner	O
.	O
Bowen	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
discover	O
this	O
sooner	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
neither	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
way	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
divulge	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
make	O
myself	O
in	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoners	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Prison	O
that	O
very	O
time	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Dublin	O
about	O
five	O
months	O
ago	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
Prisoners	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
prison	O
in	O
Dublin	O
in	O
Ireland	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
fourteen	O
nights	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
that	O
Gaol	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
in	O
1748	O
.	O
Savage	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
now	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
In	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
market	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
land	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
what	O
time	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
At	O
Parkgate	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
never	O
here	O
in	O
your	O
life	O
before	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
brother	O
that	O
went	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
ne	O
prize	O
money	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
were	O
prisoners	O
together	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
Bowen	O
before	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Bowen	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
witness	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Savage	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
that	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
gaol	O
,	O
was	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
countryman	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Dublin	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
know	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
Dublin	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
find	O
you	O
out	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
give	O
your	O
testimony	O
upon	O
this	O
affair	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
neighbours	O
speaking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
men	O
brought	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Lawler	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
Dublin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Since	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
England	O
,	O
when	O
had	O
you	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Savage	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
within	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
voluntary	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
subpoena	O
'd	O
me	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
before	O
such	O
time	O
,	O
when	O
and	O
upon	O
what	O
account	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
charged	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Savage	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
acquainted	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
gaol	O
in	O
December	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
hear	O
you	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
told	O
you	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
in	O
Gaol	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
a	O
chairman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
here	O
?	O
Savage	O
.	O
No	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
over	O
with	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
Newgate	O
in	O
Dublin	O
,	O
to	O
guard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
others	O
here	O
to	O
England	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea	O
prison	O
in	O
Ireland	O
?	O
Stanley	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
Christmas	O
last	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
officer	O
who	O
arrested	O
him	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
days	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
use	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
there	O
frequently	O
after	O
.	O
Stanley	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
for	O
almost	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
arrested	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
kept	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
with	O
my	O
lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
warrant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
For	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
?	O
Stanley	O
.	O
For	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
bring	O
him	O
here	O
?	O
Stanley	O
.	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
remained	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
month	O
in	O
that	O
Prison	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
debt	O
.	O
Stanley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
did	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
About	O
what	O
time	O
was	O
he	O
discharged	O
?	O
Stanley	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
?	O
Stanley	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
140	O
yards	O
of	O
holland	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
two	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Convent	O
Garden	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
is	O
a	O
hoop-petticoat	O
maker	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
brook	O
open	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
street	O
door	O
that	O
opens	O
to	O
a	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
which	O
opens	O
into	O
that	O
passage	O
,	O
was	O
burst	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
glass	O
case	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
shop	O
facing	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
hooping	O
hollands	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
remnants	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
upwards	O
of	O
140	O
yds	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
again	O
,	O
upon	O
searching	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
at	O
Dick	O
's	O
shore	O
,	O
Limehouse	O
.	O
Mary	O
Jones	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
26	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
both	O
my	O
servants	O
,	O
much	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
myself	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
bolted	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
broad	O
bolt	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
:	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
a	O
chairman	O
that	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
your	O
shop	O
door	O
is	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
flew	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
glass	O
case	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
ransacked	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
till	O
taken	O
out	O
:	O
There	O
were	O
missing	O
9	O
pieces	O
of	O
holland	O
,	O
about	O
130	O
or	O
140	O
yards	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
remnants	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
:	O
We	O
met	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
's	O
,	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
broker	O
at	O
Dick	O
's	O
Shore	O
,	O
Limehouse	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
about	O
130	O
yards	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
induced	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stewards	O
who	O
was	O
robbed	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
hours	O
before	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
people	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
his	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
large	O
parcel	O
of	O
hoopping	O
hollands	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Bury	O
's	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
hollands	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
received	O
them	O
from	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Stewards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Jones	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
Dick	O
's	O
Shore	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
,	O
searching	O
for	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
two	O
pistols	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
these	O
other	O
goods	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
word	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
weeks	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
;	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
Jemmy	O
Fields	O
,	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
;	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Garret	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
went	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
night	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
upon	O
the	O
mill	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
house-breaking	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
George	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
were	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
We	O
all	O
three	O
agreed	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
up	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
turning	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
we	O
turned	O
down	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
or	O
next	O
door	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
brown	O
bear	O
.	O
Then	O
Garret	O
Lawler	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
latch	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
found	O
another	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
brass	O
knob	O
on	O
the	O
inward	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
Carter	O
tried	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
thrust	O
our	O
shoulders	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
lock	O
fly	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
drew	O
the	O
staple	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
flew	O
open	O
:	O
we	O
then	O
left	O
Carter	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
Lawler	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
two	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
counter	O
fronting	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
glass	O
case	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
opened	O
this	O
glass	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
pieces	O
of	O
check	O
stuff	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
it	O
holland	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
several	O
remnants	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
a	O
load	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
Jemmy	O
Fields	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
broke	O
open	O
this	O
shop	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
goods	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
where	O
we	O
all	O
laid	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
lodging	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
day	O
light	O
,	O
Field	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
over	O
haul	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
put	O
them	O
off	O
:	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
six	O
pounds	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
us	O
three	O
guineas	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
dont	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
Jones	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Limehouse	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
Field	O
and	O
Jones	O
,	O
had	O
used	O
to	O
trade	O
together	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gang	O
and	O
a	O
guard	O
of	O
us	O
used	O
to	O
use	O
the	O
Fox	O
in	O
Drury	O
lane	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
candles	O
are	O
lighted	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
meet	O
there	O
together	O
;	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
set	O
in	O
one	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
;	O
and	O
entitle	O
themselves	O
the	O
Family	O
Men	O
;	O
they	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
what	O
it	O
cost	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
they	O
swear	O
,	O
to	O
save	O
one	O
another	O
's	O
lives	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
on	O
such	O
enterprizes	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Bowen	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
Carter	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
.	O
Stanley	O
,	O
and	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
.	O
D'posed	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
latter	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
Jury	O
had	O
given	O
in	O
their	O
verdict	O
;	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
robbing	O
a	O
Person	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
8.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Humston	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
blanket	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sammuel	B-pers
Wail	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Slaymaker	I-pers
,	O
Church-wardens	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
Oct.	O
28	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Workhouse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
blanket	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9.	O
Richard	B-pers
Commins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
one	O
copper	O
pot	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
26	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Flemming	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
pint	O
pot	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
John	B-pers
Hodgskins	I-pers
.	O
Deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
Prize	O
money	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
return	O
wanting	O
some	O
small	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
that	O
pot	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
;	O
but	O
meeting	O
a	O
shipmate	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
that	O
pot	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
10.	O
William	B-pers
Bews	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Oct.	O
21	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
11.	O
Michael	B-pers
Callaghan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
quilt	O
,	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
one	O
woollen	O
cap	O
,	O
one	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
all	O
valued	O
at	O
about	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cardwell	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
23	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cardwell	I-pers
lives	O
at	O
Molson	O
's	O
Dock	O
,	O
in	O
Surry	O
;	O
and	O
Owen	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
keeps	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
to	O
whose	O
house	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
carried	O
the	O
bundle	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
laid	O
down	O
by	O
them	O
and	O
slept	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
industrious	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
an	O
unhappy	O
mad	O
man	O
when	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
done	O
when	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
case	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
12.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
carcase	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Highton	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13.	O
James	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
after	O
midnight	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
thence	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tower-street	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
:	O
between	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
a	O
person	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
some	O
body	O
had	O
broke	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
money	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
looking	O
about	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
rice	O
barrel	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
pulled	O
the	O
paniel	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
with	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
marks	O
made	O
with	O
some	O
iron	O
instrument	O
to	O
wrench	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
f	O
ound	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
half	O
pence	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
:	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawer	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
7	O
s	O
and	O
odd	O
in	O
half	O
pence	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
evidence	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sterling	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	O
Collison	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Lunas	I-pers
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14	O
George	B-pers
Cammel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckle	O
,	O
val	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
drives	O
a	O
Coach	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
dozing	O
on	O
his	O
box	O
in	O
White	B-place
Chappel	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
buckle	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shoe	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
?	O
which	O
awaked	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
who	O
drove	O
his	O
horses	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
running	O
down	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
the	O
buckle	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
fell	O
.	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15.	O
Hannah	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Hill	I-pers
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
milk	O
pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Keet	I-pers
's	I-pers
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16.	O
William	B-pers
Tidd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
James	O
Mercer	O
(	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
;	O
and	O
stole	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
three	O
copper	O
sauce	O
pans	O
,	O
two	O
wooden	O
casks	O
,	O
four	O
quarts	O
of	O
spirituous	O
liquors	O
,	O
one	O
pewter	O
crane	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Matthew	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Valentine	O
Godwin	O
,	O
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Body	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Aplen	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Aplen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
Accomplice	O
with	O
Valentine	O
Godwin	O
and	O
Johnson	O
,	O
whose	O
tryal	O
is	O
(	O
No	O
:	O
422	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Mayoralty	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Pleader	O
is	O
referred	O
17.	O
William	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18.	O
John	B-pers
Ricketts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Raymond	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19.	O
Susannah	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
to	I-pers
George	I-pers
Sackvile	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
29	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Park	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
among	O
the	O
thickest	O
of	O
the	O
trees	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
my	O
dear	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
my	O
girl	O
,	O
how	O
goes	O
trading	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
very	O
dull	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
took	O
hansel	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
penny	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
in	O
half-pence	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
willing	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
broke	O
her	O
fast	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
condition	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
dram	O
afterwards	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
agreed	O
;	O
so	O
to	O
the	O
diversion	O
we	O
went	O
-	O
afterwards	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
from	O
Rosamonds	O
pond	O
,	O
towards	O
the	O
iron	O
gate	O
,	O
into	O
Queen's-Square	O
,	O
the	O
lamp	O
gave	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
lass	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
before	O
:	O
when	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
as	O
it	O
happened	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
by	O
in	O
a	O
mean	O
dress	O
with	O
a	O
leather	O
apron	O
on	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
broad	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
gin	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
about	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
her	O
trade	O
that	O
ever	O
refused	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
suspicious	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
rob	O
me	O
;	O
feeling	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
from	O
Queen	O
's	O
Square	O
,	O
the	O
nearest	O
to	O
the	O
Globe	O
tavern	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
close	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
lamp	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
said	O
;	O
Madam	O
my	O
Watch	O
?	O
the	O
gentleman	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
secured	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
Lediard	O
,	O
in	O
Palace	O
Yard	O
;	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
told	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
but	O
you	O
might	O
loose	O
your	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
upon	O
the	O
grass	O
,	O
when	O
your	O
breeches	O
were	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
only	O
turned	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
turned	O
quite	O
down	O
,	O
my	O
job	O
was	O
so	O
streight	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
fell	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
then	O
was	O
so	O
curious	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
,	O
into	O
an	O
inward	O
room	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
my	O
breeches	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
watch	O
the	O
moment	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
sure	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
death	O
;	O
though	O
she	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
his	O
sword	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
)	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
me	O
thro	O
'	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
lie	O
down	O
for	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
bawdy-house	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
right	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
thinks	O
I	O
this	O
is	O
but	O
a	O
poor	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
but	O
a	O
penny	O
;	O
I	O
chose	O
rather	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
;	O
than	O
he	O
came	O
running	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
neck	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
had	O
many	O
a	O
watch	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
had	O
mine	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
20.	O
Christian	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Flack	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
diaper	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
diaper	O
clouts	O
,	O
val	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
towel	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
,	O
July	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21.	O
William	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Perukes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
one	O
peruke	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Morris	B-pers
Clutton	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Peruke	O
the	O
Property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
master	O
was	O
much	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
sufficiency	O
allowed	O
him	O
for	O
victuals	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
made	O
of	O
these	O
Wigs	O
,	O
was	O
laid	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
23.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king's-highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
seal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
l.	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
8	O
diamonds	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
l.	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
ar	O
,	O
one	O
peruke	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
8	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
merchant	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
Oct.	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
a	O
lady	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
servant	O
for	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Prescot	O
street	O
Goodmans	O
Fields	O
;	O
I	O
conducted	O
her	O
safe	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
discharged	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
comming	O
home	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
(	O
with	O
another	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
)	O
followed	O
me	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
street	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Sir	O
Clifford	O
Phillips	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Patrick	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
I	O
tried	O
to	O
disengage	O
my	O
self	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
dont	O
be	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
hurry	O
pray	O
,	O
and	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
collar	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
least	O
noise	O
;	O
Edward	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
had	O
the	O
hanger	O
.	O
Immediately	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
rifle	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
resistance	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
plain	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
seal	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
diamond	O
ring	O
with	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
diamonds	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
all	O
my	O
silver	O
,	O
my	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
knife	O
,	O
a	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
my	O
wig	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
Edward	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
's	O
head	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
star-light	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
a	O
lamp	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
mistaken	O
in	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
describe	O
their	O
particular	O
actions	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
Patrick	O
seems	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
cloaths	O
now	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
;	O
Edward	O
had	O
quite	O
another	O
dress	O
then	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
risling	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
their	O
hands	O
in	O
by	O
turns	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
gentleman	O
by	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
street	O
,	O
Patrick	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
Edward	O
staid	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
kept	O
fumbling	O
about	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
all	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hat	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
?	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
all	O
done	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
wig	O
again	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
wrapt	O
out	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
came	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
bidding	O
me	O
go	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
he	O
ordered	O
,	O
but	O
making	O
a	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
forwards	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Patrick	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Rion	I-pers
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Edward	O
till	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Gaol	O
,	O
Surry	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
sight	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Burne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Mackever	I-pers
,	O
who	O
took	O
Edward	B-pers
Dempsey	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
them	O
before	O
he	O
absconded	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
hide	O
himself	O
on	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
search	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
24	O
John	B-pers
Hackey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
kettle	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
15	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
is	O
a	O
brasier	O
in	O
Rotherith	O
he	O
lent	O
it	O
a	O
captain	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
to	O
do	O
some	O
business	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Ship	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
shop	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25.	O
Henry	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
Sept	O
.	O
19	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
26	O
James	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
Spanish	O
coin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
Guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dunlop	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Dunlop	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
3	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dunlop	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Thistle	B-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
,	I-place
Charing	I-place
Cross	I-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
club	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
every	O
Wednesday	O
Evening	O
,	O
of	O
tradesmen	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
's	O
Servants	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Nov.	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
having	O
money	O
borrowed	O
six	O
pence	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
altogether	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
back	O
,	O
to	O
open	O
a	O
drawer	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
silver	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
so	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
be	O
merry	O
,	O
here	O
's	O
money	O
enough	O
,	O
putting	O
back	O
his	O
elbow	O
to	O
the	O
drawers	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
late	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
David	B-pers
Bayly	I-pers
to	O
get	O
leave	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
lie	O
there	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
and	O
David	O
Bayly	O
lay	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
counting	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
brewer	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
with	O
this	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
drawer	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
upon	O
her	O
saying	O
so	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
returned	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
drawers	O
had	O
been	O
opened	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
coach	O
at	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Monmouth	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
good	O
suit	O
of	O
cloaths	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
night	O
house	O
in	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
9	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
spanish	O
dollar	O
,	O
in	O
searching	O
him	O
the	O
Spanish	O
dollar	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
beadle	O
;	O
this	O
dollar	O
was	O
put	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bill	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
cloaths	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
salesman	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
bought	O
such	O
a	O
suit	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
old	O
cloaths	O
with	O
him	O
which	O
was	O
there	O
produced	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
the	O
Watchman	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
lived	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
often	O
seen	O
tho	O
Spanish	O
Dollar	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Prosecutors	O
Property	O
.	O
David	O
bayly	O
After	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
for	O
his	O
comb	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
my	O
landlady	O
talk	O
of	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
and	O
never	O
returned	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Dunlop	O
deposed	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
David	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
did	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
till	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
very	O
late	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
for	O
his	O
comb	O
and	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
upon	O
her	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
hurried	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
also	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27.	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Michael	I-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
one	O
silk	O
purse	O
value	O
1	O
penny	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
thimble	O
and	O
eight	O
26	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
November	O
28	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
hired	O
servant	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
return	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
against	O
her	O
on	O
Nov.	O
20.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
after	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
for	O
my	O
keys	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
inward	O
room	O
,	O
standing	O
by	O
my	O
drawers	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
here	O
is	O
all	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
delivered	O
me	O
the	O
purse	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
except	O
two	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
we	O
stripped	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
dropped	O
from	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
putting	O
her	O
stomacher	O
on	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
we	O
never	O
could	O
find	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Spratt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Baflet	I-pers
,	O
all	O
depose	O
they	O
saw	O
her	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
fall	O
from	O
her	O
stomacher	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
by	O
diligent	O
search	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
from	O
thence	O
56	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
flax	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
bag	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
Person	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
602.	O
Edward	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Broad	B-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
seller	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
wrench	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
a	O
linnen	O
bag	O
,	O
with	O
upwards	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
hundred	O
of	O
flax	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Osman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
three	O
o'clock	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Edward	B-pers
Lowry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
sauce	O
pan	O
,	O
val	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30.	O
Mary	B-pers
Macdonal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
holland	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
one	O
Russia	O
table	O
cloath	O
,	O
val	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
.	O
And	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nightley	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
31	O
.	O
32.	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7.	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
6	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Guilty	O
Mary	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33.	O
Edward	B-pers
Simpkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cheshire	O
cheese	O
,	O
46	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
and	O
one	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Yerbury	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
one	O
silver	O
quart	O
tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
silver	O
pint	O
mugs	O
,	O
val	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
half-pint	O
mug	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
sauce	O
boat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
5	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
4	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
strainer	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
The	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
17	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Friday-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
boy	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
warehouse	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
except	O
one	O
pint	O
mug	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
half	O
pint	O
mug	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
my	O
boy	O
was	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Devet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fleming	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rise	O
up	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
rose	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
entry	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
must	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
he	O
walked	O
slowly	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
up	O
towards	O
the	O
Old	O
Change	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
tankard	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
missed	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
towards	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
near	O
St.	O
Paul's-Church-Yard	O
he	O
flung	O
a	O
tankard	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
stopt	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
butter-boat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
trund	O
led	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
pursued	O
and	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
brought	O
him	O
cross	O
St.	O
Paul's-Church-Yard	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
then	O
carrying	O
him	O
down	O
the	O
Old	O
Change	O
to	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
lay	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
hurt	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
rose	O
up	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
touch	O
'd	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
stab	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
stabb	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Austin	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
up	O
Little	O
Carter-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mob	O
pelted	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
dirt	O
and	O
stones	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
into	O
St.	O
Paul's-Church-Yard	O
.	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Alsop	O
a	O
Barber	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
minute	O
's	O
time	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
then	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
out	O
again	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
three	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half-pint	O
silver	O
mug	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Morris	O
.	O
Servant	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
these	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
beauset	O
that	O
day	O
at	O
2	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
James	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
a	O
pairing-shovel	O
seconded	O
the	O
blow	O
given	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alsop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
his	O
cutting	O
Mr.	O
Ashton	O
in	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
his	O
saying	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
killed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
had	O
not	O
cut	O
a	O
dozen	O
more	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ashton	O
shewed	O
the	O
wound	O
on	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
what	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
swore	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
and	O
searching	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
a	O
milliner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
home	O
with	O
some	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
near	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
exactly	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
He	O
met	O
with	O
three	O
men	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
almost	O
by	O
Walbrook-Church	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
overtook	O
me	O
again	O
almost	O
by	O
Bow-Church	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
not	O
this	O
tankard	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
paid	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
this	O
ago	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
Not	O
above	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
woman	O
swore	O
too	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
there	O
for	O
perjury	O
.	O
35.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
china	O
bowl	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Dec.	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36.	O
Paul	B-pers
Gorman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
compasses	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Macmaster	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
37	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
2d	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
John	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
case	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
90	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
corral	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
80	O
l.	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
14.	O
Paul	B-pers
Gorman	I-pers
came	O
to	O
England	O
in	O
captain	O
Hardy	O
's	O
ship	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
John	B-pers
More	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
watchman	O
with	O
the	O
case	O
of	O
corral	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
ship	O
towards	O
Ratcliff-Lane	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
against	O
Gorman	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
.	O
Gorman	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
More	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
3	O
silver	O
tankards	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
l.	O
one	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
one	O
soop	O
spoon	O
,	O
one	O
soop	O
ladle	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
7	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Highlander	I-place
by	I-place
Wapping-Dock	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
saying	O
my	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
bar	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bar	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
window	O
shutters	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
all	O
fast	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
shut	O
up	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Goldsmith's-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
papers	O
sent	O
round	O
in	O
the	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
had	O
the	O
goods	O
advertised	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
telling	O
how	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
handed	O
down	O
2	O
tankards	O
with	O
a	O
string	O
from	O
the	O
dining-room	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
another	O
tankard	O
and	O
a	O
soop	O
spoon	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
way	O
off	O
.	O
