TOKEN	NE
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
23d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1749	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Public	O
may	O
be	O
assured	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
during	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CALVERT	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
)	O
the	O
Sessions-Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
Four-pence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
Sessions	O
shall	O
be	O
carefully	O
compriz	O
'd	O
in	O
One	O
such	O
Four-penny	O
Book	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
farther	O
Burthen	O
on	O
the	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CALVERT	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
FOSTER	O
,	O
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Ravinghall	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Cyrill	B-pers
Grubbe	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Rhenolds	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bissel	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Legg	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Brinkley	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Des	I-pers
Champs	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huddle	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boozsher	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Harrap	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sandwith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Manvell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gaff	I-pers
.	O
371.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mopps	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
other	O
Persons	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
steel	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
steel-seals	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
June	O
2d	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
through	O
Cheap-side	B-place
betwixt	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
others	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
all	O
dressed	O
in	O
sailors	O
habits	O
,	O
near	O
Queen-street	B-place
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
just	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
he	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
my	O
right-side	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
catch	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
The	O
Man	O
had	O
an	O
oaken	O
stick	O
with	O
a	O
tuck	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
pointed	O
the	O
tuck	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
his	O
tuck	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
spear	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
watch-chain	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
it	O
with	O
such	O
force	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
chain	O
broke	O
at	O
the	O
swivel	O
.	O
I	O
catched	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
run	O
down	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
run	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
them	O
how	O
they	O
got	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Pancras-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Whitaker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
about	O
their	O
stopping	O
you	O
in	O
Cheap-side	O
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
minute	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
chain	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
hold	O
on	O
:	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
watch-chain	O
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
doubt	O
about	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
chain	O
from	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
372.	O
Mary	B-pers
Linck	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Clements	I-place
Dane	I-place
,	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Freeland	I-pers
.	O
June	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
373.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
upon	O
Ann	B-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
knife	O
made	O
of	O
iron	O
and	O
steel	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
right-hand	O
on	O
the	O
neck	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
,	O
did	O
give	O
a	O
mortal	O
wound	O
one	O
inch	O
long	O
and	O
half	O
an	O
inch	O
deep	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
languish	O
from	O
the	O
13th	O
till	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
stood	O
likewise	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
chairmen	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
.	O
She	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
abused	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
language	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
at	O
last	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
cease	O
this	O
noise	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
charge	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
chairmen	O
that	O
were	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
paid	O
their	O
reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
together	O
:	O
she	O
staid	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
scolding	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
house-door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
:	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
above	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
returned	O
with	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
her	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
hurt	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
blood	O
run	O
over	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
form	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
hand	O
and	O
apron	O
from	O
her	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
blood	O
fly	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
neck	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
murdered	O
your	O
wife	O
:	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
in	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
:	O
so	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
watchman	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
perceive	O
any	O
blood	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
led	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
hold	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
run	O
away	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lived	O
till	O
the	O
Sunday	O
sevennight	O
following	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
busy	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
change	O
her	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
bail	O
her	O
husband	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
chairman	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
foul-mouth	O
'd	O
woman	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dalley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
a	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
strike	O
the	O
prisoner	O
several	O
times	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
and	O
shoulders	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
very	O
good-humoured	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
's	O
time	O
with	O
her	O
hand	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
neck	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
the	O
blood	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
rogue	O
shall	O
not	O
murder	O
me	O
:	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
hand	O
from	O
her	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
blood	O
spout	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
murdered	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
hanged	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
,	O
and	O
smiled	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
glad	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
knife	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
never	O
a	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
landlord	O
take	O
the	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
bloody	O
?	O
Daliey	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
bloody	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
fresh	O
blood	O
being	O
moist	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
knife	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
my	O
reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
landlord	O
sent	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
shewed	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
a	O
common	O
sheaf-knife	O
with	O
a	O
sharp	O
point	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morgain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
watchman	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
betwixt	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
and	O
candle	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
running	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
round	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
overtake	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
must	O
die	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
die	O
in	O
good	O
company	O
:	O
she	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
as	O
yet	O
been	O
so	O
nigh	O
her	O
as	O
to	O
touch	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
for	O
there	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
give	O
the	O
wound	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Maplethorp	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
hospital	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
neck	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
dressed	O
by	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
woman	O
seemed	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
health	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
bad	O
symptoms	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
remove	O
the	O
dressings	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
dressing	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
wound	O
pretty	O
deep	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mortal	O
then	O
:	O
she	O
continued	O
seemingly	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
health	O
till	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
eat	O
the	O
common	O
diet	O
as	O
is	O
there	O
allowed	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
seized	O
suddenly	O
with	O
a	O
fit	O
,	O
was	O
never	O
sensible	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
.	O
The	O
reason	O
of	O
her	O
having	O
this	O
fit	O
I	O
apprehend	O
was	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
violent	O
passion	O
she	O
threw	O
herself	O
in	O
for	O
the	O
concern	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
being	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
shewed	O
a	O
great	O
concern	O
for	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Hospital	O
;	O
she	O
once	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
sign	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
released	O
out	O
of	O
prison	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
this	O
wound	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
on	O
her	O
neck	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
?	O
Maplethorp	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
bad	O
consequences	O
that	O
followed	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
landlord	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
abused	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
tongue	O
,	O
calling	O
me	O
many	O
names	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
passionate	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
flung	O
the	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
hurting	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
a	O
dog	O
or	O
cat	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
,	O
knowing	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sent	O
word	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
get	O
me	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
drank	O
it	O
together	O
;	O
she	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
herself	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
blame	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
desired	O
God	O
to	O
bless	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Hospital	O
directly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
374	O
,	O
375.	O
William	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Turnpine	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Vandome	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Esther	O
.	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Vandome	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
with	O
another	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
They	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
eat	O
their	O
salmon	O
,	O
they	O
sat	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
clear	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
left	O
but	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
backward	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
reckoning	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
Fryer	O
,	O
held	O
a	O
sixpence	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
behind	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
tankard	O
stood	O
.	O
A	O
witness	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
he	O
pushed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
bottom-edge	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
hats	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
found	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
tankard	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
out	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
employed	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
to	O
look	O
about	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
day	O
last	O
week	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
witnesses	O
brought	O
Shepherd	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
company	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
washing	O
themselves	O
in	O
the	O
river	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
forgot	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
why	O
should	O
I	O
judge	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Vandome	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
night-gown	O
and	O
slippers	O
,	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
?	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Vandome	O
is	O
backward	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
the	O
biggest	O
boy	O
,	O
Fryer	O
,	O
stood	O
still	O
with	O
the	O
tankard	O
by	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no-body	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
but	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
room	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
Fryer	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
another	O
tankard	O
,	O
come	O
back	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
when	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
another	O
pint	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
;	O
Fryer	O
called	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
him	O
:	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
2	O
tankards	O
scored	O
,	O
I	O
apprehend	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
;	O
he	O
gives	O
Mrs.	O
Vandome	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
right-hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
hat	O
betwixt	O
his	O
legs	O
in	O
his	O
left-hand	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
very	O
moment	O
the	O
land-lady	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
that	O
moment	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
pushed	O
very	O
furiously	O
through	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
tankard	O
and	O
him	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
must	O
cover	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
three	O
boys	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
drinking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
described	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Fryer	O
's	O
hat	O
between	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
cover	O
something	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
salmon	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
drank	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
tankard	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
fore-room	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Hains	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
Fryer	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
there	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
remember	O
them	O
both	O
well	O
.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
nor	O
drunk	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
376.	O
John	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
Stable-keeper	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
knife	O
made	O
of	O
iron	O
and	O
steel	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
upon	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
belly	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
,	O
breadth	O
two	O
inches	O
,	O
and	O
depth	O
three	O
;	O
whereupon	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
did	O
languish	O
from	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
to	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
:	O
He	O
also	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
Man-slaughter	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
came	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
quarter-day	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
little	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
of	O
Bailey	O
's	O
:	O
presently	O
comes	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
voice	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
tap	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
any	O
man	O
open	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
peril	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
opened	O
inwards	O
,	O
he	O
shoved	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
clapp	O
'd	O
their	O
hands	O
on	O
the	O
lock	O
to	O
secure	O
it	O
;	O
Smith	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
,	O
shoving	O
hard	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
flew	O
open	O
immediately	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
burst	O
open	O
by	O
violence	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fetched	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
weapon	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
wound	O
till	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
words	O
pass	O
between	O
them	O
after	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
former	O
quarrels	O
between	O
them	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
forewarn	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
his	O
house	O
;	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
belonging	O
to	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
premisses	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
gone	O
from	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
a	O
servant	O
there	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
there	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
supper	O
with	O
my	O
fellow	O
servants	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
the	O
deceased	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
his	O
whip	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
knuckles	O
;	O
presently	O
the	O
door	O
flew	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
shreek	O
out	O
,	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
shewed	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
a	O
long	O
Clasp	O
knife	O
with	O
a	O
sharp	O
point	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
knife	O
open	O
?	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
bloody	O
?	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
blood	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
helped	O
the	O
deceased	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
him	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
any	O
quarrelling	O
between	O
them	O
before	O
this	O
?	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
deceased	O
abuse	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
rogue	O
and	O
scoundrel	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
there	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
landlord	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Segwick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
thing	O
happened	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
come	O
in	O
with	O
his	O
whip	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
flew	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
came	O
and	O
rushed	O
forward	O
towards	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
who	O
came	O
first	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
behind	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
almost	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
fright	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
knife	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
appeared	O
as	O
such	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Husband	O
Messinger	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
bowels	O
lying	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
body	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
very	O
soon	O
after	O
it	O
happened	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
judgment	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
all	O
about	O
me	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
near	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
visited	O
him	O
six	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sensible	O
during	O
the	O
whole	O
till	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
insensible	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
wound	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
?	O
Messinger	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
how	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
by	O
that	O
man	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
driven	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
senses	O
.	O
Bathsheba	B-pers
Chethem	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
stand	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bartholomew	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
forbid	O
him	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
has	O
gone	O
about	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
like	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
public	O
inn	O
the	O
prisoner	O
kept	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
let	O
out	O
coaches	O
and	O
chaises	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
soft	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
once	O
put	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
come	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cherrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
inn	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
Plough	O
inn	O
in	O
Princess-street	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
as	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
servant	O
then	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
let	O
any	O
man	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
upon	O
his	O
peril	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
him	O
presently	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
baily	O
there	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
pushed	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
weapen	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
passion	O
?	O
Christian	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
Smith	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
enemy	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
troubled	O
him	O
many	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
thus	O
using	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Christian	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
greater	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
than	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
made	O
any	O
observations	O
of	O
that	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Christian	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
man	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
hard	O
labouring	O
man	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Bedle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
appeared	O
extraordinary	O
good	O
,	O
a	O
pains-taking	O
man	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
talked	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
was	O
too	O
great	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
but	O
how	O
far	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Hen	O
.	O
Kellsoe	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
traded	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
passion	O
?	O
Kellsoe	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
or	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
passionate	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
man-slaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
377.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold-watch	O
and	O
gold-chain	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
Robert	O
Lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
betwixt	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Russel-street	B-place
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
this	O
woman	O
was	O
with	O
four	O
men	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
betwixt	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
her	O
hand	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
bosom	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
:	O
immediately	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
difficulty	O
,	O
by	O
twisting	O
my	O
fingers	O
in	O
the	O
chain	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
again	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
to	O
secure	O
her	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
slight	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
shoulders	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
bitch	O
alone	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
only	O
drunk	O
;	O
she	O
immediately	O
turned	O
up	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
men	O
stood	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
following	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
more	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
the	O
woman	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wetherby	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
above	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
returned	O
with	O
his	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
run	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
court	O
was	O
no	O
thorough-fare	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
meddled	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
secure	O
the	O
men	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
378.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mac-Parson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
four	O
holland	O
shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Anson	I-pers
.	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
Abigail	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
landry-maid	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Anson	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
these	O
things	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
last	O
at	O
two	O
pawn-brokers	O
,	O
four	O
shirts	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
of	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
,	O
seven	O
napkins	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
neckcloth	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
;	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
's	O
servant	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bringing	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
379.	O
Richard	B-pers
Highmore	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Lassels	I-pers
.	O
May	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
380.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
forty-four	O
yards	O
of	O
sattin-ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
May	O
31	O
.	O
Sweeting	O
Richards	O
,	O
the	O
apprentice	O
,	O
proved	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
master	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
on	O
telling	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
maid	O
come	O
and	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
she	O
the	O
said	O
prisoner	O
produced	O
the	O
pieces	O
:	O
they	O
both	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
and	O
Com	O
.	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
381.	O
George	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifty	O
yards	O
of	O
galloon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
and	O
Co	O
.	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
Sweeting	O
Richards	O
proved	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
galloon	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
and	O
Co.	O
property	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
382.	O
David	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Woods	I-pers
,	O
June	O
12	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
383.	O
William	B-pers
Warring	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
May	O
31	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
384.	O
William	B-pers
Hudspitch	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
glass	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
coach-door	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Orme	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
385.	O
James	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
periwig	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
against	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
May	O
16	O
Thomas	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
near	O
Round	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
periwig	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
clap	O
'd	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
hat	O
to	O
save	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
wig	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
run	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
crying	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
above	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
me	O
fight	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
moon-light	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
periwig	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
between	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
coming	O
by	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
up	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
wig	O
that	O
lay	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
wig	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
386.	O
Jane	B-pers
Rushing	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cambrick	O
hood	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cambrick	O
ruffles	O
lac	O
'd	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
cotton	O
curtains	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dukey	I-pers
,	O
April	O
11	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dukey	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
pawn	O
where	O
she	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
declared	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
goods	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
387.	O
Mary	B-pers
Willey	I-pers
,	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hooten	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
388.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
pocket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
,	O
June	O
7	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
pocket	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
389	O
,	O
390.	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rachael	B-pers
Horne	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
damask	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
table	O
cloth	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
fustian	O
frock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
May	O
21	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
White	I-pers
Guilty	O
,	O
Rach	B-pers
Horne	I-pers
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
391.	O
George	B-pers
Stracy	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Leydon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
Newark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
one	O
damask	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
nine	O
napkins	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
streamer	O
,	O
nine	O
punch-bowls	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Leydon	I-pers
,	O
December	O
26	O
.	O
The	O
principal	O
evidence	O
was	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
he	O
did	O
before	O
against	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
Newark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
supported	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
evidence	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
392	O
,	O
393.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Darwey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Dumsey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
check	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Darwey	I-pers
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Edward	O
Dumsey	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Shelley	I-pers
,	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
394.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nelthorpe	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Harling	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
White-chappel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
John	B-pers
Harling	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
husband	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nelthorpe	I-pers
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Tom	B-pers
Nelthorpe	I-pers
in	O
the	O
year	O
1739	O
,	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Fair	I-pers
-time	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
ceremony	O
of	O
the	O
Church	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bayce	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
King's-house	O
by	O
Fleet-ditch	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
away	O
in	O
marriage	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
cohabit	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
Castle-tavern	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Nelthorpe	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
ago	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
Porter	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
my	O
sorrow	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
White-chapel	B-place
Church	I-place
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1740	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
very	O
sensible	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
maid	O
when	O
I	O
married	O
you	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
said	O
to	O
have	O
another	O
Husband	O
before	O
.	O
Harling	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
you	O
was	O
a	O
maid	O
.	O
The	O
Rev	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Troborne	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
Register	O
of	O
St.	O
Mary	O
's	O
,	O
White-chapel	O
,	O
1740	O
,	O
14	O
Sept	O
.	O
I	O
married	O
John	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
and	O
Lucretia	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
name	O
she	O
then	O
went	O
by	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harling	I-pers
took	O
me	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
married	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
maintenance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
bond	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
never	O
to	O
molest	O
me	O
.	O
That	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
Hudson	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
h	O
e	O
had	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
swearing	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
another	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
.	O
All	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
afterwards	O
contradicted	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
evidences	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
395.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cannon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
396.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
straw-hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
Camblet	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
June	O
11	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
397	O
,	O
398.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Obrian	I-pers
and	O
Martin	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
both	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
,	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
blankets	O
,	O
five	O
harrateen	O
Curtains	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
May	O
20	O
.	O
Isabella	O
Gardner	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
shed	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
May	O
20.	O
John	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
.	O
The	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
and	O
Nathan	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
that	O
lives	O
at	O
Ben	O
.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
head	O
at	O
Stepney	O
,	O
we	O
being	O
there	O
saw	O
those	O
two	O
prisoners	O
pass	O
by	O
with	O
large	O
bundles	O
on	O
their	O
backs	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
these	O
two	O
fellows	O
have	O
got	O
each	O
a	O
load	O
which	O
seem	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
their	O
own	O
;	O
let	O
us	O
stop	O
them	O
and	O
enquire	O
whether	O
they	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
and	O
stop	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
if	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
their	O
own	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
Spittlefields	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Limehouse-hole	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Black-wall	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
we	O
shall	O
stop	O
you	O
on	O
suspicion	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
an	O
Officer	O
and	O
a	O
Watchman	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
with	O
the	O
bundles	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Limehouse	O
Hole	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
there	O
:	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
plying	O
place	O
who	O
told	O
us	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
such	O
persons	O
come	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
they	O
had	O
charg	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
with	O
hindering	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
Constable	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
high-way	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Rickets	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Nathan	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Obrian	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
hired	O
us	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
House	O
,	O
Deptford	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Lacy	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
met	O
us	O
in	O
that	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
carry	O
these	O
goods	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
3	O
s.	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
'll	O
give	O
us	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
we	O
'll	O
carry	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
stop	O
'd	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
us	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
House	O
in	O
Deptford	O
;	O
said	O
they	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
followed	O
us	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
since	O
you	O
are	O
after	O
us	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
where	O
you	O
will	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
Old	O
Gravel	O
Lane	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
399.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-bon	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hip-rafter	O
,	O
nine	O
pieces	O
of	O
wood	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Strutton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
160	O
pantiles	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Parish	I-pers
.	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
400.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
knife	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
401.	O
George	B-pers
Platt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
hempen	O
sacks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
.	O
June	O
21	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
402.	O
George	B-pers
Parish	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sedel	I-pers
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Dobney	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
403.	O
James	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
WhiteChapel	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
odd	O
shoes	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
June	O
17	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
404.	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
Felony	O
and	O
Murder	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
on	O
Ann	B-pers
his	O
wife	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
knife	O
made	O
of	O
iron	O
and	O
steel	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
throat	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
,	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
cut	O
,	O
giving	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
,	O
length	O
five	O
inches	O
,	O
depth	O
three	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
lived	O
a	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
breakfast	O
together	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
what	O
words	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
boy	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
had	O
killed	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
bar-door	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
wound	O
on	O
her	O
neck	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Doctor	O
or	O
Surgeon	O
;	O
the	O
wind	O
and	O
blood	O
coming	O
out	O
so	O
fast	O
,	O
she	O
died	O
directly	O
.	O
Her	O
throat	O
and	O
wind-pipe	O
were	O
cut	O
a-cross	O
,	O
almost	O
from	O
ear	O
to	O
ear	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
rogue	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
stir	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
be	O
hanged	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
twice	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
knife	O
was	O
shewed	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
a	O
case-knife	O
with	O
a	O
round	O
point	O
.	O
]	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
blood	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
his	O
hands	O
trembled	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
and	O
curs	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
first	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
daunted	O
at	O
the	O
thing	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
die	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
backwards	O
behind	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
shrike	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
wound	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
for	O
a	O
Doctor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
with	O
the	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
she	O
fell	O
I	O
past	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
Now	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
he	O
beat	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
her	O
with	O
bad	O
names	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
kill	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Ryon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
betwixt	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
murdered	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
(	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
servants	O
and	O
a	O
lodger	O
and	O
I	O
)	O
You	O
whore	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
an	O
end	O
of	O
you	O
:	O
no-body	O
shall	O
see	O
you	O
more	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
spoke	O
in	O
the	O
fore-room	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
heard	O
this	O
,	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
Bristol	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
struck	O
her	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
over	O
the	O
face	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
clothes	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
early	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
till	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
at	O
the	O
back-door	O
,	O
and	O
slept	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
been	O
asking	O
for	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
on	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
near	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
grumbling	O
words	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
talk	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
alone	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
stepped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
towards	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
throat	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
beckon	O
'd	O
after	O
me	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
hands	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
fore-door	O
,	O
I	O
cried	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
has	O
killed	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
killed	O
your	O
wife	O
with	O
?	O
It	O
is	O
done	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
wanted	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Keneley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
.	O
He	O
signed	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
West-Indies	O
in	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
War	O
,	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
from	O
Bristol	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
we	O
lived	O
together	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
voyage	O
to	O
the	O
Northward	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
agreeable	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
:	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
welcome	O
to	O
let	O
my	O
wife	O
be	O
there	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
save	O
expences	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
strangest	O
alteration	O
,	O
she	O
looked	O
quite	O
cold	O
and	O
black	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
private	O
she	O
would	O
use	O
me	O
very	O
barbarously	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday-night	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
task	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Reason	O
of	O
this	O
alteration	O
?	O
She	O
called	O
me	O
Old	O
Dog	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
my	O
nose	O
bleed	O
.	O
Betwixt	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
o'clock	O
next	O
morning	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
(	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
swear	O
before	O
)	O
she	O
would	O
never	O
lie	O
in	O
a	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
more	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
till	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
afterwards	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
her	O
usage	O
last	O
night	O
?	O
I	O
kick	O
'd	O
her	O
back-side	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
mind	O
to	O
turn	O
you	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
(	O
she	O
encouraged	O
that	O
very	O
boy	O
to	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
looked	O
black	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
none	O
of	O
this	O
;	O
if	O
she	O
is	O
your	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
6	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
reconciled	O
:	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
lie	O
in	O
a	O
bed	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
then	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
my	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
very	O
willingly	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
my	O
things	O
up	O
,	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
)	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
perfectly	O
shoved	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
folly	O
to	O
return	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
vessel	O
,	O
and	O
related	O
the	O
story	O
to	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
be	O
reconciled	O
.	O
The	O
tide	O
served	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
wherry	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
back-door	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
3	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
knocked	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
clothes	O
upon	O
a	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
satisfy	O
you	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
go	O
up	O
street	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
house	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
people	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
by	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
earnestly	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
shut	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
door	O
opened	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
every	O
body	O
about	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
no-body	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
my	O
wife	O
till	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
after	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
things	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
business	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
your	O
things	O
,	O
have	O
here	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
away	O
without	O
letting	O
the	O
world	O
know	O
the	O
reason	O
?	O
besides	O
,	O
I	O
owe	O
the	O
landlord	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
pay	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
toast	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
bread	O
upon	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
that	O
knife	O
.	O
I	O
leaned	O
my	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
to	O
her	O
very	O
seriously	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
no	O
discourse	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
salute	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
clapped	O
both	O
her	O
hands	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
me	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
it	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
violence	O
in	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
catched	O
up	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
a	O
stroke	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
cut	O
;	O
she	O
started	O
and	O
run	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
looked	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
offered	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Wilful	O
Murder	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
405.	O
John	B-pers
Luise	I-pers
Juncker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
and	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
studs	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Billets	I-pers
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
studs	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Merder	I-pers
,	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Condra	B-pers
Dedrick	I-pers
.	O
Apr	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
German	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
English	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
by	O
half	O
the	O
London-Jury	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
the	O
Jury	O
of	O
Foreigners	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
interpreter	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
what	O
each	O
witness	O
deposed	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
possession	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gone	O
off	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Kingston	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
406.	O
John	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
walking	O
cane	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
eight	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
June	O
23	O
.	O
Dedrick	O
Jacob	B-pers
Hane	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
London-stone	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
down	O
in	O
Swithin's-lane	B-place
by	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
people	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
cane	O
and	O
eight	O
shillings	O
and	O
upwards	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
a	O
word	O
before	O
they	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
best	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
another	O
bid	O
him	O
shoot	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
into	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
up	O
to	O
Walbrook	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
evidences	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
being	O
much	O
surprized	O
,	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
summoned	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
Alderman	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
wig	O
was	O
found	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
kennel	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
Cannon-street	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Swithin's-lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
pursuing	O
him	O
closely	O
without	O
hat	O
or	O
wig	O
,	O
crying	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
were	O
they	O
running	O
?	O
Priest	O
.	O
Out	O
of	O
Swithin's-lane	O
into	O
Cannon-street	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
door	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Swithin's-lane	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pursue	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
Wallbrook	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
again	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
watchman	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
was	O
gone	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
carried	O
that	O
night	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry-counter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
very	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
running	O
out	O
of	O
Swithin's-lane	O
?	O
Priest	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
running	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
pursuing	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
nine-pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
clasp	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hussington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
screaming	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
listened	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
repeated	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
they	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
unbolting	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
run	O
by	O
me	O
very	O
swiftly	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
without	O
hat	O
or	O
wig	O
,	O
in	O
looking	O
about	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
kennel	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
crab-stick	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
thus	O
searching	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
word	O
was	O
brought	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
fellows	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
prevailed	O
upon	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
surprised	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
returning	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Priest	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
our	O
watchmen	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Priest	O
gave	O
a	O
particular	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Hane	O
pursuing	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
giving	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
he	O
does	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
prisoner	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
running	O
away	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
?	O
His	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
riot	O
and	O
quarrel	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
drawn	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
Who	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
no	O
satisfactory	O
answer	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
as	O
before	O
mentioned	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
in	O
his	O
jacket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
his	O
discharge	O
from	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
service	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
by	O
Alderman	O
Winterbottom	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
asked	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
innocent	O
person	O
?	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
He	O
heard	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
fearing	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
Alderman	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
innocent	O
person	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
and	O
assisted	O
the	O
person	O
robbed	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Reader	I-pers
.	O
The	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
in	O
Swithin	O
's	O
lane	O
standing	O
up	O
at	O
Alderman	O
Atkins	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
our	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
our	O
watchman	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
:	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
size	O
and	O
dress	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
minutes	O
before	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
out-cry	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
fellows	O
run	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
they	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
towards	O
Lumbard-street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry-Counter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
description	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
description	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
still	O
think	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
I	O
saw	O
standing	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
a	O
clock	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
them	O
?	O
Reader	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
at	O
least	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
,	O
I	O
passed	O
by	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
about	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
407.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
June	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
408.	O
Ann	B-pers
Sherrington	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
coverlid	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
brass-candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
box-iron	O
and	O
two	O
heaters	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Hewerton	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
409.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
June	O
15	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
410.	O
John	B-pers
Cropley	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
an	O
Exchange	O
bill	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
and	O
did	O
utter	O
and	O
publish	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
a	O
true	O
bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
second	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
forgery	O
of	O
a	O
bill	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
publishing	O
of	O
another	O
bill	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
150	O
l.	O
As	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
clerk	O
to	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
agent	O
for	O
several	O
regiments	O
,	O
his	O
method	O
was	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
bill	O
had	O
been	O
paid	O
at	O
the	O
bankers	O
,	O
witnessed	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
keeping	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
erase	O
out	O
the	O
name	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
it	O
again	O
by	O
another	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
over	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
be	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
be	O
destroyed	O
those	O
bills	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
learned	O
arguments	O
of	O
the	O
Counsel	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
crime	O
was	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
nature	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
in	O
being	O
to	O
found	O
an	O
indictment	O
upon	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
therefore	O
acquitted	O
by	O
the	O
Court	O
without	O
examining	O
any	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
trial	O
,	O
for	O
high	O
crimes	O
and	O
misdemeanours	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
Hick's-Hall	O
.	O
411.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
holland	O
sleeves	O
,	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
,	O
one	O
dimetty	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
one	O
velvet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Elise	I-pers
.	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
goods	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
some	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
pledged	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
from	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
to	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
parcels	O
brought	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Old-street	O
near	O
the	O
church	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Dear	O
Mr.	O
Bird	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
come	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
you	O
every	O
thing	O
I	O
pawned	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
assist	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
412.	O
Ann	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
coat	O
,	O
one	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Armiger	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
June	O
16	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Armiger	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
exceeding	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
her	O
mistress	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
mend	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
wanted	O
below	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
her	O
stays	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
shoes	O
by	O
the	O
bed-side	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
way	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
met	O
her	O
on	O
those	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
on	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
which	O
belong	O
to	O
Nathanael	O
Day	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wig	O
.	O
I	O
seized	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
skirt	O
of	O
the	O
coat	O
at	O
the	O
stair-foot	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Young	O
gentleman	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
When	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
over-persuaded	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
master	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
settled	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
gave	O
her	O
that	O
advice	O
at	O
Hornsey	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
two	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linnen-cloth	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
:	O
she	O
gave	O
very	O
little	O
account	O
of	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
she	O
will	O
find	O
mercy	O
.	O
Nathanael	O
Day	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Armiger	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
Stop	O
thief	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
with	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
breeches	O
on	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
shirt	O
in	O
each	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
other	O
stairs	O
dressed	O
in	O
man	O
's	O
clothes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
dressed	O
myself	O
in	O
man	O
's	O
habit	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
prettier	O
boy	O
than	O
a	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
did	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
joke	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
413.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
cask	O
with	O
four	O
iron	O
hoops	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
.	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
414.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Spalding	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
corral	O
set	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
two	O
flannel	O
petticoats	O
,	O
one	O
diaper	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winston	I-pers
.	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
415	O
,	O
416	O
,	O
417.	O
David	B-pers
Fenn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cerner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
foreign	O
gold	O
coin	O
,	O
called	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Belsee	I-pers
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Belsee	I-pers
,	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
418.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
May	O
20	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
and	O
three	O
journeymen	O
packers	O
left	O
work	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bull-head	O
in	O
Jewin-street	O
;	O
I	O
get	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
my	O
reckoning	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Red	B-place
cross-street	I-place
,	O
there	O
I	O
tumbled	O
down	O
,	O
being	O
quite	O
stupified	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
go	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
my	O
watch	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
read	O
in	O
the	O
Advertiser	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
people	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
Kingsland-road	O
and	O
divers	O
things	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
taphouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
your	O
watch	O
last	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
About	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
.	O
This	O
watch	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Whitingburg	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
produce	O
it	O
if	O
required	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
419.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary-le-bone	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
printed	O
book	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Noyes	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
420.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Maxwell	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
9th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
421.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Wanmore	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Matthew	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
,	O
May	O
22d	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
422	O
,	O
423.	O
Valentine	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Tidd	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
upon	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Aplen	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
steal	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Aplen	I-pers
,	O
June	O
25	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Aplen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Whitechapel	B-place
on	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
driving	O
a	O
drove	O
of	O
sheep	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
men	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
drove	O
sheep	O
along	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
They	O
stood	O
round	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
do	O
not	O
disturb	O
the	O
sheep	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
all	O
five	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
distance	O
,	O
then	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
Valentine	O
Godwin	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
stood	O
still	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
quite	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
you	O
have	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
every	O
farthing	O
of	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
myself	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
threepence	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Johnson	O
drew	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
my	O
head	O
off	O
,	O
or	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
all	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
saying	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
:	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
to	O
search	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
strip	O
me	O
naked	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
buckles	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
took	O
great	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
they	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
promise	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
promised	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
men	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
ale	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
an	O
accomplice	O
who	O
is	O
come	O
here	O
as	O
a	O
witness	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
three	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
last	O
Sunday	O
se'nnight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Tidd	I-pers
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
up	O
White-chapel	B-place
:	O
we	O
cross	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
Mount	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
with	O
a	O
drove	O
of	O
sheep	O
before	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
do	O
n't	O
disturb	O
the	O
sheep	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
troubled	O
to	O
look	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
our	O
company	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Tidd	O
and	O
Godwin	O
;	O
Tidd	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
all	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
Godwin	O
had	O
one	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
one	O
after	O
another	O
,	O
Johnson	O
stood	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
his	O
throat	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
more	O
money	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
we	O
went	O
towards	O
Stepney-fields	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
round	O
we	O
met	O
five	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
we	O
had	O
fire-arms	O
they	O
never	O
attempted	O
to	O
meddle	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Johnson	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
rip	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
lame	O
I	O
laid	O
myself	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
bank	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
presently	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Godwin	O
take	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
do	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
pales	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
Johnson	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Anderson	O
.	O
Yes	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hemms	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
at	O
White-chapel	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
my	O
sheep	O
are	O
lost	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
there	O
as	O
he	O
does	O
here	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
telling	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
another	O
witness	O
brought	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Anderson	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Argent	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
coming	O
crying	O
out	O
thieves	O
!	O
&	O
c.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Stepney-fields	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
these	O
five	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
through	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
company	O
behind	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
but	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
five	O
fellows	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
.	O
Johnson	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
lay	O
hands	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
these	O
words	O
were	O
spoke	O
they	O
all	O
run	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
drop	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Father	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
here	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ind	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
the	O
witness	O
Anderson	O
was	O
brought	O
prisoner	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
robbing	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
who	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Valentine	O
Godwin	O
worked	O
with	O
Justice	O
Rickets	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
goal	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
going	O
hence	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
robbery	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Since	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
evidence	O
here	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
,	O
saying	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
them	O
sometimes	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
sometimes	O
on	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
.	O
Johnson	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
us	O
last	O
night	O
for	O
robbing	O
a	O
barber	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
this	O
morning	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Valentine	O
Godwin	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
Anderson	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Hick	O
's	O
hall	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
him	O
fudled	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
brags	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
liberty	O
.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
on	O
Saturday-night	O
at	O
the	O
Bull-head	O
ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
along	O
White-chapel	O
watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
his	O
fellow-prisoner	O
)	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
gin-shop	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
Mount	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
walked	O
along	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
with	O
some	O
sheep	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
hay-cock	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
is	O
gone	O
went	O
and	O
did	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
424.	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrew	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
casters	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
candlestick	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
six	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
salt	O
shovels	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
July	O
3d	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Southampton	B-place
buildings	I-place
,	I-place
Chancery-lane	I-place
;	O
on	O
Monday	O
last	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
my	O
chambers	O
at	O
Clifford	O
's	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
fore	O
parlour-window	O
reading	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
dinner	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
back-parlour	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
dine	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
sat	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
with	O
some	O
table-beer	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
running	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
i.	O
e	O
called	O
out	O
and	O
immediately	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
fore-parlour	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
plate	O
is	O
all	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
run	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
turning	O
being	O
so	O
short	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
King's-head	O
tavern	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Holborn	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
stood	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
looking	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cross	O
over	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
heels	O
,	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
suspicion	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
he	O
running	O
made	O
me	O
run	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
down	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
gone	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
:	O
said	O
another	O
woman	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
gone	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
stairs	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
caught	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
guilt	O
appear	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
immediately	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
sirrah	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
flutter	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
pulling	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
near	O
us	O
saw	O
something	O
shine	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
pen-knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
silver	O
salt-shovels	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
whatever	O
you	O
brought	O
in	O
that	O
bundle	O
must	O
be	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
.	O
His	O
excuse	O
for	O
running	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
running	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
where	O
had	O
you	O
these	O
two	O
silver	O
shovels	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
drop	O
'd	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
same	O
story	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
neighbours	O
staid	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
search	O
'd	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
plate	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
witness	O
that	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
apron	O
that	O
was	O
tied	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
plate	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Buffet	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
removed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
fore-parlour	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
distant	O
were	O
you	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Holborn	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
Middle-row	O
.	O
(	O
Cross	O
exam	O
in	O
'd	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
view	O
from	O
the	O
fore-parlour	O
to	O
the	O
back-parlour	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
run	O
into	O
Holborn	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
which	O
way	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
the	O
Counsel	O
,	O
whose	O
house	O
is	O
opposite	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
mother	O
seeing	O
the	O
maid	O
and	O
I	O
run	O
out	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
brown	O
cloaths	O
run	O
under	O
the	O
arch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
out-cry	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
about	O
our	O
windows	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
often	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
seen	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
him	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
turn	O
his	O
back	O
and	O
lean	O
on	O
a	O
post	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
?	O
Mason	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
about	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
in	O
one	O
dress	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
robbery	O
committed	O
?	O
Mason	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
two	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
with	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
fore-parlour	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
plate	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
I	O
run	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
'till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
jingle	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
run	O
out	O
?	O
Mason	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
plate	O
last	O
before	O
this	O
?	O
Mason	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
for	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nesbit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
just	O
facing	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
run	O
very	O
hard	O
in	O
his	O
night-gown	O
and	O
slippers	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
particular	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
a	O
man	O
has	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
up	O
a	O
court	O
which	O
was	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
;	O
then	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
another	O
woman	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
strive	O
to	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
as	O
it	O
appeared	O
bright	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
ungrasped	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
took	O
out	O
these	O
two	O
salt-shovels	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
looked	O
about	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
man	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
there	O
was	O
word	O
come	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
the	O
plate	O
would	O
be	O
found	O
there	O
among	O
some	O
dust	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hillis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
ran	O
through	O
the	O
court	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
Holborn	O
,	O
seeing	O
somebody	O
run	O
towards	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
that	O
way	O
and	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
somebody	O
else	O
hold	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
plate	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
searched	O
about	O
,	O
but	O
