TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
and	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
22d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1749	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Public	O
may	O
be	O
assured	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
during	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CALVERT	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
)	O
the	O
Sessions-Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
Four-pence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
Sessions	O
shall	O
be	O
carefully	O
compriz	O
'd	O
in	O
One	O
such	O
four-penny	O
Book	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
farther	O
Burthen	O
on	O
the	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CALVERT	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
hon	O
.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WRIGHT	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BIRCH	O
,	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Osmar	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Luke	I-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Hotchkin	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Winckworthy	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Kinman	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Foolle	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
Denis	B-pers
Mourgue	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Porton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
Colin	B-pers
Donaldson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Colborne	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brooke	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
.	O
160.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Leeson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pearl	O
necklace	O
with	O
a	O
diamond	O
locket	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lafoffe	I-pers
,	O
December	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
161.	O
George	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1724	O
,	O
did	O
marry	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Ratliff	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1739	O
.	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Cobeth	I-pers
,	O
the	O
former	O
wife	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
by	O
three	O
captains	O
of	O
vessels	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
master	O
of	O
a	O
vessel	O
trading	O
to	O
Virginia	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Ann	B-pers
Ratliff	I-pers
hath	O
now	O
a	O
husband	O
living	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Ratliff	I-pers
,	O
on	O
York	O
river	O
in	O
Virginia	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
162.	O
John	B-pers
Raven	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
quart	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
January	O
28	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Russel	B-place
court	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
Thistle	B-place
and	I-place
Crown	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
nor	O
saw	O
it	O
after	O
till	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
,	O
drinking	O
with	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
quart	O
mug	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
presently	O
there	O
arose	O
a	O
dispute	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
small	O
reckoning	O
,	O
which	O
drew	O
the	O
people	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
places	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
shift	O
his	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
says	O
Mrs.	O
Thomas	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
a	O
tankard	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
We	O
immediately	O
divided	O
ourselves	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
searched	O
houses	O
of	O
bad	O
repute	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
two	O
soldiers	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
come	O
to	O
inquire	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
mug	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
About	O
one	O
o'clock	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Tilt-yard	O
upon	O
duty	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
call	O
for	O
one	O
Bonner	O
;	O
I	O
,	O
knowing	O
Bonner	O
's	O
character	O
to	O
be	O
bad	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
Bonner	O
?	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
mug	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
so	O
by	O
holding	O
my	O
bayonet	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
surrendered	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
owner	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
quart	O
mug	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
White	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
fellow	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
163.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
copper	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
15	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Ambler	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
February	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
164.	O
Mary	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodgings	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
pillow	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Morrison	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
165.	O
John	B-pers
Slegg	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
tenent	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Duroos	I-pers
,	O
February	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
ordered	O
private	O
correction	O
and	O
turned	O
out	O
immediately	O
.	O
169.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Mooney	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Andrews	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
silver	O
hilted	O
sword	O
,	O
January	O
20	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Short	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
James	O
street	O
,	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
where	O
the	O
thing	O
happened	O
.	O
The	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
about	O
five	O
yards	O
up	O
Bedford-row	B-place
,	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
persons	O
coming	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
tallest	O
man	O
came	O
first	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
resolve	O
myself	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
behind	O
;	O
says	O
the	O
person	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
do	O
you	O
no	O
hurt	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
forward	O
and	O
then	O
turned	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
;	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
sword	O
and	O
ran	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
speaking	O
of	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
moon-light	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
wound	O
with	O
your	O
sword	O
?	O
Short	O
.	O
My	O
sword	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
resistance	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
at	O
first	O
it	O
had	O
past	O
betwixt	O
his	O
arm	O
and	O
body	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
examining	O
him	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
slight	O
wound	O
,	O
and	O
passed	O
betwixt	O
his	O
skin	O
and	O
his	O
ribs	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
my	O
sword	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
save	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
he	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
his	O
sword	O
?	O
Cut	O
his	O
arm	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
it	O
go	O
immediately	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
,	O
away	O
,	O
away	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
about	O
300	O
yards	O
down	O
Brownlow-street	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
my	O
sword	O
with	O
a	O
reward	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hat	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
remarkable	O
button	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
edged	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
button	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
on	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
put	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
gilt	O
button	O
)	O
the	O
Justice	O
appointed	O
a	O
time	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
off	O
the	O
hilt	O
of	O
my	O
sword	O
;	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
clothes	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
wig	O
?	O
Short	O
.	O
Much	O
the	O
same	O
you	O
now	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
hat	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
put	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
employ	O
?	O
Short	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
organist	O
and	O
musick-master	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
watchman	O
in	O
Great	O
Wild-street	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
houses	O
in	O
my	O
watch	O
I	O
had	O
orders	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
careful	O
of	O
,	O
where	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
attempts	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
to	O
break	O
in	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
eleven	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
safe	O
,	O
near	O
twelve	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
houses	O
I	O
found	O
.	O
by	O
trying	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
staff	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
rushed	O
in	O
directly	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
by	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
alarmed	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
looked	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
and	O
examined	O
all	O
backwards	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
all	O
safe	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
voice	O
saying	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
watchman	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
mistake	O
that	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
.	O
[	O
this	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
wise	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
left	O
all	O
right	O
at	O
twelve	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
at	O
my	O
stand	O
till	O
almost	O
two	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
tall	O
men	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
man	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
shun	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
hour	O
the	O
contrary	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
over	O
my	O
shoulder	O
to	O
watch	O
their	O
motions	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
calling	O
the	O
hour	O
down	O
Little	O
Wild-street	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
round	O
to	O
an	O
obscure	O
place	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
moving	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
stand	O
rapping	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
alarmed	O
the	O
people	O
before	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
good	O
morning	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
good	O
morrow	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
crying	O
the	O
hour	O
into	O
Great	O
Wild-street	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
some	O
assistance	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
continued	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
house	O
beset	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
his	O
candle	O
I	O
'd	O
approach	O
,	O
by	O
this	O
means	O
we	O
should	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
let	O
them	O
move	O
off	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
would	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
light	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
hanger	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
with	O
my	O
staff	O
in	O
my	O
other	O
hand	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
advanced	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
light	O
my	O
candle	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
show	O
me	O
where	O
you	O
live	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
goes	O
to	O
pass	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
flat	O
touch	O
with	O
my	O
hanger	O
over	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
very	O
pale	O
and	O
retreated	O
back	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
retreated	O
I	O
kept	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
candlestick	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
says	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
your	O
lodgings	O
?	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
partner	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
belt	O
,	O
his	O
accomplice	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
arm	O
and	O
pushed	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
down	O
Great	O
Wild-street	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
it	O
fared	O
with	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
saying	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
hanger	O
hang	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
calf	O
of	O
his	O
left	O
leg	O
,	O
my	O
partner	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
directly	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
retreated	O
back	O
quite	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
cut	O
your	O
hand	O
off	O
if	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
stir	O
an	O
inch	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
disputing	O
down	O
dropp	O
'd	O
a	O
pistol	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
towards	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
blow	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
stirr	O
'd	O
or	O
made	O
any	O
motion	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
body	O
.	O
Presently	O
another	O
pistol	O
dropt	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
clothes	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
very	O
readily	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
:	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
pistols	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
loaded	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
held	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
must	O
expect	O
if	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
stir	O
from	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
another	O
watchman	O
and	O
desired	O
his	O
assistance	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pistols	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
watch-house	O
;	O
we	O
delivered	O
the	O
pistols	O
and	O
the	O
hanger	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
two	O
powder	O
horns	O
,	O
a	O
bullet	O
mould	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
screw-driver	O
;	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
his	O
landlady	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
move	O
their	O
goods	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
partner	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
3	O
chairs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
bundle	O
of	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
moving	O
the	O
bed	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
gold	O
laced	O
hat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Short	O
has	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ellice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
watch	O
Prince's-street	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
partner	O
Great	O
and	O
Little	O
Wild-streets	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
as	O
his	O
brother	O
watchman	O
had	O
done	O
before	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
watchmen	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
pistols	O
and	O
hanger	O
,	O
here	O
they	O
be	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
two	O
horns	O
of	O
gunpowder	O
,	O
one	O
bullet-mould	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
screw-turner	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
Mr.	O
Short	O
's	O
silver	O
hilt	O
to	O
his	O
sword	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ind	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
turnkey	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
to	O
me	O
many	O
robberies	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
,	O
at	O
Constitution-hill	O
and	O
other	O
places	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
given	O
information	O
against	O
two	O
persons	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
innocent	O
persons	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
place	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
wound	O
in	O
his	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
likewise	O
the	O
blood	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
run	O
through	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Short	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
signified	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
before	O
I	O
impeached	O
those	O
five	O
of	O
my	O
gang	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
Lordship	O
will	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
too	O
late	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
trials	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
167.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Duval	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
168.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mary	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
field	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
January	O
the	O
20th	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Limehouse	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
near	O
Limehouse	B-place
church	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
shoulder	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
open	O
,	O
holding	O
the	O
point	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
search	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Buscoe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
when	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
assaulted	O
her	O
first	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
rob	O
her	O
?	O
Buscoe	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
her	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
us	O
near	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
with	O
my	O
cart	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
going	O
to	O
cut	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
throat	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
cart	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
my	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
pocket	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
this	O
knife	O
,	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
corkscrew	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
I	O
returned	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
confest	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
at	O
Hackney	O
the	O
stealing	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Sarah	B-pers
Buscoe	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
thimble	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
January	O
20	O
Sarah	B-pers
Buscoe	I-pers
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
Mary	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
thimble	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
prayed	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
six	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
being	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
that	O
knife	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
Sarah	B-pers
Buscoe	I-pers
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
robbed	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
thimble	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
searched	O
me	O
he	O
searched	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
As	O
before	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
thimble	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
six	O
pence	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
there	O
also	O
impeached	O
three	O
more	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
pray	O
my	O
Lord	O
consider	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
169.	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
January	O
5	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
170	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
24	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
candles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Everard	B-pers
Faukener	I-pers
,	O
January	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
171.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brisington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
,	O
January	O
17	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
months	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
candle	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
person	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
cried	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
?	O
the	O
person	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
could	O
find	O
nobody	O
but	O
the	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
my	O
brother	O
came	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
box	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
house	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
box	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Trent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
box	O
when	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Shirley	O
.	O
It	O
stood	O
in	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
bed-chamber	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
at	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
returned	O
me	O
a	O
three	O
pound	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
piece	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
Justice	O
Trent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
his	O
confession	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
?	O
Shirley	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
sign	O
it	O
?	O
Shirley	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sign	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
turnkey	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
signing	O
his	O
own	O
death	O
.	O
-	O
Jervice	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
the	O
three-pound	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shirley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Colefax	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
it	O
to	O
Thomas	O
Shirley	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Dunce	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
these	O
witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
it	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Shirley	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
their	O
suspicion	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
return	O
the	O
three	O
pound	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
piece	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
except	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
company	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
at	O
cribbage	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
These	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
drank	O
heartily	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
what	O
money	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
swear	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
against	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
swear	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Colefax	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
us	O
what	O
money	O
you	O
can	O
raise	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
what	O
money	O
I	O
could	O
raise	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
confest	O
the	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
three	O
pound	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
piece	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
39	O
s.	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
172.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Francia	I-pers
,	O
February	O
13	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
173.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hudell	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-board	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
earthen	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
china	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
February	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
174.	O
John	B-pers
Kirkham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
Holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morphy	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
175.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gallon	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Trovel	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
176.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
January	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
177.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
box	O
and	O
tortoishell	O
case	O
,	O
studded	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
December	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
178.	O
George	B-pers
Hopewell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
had	O
stolen	O
75	O
guineas	O
and	O
12	O
Portugal	O
pieces	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
declaring	O
upon	O
oath	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
179.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Rotten	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
Saterly	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Suffolk	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
as	O
being	O
a	O
notorious	O
smuggler	O
,	O
for	O
not	O
surrendering	O
himself	O
according	O
to	O
order	O
of	O
Council	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
certain	O
facts	O
,	O
contained	O
in	O
a	O
suggestion	O
founded	O
on	O
a	O
late	O
act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
,	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
19th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
Majesty	O
,	O
intituled	O
,	O
An	O
act	O
for	O
the	O
farther	O
punishment	O
of	O
persons	O
concerned	O
in	O
landing	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
uncustomed	O
goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
bring	O
in	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
persons	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
great	O
and	O
violent	O
offences	O
,	O
to	O
surrender	O
themselves	O
to	O
justice	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
before	O
a	O
day	O
fixed	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
order	O
in	O
Council	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
declared	O
to	O
be	O
felons	O
convicted	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
suffer	O
death	O
as	O
other	O
felons	O
.	O
The	O
King	O
's	O
Attorney-General	O
suggested	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
since	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
place	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
1748.	O
was	O
charged	O
before	O
John	B-pers
Oxenford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
for	O
the	O
Liberty	O
of	O
the	O
Tower	O
;	O
by	O
information	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Colliton	I-pers
upon	O
oath	O
before	O
this	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
subscribed	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Colliton	I-pers
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
that	O
he	O
named	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
three	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
were	O
assembled	O
together	O
at	O
Benacre	O
,	O
in	O
Suffolk	O
,	O
October	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
1746.	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
landing	O
uncustomed	O
goods	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
farther	O
suggested	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
Justice	O
Oxenford	O
certified	O
this	O
information	O
under	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
seal	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Bedford	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
principal	O
Secretaries	O
of	O
State	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
Grace	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
laid	O
this	O
before	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Privy	O
Council	O
,	O
(	O
his	O
Majesty	O
being	O
then	O
beyond	O
the	O
seas	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Privy	O
Council	O
made	O
an	O
order	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
surrender	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
Lords	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
,	O
or	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
within	O
40	O
days	O
after	O
its	O
publication	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
further	O
suggested	O
,	O
that	O
after	O
making	O
this	O
order	O
of	O
Council	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
copies	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
printer	O
of	O
the	O
Gazette	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
printed	O
in	O
it	O
the	O
25th	O
and	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
the	O
High-Sheriff	O
of	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Suffolk	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
High-Sheriff	O
,	O
caused	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
published	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
ten	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
within	O
fourteen	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
two	O
market	O
towns	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
Southam	O
and	O
Beckles	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
each	O
of	O
those	O
towns	O
,	O
in	O
some	O
publick	O
place	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
surrender	O
himself	O
according	O
to	O
this	O
order	O
of	O
Council	O
,	O
therefore	O
it	O
is	O
suggested	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
attainted	O
and	O
convicted	O
of	O
felony	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Attorney-General	O
did	O
press	O
that	O
execution	O
might	O
be	O
made	O
.	O
These	O
suggestions	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
by	O
proper	O
witnesses	O
in	O
every	O
step	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
alledged	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
another	O
person	O
intended	O
and	O
not	O
himself	O
;	O
Samuel	B-pers
Colliton	I-pers
swore	O
to	O
the	O
identity	O
of	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
intended	O
in	O
that	O
order	O
:	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
the	O
issues	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
180.	O
John	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Terence	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
of	O
one	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
February	O
3	O
.	O
Terence	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn	B-place
fields	I-place
,	O
near	O
Justice	O
Dennison	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
breast	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
deliver	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
stepped	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
paces	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
and	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
stick	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
damn	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
deliver	O
your	O
money	O
I	O
will	O
rip	O
you	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
and	O
ran	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
down	O
Duke	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
square	O
;	O
there	O
squire	O
Oshurae	O
's	O
man	O
met	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
him	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
another	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
watchman	O
and	O
Judge	O
Dennison	O
's	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Walden	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
passed	O
the	O
arch	O
he	O
ran	O
through	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
?	O
Walden	O
.	O
My	O
crying	O
out	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
squire	O
Osburne	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
20	O
yards	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
murder	O
!	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
heard	O
somebody	O
run	O
and	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
then	O
I	O
stood	O
still	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
service	O
;	O
presently	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
through	O
the	O
middle	O
arch	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
strained	O
my	O
leg	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
hold	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
somebody	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
quite	O
dismist	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
since	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Peirce	O
Frances	O
.	O
On	O
February	O
the	O
3d	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
that	O
was	O
backwards	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
!	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
listened	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
found	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
now	O
thinks	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
time	O
enough	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
pistol	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
shelf	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
was	O
carried	O
home	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
person	O
that	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
blow	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
he	O
stirred	O
.	O
Terence	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
was	O
in	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
upbraiding	O
him	O
with	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
person	O
came	O
much	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
clasp	O
knife	O
open	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
the	O
bundle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
saying	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
!	O
this	O
is	O
what	O
you	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
in	O
doubling	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
thrown	O
away	O
the	O
stick	O
and	O
the	O
parcel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Frances	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
blow	O
;	O
pretending	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
appearance	O
of	O
any	O
blow	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn	O
Fields	O
;	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
heard	O
murder	O
cried	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
directly	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
towards	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Duke	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
Judge	O
Dennison	O
's	O
servant	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
stirred	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
We	O
guarded	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
White	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
doors	O
below	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
clasp	O
knife	O
open	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
John	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
we	O
took	O
;	O
I	O
attended	O
him	O
to	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
knife	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
men	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
stick	O
Mr.	O
Walden	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
knife	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
thus	O
.	O
[	O
They	O
were	O
shewn	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
to	O
Walden	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
stick	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knocked	O
you	O
down	O
with	O
?	O
Walden	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
stick	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
it	O
over	O
me	O
long	O
enough	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Renolds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
prison	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
delivered	O
to	O
us	O
by	O
the	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sea-faring	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Wapping	O
;	O
betwixt	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
coming	O
home	O
by	O
Lincoln's-Inn	O
Fields	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
New	O
market	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
my	O
hat	O
took	O
off	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
thief	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
dog	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
run	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
cut	O
you	O
down	O
with	O
my	O
hanger	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
these	O
people	O
met	O
and	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
and	O
robbed	O
myself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
181.	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robing	O
Catherine	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
silk	O
camlet	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
Jan.	O
28	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
my	O
child	O
for	O
a	O
stay	O
and	O
shirt	O
,	O
January	O
the	O
28th	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
ever	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
know	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carman	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
with	O
my	O
cart	O
through	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
up	O
by	O
London	O
wall	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
shirt	O
and	O
a	O
stay	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
counter	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
mother	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
bundle	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
Just	O
by	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Wood-street	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
tacked	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
been	O
for	O
a	O
dray-man	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
she	O
rest	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
through	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
when	O
the	O
carman	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
bundle	O
down	O
just	O
by	O
a	O
post	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Wood-street	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
carman	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
close	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
them	O
.	O
Hilton	O
.	O
His	O
back	O
was	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
the	O
carman	O
's	O
heels	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
London-wall	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
that	O
carman	O
,	O
who	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
bundle	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
brains	O
beat	O
out	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
quitted	O
his	O
hold	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
gone	O
my	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
another	O
gentleman	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
justice	O
done	O
me	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
January	O
28	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Fore-street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
run	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
and	O
turn	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Wood-street	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
follow	O
him	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
the	O
carman	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
flesh	O
tore	O
off	O
his	O
bones	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
such	O
a	O
little	O
child	O
as	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
green-stall	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
child	O
standing	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
this	O
a	O
shame	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
clothes	O
torn	O
after	O
this	O
manner	O
?	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
no	O
shame	O
at	O
all	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
robbed	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
directly	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
that	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
justice	O
done	O
you	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Sun	O
alehouse	O
London-wall	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
hunch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
fool	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
mother	O
came	O
before	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
but	O
through	O
the	O
intercession	O
of	O
his	O
prosecutrix	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
for	O
transportation	O
.	O
182	O
,	O
183.	O
William	B-pers
Kenderick	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
others	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
one	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
2	O
canisters	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
ounces	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
walking	O
cane	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
And	O
George	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
of	O
them	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Kenderick	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
Robertson	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
184.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
large	O
cases	O
for	O
the	O
covering	O
of	O
two	O
stools	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
185.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
,	O
signed	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
payable	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Meek	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
186	O
,	O
187.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Keen	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
120	O
ells	O
of	O
linnen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
192	O
yards	O
of	O
linnen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
l.	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
And	O
William	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Keen	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
.	O
Wade	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
188.	O
Mary	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
Wapping	I-place
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
cheese	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
buckles	O
,	O
one	O
tin	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lein	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
189.	O
Jeremy	B-pers
Casway	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
violently	O
assaulting	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
,	O
January	O
26	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
betwixt	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Well-close	B-place
Square	I-place
,	O
he	O
hit	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
it	O
stunned	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
quite	O
fall	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
at	O
a	O
wrong	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
delivering	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
one	O
farthing	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
doubt	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
feel	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
felt	O
my	O
wristbands	O
for	O
my	O
buttons	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
buttons	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
but	O
penny	O
buttons	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
do	O
you	O
no	O
service	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
silver	O
ones	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
pretended	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
myself	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
his	O
stick	O
being	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
feared	O
another	O
blow	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
none	O
else	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
stepped	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
with	O
my	O
fist	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
had	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
tussle	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
finding	O
me	O
resolute	O
let	O
the	O
stick	O
go	O
,	O
which	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
watch	O
!	O
watch	O
!	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
down	O
a	O
place	O
that	O
comes	O
into	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
towards	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
at	O
him	O
he	O
turned	O
short	O
down	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
White	O
Horse	O
alley	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
step	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
jumped	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
resistance	O
I	O
would	O
knock	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
met	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
him	O
at	O
Justice	O
Manwaring	O
's	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
thing	O
:	O
Likewise	O
told	O
us	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Church-lane	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
carried	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
received	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Pett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
beadle	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
Wapping	O
;	O
my	O
duty	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
is	O
four	O
nights	O
a-week	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
duty	O
;	O
betwixt	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
near	O
twelve	O
,	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
watch	O
!	O
watch	O
!	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
watchmen	O
to	O
light	O
up	O
their	O
candles	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
thought	O
some	O
body	O
was	O
in	O
pursuit	O
;	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
I	O
must	O
the	O
noise	O
;	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
well	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
bringing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
this	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
:	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
stick	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
an	O
iron	O
ferrel	O
on	O
the	O
end	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
the	O
ferrel	O
;	O
his	O
face	O
then	O
was	O
muddy	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
like	O
a	O
blow	O
with	O
a	O
dirty	O
stick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
blood	O
?	O
Pett	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
blood	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
before	O
Justice	O
Manwaring	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
adding	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
that	O
ever	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Guilty	O
transportation	O
.	O
190.	O
Joseph	B-pers
King	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
wooden	O
cags	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
quarts	O
of	O
geneva	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Allien	I-pers
,	O
January	O
the	O
16th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
191.	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mackbridge	I-pers
of	O
a	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Archibald	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
,	O
February	O
14	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mackbridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
ten	O
,	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
purse	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
six	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
awake	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
inquiry	O
of	O
the	O
landlady	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
found	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
other	O
people	O
lodge	O
in	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
Mackbridge	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
bed	O
with	O
two	O
people	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
they	O
as	O
well	O
have	O
taken	O
your	O
money	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Mackbridge	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
before	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
lie	O
with	O
you	O
before	O
?	O
Mackbridge	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
one	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
get	O
up	O
then	O
?	O
Mackbridge	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
pocket	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Mackbridge	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
lane	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
accused	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Shambrook	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Windmill	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Richbel	B-pers
's	O
regiment	O
of	O
marine	O
s	O
;	O
a	O
townsman	O
of	O
mine	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
hatter	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
one	O
price	O
7	O
s.	O
he	O
was	O
inclinable	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
money	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
get	O
fuddled	O
and	O
lose	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
left	O
three	O
guineas	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
saying	O
he	O
owed	O
a	O
woman	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
five	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
prize	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
money	O
?	O
Shambrook	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
no	O
otherways	O
than	O
this	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
30	O
pounds	O
prize	O
money	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
to	O
take	O
coach	O
and	O
met	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
shipmates	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
Alderman	O
Parson	O
's	O
head	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
of	O
hot	O
;	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Glass	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
purse	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
of	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
Wapping	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Duckingfield	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
found	O
this	O
purse	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
going	O
up	O
Glass	O
's	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
down	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
going	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
purse	O
by	O
an	O
ilet	O
hole	O
that	O
was	O
made	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Worship	O
looked	O
on	O
it	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
described	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
purse	O
and	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
192	O
Matth.ias	B-pers
Rhemes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Brian	B-pers
Parkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
out	O
thence	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
20	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
February	O
4	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Brittain	I-pers
,	O
February	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
193.	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Holland	O
ruffled	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Phosper	I-pers
,	O
January	O
20	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Phosper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Poplar	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
every	O
morning	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
my	O
horse	O
and	O
clean	O
my	O
shoes	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
Holland	O
shirt	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Phosper	O
.	O
In	O
Rag-fair	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
shirt	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
194	O
,	O
195.	O
Robert	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Welsley	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
,	O
February	O
5	O
.	O
Watson	O
guilty	O
.	O
Westley	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
196	O
,	O
197.	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Caster	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
yellow	O
metal	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Divine	I-pers
,	O
January	O
14	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Caster	I-pers
,	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Thomas	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Caster	O
:	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
198.	O
Francis	B-pers
Throgmorton	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Fields	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
harrateen	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
blanket	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
from	O
his	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodgings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Balendine	I-pers
,	O
January	O
3	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Balendine	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Tottenham-court	B-place
road	I-place
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
lodgings	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
curtains	O
,	O
one	O
blanket	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Balendine	O
.	O
About	O
20	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Balendine	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
way	O
,	O
acquainted	O
;	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
physician	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
my	O
wife	O
not	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
pretending	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
that	O
would	O
affright	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
anatomy	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
curtains	O
were	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Bibby	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Stanhope-street	O
;	O
the	O
blanket	O
and	O
sheet	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
agree	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
things	O
lie	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
a	O
valuable	O
consideration	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Balendine	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
humanity	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
take	O
my	O
note	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
agreed	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
been	O
to	O
have	O
compounded	O
felony	O
;	O
indeed	O
I	O
was	O
ignorant	O
of	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
consent	O
to	O
such	O
an	O
agreement	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Balendine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
clean	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
key	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
anatomy	O
that	O
will	O
fright	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
continued	O
in	O
that	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
fray	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
for	O
abusing	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
one	O
,	O
that	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
carry	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
husband	O
mentioned	O
before	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
two	O
green	O
curtains	O
to	O
pawn	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
December	O
19	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
four	O
shillings	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
shillings	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
curtains	O
were	O
these	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Balendine	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
saw	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
upon	O
his	O
quarrel	O
,	O
I	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
found	O
no	O
sheets	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
they	O
said	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
seem	O
very	O
well	O
satisfied	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
encouragement	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
,	O
I	O
having	O
a	O
law-suit	O
depending	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
character	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
fray	O
one	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
as	O
many	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
now	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
failed	O
in	O
my	O
law-suit	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
turned	O
Cat	O
in	O
pan	O
as	O
the	O
phrase	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
appeal	O
to	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
malicious	O
prosecution	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
raise	O
that	O
money	O
.	O
Balendine	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
matter	O
up	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
my	O
things	O
:	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
had	O
agreed	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
have	O
taught	O
you	O
how	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
such	O
things	O
as	O
these	O
;	O
I	O
'd	O
have	O
made	O
you	O
remember	O
your	O
compounding	O
of	O
felony	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
199	O
,	O
200.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jurnigan	I-pers
,	O
February	O
1	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
guilty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
201	O
,	O
202.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haydon	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
28	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
water-side	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
women	O
very	O
well	O
dressed	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
a	O
lodging	O
?	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
wanted	O
something	O
to	O
eat	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
something	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
Besides	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
two	O
linnen	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reasons	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
accuse	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
awoke	O
;	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
that	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
bid	O
me	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
out	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
lose	O
my	O
life	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
and	O
saw	O
an	O
out-house	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
crept	O
in	O
there	O
and	O
lay	O
till	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
Haydon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
bare-footed	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
catch	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
then	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
go	O
past	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
buckles	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
woman	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
convey	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
being	O
behind	O
her	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
,	O
or	O
when	O
you	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
come	O
home	O
from	O
Virginia	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
but	O
little	O
rest	O
for	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
and	O
nights	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
robbed	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
sleeping	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
you	O
had	O
your	O
things	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
money	O
just	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
paid	O
it	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
that	O
took	O
you	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
two	O
women	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
when	O
I	O
awoke	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
awake	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
again	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
your	O
shilling	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
fine	O
damsels	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
tall	O
thin	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
My	O
shoe-buckles	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Haydon	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
you	O
awoke	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
threaten	O
'd	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ellise	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
of	O
White-Chapel	O
parish	O
;	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
this	O
morning	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
boys	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
had	O
been	O
stripp	O
'd	O
in	O
Bakers-Arms	B-place
Alley	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
this	O
sailor	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
bare-footed	O
:	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
noted	O
place	O
for	O
thieves	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
blue	O
jacket	O
has	O
got	O
my	O
buckles	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
white	O
paper	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
girls	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
sad	O
dishabil	O
,	O
ragged	O
,	O
and	O
bare-footed	O
;	O
they	O
tightened	O
themselves	O
up	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
insisted	O
on	O
taking	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
having	O
his	O
eye	O
towards	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
has	O
my	O
shoe-buckles	O
;	O
he	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
without	O
shoe	O
or	O
stocking	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
run	O
,	O
got	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
girls	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
four	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
all	O
close	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
together	O
at	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
too	O
soon	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
then	O
afterwards	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
Heydon	O
confessed	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
she	O
dropp	O
'd	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
just	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
saw	O
them	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
with	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
before	O
described	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
bought	O
them	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
deliver	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Ellise	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
contract	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
much	O
distress	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
then	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
that	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
more	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
this	O
prosecution	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
agreed	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
keep	O
the	O
buckles	O
till	O
he	O
pays	O
me	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
coming	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
sailor	O
walking	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
in	O
a	O
dismal	O
manner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
mentioning	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
running	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
that	O
had	O
his	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
him	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
in	O
here	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
women	O
laid	O
down	O
:	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
this	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
himself	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
pursuing	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
him	O
,	O
designing	O
that	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
giving	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Haydon	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
203	O
,	O
204.	O
James	B-pers
Oderway	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Airs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
one	O
copper	O
teakettle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Airs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Windmil-Hill	B-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
all	O
day	O
at	O
my	O
labour	O
,	O
February	O
the	O
eighth	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
eleven	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pain	O
of	O
glass	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
broke	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
?	O
Airs	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
that	O
holds	O
two	O
gallons	O
,	O
a	O
teakettle	O
,	O
three	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
snuffers	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
farther	O
than	O
their	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
goods	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
saucepan	O
they	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
on	O
Saffron-Hill	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Seven	O
Stars	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
was	O
out	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
business	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
205.	O
Mary	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
ounces	O
of	O
raw	O
silk	O
:	O
And	O
206.	O
Catharine	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Mary	O
Green	O
guilty	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
207.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
copper	O
saucepans	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
directions	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
208.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-eight	O
pounds	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Steven	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
27	O
.	O
Steven	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
away	O
half	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sumeroise	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Flower	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
two	O
persons	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
cheese	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
is	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
serving	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
third	O
person	O
slipp	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
stole	O
half	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
about	O
eight	O
doors	O
from	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
209.	O
Lidia	B-pers
Wild	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
210.	O
Ann	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
211.	O
George	B-pers
Burrel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
hair	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
212.	O
William	B-pers
Wolloston	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
21	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
213.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Machgrigon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Seabottom	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
19	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Seabottom	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
down	O
Fleet-street	B-place
.	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
part	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
part	O
out	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
rascal	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
stand	O
search	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
several	O
people	O
,	O
whose	O
pockets	O
were	O
pick	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
He	O
once	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
struggle	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
both	O
down	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
214.	O
Mary	B-pers
Buttler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
three	O
check	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Josiah	B-pers
Overly	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Overly	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
trust	O
in	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
thought	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
twenty-first	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
we	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
wash	O
a	O
coloured	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
this	O
apron	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
declar	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
thief	O
.	O
For	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
not	O
blame	O
any	O
person	O
else	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
one	O
Taylor	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
surprized	O
,	O
as	O
when	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
myself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
215.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
ready	O
furnish	O
'd	O
lodgings	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
frying-pan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Church-house	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
217.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Demsey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hart-Street	B-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
lawn	O
aprons	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
parlour	O
.	O
Cassey	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
Mrs.	O
Clark	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
aprons	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
indebted	O
to	O
his	O
landlady	O
fourpence	O
halfpeny	O
for	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
for	O
having	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
no	O
man	O
shall	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
ordered	O
it	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
walked	O
behind	O
cassey	O
and	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
daughter	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
get	O
them	O
without	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
cassey	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
cassey	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
for	O
three	O
pence	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
any	O
farther	O
,	O
than	O
cassey	O
said	O
she	O
forced	O
him	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
:	O
she	O
did	O
own	O
she	O
had	O
sixpence	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
cassey	O
staid	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
owned	O
them	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ind	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
this	O
cassey	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
liv	O
'd	O
strolling	O
about	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
where	O
this	O
gentlewoman	O
lives	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
where	O
they	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Demsey	I-pers
,	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
where	O
cassey	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
but	O
cassey	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
looking	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
cassey	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
woman	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
Fisher	O
,	O
alias	O
cassey	O
,	O
guilty	O
,	O
Demsey	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
218.	O
William	B-pers
Sheafe	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
Enfield	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
hens	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chessey	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
7	O
.	O
Rebeccah	O
Chessey	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
hens	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
hen	O
roost	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
hanging	O
with	O
her	O
head	O
downwards	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
neighbour	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
brought	O
me	O
another	O
of	O
my	O
hens	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
her	O
about	O
seven	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
dead	O
fowl	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
(	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
had	O
knock	O
'd	O
it	O
down	O
by	O
slinging	O
at	O
it	O
)	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Chessey	O
owned	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
219	O
,	O
220	O
,	O
221.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Blare	I-pers
,	O
surgeon	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
13	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
a	O
coach-harness	O
maker	O
,	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Aubury	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
what	O
happened	O
on	O
the	O
thirteenth	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Cumberland	O
's	O
work	O
;	O
we	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
at	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
lie	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
night	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
will	O
get	O
up	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
He	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Chandois-Street	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
's	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
light	O
to	O
light	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
In	O
our	O
return	O
coming	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
passage	O
called	O
Mr.	B-place
Durand	I-place
's	I-place
Passage	I-place
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
we	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
leaning	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
foremost	O
;	O
and	O
whether	O
the	O
deceased	O
kick	O
'd	O
his	O
foot	O
against	O
a	O
stone	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
against	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
's	O
foot	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
fallen	O
down	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
words	O
arose	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
blows	O
struck	O
on	O
either	O
side	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
on	O
about	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
stopp	O
'd	O
there	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
the	O
gentleman	O
why	O
he	O
insults	O
me	O
thus	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
we	O
returned	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
passage	O
where	O
we	O
first	O
had	O
the	O
words	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
then	O
William	O
Howard	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
,	O
putting	O
his	O
hands	O
by	O
his	O
sides	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
be	O
insulted	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
streets	O
?	O
The	O
gentleman	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
as	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
but	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
this	O
passage	O
immediately	O
;	O
this	O
door	O
is	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
street	O
where	O
we	O
first	O
found	O
him	O
standing	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
down	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
officer	O
's	O
clothes	O
,	O
[	O
since	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
Captain	O
Campbel	B-pers
]	O
who	O
ran	O
immediately	O
and	O
collared	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
passage	O
door	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
deceased	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
collaring	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
word	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
do	O
right	O
in	O
collaring	O
my	O
friend	O
;	O
you	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
behave	O
as	O
such	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
reason	O
why	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
fault	O
we	O
will	O
ask	O
your	O
pardon	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
last	O
word	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
mouth	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
catched	O
the	O
blow	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
did	O
but	O
just	O
touch	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
let	O
go	O
his	O
hand	O
he	O
repeated	O
his	O
blow	O
upon	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
fray	O
began	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
go	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
collar	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
blows	O
struck	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
Campbel	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
several	O
blows	O
during	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
from	O
whom	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
knocked	O
down	O
twice	O
,	O
rising	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
naked	O
swords	O
,	O
or	O
one	O
sword	O
and	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
upon	O
seeing	O
them	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
run	O
for	O
assistance	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
immediately	O
killed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
the	O
watch-house	O
off	O
from	O
that	O
place	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
It	O
may	O
be	O
about	O
100	O
yards	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
and	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
assistance	O
;	O
in	O
our	O
return	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
lying	O
between	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
first	O
begun	O
and	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
belly	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
betwixt	O
where	O
the	O
quarrel	O
began	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
and	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
?	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
ever	O
spoke	O
after	O
were	O
,	O
O	O
dear	O
Ned	O
!	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
the	O
plaisterer	O
turned	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
what	O
poor	O
Will	O
Howard	O
.	O
Benson	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
somebody	O
pulled	O
up	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
body	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
ran	O
for	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Perkins	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
which	O
Blare	O
knocked	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
came	O
Captain	O
Campbel	B-pers
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
directly	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
knock	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
up	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
they	O
were	O
admitted	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
live	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
In	O
Chequer	O
court	O
,	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
:	O
When	O
we	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Carr	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Hall	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
by	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
Blare	O
and	O
Campbel	O
were	O
gone	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
these	O
people	O
come	O
out	O
that	O
struck	O
you	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
where	O
Blare	O
rapped	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
before	O
Campbel	O
collared	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
or	O
when	O
those	O
people	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Instantly	O
upon	O
his	O
striking	O
the	O
deceased	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
up	O
you	O
saw	O
a	O
sword	O
or	O
swords	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
can	O
you	O
tell	O
,	O
was	O
Campbel	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
sword	O
must	O
be	O
brought	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
he	O
parted	O
from	O
the	O
deceased	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
saw	O
two	O
such	O
weapons	O
come	O
down	O
those	O
stairs	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
sword	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
brought	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
naked	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
could	O
you	O
do	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
several	O
tradesmen	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
two	O
tankards	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
in	O
Long	O
Acre	O
between	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
drink	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
those	O
other	O
house	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
rum	O
at	O
the	O
currier	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
drink	O
nothing	O
more	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
two	O
tankards	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
punch	O
between	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
we	O
drank	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
left	O
work	O
till	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
thing	O
happened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
drink	O
none	O
at	O
work	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
in	O
tippling	O
time	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
each	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
size	O
man	O
was	O
this	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
A	O
middle	O
size	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
working	O
clothes	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
apron	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
esteem	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
;	O
a	O
courageous	O
fellow	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
quiet	O
,	O
peacable	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
began	O
to	O
use	O
this	O
language	O
first	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
spoke	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
back	O
call	O
out	O
for	O
assistance	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
only	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
Pickpocket	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
such	O
word	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
said	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
since	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
merry	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
drunk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
deceased	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
quarrelsome	O
sometimes	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
quiet	O
peacable	O
man	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Hall	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
Captain	O
Campbel	B-pers
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Hall	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
brought	O
Captain	O
Campbel	B-pers
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Morton	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
call	O
in	O
by	O
accident	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
neither	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
and	O
company	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
Captain	O
Campbel	B-pers
come	O
to	O
see	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
rooms	O
,	O
Campbel	O
and	O
Blare	O
were	O
in	O
one	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
Morton	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
Captain	O
Clark	O
asked	O
who	O
was	O
above	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
had	O
brought	O
in	O
Captain	O
Campbel	B-pers
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
young	O
gentleman	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
Blare	O
or	O
Campbel	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
call	O
for	O
you	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
who	O
were	O
above	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
call	O
him	O
Captain	O
Campbel	B-pers
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
fancy	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
during	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
whether	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morton	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
this	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
affair	O
happened	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
room	O
and	O
heard	O
it	O
begin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
two	O
men	O
say	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
sailor	O
with	O
a	O
fine	O
laced	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
little	O
prize	O
money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
their	O
faces	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
cried	O
out	O
murder	O
,	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
insulted	O
by	O
two	O
pickpockets	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
till	O
then	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
his	O
voice	O
before	O
Captain	O
Campbel	B-pers
cried	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
Blare	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
assist	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
strove	O
to	O
keep	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
my	O
landlady	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shove	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
from	O
her	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
himself	O
;	O
we	O
within	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
quite	O
close	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
scuffle	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Campbel	O
carry	O
any	O
sword	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
little	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
minutes	O
Captain	O
Campbel	B-pers
came	O
and	O
rapped	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
certainly	O
two	O
pickpockets	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
drank	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
glasses	O
of	O
wine	O
with	O
Captain	O
Clark	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
hurt	O
his	O
finger	O
:	O
This	O
other	O
witness	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
either	O
kill	O
or	O
be	O
killed	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
head	O
this	O
noise	O
,	O
those	O
two	O
men	O
fell	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
murder	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
waiting	O
there	O
till	O
a	O
person	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
Campbel	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
on	O
this	O
second	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
Captain	O
Clark	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
his	O
sword	O
