TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
23d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1749	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Public	O
may	O
be	O
assured	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
during	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CALVERT	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
)	O
the	O
Sessions-Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
Four-pence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
Sessions	O
be	O
carefully	O
compriz	O
'd	O
in	O
One	O
such	O
Four-penny	O
Book	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
farther	O
Burthen	O
on	O
the	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CALVERT	I-pers
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLS	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
LEGG	I-pers
,	O
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cordwell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hippor	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gruby	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sparshott	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tomkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Whitmore	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	O
Hampshire	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicoll	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Mencelin	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Alberry	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Sexton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Geayes	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
475	O
,	O
476	O
,	O
477.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanly	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Anthony	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Batty	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Coxon	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
one	O
holland	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
Leghorn	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
August	O
19	O
.	O
All	O
acquitted	O
.	O
478.	O
Edward	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
moidore	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
nine	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rust	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
479.	O
James	B-pers
Walock	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lawrance	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
offensive	O
weapon	O
called	O
a	O
tinder-box	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Abraham	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
August	O
5	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
a	O
stile	O
in	O
Stepney	B-place
fields	I-place
,	O
August	O
5	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
You	O
Quaker	O
,	O
stand	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Stand	O
,	O
you	O
dog	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
?	O
He	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
covering	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
barrel	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
through	O
the	O
body	O
.	O
Hold	O
your	O
tongue	O
,	O
you	O
dog	O
,	O
said	O
I.	O
Hush	O
,	O
hush	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
immediately	O
.	O
I	O
shifted	O
about	O
and	O
parlied	O
with	O
my	O
stick	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
mark	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Paterson	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
assistance	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
through	O
the	O
posts	O
quick	O
enough	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
through	O
the	O
body	O
if	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
advanced	O
upon	O
him	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
blow	O
with	O
my	O
stick	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
covered	O
the	O
supposed	O
barrel	O
of	O
his	O
tinder-box	O
with	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
bank	O
and	O
run	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ashby	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Macoliston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hindon	I-pers
,	O
all	O
proved	O
the	O
pursuing	O
and	O
taking	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
pistol	O
timber-box	O
was	O
shewed	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
480	O
,	O
481	O
,	O
482.	O
John	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
Bosavern	B-pers
Pen	I-pers
Lez	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Launder	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
forty	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
being	O
feloniously	O
and	O
riotously	O
assembled	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
disturbance	O
of	O
the	O
public	O
peace	O
,	O
did	O
begin	O
to	O
demolish	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
July	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
star	B-place
in	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
;	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
betwixt	O
the	O
2d	O
and	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
betwixt	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
400	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
ringing	O
a	O
bell	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
host	O
,	O
the	O
host	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
running	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
coming	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
coming	O
.	O
About	O
fifty	O
of	O
them	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
hopes	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
a	O
bow	O
and	O
said	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
as	O
the	O
bell	O
came	O
opposite	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
that	O
were	O
past	O
my	O
door	O
wheel	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
fell	O
back	O
towards	O
George	O
's	O
coffee-house	O
door	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
surrounded	O
the	O
whole	O
place	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
stroke	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
lamp	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
advanced	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
directly	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
mercy	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
wrong	O
,	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
or	O
any	O
place	O
of	O
safety	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
fell	O
to	O
breaking	O
my	O
windows	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
fell	O
upon	O
my	O
knees	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
sashes	O
and	O
the	O
glass	O
of	O
my	O
windows	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
10	O
l.	O
nay	O
20	O
l.	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
desist	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
they	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
stop	O
a	O
little	O
:	O
somebody	O
amongst	O
them	O
called	O
out	O
here	O
is	O
10	O
l.	O
here	O
is	O
20	O
l.	O
offered	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
this	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
grave	O
gentleman	O
came	O
jumping	O
from	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
man	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Wrench	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
gentleman	O
,	O
whose	O
Bill	O
was	O
found	O
ignoramus	O
at	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
credit	O
and	O
reputation	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
boys	O
haul	O
away	O
,	O
never	O
mind	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
stop	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
laid	O
all	O
open	O
,	O
they	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
came	O
in	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Eight	O
or	O
ten	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
Willson	O
and	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
breaking	O
between	O
the	O
passage	O
and	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
break	O
the	O
partition	O
with	O
their	O
sticks	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
pieces	O
out	O
with	O
their	O
hands	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
furniture	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
was	O
destroyed	O
;	O
they	O
threw	O
all	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Launder	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
assisting	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
partition	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
my	O
seeing	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
broke	O
down	O
my	O
bar	O
,	O
standing	O
between	O
the	O
fore-parlour	O
and	O
the	O
back-parlour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
break	O
down	O
that	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Launder	O
broke	O
the	O
window	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
lay	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
kill	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
hearing	O
that	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
lie	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
,	O
thinking	O
by	O
that	O
to	O
raise	O
their	O
compassion	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back-parlour	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
immediately	O
say	O
what	O
they	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
and	O
Willson	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
dog	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
dead	O
yet	O
?	O
They	O
cried	O
,	O
all	O
up	O
,	O
all	O
up	O
,	O
all	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
kneel	O
'd	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
knees	O
,	O
kissed	O
their	O
hands	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Launder	O
there	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
below	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
your	O
family	O
and	O
you	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
All	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
excepting	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
then	O
came	O
the	O
guard	O
with	O
a	O
drum	O
beating	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
took	O
to	O
slight	O
;	O
they	O
without	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
guards	O
,	O
the	O
guards	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
all	O
away	O
that	O
could	O
directly	O
.	O
Launder	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
condition	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
before	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
pictures	O
,	O
chairs	O
,	O
a	O
mahogany	O
table	O
and	O
other	O
furniture	O
;	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
except	O
a	O
little	O
marble	O
slab	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
all	O
torn	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
the	O
frames	O
all	O
pulled	O
down	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
meddled	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
walked	O
by	O
your	O
door	O
at	O
first	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
About	O
fifty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
prisoners	O
were	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
ringing	O
of	O
the	O
bell	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Between	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Council	O
for	O
Launder	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Launder	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
their	O
first	O
coming	O
up	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
any	O
time	O
before	O
the	O
guards	O
came	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
the	O
guards	O
came	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
guards	O
came	O
did	O
not	O
the	O
tumult	O
cease	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
all	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
their	O
escape	O
.	O
Council	O
for	O
Willson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Willson	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
mark	O
any	O
particular	O
thing	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
laid	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
others	O
besides	O
him	O
break	O
the	O
shutters	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
many	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
come	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
positive	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
among	O
so	O
many	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
kissing	O
their	O
hands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
kiss	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
all	O
three	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
kiss	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
others	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Willson	O
and	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Six	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
rent	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
pay	O
the	O
scavenger	O
and	O
the	O
taxes	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
pay	O
the	O
scavenger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
pays	O
that	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Thompson	O
does	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Thompson	O
the	O
tenant	O
of	O
this	O
house	O
or	O
you	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
does	O
Thompson	O
pay	O
the	O
scavengers	O
rates	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
reason	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
give	O
that	O
reason	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
pay	O
30	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
to	O
George	O
-	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
answer	O
my	O
question	O
,	O
why	O
does	O
he	O
that	O
is	O
neither	O
tenant	O
or	O
landlord	O
pay	O
the	O
scavengers	O
rates	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
The	O
reason	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
some	O
people	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
disorderly	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
paid	O
it	O
,	O
although	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
other	O
rates	O
does	O
Thompson	O
pay	O
besides	O
the	O
scavenger	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
rates	O
do	O
you	O
pay	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
rates	O
I	O
do	O
pay	O
?	O
Q.	O
Recollect	O
them	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
pay	O
the	O
land-tax	O
and	O
the	O
doctor	O
's	O
dues	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
thoughts	O
of	O
letting	O
Thompson	O
have	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lett	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
the	O
scavenger	O
receive	O
the	O
rates	O
of	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
name	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
receipts	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
In	O
Thompson	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
your	O
house	O
but	O
Thompson	O
's	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
lett	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
Thompson	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
not	O
an	O
answer	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
do	O
n't	O
Thompson	O
pay	O
the	O
duty	O
of	O
excise	O
as	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
The	O
licence	O
is	O
in	O
Thompson	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
name	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
renewed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
name	O
was	O
the	O
licence	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
no	O
licence	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
information	O
given	O
against	O
Thompson	O
and	O
me	O
for	O
retailing	O
liquors	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
pay	O
twenty	O
pound	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
Thompson	O
live	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
no	O
share	O
in	O
the	O
profit	O
arising	O
from	O
the	O
sale	O
of	O
the	O
liquors	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
my	O
legs	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
betwixt	O
me	O
and	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
begging	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
desist	O
;	O
they	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
destroy	O
all	O
the	O
bawdy-houses	O
in	O
general	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
guards	O
came	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
begining	O
of	O
the	O
riot	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
this	O
Thompson	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
live	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
not	O
he	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
profits	O
of	O
your	O
business	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
profits	O
of	O
my	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pay	O
all	O
the	O
rent	O
with	O
my	O
own	O
money	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
night	O
the	O
2d	O
or	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
12	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Willson	O
and	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
sticks	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
tearing	O
down	O
the	O
wainscot	O
and	O
knocking	O
it	O
with	O
their	O
sticks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
there	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
eight	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
hung	O
about	O
their	O
necks	O
and	O
begged	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
desist	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
threatened	O
to	O
murder	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
pulled	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
my	O
cap	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Willson	O
and	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
sometimes	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
,	O
sometimes	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
breaking	O
and	O
destroying	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
them	O
10	O
or	O
20	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
seemed	O
at	O
first	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
appeased	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Irishman	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
inclined	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
elderly	O
man	O
came	O
from	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
pull	O
away	O
,	O
my	O
boys	O
,	O
take	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
bawdy-houses	O
,	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
bawdy-houses	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
cried	O
out	O
where	O
are	O
your	O
whores	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
broke	O
all	O
the	O
china	O
,	O
then	O
into	O
the	O
back-parlour	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
buroe	O
and	O
glass	O
case	O
,	O
about	O
50	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
they	O
tore	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
and	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
hurry	O
,	O
hurry	O
down	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
boys	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lander	O
I	O
saw	O
knocking	O
at	O
the	O
clock	O
with	O
an	O
oaken	O
stick	O
or	O
great	O
cane	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
that	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
shoved	O
me	O
about	O
like	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
they	O
put	O
their	O
hands	O
all	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
cried	O
all	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
all	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
beating	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
Lander	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
beaten	O
almost	O
to	O
a	O
jelly	O
;	O
they	O
broke	O
a	O
great	O
sconce	O
glass	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
we	O
dare	O
not	O
whisper	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
might	O
all	O
the	O
damage	O
amount	O
to	O
together	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
300	O
l.	O
will	O
not	O
make	O
us	O
amends	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
Lander	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
soldiers	O
came	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
demolished	O
before	O
the	O
soldiers	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Willson	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
since	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
face	O
and	O
stroaked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
they	O
would	O
desist	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
broke	O
your	O
windows	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
The	O
windows	O
were	O
all	O
open	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
seeing	O
the	O
windows	O
broken	O
,	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
all	O
in	O
.	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
broke	O
the	O
clock	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
inside	O
partition	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Willson	O
do	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
say	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
by	O
somebody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Nixon	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
married	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
scavenger	O
coming	O
to	O
demand	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
rates	O
were	O
due	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Thompson	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
Thompson	O
ever	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
since	O
you	O
came	O
there	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
come	O
sometimes	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
ladies	O
hair	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
distinguish	O
them	O
when	O
the	O
lamp	O
was	O
broke	O
.	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
ten	O
candles	O
brought	O
and	O
lighted	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
this	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
affair	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
whole	O
action	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
mob	O
a	O
coming	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
before	O
they	O
got	O
there	O
:	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
clock	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
break	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
fore-parlour	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
pay	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
glasses	O
,	O
the	O
pictures	O
;	O
beat	O
down	O
the	O
bird-cages	O
;	O
the	O
partition	O
that	O
parts	O
the	O
entry	O
from	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
greatest	O
rascal	O
amongst	O
them	O
all	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
You	O
dog	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
dead	O
yet	O
?	O
I	O
saw	O
Willson	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
settee	O
bed	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
thrown	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
help	O
to	O
lift	O
the	O
bed	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
done	O
above	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Lander	O
there	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Lander	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
guards	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
strike	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
back	O
was	O
towards	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
push	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
partition	O
boards	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
lighted	O
the	O
man	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
that	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
there	O
to	O
hide	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
at	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
Willson	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Lander	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
entry	O
door	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
remain	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
then	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
tell	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
began	O
breaking	O
the	O
windows	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
first	O
without	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
no	O
signification	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
see	O
this	O
assembly	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
Just	O
beyond	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
church	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
Lander	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
guards	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
any	O
farther	O
mischief	O
than	O
with	O
his	O
shoulder	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
Willson	O
in	O
the	O
fore-parlour	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
He	O
helped	O
to	O
lift	O
out	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
striking	O
about	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
constantly	O
with	O
Mr.	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Wood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
lamp	O
broken	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
waiter	O
or	O
servant	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
coming	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
crying	O
,	O
Huzza	O
,	O
the	O
star	O
,	O
the	O
star	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
stick	O
,	O
three	O
foot	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
or	O
four	O
foot	O
long	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wood	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
break	O
the	O
clock	O
with	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
short	O
stick	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
struck	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Wood	O
.	O
Not	O
long	O
enough	O
to	O
walk	O
with	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nixon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
,	O
I	O
collect	O
the	O
scavenger	O
's	O
rate	O
.	O
On	O
April	O
the	O
fourth	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wood	O
for	O
the	O
rate	O
due	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
to	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
here	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
paid	O
me	O
in	O
Thompson	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
the	O
sum	O
was	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
Wood	O
or	O
his	O
wife	O
are	O
persons	O
to	O
be	O
believed	O
upon	O
their	O
oaths	O
?	O
Nixon	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
word	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
not	O
;	O
for	O
my	O
part	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hang	O
a	O
dog	O
or	O
a	O
cat	O
upon	O
their	O
evidence	O
,	O
they	O
keep	O
such	O
a	O
bad	O
house	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
threatened	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
neighbours	O
are	O
afraid	O
to	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
Willson	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Slege	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Tooly	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
Willson	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
journeyman	O
shoemaker	O
;	O
he	O
dined	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
till	O
3	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
was	O
mentioned	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
that	O
day	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
divine	O
service	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
reckoned	O
him	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mealyon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
bell	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
ostler	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
John	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
about	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
served	O
his	O
apprenticeship	O
where	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
lives	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
alone	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
again	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Black-friers	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
mentioned	O
this	O
riot	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
reckon	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
hard	O
at	O
his	O
trade	O
for	O
a	O
living	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lidon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Willson	O
about	O
18	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
master	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Willson	O
about	O
18	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
his	O
business	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
any	O
I	O
know	O
in	O
the	O
trade	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
in	O
riots	O
or	O
quarrels	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Willson	O
about	O
a	O
Year	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
ready	O
to	O
run	O
into	O
such	O
sort	O
of	O
mischief	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
thought	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
Lander	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Lander	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
in	O
Bridges-street	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
many	O
more	O
till	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
company	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
back-room	O
with	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
;	O
how	O
long	O
they	O
staid	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
mention	O
made	O
of	O
this	O
riot	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
Lander	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Bridges-street	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
directly	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ball	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Ryon	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Kelley	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Ryan	I-pers
.	O
Lander	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
us	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Bridges-street	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
towards	O
Charing	O
cross	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
guards	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
Cecil-Court	O
and	O
Round-court	O
;	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
Soldier	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
disperse	O
a	O
mob	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
it	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
dry	O
;	O
says	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lander	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
can	O
see	O
a	O
house	O
open	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
Lander	O
drank	O
to	O
the	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
on	O
fair	O
and	O
easy	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
affairs	O
;	O
the	O
soldiers	O
pursued	O
the	O
mob	O
towards	O
Temple-bar	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
seems	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
Wood	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
Wood	O
's	O
door	O
?	O
Ryon	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
past	O
one	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
mob	O
disperse	O
at	O
the	O
soldiers	O
coming	O
?	O
Ryon	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
off	O
when	O
the	O
drum	O
beat	O
,	O
and	O
Lander	O
was	O
there	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ives	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
guard	O
that	O
was	O
detach	O
'd	O
on	O
this	O
Riot	O
Sunday	O
,	O
July	O
2	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
dry	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
any	O
water	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
.	O
Presently	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
last	O
witness	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lander	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
near	O
Southampton-street	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cellar	O
open	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drank	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
drink	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
did	O
not	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
thank	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
my	O
command	O
,	O
and	O
over-took	O
them	O
near	O
Somerset-house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
window-shutters	O
were	O
demolished	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
party	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
minutes	O
for	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
Stairs	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lander	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Rioters	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
such	O
Rascals	O
as	O
you	O
cause	O
us	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
trouble	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
gentleman	O
soldier	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
speak	O
;	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
story	O
of	O
his	O
giving	O
me	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
up	O
stairs	O
or	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
man	O
,	O
describing	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
his	O
cloaths	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
this	O
relation	O
to	O
be	O
all	O
true	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
do	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
The	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Newgate	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
.	O
Lander	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
lad	O
as	O
ever	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cleyton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Lander	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
.	O
Lander	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
an	O
unspotted	O
character	O
,	O
for	O
whatever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Dominick	O
Fullam	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Lander	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
For	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
about	O
14	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
fellow	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Peruke	O
maker	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
a	O
clergyman	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
inclinable	O
to	O
riotous	O
proceedings	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
keeping	O
a	O
birth	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Horse-shoe	O
,	O
Temple	O
bar	O
,	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
journeyman	O
upwards	O
of	O
16	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Plank	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
keeping	O
bad	O
company	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Black	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
above	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Keen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
industrious	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lidal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
between	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Karr	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
April	O
to	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
no	O
servant	O
could	O
behave	O
better	O
.	O
Willson	O
and	O
Pen	O
Lez	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
.	O
Lander	O
acquitted	O
.	O
483.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Guinea	O
,	O
2	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
1	O
pound	O
of	O
Jourdan	B-pers
Almonds	I-pers
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
,	O
May	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
with	O
honour	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
Ordered	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
inserted	O
by	O
the	O
London	O
jury	O
that	O
tried	O
them	O
.	O
484.	O
David	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
160	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
35	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
Pooley	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
12	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
in	O
divers	O
parcels	O
,	O
had	O
taken	O
these	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
486.	O
James	B-pers
Eakins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
transportation	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
time	O
prefix	O
'd	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
indictment	O
laid	O
against	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Clap	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
wages	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
sister	O
,	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
ships	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
70	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
transported	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1739.	O
and	O
that	O
witnesses	O
were	O
subpena	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
industry	O
of	O
Clap	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
kingdom	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1741.	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
487.	O
James	B-pers
Jewel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Boshet	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
conceal	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
brass	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
488	O
,	O
489	O
,	O
490.	O
David	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
Griffith	B-pers
Cheriton	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
M'Daniel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
,	O
4	O
silver	O
teaspoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sh	O
ammy-gloves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
longlawn	O
,	O
12	O
pewter-plates	O
,	O
6	O
China-cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
1	O
periwig	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
491	O
,	O
492.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kempton	I-pers
and	O
Moses	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Will	I-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Manley	O
Nichols	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edw	B-pers
Lions	I-pers
,	O
3	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
diaper	O
napkin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Lions	I-pers
;	O
2	O
linen	O
wastcoats	O
,	O
1	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
1	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
3	O
brass-candlesticks	O
,	O
1	O
copper-pot	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Here	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
evidence	O
,	O
than	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Kempton	O
had	O
said	O
against	O
Wright	O
and	O
Nichols	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
did	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
493.	O
John	B-pers
Mooney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Seymour	B-pers
Stocker	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
1	O
gold-watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Aug.	O
20	O
.	O
Seymour	B-pers
Stocker	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
home	O
from	O
Stepney	O
,	O
near	O
Ratcliff-cross	B-place
,	O
Aug.	O
20	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
met	O
me	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
,	O
demanding	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
immediately	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
a	O
second	O
person	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
;	O
this	O
second	O
person	O
took	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
trip	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
upon	O
me	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
robbed	O
another	O
person	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
omitted	O
mentioning	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
the	O
sum	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
and	O
laid	O
him	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
telling	O
us	O
they	O
would	O
shoot	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
stir	O
;	O
then	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
we	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
Seymour	B-pers
Stocker	I-pers
,	O
sen	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
father	O
to	O
the	O
prosecuter	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
porter	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
from	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Magpy	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
place	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
directed	O
by	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Keates	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Chandos-street	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
son	O
.	O
Isabelia	O
Keates	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
that	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
herself	O
Judith	O
Wallice	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Capt	O
.	O
Bayley	O
's	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
advertisement	O
,	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
stop	O
it	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Wallice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Keates	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
being	O
blooded	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
blooded	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
by	O
Dr.	O
Swinney	O
,	O
)	O
who	O
had	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
ever	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
wore	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Bayley	O
wore	O
one	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
captain	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
20	O
guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
20	O
I	O
must	O
get	O
15.	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
each	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
men	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
ship-mates	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
all	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
wanted	O
20	O
guineas	O
on	O
Capt	O
.	O
Bayley	O
's	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
angry	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
father	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
and	O
committed	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
witnesses	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
full	O
of	O
contradiction	O
amongst	O
themselves	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
494.	O
Ann	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
495.	O
John	B-pers
Barcley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
silver	O
pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
good	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
496.	O
James	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
certain-field	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Whitebread	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
1	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
3	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Whitebread	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
New	B-place
River	I-place
head	I-place
,	O
there	O
met	O
me	O
3	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
a	O
little	O
wanting	O
of	O
eleven	O
;	O
immediately	O
he	O
clap	O
'd	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
:	O
two	O
more	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
a	O
stick	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pockets	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
keys	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
immediately	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
was	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
taller	O
than	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
accomplice	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
to	O
be	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
The	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
being	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
one	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
were	O
coming	O
home	O
to	O
Chick	O
lane	O
from	O
towards	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
New-market	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
Arnold	O
and	O
Bedford	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Arnold	O
before	O
;	O
they	O
two	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
first	O
fields	O
by	O
Clarkenwell	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
stop	O
the	O
first	O
gentleman	O
he	O
came	O
nigh	O
,	O
which	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
standing	O
together	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
)	O
I	O
hear	O
a	O
step	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
money	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
drink	O
his	O
health	O
:	O
with	O
that	O
Bedford	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
!	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
you	O
have	O
about	O
you	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
having	O
the	O
pistol	O
at	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
breast	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
feel	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
ere	O
a	O
lodge	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
three	O
little	O
keys	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
so	O
doing	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
swivel	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
into	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
and	O
I	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
over	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
New-market	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
Bedford	O
carry	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
to	O
a	O
night-house	O
,	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Crown	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
sat	O
and	O
drank	O
till	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
Matthew	O
Bedford	O
carry	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
to	O
two	O
Jews	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
share	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
Bedford	O
gave	O
him	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
Matthew	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
surrendered	O
myself	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
the	O
whole	O
truth	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
at	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Whitebread	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
drink	O
your	O
health	O
?	O
Whitebread	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
but	O
a	O
shilling	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
drink	O
my	O
health	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
swivil	O
of	O
your	O
watch	O
broke	O
in	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Whitebread	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
497.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bowdey	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bowdey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
1	O
close-stool	O
pan	O
,	O
1	O
pewter	O
chamber	O
pot	O
,	O
1	O
pewter	O
pot	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Kenneth	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
9	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
498	O
,	O
499.	O
John	B-pers
Collison	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Altridge	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
bay	O
gelding	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
mare	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Hersel	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Aug.	O
21	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hersel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Chatham	B-place
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
my	O
servant	O
s.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
farm	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
horse	O
and	O
mare	O
Aug.	O
22.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
yard	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
stop	O
'd	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
sent	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
the	O
horse	O
and	O
mare	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
hop	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cow-lane	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
horse	O
and	O
mare	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
no	O
sooner	O
bid	O
them	O
6	O
pounds	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
being	O
worth	O
much	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
inquiry	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
vouchers	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
none	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
their	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
sent	O
her	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
horse	O
and	O
mare	O
as	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burchet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
suspicious	O
persons	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
asked	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
horses	O
;	O
he	O
stood	O
as	O
though	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
put	O
words	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
from	O
Lee	O
in	O
Essex	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
replied	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
know	O
without	O
being	O
told	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
talked	O
thus	O
to	O
him	O
of	O
our	O
suspicion	O
,	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
lose	O
his	O
horses	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
must	O
lose	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
lose	O
them	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
witness	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
an	O
old	O
soldier	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
horses	O
were	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
their	O
money	O
and	O
laughed	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
ragged	O
coat	O
looked	O
more	O
likely	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
horse	O
than	O
to	O
vouch	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Collison	O
said	O
,	O
Aldridge	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
his	O
mistress	O
's	O
son	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
horse	O
and	O
mare	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
500.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
quart	O
mug	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
12	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Dolphin	B-place
in	O
Honey-lane-market	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
some	O
time	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
tankard	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
June	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
paid	O
and	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
when	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
the	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
501.	O
John	B-pers
Jeb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pieces	O
of	O
cut	O
leather	O
for	O
shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
other	O
pieces	O
cut	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
House	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
28	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
502	O
,	O
503.	O
John	B-pers
Ivery	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Shuttel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
504	O
,	O
505.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Colebeck	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entring	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Lowrey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
salts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
cream-pots	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
five	O
large	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
salt	O
shovels	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
punch-ladle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pewter	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Rob	B-pers
Lowrey	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
15	O
.	O
The	O
only	O
evidence	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
an	O
Accomplice	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
506	O
,	O
507.	O
David	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Dumsey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
Edward	B-pers
Neway	I-pers
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
Aug.	O
6	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Neway	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
by	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Saltpeter-bank	B-place
,	O
through	O
Fleming	B-place
's	I-place
church-yard	I-place
,	O
a	O
man	O
collared	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
up	O
came	O
three	O
more	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
gates	O
of	O
the	O
glass-house	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
and	O
rummaged	O
my	O
pockets	O
;	O
one	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
wig	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
beat	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
barbarous	O
manner	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Murder	O
.	O
A	O
coach	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
Boyd	O
staid	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
after	O
the	O
coach	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
-	O
Galway	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
that	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Edward	B-pers
Neway	I-pers
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight-o'clock	O
,	O
his	O
face	O
and	O
head	O
were	O
all	O
bloody	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
men	O
met	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Salt-peterbank	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
told	O
they	O
run	O
towards	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
directed	O
to	O
Murphey	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	O
.	O
Murphy	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
hanger	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
Murphy	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
came	O
out	O
;	O
David	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
drew	O
his	O
hanger	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
without	O
a	O
stick	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
a	O
fellow	O
servant	O
,	O
lend	O
me	O
your	O
stick	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
to	O
their	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Nightingale-lane	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
followed	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
down	O
Black-horse-yard	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
directed	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
New-rag	O
fair	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
then	O
about	O
twelve	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
Boyd	O
liv	O
'd	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
doors	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
surrounded	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Boyd	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
who	O
followed	O
us	O
,	O
get	O
some	O
links	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
we	O
lighted	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Murphy	O
;	O
Boyd	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
stick	O
was	O
shewed	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
bloody	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
Murphy	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
Boyd	O
run	O
up	O
stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
concluded	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
darted	O
an	O
iron	O
spindle	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
wooden	O
handle	O
)	O
at	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
from	O
above	O
,	O
but	O
missed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
drew	O
back	O
.	O
Then	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
company	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
chair	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
walked	O
near	O
him	O
with	O
an	O
iron	O
bar	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
glass-house	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
Dumsey	O
was	O
jump	O
'd	O
into	O
bed	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
cloaths	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
Boyd	O
run	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
.	O
Three	O
other	O
witnesses	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
Boyd	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
the	O
bloody	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
was	O
that	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
so	O
ill	O
with	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
Dumsey	O
.	O
Boyd	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Dumsey	O
acquitted	O
.	O
508	O
,	O
509.	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Macguire	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Macguire	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
gallons	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
1	O
gallon	O
of	O
carraway-water	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
wooden	O
casks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
19	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
510.	O
James	B-pers
Masterson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Winn	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
;	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Aug.	O
16	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
511.	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodgings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Valentine	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
512	O
,	O
513.	O
William	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mun	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Aug.	O
14	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
514	O
,	O
515.	O
Adam	B-pers
Romley	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Douglass	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Batty	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
July	O
25	O
.	O
Romley	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Douglass	O
,	O
guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
516.	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Wyburd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pewter	O
plate	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
517.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mackelly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gwinn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
linnen	O
check	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
30	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
Feb.	O
24	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
518.	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Conoley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Aug.	O
17	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
519.	O
Peter	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
hilt	O
to	O
a	O
sword	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Noah	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
520.	O
John	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
India	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tatam	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
521.	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
1	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Foss	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
522.	O
Charles	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Feltham	I-pers
,	O
July	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
523.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
half	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
July	O
7	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
524.	O
George	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bonafous	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
525.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Wale	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
to	O
the	O
alderman	O
before	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
526.	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Donover	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
1	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
mother	O
of	O
pearl	O
buttons	O
,	O
1	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
Aug.	O
12	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Kentish	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
over-against	O
Pancras	B-place
church	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
seised	O
me	O
instantly	O
;	O
they	O
unbuttoned	O
my	O
breeches	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Mocoa	O
buttons	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
hat	O
and	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
bad	O
36	O
shillings	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
shillings	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
to	O
terrify	O
me	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
my	O
knee-buckles	O
was	O
silver	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
attempting	O
to	O
take	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
silver	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
never	O
meddled	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
they	O
stood	O
over	O
me	O
consulting	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
pray	O
do	O
n't	O
make	O
surgeon	O
's	O
work	O
on	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
looked	O
hard	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
what	O
shall	O
we	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
another	O
said	O
,	O
bind	O
him	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
halter	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
and	O
pushed	O
me	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
way	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
four	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
Satlor	O
near	O
Temple	O
bar	O
,	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
examined	O
apart	O
,	O
they	O
appeared	O
full	O
of	O
contradiction	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
jury	O
gave	O
no	O
credit	O
to	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
527	O
,	O
528.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Knot	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
sixpence	O
half	O
penny	O
,	O
July	O
22	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Knot	I-pers
.	O
The	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
stopped	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
lane	O
,	O
over-against	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
east	I-place
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
10	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Robinson	O
seised	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
running	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
me	O
against	O
a	O
bank	O
.	O
Cross	O
the	O
black	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
Robinson	O
called	O
out	O
help	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
a	O
bitch	O
would	O
be	O
gone	O
.	O
Cross	O
run	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
Thompson	O
several	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
six	O
pence	O
half-penny	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
run	O
away	O
and	O
Thompson	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
black	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
moonlight	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
within	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
the	O
accomplice	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Henry	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
but	O
being	O
cast	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
that	O
.	O
529	O
,	O
530.	O
John	B-pers
Wilde	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Lucking	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Yates	I-pers
Warring	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
petticoat	O
,	O
shift	O
,	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
straw	O
hat	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
531.	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
mahogony	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
3	O
tea-canisters	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
silver	O
spoons	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Heaven	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
532.	O
Philip	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Tidd	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Henry	B-pers
Aplen	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
half-penny	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
July	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
an	O
accomplice	O
with	O
Valentine	O
Godwin	O
and	O
James	O
Johnson	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
cast	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
executed	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
tryal	O
the	O
reader	O
is	O
referred	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
422	O
,	O
423.	O
in	O
the	O
July	O
sessions	O
paper	O
.	O
533.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
geese	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tollman	I-pers
,	O
July	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
534.	O
George	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
yards	O
of	O
English	O
canvas	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
535.	O
Peter	B-pers
Halfpeny	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
german	O
serge	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
,	O
July	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
536.	O
John	B-pers
Davidson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
leaden	O
weight	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Legg	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
537.	O
George	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Heartly	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
538.	O
John	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
saws	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
4	O
moulding	O
planes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
with	O
other	O
carpenters	O
tools	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
and	O
others	O
,	O
July	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
539.	O
Griffith	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
brass	O
mould	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pickard	I-pers
.	O
Aug.	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
540.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Westfield	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
541.	O
Edward	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
brass	O
cock	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
leaden	O
pipe	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edw	B-pers
.	I-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
542.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
ripping	O
,	O
cutting	O
and	O
carrying	O
away	O
20	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mellvin	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
543.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Close	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
544.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
pound	O
weight	O
and	O
1	O
half	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Osbourn	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
and	O
Co	O
.	O
Aug.	O
4	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
545.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
linnen	O
apron	O
and	O
4	O
linnen	O
caps	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
Hawley	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
546.	O
George	B-pers
Platt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
bundles	O
of	O
iron	O
hoops	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Backhouse	I-pers
,	O
June	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
547	O
,	O
548.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kempton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s	O
.	O
4	O
flaxen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
2	O
dowlass	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
damask	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
3	O
linnen	O
aprons	O
,	O
3	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
daughter	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Pear-tree	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
The	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drying	O
loft	O
;	O
Kempton	O
when	O
taken	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
door	O
that	O
opens	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
dwelling-house	O
into	O
the	O
drying-lost	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
we	O
go	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
buying	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Kempton	O
confessed	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
Nichols	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
549.	O
Eleford	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
quart	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Batiscome	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Daniel	O
,	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Batiscome	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Butchers-arms	B-place
in	O
Hare-street	B-place
,	I-place
Bethnal-green	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
presently	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
third	O
person	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
having	O
paid	O
for	O
his	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
tankard	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
where	O
it	O
stood	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
change	O
,	O
while	O
my	O
back	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
beer	O
was	O
flung	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
tankard	O
were	O
gone	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
pursue	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
lighting	O
my	O
pipe	O
by	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gear	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Drury	O
lane	O
;	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
mother	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
fit	O
him	O
out	O
for	O
sea	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
3	O
l.	O
was	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
your	O
mother	O
to	O
justify	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
money	O
you	O
ask	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
advertise	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
tankard	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
father	O
in	O
law	O
a	O
dyer	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
former	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
550.	O
John	B-pers
Alford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lillwall	I-pers
,	O
and	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
did	O
put	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
15	O
d.	O
in	O
monies	O
,	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
.	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lillwall	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Stepney	B-place
to	O
Bow	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Stepney	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
(	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
on	O
foot	O
)	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
turn	O
'd	O
short	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
money	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
;	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
bayonet	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
held	O
it	O
pointing	O
to	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
six-pences	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
half-pence	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
green	O
plush	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
lac	O
'd	O
hat	O
,	O
the	O
sides	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
put	O
down	O
before	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
more	O
behind	O
,	O
the	O
token	O
is	O
this	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
stop	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
nothing	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
molest	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tribes	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
describing	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
another	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
one	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
description	O
given	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
person	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
inquire	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
whom	O
he	O
said	O
knew	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Shoulder	O
of	O
Mutton	O
in	O
the	O
Mint	O
,	O
near	O
George	O
's	O
fields	O
,	O
in	O
Southwark	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
there	O
betwixt	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
two-penny	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
companions	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
They	O
would	O
not	O
serve	O
us	O
with	O
any	O
beer	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
both	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
secure	O
him	O
from	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
constable	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
without	O
a	O
warrant	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
last	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
wav	O
'd	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
before	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
gamming	O
way	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
look	O
,	O
am	O
I	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
,	O
repeating	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
his	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
three	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Maynard	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
justice	O
Clark	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
mistake	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lester	I-pers
and	O
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Mackings	I-pers
,	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
their	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
playing	O
a	O
game	O
at	O
cards	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
Wm	O
Pope	O
a	O
coachman	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
his	O
house	O
with	O
his	O
coach	O
,	O
stop	O
'd	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
3	O
tankards	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
one	O
Roberson	O
a	O
diover	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
9	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Roberson	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
who	O
described	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
have	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
boxes	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
coachman	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
had	O
a	O
printed	O
linen	O
gown	O
on	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
mistress	O
had	O
a	O
brown	O
calamanco	O
gown	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
Elix	O
.	O
Matterson	O
,	O
a	O
near	O
neighbour	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
a	O
flower	O
'd	O
short	O
linen	O
gown	O
on	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
contradictions	O
:	O
all	O
the	O
witnesses	O
were	O
examin	O
'd	O
a	O
part	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
551.	O
Martin	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
duffel	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Bricker	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
Aug.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
552.	O
John	B-pers
Bowley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
.	O
July	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
553.	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
dark	O
brown	O
wig	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carril	I-pers
,	O
1	O
flaxen	O
colour	O
'd	O
wig	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Graswate	I-pers
.	O
July	O
28	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
554.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Graising	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
veal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
lamb	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ransford	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
555.	O
Francis	B-pers
Seacons	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
personating	O
one	O
Ignazio	B-pers
D'Ignazi	I-pers
,	O
and	O
receiving	O
3	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
11	O
d.	O
due	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
D'Ignazi	O
,	O
for	O
services	O
done	O
on	O
board	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
ships	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Pay	O
Office	O
.	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
on	O
the	O
indictment	O
for	O
the	O
crown	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
a	O
cheat	O
in	O
common	O
law	O
.	O
556.	O
Jane	B-pers
Ferry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
ounces	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
.	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
557.	O
William	B-pers
Kane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
large	O
bell	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
558.	O
John	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Saven	B-pers
Nellson	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
penny	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Saven	O
.	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
Saven	O
Nellson	O
.	O
The	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
coming	O
over	O
Tower-hill	B-place
,	O
there	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
three	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
with	O
drawn	O
cutlasses	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
cut	O
me	O
to	O
pieces	O
;	O
while	O
one	O
stood	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
perceiving	O
the	O
watchman	O
coming	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
watch	O
,	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
was	O
carry	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ditchet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
and	O
7	O
pence	O
,	O
upon	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Leget	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
beadle	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
watch	O
,	O
watch	O
,	O
July	O
19	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
prosecuter	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
others	O
just	O
gone	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
discharge	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
vessels	O
:	O
I	O
sold	O
my	O
ticket	O
at	O
the	O
Half-way-house	O
,	O
between	O
Greenwich	O
and	O
Woolwich	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
enter	O
on	O
board	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
ships	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
myself	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Tyger	O
that	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Towerhill	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Hamburgh	O
Arms	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
before	O
,	O
thinking	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
morning	O
;	O
coming	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
late	O
;	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
above	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Caveragh	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
Hazard	O
,	O
said	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
a	O
friend	O
said	O
I	O
;	O
before	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
will	O
they	O
not	O
let	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
will	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
disturbance	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
came	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
fled	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
this	O
man	O
seeing	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
mistaken	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
men	O
,	O
any	O
further	O
than	O
seeing	O
them	O
here	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
where	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
no	O
house	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
559.	O
John	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
alias	O
Blare	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
assizes	O
,	O
holden	O
at	O
Croyden	O
in	O
Surrey	O
,	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
wherein	O
Thomas	B-pers
Supple	I-pers
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
upon	O
Adam	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
alias	O
Blare	O
,	O
did	O
feloniously	O
receive	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
produc	O
'd	O
the	O
record	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
office	O
of	O
the	O
clark	O
of	O
the	O
ossize	O
for	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Surrey	O
.	O
The	O
record	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
August	O
the	O
3d	O
before	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
and	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Abney	I-pers
,	O
Kt	O
.	O
July	O
1.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Supple	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Adam	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
1	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
1	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
1	O
polish	O
'd	O
steel	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
2	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
coin	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Adam	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mackhey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Fenix-ally	O
by	O
Long	O
Acre	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
Supple	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
July	O
we	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Renolds	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hughs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
Gallows-hill	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
mile	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
Kingston	O
;	O
Supple	O
went	O
and	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
first	O
Chaise	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Renolds	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
3	O
diamond	O
rings	O
,	O
2	O
diamond	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
2	O
of	O
these	O
were	O
mourning	O
rings	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
rose	O
diamond	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
there	O
were	O
5	O
diamonds	O
in	O
each	O
of	O
these	O
rings	O
,	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
had	O
9	O
diamonds	O
in	O
each	O
ear	O
ring	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
steel-chain	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
seal	O
with	O
a	O
cornelian	O
set	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
cornelian	O
in	O
it	O
:	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Renolds	O
we	O
took	O
2	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
his	O
desiring	O
the	O
rings	O
,	O
we	O
gave	O
him	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
committed	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
us	O
what	O
luck	O
,	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
pretty	O
well	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
being	O
Sunday	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
lodged	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
till	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
for	O
13	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
paying	O
5	O
l.	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
Supple	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
ther	O
e	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
6	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
each	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
me	O
till	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
Supple	O
gave	O
him	O
order	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
other	O
30	O
s.	O
to	O
nobody	O
but	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
had	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
blam	O
'd	O
his	O
wife	O
for	O
offering	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
number	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
pistols	O
and	O
lodged	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
for	O
3	O
days	O
and	O
nights	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
before	O
justice	O
Clark	O
and	O
justice	O
Hammond	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
.	O
Supple	O
is	O
since	O
executed	O
,	O
and	O
hangs	O
in	O
chains	O
on	O
Gallows-hill	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Mackhey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Godard	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
scarlet	O
night-cap	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
glass	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
near	O
and	O
saw	O
three	O
persons	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
ribbon	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
rings	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
off	O
a	O
seal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
have	O
,	O
two	O
diamond	O
rings	O
on	O
his	O
little	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
his	O
fore-finger	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Supple	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
up	O
5	O
l.	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
Supple	O
the	O
5	O
l.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
my	O
husband	O
receive	O
a	O
penny	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
have	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
10	O
l.	O
for	O
they	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
my	O
Husband	O
and	O
Supple	O
)	O
were	O
but	O
young	O
in	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
.	O
July	O
the	O
1st	O
Mr.	O
Reynolds	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
was	O
by	O
him	O
also	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Kingston	O
to	O
London	O
this	O
Mackhey	O
and	O
Supple	O
did	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
worth	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
gold	O
seal	O
about	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
other	O
silver	O
one	O
about	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
steel	O
polish	O
'd	O
chain	O
I	O
gave	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
Mackhey	O
gave	O
