TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
22d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
Cooper	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1749	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Public	O
may	O
be	O
assured	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
during	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
)	O
the	O
Sessions-Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
Four-pence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
Sessions	O
shall	O
be	O
carefully	O
compriz	O
'd	O
in	O
One	O
such	O
Four-penny	O
Book	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
farther	O
Burthen	O
on	O
the	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CALVERT	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
hon	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ABNEY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
the	O
hon	O
.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
,	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
Mark	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Paine	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Blandy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bamford	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Cackett	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Leightenhouse	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
,	O
Duncan	B-pers
Cambell	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bosworth	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cosh	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
240.	O
John	B-pers
Turnbull	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
March	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
241.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cain	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
20	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
Bacon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kinister	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	B-place
,	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
there	O
;	O
said	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
step	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
behind	O
some	O
casks	O
to	O
observe	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
at	O
;	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
was	O
then	O
behind	O
his	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
Bacon	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
struggled	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
coming	O
by	O
helped	O
me	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
242.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edmond	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
243.	O
Jane	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
teaspoon	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Mansel	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Feb	O
25	O
,	O
1747	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Mansel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Broad-way	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
formerly	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
above	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
my	O
cloak	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Strand	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
near	O
the	O
Cock-pit	O
;	O
she	O
untied	O
the	O
Cloak	O
,	O
and	O
bide	O
take	O
it	O
and	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
crying	O
o	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
being	O
old	O
and	O
infirm	O
could	O
not	O
pursue	O
her	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
was	O
made	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
mantua	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Martha	B-pers
Mansel	I-pers
.	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Mansel	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
mantua	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
match	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
being	O
but	O
small	O
,	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
two	O
gowns	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Constable	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
describe	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
before	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
244.	O
Mary	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
and	O
38	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
26	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
245.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
Hanover-square	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
saltseller	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
snuffers	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Stephen	B-pers
Points	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
246.	O
William	B-pers
Barrat	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
blue	O
Coffeau	O
chair	O
seat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hucherson	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
28	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hucherson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chair-man	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
seat	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
chair	O
in	O
Bloomsbury-square	B-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
confest	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
the	O
cushion	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
has	O
sworn	O
to	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
by	O
another	O
chairman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
247.	O
John	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
cask	O
with	O
four	O
iron	O
hoops	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
and	O
Company	O
,	O
March	O
21	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
248.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
with	O
gold	O
buttonholes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s	O
.	O
two	O
Holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
check	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
scarlet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
four	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
several	O
pair	O
of	O
stocking	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
.	O
These	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
Spring	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	I-place
Stepney	I-place
.	O
I	O
knew	O
not	O
any	O
body	O
so	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
my	O
room	O
as	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
servant	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
late	O
turned	O
away	O
.	O
-	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
these	O
goods	O
at	O
the	O
Gun	O
and	O
Holly-bush	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Higgins	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
249	O
,	O
250.	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Shovell	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Lawrence	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass-copper	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Pocock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
copper	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
back	O
house	O
.	O
-	O
Carrey	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Mills	O
brought	O
the	O
copper	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
dead	O
and	O
his	O
mother	O
sent	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
see	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
brought	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
is	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
your	O
mother	O
?	O
he	O
answered	O
no	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
they	O
could	O
prove	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
boy	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Jacob	O
's	O
Well-yard	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
copper	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Mills	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Shovel	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
251.	O
Anne	B-pers
Hinemoor	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
Stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
March	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
252	O
,	O
253.	O
Dominick	B-pers
White	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Horner	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Virginia-street	B-place
,	I-place
Ratcliff	I-place
High-way	I-place
,	O
when	O
I	O
shut	O
up	O
shop	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cellar-door	O
safe	O
bolted	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
found	O
sleep	O
when	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
I	O
was	O
awaked	O
by	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
that	O
are	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
their	O
evidence	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
cellar	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Describe	O
the	O
situation	O
of	O
your	O
cellar	O
.	O
Rogers	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
under	O
my	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
door	O
opens	O
into	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
door	O
and	O
stairs	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
kitchen	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
bulk	O
or	O
place	O
for	O
headroom	O
made	O
rising	O
up	O
,	O
done	O
with	O
boards	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
beat	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
a	O
little	O
child	O
might	O
creep	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
hooks	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
were	O
wrenched	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
posts	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
Horner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shrumsher	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Motes	I-pers
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
crape	O
my	O
wife	O
found	O
afterwards	O
to	O
tie	O
over	O
a	O
face	O
with	O
strings	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shrumsher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
Excise	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Motes	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Virginia-street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
o	O
Trott	O
's	O
court	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Motes	O
saw	O
a	O
stick	O
lie	O
with	O
the	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
slap	O
of	O
the	O
cellar-window	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
somebody	O
here	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
cellar-door	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
cutlasses	O
and	O
lanthorns	O
in	O
our	O
hands	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
shall	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
clap	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
down	O
and	O
I	O
stood	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
friend	O
stood	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
thieves	O
!	O
thieves	O
!	O
some	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
apprehend	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
push	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
kept	O
beating	O
with	O
the	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
back	O
farther	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
:	O
then	O
Mr	O
Fontoloroy	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
handed	O
me	O
a	O
musket	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
valu	O
'd	O
no	O
body	O
:	O
(	O
fearing	O
thieves	O
without	O
before	O
)	O
By	O
this	O
time	O
we	O
had	O
alarm	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
,	O
another	O
neighbour	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Fontoloroy	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
where	O
the	O
thieves	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Fontoloroy	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Horner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Come	O
along	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
assistance	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
that	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
farther	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
White	O
with	O
a	O
Pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
who	O
held	O
it	O
right	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
charg	O
'd	O
?	O
Shrumsher	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
drawn	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
four	O
fingers	O
deep	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
large	O
slug	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
twenty	O
shot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
seize	O
him	O
?	O
Shrumsher	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
for	O
his	O
pistol	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Fontoloroy	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
by	O
my	O
side	O
with	O
his	O
musket	O
charg	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
drop	O
his	O
pistol	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
lowered	O
the	O
muzzel	O
of	O
his	O
pistol	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
drop	O
it	O
:	O
We	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
clasp-knife	O
lying	O
by	O
his	O
foot	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
fall	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
here	O
?	O
He	O
held	O
it	O
fast	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
bottle	O
with	O
gunpowder	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
tied	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fontoloroy	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
this	O
Night	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
o'clock	O
by	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
Thieves	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
step	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
gun	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
keep	O
loaded	O
by	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
safety	O
.	O
I	O
threw	O
up	O
my	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
shoot	O
him	O
dead	O
,	O
thinking	O
some	O
honest	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
overpower	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
hearing	O
the	O
noise	O
of	O
sticks	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Where	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
One	O
of	O
these	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Excise	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
are	O
thieves	O
in	O
this	O
cellar	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
stair-case	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Excise	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
my	O
gun	O
ready	O
cock	O
'd	O
and	O
prim	O
'd	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
keep	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
with	O
you	O
presently	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
,	O
put	O
my	O
cloaths	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
bayonet	O
and	O
a	O
sword	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
's	O
cellar	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
there	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Excise	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
sword	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bayonet	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
gun	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
warrant	O
you	O
we	O
'll	O
secure	O
them	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
both	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
we	O
saw	O
was	O
Horner	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
gun	O
presented	O
towards	O
him	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Surrender	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
without	O
any	O
great	O
trouble	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
persons	O
there	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
cellar	O
(	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
double	O
cellar	O
under	O
the	O
whole	O
house	O
)	O
then	O
we	O
turned	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
in	O
the	O
farther	O
corner	O
stood	O
White	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
lights	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
his	O
pistol	O
directed	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
sprung	O
myself	O
forward	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
muzzle	O
of	O
my	O
gun	O
;	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
hesitating	O
;	O
I	O
threw	O
my	O
piece	O
back	O
with	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
left	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
as	O
before	O
described	O
;	O
in	O
his	O
other	O
hand	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
sword	O
or	O
tuck	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
dangerous	O
weapon	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
to	O
call	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
iron	O
found	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
instrument	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
to	O
splice	O
roaps	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
which	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
probable	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
wrenched	O
open	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
followed	O
these	O
two	O
last	O
witnesses	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
their	O
instruments	O
after	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
poysing	O
to	O
coleway	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
instrument	O
last	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Motes	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
officer	O
of	O
Excise	O
,	O
confirmed	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
before	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shrumsher	I-pers
.	O
Prisoners	O
defence	O
.	O
White	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
the	O
steps	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
steps	O
.	O
Horner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
saw	O
this	O
cellar	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Thieves	O
thieves	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
surrendered	O
directly	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
254.	O
Edward	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Sarah	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
for	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
Jan.	O
13	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
in	O
the	O
stage-coach	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
high-way	O
beyond	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
mounted	O
on	O
a	O
shabby	O
horse	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
brown	O
wig	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
coach-man	O
,	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
stand	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
I	O
sat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
must	O
he	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
trumpery	O
?	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
he	O
be	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
side	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
within	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
The	O
moon	O
shone	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Park	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
towards	O
Chelsea	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
centinels	O
boxes	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Mall	O
,	O
my	O
Mamma	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
that	O
man	O
?	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
us	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
We	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
looked	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
gentleman	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
had	O
met	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Matherson	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
in	O
Jew	O
's	O
Row	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Matherson	O
said	O
,	O
be	O
sure	O
what	O
you	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
here	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
at	O
stake	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
fully	O
convinced	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Bates	O
the	O
baker	O
lived	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
higher	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
voice	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
Feb.	O
25	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
remark	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
by	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
remarkable	O
look	O
about	O
his	O
eye	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
duffel	O
coat	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
in	O
the	O
Mall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
passengers	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
my	O
Mamma	O
,	O
myself	O
,	O
a	O
servant	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
master	O
.	O
Mamma	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
our	O
faces	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
;	O
Mamma	O
sat	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
side	O
the	O
coach	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
to	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
To	O
my	O
side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
My	O
Mamma	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
our	O
oaths	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
his	O
horse	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
betwixt	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
then	O
have	O
him	O
seized	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
Chelsea	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
then	O
in	O
King	O
's	O
Road	O
,	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
Johanna	B-pers
Frankling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
repeat	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
already	O
said	O
by	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
ready	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
attacked	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
going	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
rid	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
in	O
.	O
My	O
daughter	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
that	O
man	O
has	O
no	O
ill	O
design	O
upon	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Turnpike	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
coachman	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
rode	O
by	O
us	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
he	O
would	O
ride	O
slower	O
,	O
and	O
guard	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
by	O
and	O
by	O
my	O
daughter	O
saw	O
him	O
turn	O
,	O
he	O
rid	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
demanded	O
her	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
gave	O
him	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
little	O
oranges	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
can	O
I	O
do	O
with	O
these	O
?	O
So	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
daughter	O
say	O
thank	O
'	O
y	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
;	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
:	O
At	O
last	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
doubted	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
felt	O
her	O
hand	O
for	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
stripped	O
her	O
glove	O
off	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
see	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
interim	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
glove	O
with	O
my	O
ring	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
see	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
ring	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
half	O
pence	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
the	O
young	O
gentleman	O
for	O
his	O
money	O
:	O
Who	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
do	O
n't	O
shoot	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
drive	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Frankling	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
knowing	O
my	O
own	O
counsel	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
for	O
years	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
coach-window	O
up	O
or	O
down	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Franklin	O
.	O
That	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
was	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
so	O
well	O
then	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Frankling	O
.	O
I	O
leaned	O
forward	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
expected	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
your	O
hand	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Frankling	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
your	O
daughter	O
's	O
hand	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Frankling	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
stripped	O
her	O
glove	O
off	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
your	O
hand	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
hard	O
or	O
soft	O
hand	O
?	O
S.	O
Barker	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Mrs.	O
Frankling	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Frankling	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
as	O
positive	O
there	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
now	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Frankling	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
quite	O
certain	O
you	O
was	O
positive	O
then	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Frankling	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
word	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
your	O
daughter	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Frankling	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
then	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Frankling	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
light-coloured	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
a	O
coloured	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
a	O
brown	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
low	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
Memorandum	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Mathewson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
London	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Frankling	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
;	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
Mrs.	O
Barker	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
change	O
countenance	O
;	O
says	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
you	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
?	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
Mamma	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
look	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
:	O
She	O
looked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Says	O
I	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Frankling	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
very	O
great	O
concern	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
.	O
She	O
and	O
her	O
Mother	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
some	O
minutes	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
to	O
be	O
certain	O
;	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
hear	O
his	O
voice	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
more	O
sure	O
,	O
if	O
possible	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
assist	O
you	O
till	O
I	O
find	O
you	O
are	O
sure	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Bates	O
,	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
lived	O
?	O
He	O
answered	O
her	O
,	O
somebody	O
else	O
answered	O
her	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
see	O
bread	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
past	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
voice	O
,	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
Hans	B-pers
Sloane	I-pers
's	O
Lodge	O
that	O
evening	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
from	O
about	O
5	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
till	O
10.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Colonel	O
Du	B-pers
Mar	O
's	O
in	O
Chelsea	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
young	O
master	O
sat	O
with	O
our	O
backs	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
S.	O
Hardy	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
very	O
plain	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
wooden	O
windows	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
drawn	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
were	O
stopp	O
'd	O
?	O
S.	O
Hardy	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
;	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
clock	O
had	O
struck	O
7	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
S.	O
Hardy	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
S.	O
Hardy	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
rings	O
;	O
he	O
felt	O
of	O
both	O
my	O
hands	O
for	O
my	O
rings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
feeling	O
your	O
hands	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
a	O
hand	O
like	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
it	O
soft	O
?	O
S.	O
Hardy	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
soft	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
moon	O
,	O
seemingly	O
white	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
working	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
now	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
then	O
:	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
us	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
swear	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
lusty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dress	O
'd	O
?	O
S.	O
Hardy	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
light	O
duffel	O
coat	O
,	O
almost	O
new	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
wig	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
S.	O
Hardy	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
but	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
for	O
matter	O
of	O
light	O
?	O
S.	O
Hardy	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
pretty	O
light	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
frighten	O
'd	O
so	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
great	O
observations	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
were	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
should	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
swear	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
He	O
damn	O
'd	O
the	O
coachman	O
once	O
,	O
saying	O
:	O
Damn	O
you	O
,	O
ca	O
n't	O
you	O
stop	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dress	O
'd	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
white	O
duffel	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
public-house	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
Ranelaugh	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
sight	O
enough	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
committed	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
was	O
his	O
wig	O
,	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
wig	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
he	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
his	O
hat	O
was	O
put	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
sworn	O
at	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
's	O
?	O
Hunt	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Geo	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
coach	O
that	O
day	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
least	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
few	O
days	O
,	O
these	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
last	O
years	O
past	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
view	O
of	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
him	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
coach	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
his	O
voice	O
like	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Justice	O
Ellis	O
I	O
believed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
guilty	O
person	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
satisfied	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
he	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
make	O
any	O
declarations	O
you	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
time	O
my	O
coach	O
was	O
robbed	O
was	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
.	O
One	O
person	O
I	O
believe	O
robbed	O
it	O
three	O
times	O
:	O
Then	O
his	O
horse	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
tired	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
added	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
hanged	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
that	O
place	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
.	O
That	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
robbed	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
was	O
no	O
way	O
so	O
big	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
his	O
voice	O
,	O
nor	O
manner	O
of	O
behaviour	O
.	O
My	O
coach	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
robbed	O
since	O
Mudget	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Shafaley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
these	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Waterman	O
and	O
Lighterman	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
brought	O
some	O
oil	O
up	O
by	O
water	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
for	O
Sir	O
Hans	B-pers
Sloane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
hot	O
in	O
the	O
Lodge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
before	O
five	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
?	O
Shafaley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
receipt	O
in	O
my	O
pocketbook	O
makes	O
me	O
remember	O
the	O
day	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Bockam	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
bring	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
Sir	O
Hans	O
,	O
the	O
Porter	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
delivering	O
it	O
,	O
gives	O
me	O
a	O
receipt	O
:	O
It	O
was	O
shewed	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
hot	O
pot	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
At	O
six	O
I	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
continued	O
there	O
,	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
bell	O
rung	O
nine	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
going	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Abott	O
.	O
Mr.	O
King	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
eight	O
.	O
Raimont	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
Sir	O
Hans	B-pers
Sloane	I-pers
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
's	O
in	O
Chelsea	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Abott	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Squire	O
,	O
Mr.	O
King	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Shafaley	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
lodge	O
about	O
5	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
continued	O
there	O
'till	O
ten	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
remember	O
the	O
day	O
so	O
positively	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
it	O
from	O
this	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
we	O
were	O
invited	O
to	O
the	O
Magpye	O
to	O
supper	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
Lodge	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
'till	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Abott	O
had	O
been	O
paying	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Before	O
they	O
left	O
my	O
lodge	O
they	O
took	O
down	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
doubled	O
that	O
one	O
up	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
without	O
shoving	O
that	O
down	O
before	O
my	O
feet	O
into	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
examined	O
them	O
about	O
their	O
playing	O
that	O
trick	O
with	O
my	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Shafaley	O
bringing	O
the	O
oil	O
and	O
minuting	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
[	O
which	O
was	O
shewed	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
always	O
enter	O
things	O
down	O
in	O
this	O
book	O
as	O
I	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
from	O
these	O
things	O
I	O
well	O
remember	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Abott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
witnesses	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
before	O
four	O
o'clock	O
:	O
first	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
Hans	O
Sloane	O
's	O
lodge	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
formed	O
the	O
company	O
drinking	O
the	O
pot	O
of	O
Hot	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
255.	O
John	B-pers
Mudgett	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
of	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
twelve-penny	O
worth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
Feb.	O
11	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Chelsea	B-place
;	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
London	B-place
going	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Chelsea	O
stage-coach	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
robbed	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
but	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
robbed	O
us	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
from	O
robbing	O
us	O
for	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
by	O
catching	O
at	O
his	O
pistol	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
his	O
face	O
:	O
one	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
him	O
four	O
halfpence	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
window	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
such	O
as	O
this	O
?	O
He	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Macdonald	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
night	O
for	O
matter	O
of	O
light	O
?	O
Mackdonald	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
as	O
fine	O
as	O
a	O
moon-light	O
as	O
ever	O
was	O
:	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
here	O
who	O
were	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
that	O
night	O
in	O
another	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wrench	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Plume	O
of	O
Feathers	O
at	O
Buckingham-gate	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
very	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
he	O
once	O
did	O
live	O
within	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
doors	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Who	O
thought	O
of	O
seeing	O
you	O
here	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mackdonald	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
you	O
robb	O
'd	O
?	O
Mackdonald	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
hearing	O
Mr.	O
Wrench	O
give	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Chesson	O
in	O
Hertsorshire	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
Chelsea	O
coach	O
that	O
day	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Macdonald	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
our	O
coach	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
Mudget	O
's	O
person	O
and	O
apparel	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
descriptions	O
given	O
by	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
evidences	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
.	O
256.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Staffordshire	I-pers
Nan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
45	O
s.	O
4	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
22d	O
.	O
The	O
principal	O
evidence	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Burry	I-pers
Husband	I-pers
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
257.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Masling	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Masling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Little	B-place
Minories	I-place
at	O
the	O
sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Goat	I-place
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drinking	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
March	O
10	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
about	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
tankard	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Masling	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
neighbours	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
room	O
,	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
rumour	O
reach	O
'd	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
there	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
privately	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
confession	O
how	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
and	O
concealed	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
apron	O
under	O
his	O
bed	O
unknown	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
7	O
l	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
John	B-pers
Acreman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
stealing	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
moreover	O
deposited	O
a	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
piece	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Briscoe	O
's	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
tankard	O
by	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gadbury	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
stealing	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
his	O
concealing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
selling	O
it	O
as	O
before	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
tankard	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
a	O
shipmate	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Cheapside	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
7	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
sailor	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
six	O
persons	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
former	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
258.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Warring	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
16	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
cast	O
upon	O
her	O
own	O
confession	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
259.	O
John	B-pers
Bellone	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
260.	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
5	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-key	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
business	O
to	O
do	O
at	O
the	O
Swan-Tavern	O
opposite	O
Somerset-house	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
I	O
stayed	O
there	O
pretty	O
late	O
March	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
'till	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
of	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
parted	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Ives	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
another	O
person	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
betwixt	O
Catherine-street	B-place
end	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
New	B-place
Church	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
they	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
held	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
then	O
a	O
loose	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
5	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
stooped	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
buckle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
left	O
shoe	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
strap	O
of	O
my	O
shoe	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Turberfile	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
not	O
to	O
understand	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
upon	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
after	O
observing	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Are	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
Sport	O
;	O
then	O
have	O
at	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
to	O
their	O
heels	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
towards	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
stumbled	O
and	O
fell	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Turberfile	O
was	O
foremost	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
close	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
more	O
assistance	O
come	O
by	O
my	O
calling	O
out	O
Watch	O
!	O
Watch	O
!	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
drop	O
'd	O
down	O
betwixt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
legs	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hussey	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
strap	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
two	O
different	O
hands	O
who	O
picked	O
them	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Turberfile	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
from	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
suspecting	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
no	O
good	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
other	O
ran	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
one	O
ran	O
up	O
Eagle-court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
towards	O
the	O
New-church	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
took	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
between	O
his	O
feet	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
robbing	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stumbled	O
and	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
that	O
you	O
took	O
?	O
Turberfile	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
?	O
Henry	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Turberfile	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
Watch	O
!	O
Watch	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Flemming	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
saw	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
feet	O
the	O
watch	O
lie	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
drop	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
a	O
brewer	O
.	O
Harper	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hussey	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
knowing	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Hussey	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
Watch	O
,	O
at	O
little	O
Drury-lane	O
end	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
with	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
and	O
staff	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
these	O
four	O
gentlemen	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bloody	O
nose	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Fleming	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
much	O
oppos	O
'd	O
going	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
blows	O
to	O
quell	O
his	O
obstinacy	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
261	O
,	O
362.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Elder	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
guineas	O
and	O
22	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
March	O
6	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
263.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hobson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hazard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Cavenaugh	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
prosecuter	O
varied	O
in	O
his	O
account	O
from	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
264.	O
William	B-pers
Maclocklin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Tribe	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoebuckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Tribe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
three	O
Tuns	O
at	O
Bow	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
London	O
about	O
my	O
wine	O
licence	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
I	O
took	O
Archibald	B-pers
Forister	I-pers
the	O
watchman	O
at	O
Mile	B-place
end	I-place
to	O
light	O
me	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
met	O
us	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
more	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
first	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
watchman	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
White-chappel	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
came	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
full	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
turned	O
with	O
our	O
faces	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
directing	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
person	O
came	O
up	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
trip	O
on	O
my	O
heel	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
fell	O
against	O
the	O
bank	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
upon	O
my	O
throat	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
from	O
making	O
a	O
noise	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
,	O
friend	O
?	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
you	O
dog	O
!	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
grabble	O
in	O
my	O
right-hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
right-hand	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
lame	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
money	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
side	O
:	O
in	O
this	O
time	O
the	O
watchman	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
his	O
light	O
put	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
crying	O
out	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
knowing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Bar	O
,	O
inadvertently	O
said	O
,	O
Macklocklin	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
you	O
so	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
you	O
two	O
days	O
and	O
a	O
night	O
in	O
custody	O
for	O
knocking	O
a	O
man	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
lent	O
you	O
my	O
hat	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
he	O
speaking	O
that	O
word	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
him	O
cry	O
out	O
more	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
have	O
mercy	O
on	O
me	O
:	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
pray	O
gentlemen	O
do	O
n't	O
commit	O
murder	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
money	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
pocket	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
by	O
my	O
intreaties	O
they	O
seemed	O
a	O
little	O
softned	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
left	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
all	O
had	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
robbing	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
and	O
welcome	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
buckles	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
with	O
my	O
left	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
right	O
shoebuckle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Tribe	O
.	O
One	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
took	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
off	O
me	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
lying	O
against	O
the	O
bank	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
haul	O
'd	O
the	O
watchman	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
legs	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
pray	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
helped	O
me	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
sooner	O
on	O
my	O
legs	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
(	O
I	O
suppose	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
took	O
me	O
a	O
violent	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Deliver	O
!	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
delivered	O
:	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
Deliver	O
your	O
all	O
you	O
dog	O
?	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
disorder	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
fearful	O
of	O
catching	O
cold	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
of	O
an	O
ague	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
hat	O
or	O
wig	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
held	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
wig	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
shall	O
I	O
be	O
so	O
bold	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
wig	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
my	O
hat	O
also	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
ask	O
for	O
all	O
again	O
presently	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
;	O
please	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
With	O
that	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
grumbling	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
towards	O
White-chapel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
discern	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
?	O
Tribe	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
them	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
light	O
was	O
out	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
short	O
hair	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
remarkable	O
lock	O
behind	O
.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Forister	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
light	O
Mr	O
.	O
Tribe	O
home	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
from	O
Mile-end	O
to	O
Bow	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
'till	O
we	O
pass	O
'd	O
the	O
Plough	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
way	O
between	O
Mile-end	O
and	O
Bow	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
one	O
man	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
near	O
the	O
ditch	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
pass	O
me	O
;	O
when4	O
he	O
came	O
just	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
White-chappel	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
as	O
straight	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
walk	O
:	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
with	O
something	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
hanger	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
having	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
as	O
mentioned	O
before	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
before	O
this	O
:	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
legs	O
and	O
dragg	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jump	O
'd	O
on	O
my	O
breast	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
use	O
me	O
so	O
barbarously	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
you	O
so	O
Maclocklin	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
two	O
days	O
and	O
a	O
night	O
?	O
&	O
c.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
You	O
can	O
not	O
expect	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
from	O
a	O
poor	O
watchman	O
:	O
they	O
took	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
fourpence	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
searched	O
my	O
pockets	O
and	O
took	O
an	O
old	O
knife	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
spoke	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
Irish	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
hat	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
lying	O
bound	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
that	O
same	O
night	O
:	O
When	O
they	O
left	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
done	O
up	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
I	O
found	O
Mr	O
.	O
Tribe	O
's	O
hat	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
John	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
round	O
the	O
parish	O
to	O
collect	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Three	O
Mackerels	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
there	O
:	O
Said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
The	O
watchman	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
abus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
:	O
I	O
say	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
watchman	O
that	O
was	O
abus	O
'd	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
the	O
watchman	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
abus	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
stamp	O
'd	O
on	O
my	O
breast	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
,	O
Let	O
us	O
have	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
Mile-end	O
for	O
five	O
weeks	O
before	O
that	O
:	O
said	O
the	O
landlord	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
thing	O
lodg	O
'd	O
against	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
it	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
There	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
man	O
robb	O
'd	O
and	O
a	O
watchman	O
beat	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
laid	O
on	O
you	O
:	O
Upon	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
How	O
can	O
that	O
be	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
Mile	O
end	O
these	O
five	O
weeks	O
?	O
With	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
came	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
very	O
earnestly	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
my	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
goes	O
and	O
brings	O
a	O
watchman	O
and	O
another	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
house	O
full	O
of	O
them	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
lodging	O
that	O
night	O
by	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
bed	O
before	O
nine	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
labouring	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
keeps	O
good	O
hours	O
;	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
always	O
in	O
by	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
:	O
he	O
never	O
exceeded	O
ten	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
see	O
my	O
lodgers	O
in	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
lodgers	O
have	O
you	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
six	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
they	O
give	O
a	O
night	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
Two-pence	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
turn	O
away	O
three	O
halfpence	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
we	O
want	O
to	O
see	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
?	O
John	O
Hill	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
's	O
account	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
do	O
not	O
agree	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
swore	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
come	O
from	O
Plymouth	O
above	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
265.	O
Robert	B-pers
Griffice	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
glazier	O
's	O
diamond	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lupton	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
266	O
,	O
267.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Clinch	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Steven	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
and	O
Company	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
nine	O
blue	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
pounds	O
,	O
nine	O
blue	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
pounds	O
,	O
twenty-five	O
yards	O
of	O
scarlet-cloth	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
others	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
140	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
The	O
few	O
things	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
they	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
268.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Harison	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
57	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Ewin	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
269.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Forward	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
270	O
,	O
271.	O
William	B-pers
Ellseygood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
waistcoat	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
three	O
caps	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
thirteen	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Warrin	I-pers
.	O
And	O
Eliz	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
March	O
24	O
.	O
Ellseygood	O
guilty	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Ward	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
272.	O
Nathan	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Tracy	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
of	O
one	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
holland	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Robbery	O
.	O
273.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Alien	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alien	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
value	O
20	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
My	O
house	O
is	O
in	O
Spittle-fields	B-place
market	I-place
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
grandmother	O
who	O
lived	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Bridge	O
foot	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
cloaths	O
on	O
:	O
She	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
274.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
stuff-petticoat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rickets	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Rickets	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
my	O
buckles	O
and	O
cap	O
on	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Constable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
275.	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
276.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hempen	O
sack	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
bushels	O
of	O
oats	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Fosset	I-pers
.	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
277.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Treadwell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Calamanco	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
hoop-petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
linnen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
278.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Burnet	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
calamanco	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
four	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Enoch	B-pers
Whilton	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
279.	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Dumerick	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Napton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
rope	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
280	O
,	O
281	O
,	O
282	O
,	O
283	O
,	O
284.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kingsmill	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Staymaker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fairall	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Perin	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lillewhite	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
concerned	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
30	O
persons	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
at	O
Poole	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
thirty	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
500	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
Oct.	O
7	O
.	O
1747	O
.	O
Captain	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
deputation	O
from	O
the	O
Customs	O
to	O
seize	O
prohibited	O
goods	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
1747	O
I	O
was	O
stationed	O
out	O
of	O
Statnham	O
Bay	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
Pool	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
North	O
shore	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
a	O
Cutter	O
I	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Smuggler	O
;	O
after	O
quitting	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
fight	O
of	O
the	O
Three-Brothers	O
;	O
I	O
discovered	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Eastward	O
,	O
after	O
discovering	O
her	O
she	O
put	O
before	O
the	O
wind	O
at	O
N.N.W	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
chase	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
sail	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
.	O
I	O
chased	O
her	O
from	O
before	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
till	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
After	O
firing	O
several	O
shot	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
myself	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
tea	O
,	O
brandy	O
,	O
and	O
rum	O
.	O
The	O
tea	O
was	O
in	O
canvas	O
and	O
oil-skin	O
,	O
over	O
that	O
the	O
usual	O
package	O
for	O
tea	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
run	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
delivery	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
forty-one	O
hundred	O
three	O
quarters	O
gross	O
weight	O
,	O
in	O
eighty-two	O
parcels	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
thirty-nine	O
casks	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
brandy	O
,	O
eight	O
and	O
four	O
gallons	O
casks	O
,	O
slung	O
with	O
ropes	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
load	O
upon	O
horses	O
,	O
as	O
smuggled	O
brandy	O
commonly	O
is	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
seven	O
persons	O
in	O
the	O
Cutter	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
these	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	B-place
at	I-place
Pool	I-place
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
Collector	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
there	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
The	O
tea	O
was	O
deposited	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Warehouse	O
,	O
the	O
brandy	O
and	O
rum	O
were	O
lodged	O
in	O
another	O
part	O
beneath	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
Collector	O
of	O
the	O
Customs	O
at	O
Pool	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
or	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
Captain	O
Johnson	O
brought	O
a	O
vessel	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
Three-Brothers	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
burden	O
two	O
ton	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
thirty-nine	O
casks	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
rum	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
bag	O
of	O
coffee	O
.	O
The	O
tea	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
over	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
small	O
bag	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
damaged	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
put	O
by	O
the	O
chimney	O
.	O
We	O
made	O
it	O
secure	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
took	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
?	O
Milner	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
advice	O
brought	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Officers	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
the	O
staples	O
were	O
forced	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
posts	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
foot	O
farther	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
door	O
broken	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
my	O
office	O
the	O
upper	O
pannel	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
done	O
with	O
a	O
hatchet	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
they	O
could	O
more	O
easily	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
lock	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
door	O
,	O
leading	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
ware-house	O
,	O
was	O
also	O
broke	O
in	O
pieces	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
free	O
passage	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
tea	O
ware-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tea	O
all	O
carried	O
off	O
,	O
except	O
what	O
was	O
scattered	O
over	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
Most	O
of	O
the	O
bags	O
having	O
been	O
opened	O
about	O
an	O
inch	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
condition	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
bag	O
of	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
coffee	O
.	O
They	O
never	O
attempted	O
the	O
brandy	O
and	O
rum	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
ever	O
come	O
to	O
claim	O
the	O
brandy	O
and	O
rum	O
?	O
Milner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
condemned	O
in	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
tea	O
in	O
such	O
sort	O
of	O
package	O
as	O
the	O
East-India	O
Company	O
have	O
?	O
Milner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pack	O
'd	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
for	O
run	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
brandy	O
was	O
in	O
small	O
casks	O
all	O
slung	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Raise	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
at	O
Pool	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Raise	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
soon	O
after	O
Michaelmas	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
last	O
October	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
tea	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Raise	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Raise	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
their	O
first	O
meeting	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
about	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Chaulton	O
Forest	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Richmond	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
Richard	O
Perin	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
there	O
then	O
.	O
We	O
set	O
our	O
hands	O
to	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
break	O
open	O
Pool	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Edmund	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
that	O
set	O
all	O
our	O
names	O
down	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Pool	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
arms	O
with	O
us	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
after	O
we	O
met	O
at	O
Rowland	O
's	O
Castle	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
there	O
,	O
except	O
Kingsmill	O
and	O
Fairall	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
armed	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
met	O
,	O
with	O
blunderbushes	O
,	O
carbines	O
,	O
and	O
pistols	O
;	O
some	O
lived	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
towards	O
Chichester	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
met	O
there	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
all	O
together	O
:	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
forest	O
of	O
Bare	O
,	O
joining	O
to	O
Horn-dean	O
,	O
the	O
Hawkhurst	O
gang	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
horse	O
,	O
which	O
carried	O
their	O
arms	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
company	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Lindust	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
lay	O
all	O
day	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
then	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
:	O
Then	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Pool	O
in	O
the	O
glimpse	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Pool	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
arm	O
'd	O
?	O
Raise	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
armed	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
all	O
things	O
were	O
clear	O
for	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Ware-house	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
men	O
were	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
Sloop	O
lay	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
Key	O
;	O
she	O
'll	O
plant	O
her	O
guns	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
tear	O
us	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
turning	O
our	O
horses	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
.	O
Kingsmill	O
,	O
and	O
Fairall	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
their	O
countrymen	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
do	O
it	O
ourselves	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
Hawkhurst	O
gang	O
;	O
John	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
were	O
with	O
them	O
:	O
We	O
call	O
them	O
the	O
East-country	O
people	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
fetched	O
to	O
help	O
break	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stringer	I-pers
came	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
tide	O
was	O
low	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
vessel	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
her	O
guns	O
to	O
bear	O
to	O
fire	O
upon	O
us	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
forward	O
to	O
Pool	O
:	O
We	O
rid	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
back	O
lane	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
sea-side	O
.	O
There	O
we	O
quitted	O
our	O
horses	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Perrin	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lillewhite	I-pers
staid	O
there	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
a	O
lad	O
,	O
a	O
fisherman	O
going	O
to	O
fish	O
,	O
we	O
kept	O
him	O
a	O
prisoner	O
:	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
who	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
under	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
prisoners	O
too	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
inside	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
tea	O
was	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
about	O
thirty	O
seven	O
hundred	O
,	O
three	O
quarters	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
slung	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
slings	O
,	O
and	O
loaded	O
our	O
horses	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
horses	O
were	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
off	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
.	O
We	O
sackt	O
it	O
in	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
horse-sacks	O
to	O
load	O
;	O
the	O
five	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Fording-bridge	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
breakfasted	O
,	O
and	O
fed	O
our	O
horses	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
thirty	O
one	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
thirty	O
men	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
the	O
odd	O
horse	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
East-country	O
men	O
to	O
carry	O
their	O
arms	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
assist	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
?	O
Raise	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Fairall	O
and	O
Kingsmill	O
carry	O
tea	O
from	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Brook	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
got	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
steelyards	O
,	O
and	O
weighed	O
the	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
equally	O
divided	O
to	O
each	O
man	O
his	O
share	O
;	O
it	O
made	O
five	O
bags	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
about	O
twenty-seven	O
pound	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
quantity	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
all	O
arm	O
'd	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
?	O
Raise	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
twenty	O
of	O
us	O
all	O
arm	O
'd	O
at	O
Rowland	O
's	O
Castle	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Perrin	I-pers
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
tied	O
round	O
his	O
middle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
Lilleywhite	O
arms	O
?	O
Raise	O
.	O
Lilleywhite	O
lay	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
their	O
horses	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
stable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Glover	O
ever	O
reputed	O
a	O
smuggler	O
before	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
he	O
ever	O
act	O
as	O
such	O
?	O
Raise	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
,	O
neither	O
before	O
or	O
since	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Perrin	I-pers
was	O
the	O
merchant	O
that	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Guernsey	O
to	O
buy	O
this	O
cargo	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
rum	O
,	O
and	O
tea	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
as	O
my	O
share	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
another	O
vessel	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
tea	O
by	O
the	O
Swift	O
Privateer	O
,	O
Captain	O
Johnson	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
taken	O
by	O
Captain	O
Johnson	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
we	O
met	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
met	O
in	O
Charlton	O
Forest	O
at	O
the	O
Center-tree	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
Richard	B-pers
Perrin	I-pers
was	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
us	O
there	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
October	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
to	O
conclude	O
about	O
getting	O
this	O
tea	O
out	O
of	O
Pool	O
Custom-houses	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
to	O
some	O
conclusion	O
there	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Rowland	O
's	O
Castle	O
on	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
twenty	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lilleywhite	I-pers
was	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
company	O
armed	O
?	O
Steel	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
arms	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
sun-set	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
every	O
man	O
was	O
armed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
they	O
by	O
their	O
arms	O
?	O
Steel	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
their	O
own	O
houses	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
one	O
man	O
without	O
;	O
some	O
had	O
pistols	O
,	O
some	O
blunderbusses	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
Hawkhurst	O
men	O
had	O
long	O
arms	O
,	O
flung	O
round	O
their	O
shoulders	O
.	O
Fairall	O
,	O
alias	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
from	O
Rowland	O
's	O
Castle	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
forest	O
of	O
Bare	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
joined	O
by	O
the	O
Hawkhurst	O
gang	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
Kingsmill	O
and	O
Fairall	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
horse	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
their	O
arms	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
follow	O
a	O
grey	O
horse	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
rode	O
on	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
seven	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
from	O
Dean	O
to	O
Lindost	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Pool	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
armed	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
look	O
'd	O
of	O
our	O
fire-arms	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
prim	O
'd	O
.	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
Staymaker	O
,	O
and	O
Glover	O
,	O
were	O
arm	O
'd	O
just	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Pool	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Willis	O
and	O
Stringer	O
came	O
and	O
met	O
us	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
turned	O
our	O
horses	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
East-countrymen	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
do	O
it	O
themselves	O
.	O
Then	O
came	O
Stringer	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
done	O
very	O
easy	O
.	O
We	O
turned	O
our	O
horses	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
man	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
our	O
horses	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
rail	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
put	O
along	O
a	O
Common	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
thirty-one	O
horses	O
,	O
we	O
left	O
them	O
under	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lilleywhite	I-pers
and	O
Perrin	O
;	O
we	O
,	O
every	O
man	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
Pool	O
,	O
except	O
them	O
two	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Key	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
no-body	O
came	O
to	O
molest	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
iron	O
bars	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
carrying	O
the	O
tea	O
when	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
strings	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
it	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
to	O
a	O
gravelly	O
place	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
fetched	O
our	O
horses	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
loaded	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Fording-bridge	O
,	O
we	O
baited	O
our	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
refreshed	O
ourselves	O
.	O
We	O
loaded	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Sandy-hill	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Brook	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
steelyards	O
,	O
and	O
weighed	O
the	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
five	O
bags	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
carry	O
the	O
tea	O
to	O
your	O
horses	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
bring	O
the	O
horses	O
to	O
the	O
tea	O
?	O
Steel	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
the	O
tea	O
to	O
a	O
plain	O
place	O
convenient	O
for	O
loading	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
brought	O
the	O
horses	O
forward	O
to	O
be	O
loaded	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Raise	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
carry	O
the	O
tea	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
?	O
Raise	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
employed	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
tie	O
up	O
the	O
tea	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
horses	O
were	O
with	O
the	O
tea	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
know	O
Lilleywhite	O
before	O
?	O
Steel	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
joined	O
us	O
at	O
Rowland	O
's	O
Castle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
came	O
there	O
first	O
he	O
or	O
you	O
?	O
Steel	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
there	O
first	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
arms	O
was	O
upon	O
that	O
little	O
horse	O
?	O
Steel	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
were	O
seven	O
long	O
muskets	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
arms	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
Steel	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
arms	O
before	O
that	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
for	O
their	O
own	O
use	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
Lilleywhite	O
any	O
arms	O
when	O
holding	O
the	O
horses	O
?	O
Steel	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
all	O
put	O
down	O
your	O
names	O
on	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
to	O
go	O
upon	O
this	O
affair	O
?	O
Steel	O
.	O
Each	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
put	O
down	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Lilleywhite	O
's	O
name	O
put	O
down	O
?	O
Steel	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Glover	O
ever	O
concerned	O
in	O
smuggling	O
before	O
this	O
?	O
Steel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
or	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
reluctancy	O
much	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
?	O
Steel	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
Richards	O
forced	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
Glover	O
lived	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
Richards	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
going	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
your	O
commander	O
?	O
Steel	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no-body	O
took	O
the	O
lead	O
one	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Fogden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
tea	O
was	O
seized	O
upon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
consultation	O
in	O
Charlton	O
Forest	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
concluded	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
the	O
tea	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
noted	O
tree	O
that	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
forest	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
Centre-tree	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
Rowland	O
's	O
Castle	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
with	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Common	O
just	O
below	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
you	O
was	O
at	O
?	O
Fogden	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
one	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
forest	O
of	O
Bare	O
there	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
five	O
prisoners	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
together	O
at	O
a	O
lone	O
place	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
these	O
Hawkhurst	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
were	O
thirty	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
number	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
all	O
armed	O
?	O
Fogden	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
armed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
purpose	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
there	O
?	O
Fogden	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
fetch	O
away	O
the	O
tea	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Fogden	O
.	O
By	O
force	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Lindost	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
:	O
We	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
near	O
night	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Pool	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
backside	O
of	O
the	O
Town	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
our	O
horses	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
lane	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
Pool	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
or	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
left	O
our	O
horses	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
We	O
left	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
Perrin	O
and	O
Lilleywhite	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
with	O
two	O
iron	O
bars	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
them	O
?	O
Fogden	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
tea	O
lodged	O
?	O
Fogden	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
ware-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
?	O
Fogden	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
Fogden	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
assist	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
two	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
the	O
horses	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
near	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
carried	O
the	O
tea	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
narrow	O
lane	O
where	O
we	O
stopped	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
brought	O
the	O
horses	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
more	O
open	O
place	O
for	O
loading	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
help	O
you	O
load	O
?	O
Fogden	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
put	O
an	O
equal	O
quantity	O
on	O
each	O
horse	O
?	O
Fogden	O
.	O
We	O
distributed	O
it	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
little	O
horse	O
,	O
that	O
carried	O
the	O
arms	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
horses	O
had	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
Every	O
horse	O
there	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
tea	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
town	O
called	O
Fording-bridge	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
place	O
we	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
weigh	O
'd	O
the	O
tea	O
with	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
steelyards	O
;	O
for	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
equal	O
,	O
some	O
was	O
shattered	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
bags	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
divided	O
it	O
as	O
equal	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
quartern	O
bags	O
,	O
each	O
prisoner	O
had	O
five	O
bags	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
Lilleywhite	O
first	O
?	O
Fogden	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Forest	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
there	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
you	O
?	O
Fogden	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
threats	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
should	O
discover	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
what	O
should	O
be	O
done	O
to	O
them	O
?	O
Fogden	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
Lilleywhite	O
arms	O
when	O
left	O
with	O
the	O
horses	O
?	O
Fogden	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
For	O
John	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Perrin	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Perrin	O
almost	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
among	O
his	O
neighbours	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
neglected	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
hear	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
smuggler	O
?	O
Guy	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
so	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
of	O
his	O
neglecting	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
a	O
smuggling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
hear	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
smuggler	O
?	O
Guy	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
but	O
by	O
hear-say	O
,	O
as	O
folks	O
talk	O
.	O
For	O
Glover	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
into	O
it	O
by	O
my	O
brother-in-law	O
,	O
who	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
shoot	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tapling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Richard	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
twenty	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
,	O
before	O
this	O
unhappy	O
affair	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
smuggler	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
his	O
brother-in-law	O
Richards	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Glover	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Richards	O
is	O
a	O
notorious	O
wicked	O
,	O
swearing	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
reputed	O
a	O
great	O
smuggler	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
help	O
thinking	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
Glover	O
's	O
acting	O
in	O
this	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Housel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Glover	O
of	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
young	O
lad	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
otherwise	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
I	O
ever	O
hear	O
him	O
swear	O
an	O
oath	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
hear	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
smuggler	O
?	O
Housal	O
.	O
Never	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
till	O
the	O
year	O
1744	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
dying	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
his	O
business	O
till	O
Aug.	O
1747	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
June	O
to	O
that	O
wicked	O
brother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
after	O
that	O
to	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blackden	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
Deptford-yard	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
continued	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
till	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
shipwright	O
.	O
This	O
affair	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
brother-in-law	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grasswell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Glover	O
these	O
twelve	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
smugling	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
exceeding	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
frequent	O
bad	O
company	O
,	O
or	O
guilty	O
of	O
drinking	O
or	O
swearing	O
an	O
oath	O
.	O
Woodruff	O
Drinkwater	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Glover	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
reputed	O
a	O
smuggler	O
either	O
before	O
or	O
since	O
,	O
exclusive	O
of	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
his	O
temper	O
is	O
not	O
formed	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
far	O
from	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
his	O
father	O
died	O
he	O
was	O
left	O
joint	O
executor	O
with	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
(	O
left	O
in	O
narrow	O
circumstances	O
)	O
he	O
often	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
any	O
little	O
occasion	O
for	O
five	O
or	O
ten	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
kept	O
his	O
word	O
;	O
after	O
his	O
mother	O
married	O
again	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
difference	O
in	O
his	O
family	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
his	O
going	O
to	O
Richard	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
voluntary	O
in	O
this	O
rash	O
action	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Edmonds	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Glover	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
entered	O
into	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
yard	O
at	O
Deptsord	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
following	O
;	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
he	O
has	O
behav	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
and	O
sober	O
;	O
he	O
obtain	O
'd	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
all	O
that	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
as	O
good	O
an	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
'till	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dearing	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
where	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
I	O
go	O
there	O
for	O
the	O
summer	O
season	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
eighteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
being	O
informed	O
of	O
this	O
bad	O
thing	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
come	O
to	O
London	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
say	O
what	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
had	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
bad	O
man	O
Richards	O
had	O
corrupted	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
well	O
behaved	O
lad	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
:	O
his	O
uncle	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
uncle	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
business	O
for	O
him	O
in	O
some	O
way	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
adding	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
bear	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
Richards	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
hir	O
'd	O
a	O
servant	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
took	O
him	O
:	O
just	O
after	O
this	O
bad	O
affair	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
unfortunately	O
drawn	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Revd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blackden	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Slendon	O
in	O
Sussex	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Glover	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
family	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
exceeding	O
well	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
any	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
discharg	O
'd	O
from	O
this	O
I	O
would	O
readily	O
take	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
attended	O
in	O
religious	O
service	O
publick	O
and	O
private	O
constant	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
word	O
or	O
oath	O
from	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
vulgar	O
.	O
For	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lilleywhite	I-pers
.	O
His	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
in	O
that	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
ride	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
agreed	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
fire-arms	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
any	O
way	O
concerned	O
.	O
Fra	O
.	O
Wheeler	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Lilleywhite	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
