TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
23d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Eighth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1749	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Public	O
may	O
be	O
assured	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
during	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CALVERT	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
)	O
the	O
Sessions-Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
Four-pence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
Sessions	O
shall	O
be	O
carefully	O
compriz	O
'd	O
in	O
One	O
such	O
Four-penny	O
Book	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
farther	O
Burthen	O
on	O
the	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CALVERT	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLS	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLARK	I-pers
,	O
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Oram	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Garrard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bradbury	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Millington	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Trent	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Downer	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Southulb	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Waller	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Mount	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Brayne	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Grange	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Denew	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lynall	I-pers
,	O
Champion	B-pers
Robards	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Man	I-pers
.	O
599.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
1	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
safe	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
my	O
wife	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
turned	O
the	O
curtain	O
aside	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
money	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
mentioned	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
walk	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
search	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
a	O
remarkable	O
sixpence	O
with	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
I	O
took	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
box	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
(	O
then	O
Mr	O
.	O
Kitchen	O
was	O
by	O
)	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
old	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dirty	O
hussiff	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
two	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
money	O
than	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
saying	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
:	O
the	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
of	O
mine	O
was	O
not	O
weight	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
weigh	O
'd	O
it	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
weight	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
last	O
mentioned	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
being	O
mark	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
weight	O
it	O
wanted	O
;	O
it	O
answer	O
'd	O
exactly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
600	O
,	O
601.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
and	O
Simon	B-pers
Case	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
d	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Fishstreet-hill	B-place
just	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
Crooked-lane	I-place
,	O
Clayton	O
pressed	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Case	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Clayton	O
was	O
immediately	O
secur	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
found	O
in	O
Southwark	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
602.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Penant	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
603.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
South	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
vessel	O
weighing	O
35	O
pound	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
19	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
keeps	O
a	O
brasier	O
's	O
and	O
ironmonger	O
's	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
corner	B-place
of	I-place
Coleman	I-place
street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
this	O
copper	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopped	O
with	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
witness	O
who	O
proved	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
fracture	O
in	O
his	O
scull	O
which	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
action	O
on	O
Preston	B-pers
Pans	I-pers
,	O
and	O
since	O
that	O
at	O
times	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
Senses	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
604.	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
on	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
did	O
put	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
did	O
violently	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Oct.	O
2	O
d	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
hat	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
a	O
place	O
call	O
'd	O
Ivy-bridge	B-place
,	O
which	O
is	O
very	O
steep	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
well	O
discern	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
a	O
soldier	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
)	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
lying	O
by	O
his	O
feet	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hugins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
run	O
directly	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
second	O
person	O
who	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
hat	O
taken	O
up	O
near	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Oldfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
Ivy-bridge	O
lane	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
taking	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
me	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Guilty	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
605.	O
Gyles	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
stock	O
buckle	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
in	O
another	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
bed	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
none	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
watch	O
at	O
Oxford	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
inside	O
case	O
mended	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
workman	O
spoil	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
together	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
both	O
in	O
one	O
room	O
;	O
that	O
night	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
twelve	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
betwixt	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
vault	O
;	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
'till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
Kingston	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
606.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gouge	I-pers
,	O
late	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
Bromley	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Everest	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Sept.	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
607.	O
John	B-pers
Napleton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
608.	O
Francis	B-pers
Green	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
Sept.	O
27	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
sugar	O
upon	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
him	O
a	O
hogshead	O
of	O
sugar	O
that	O
agreed	O
with	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
with	O
the	O
head	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
609.	O
James	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Gervace	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
Oct.	O
3	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Gervace	I-pers
.	O
Passing	O
through	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
Oct.	O
the	O
3d	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
something	O
press	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
ran	O
across	O
Cheap	O
side	O
,	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
cross	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
610.	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Sept.	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
611.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
light-coloured	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hassels	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
14	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
cloak	O
upon	O
her	O
after	O
missing	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
just	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
612.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Addy	I-pers
,	O
Sept	O
23	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
613.	O
Henry	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gosport	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
parish	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
Sept.	O
the	O
20th	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
C.	O
More	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
lodging	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
following	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
pawn	O
'd	O
my	O
tankard	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
for	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
she	O
waited	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
while	O
two	O
other	O
lads	O
brought	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rutherford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fraser	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
has	O
said	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
never	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
pawn	O
'd	O
there	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
614.	O
Charles	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Diamond	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
two	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
spectacles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
sixteen	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Diamond	I-pers
,	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Sept.	O
17	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Diamond	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
coming	O
along	O
Prince	B-place
's	I-place
street	I-place
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
he	O
threw	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
stop	O
'd	O
my	O
breath	O
,	O
he	O
cut	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
what	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
cloak	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
about	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
cotton	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
between	O
my	O
ribs	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
gin	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
my	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
hands	O
;	O
sirrah	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
hard	O
you	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
cold	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
abus	O
'd	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Another	O
witness	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
coming	O
from	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Diamond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
travel	O
'd	O
from	O
Naples	O
on	O
foot	O
by	O
Rome	O
,	O
through	O
Italy	O
to	O
Paris	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Kent	O
in	O
this	O
kingdom	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
earned	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
there	O
in	O
gathering	O
of	O
hope	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sashfield	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
crying	O
old	O
cloaths	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
struggling	O
for	O
these	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
in	O
searching	O
him	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spectacles	O
,	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tin	O
pot	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
man	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Humes	O
.	O
Coming	O
near	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
seeing	O
a	O
struggle	O
between	O
the	O
woman	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
woman	O
mention	O
every	O
thing	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
tin	O
pot	O
,	O
spectacles	O
,	O
and	O
wooden	O
spoon	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
615.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Scalock	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
diamond	O
rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Darking	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Oct.	O
10	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Darking	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
and	O
left	O
3	O
diamond	O
rings	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
only	O
the	O
maid-servant	O
and	O
that	O
boy	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
boy	O
and	O
rings	O
were	O
gone	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
rings	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tualler	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
brewer	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
being	O
a	O
mourning	O
ring	O
on	O
my	O
finger	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
rings	O
;	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
these	O
rings	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
white	O
stones	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
remembred	O
something	O
of	O
such	O
rings	O
in	O
the	O
Advertiser	O
,	O
I	O
step	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
described	O
with	O
15	O
guineas	O
reward	O
.	O
I	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
the	O
advertisement	O
directed	O
:	O
he	O
then	O
confest	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
marble	O
slab	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
616	O
,	O
617.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sheerman	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Sheerman	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
brass	O
cock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
iron	O
screws	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
cock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sheerman	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Jones	O
had	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
Store-room	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
lost	O
;	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
examined	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
Elizabeth	O
Sheerman	O
who	O
keeps	O
an	O
old	O
iron	O
shop	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
who	O
call	O
'd	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
goods	O
at	O
a	O
market-price	O
.	O
Jones	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Sheerman	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
618.	O
Walter	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
one	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
son	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
son	O
since	O
they	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
at	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
's	O
,	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
proof	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
619.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
late	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bever-hat	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
4	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
daughter	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
hat	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
620	O
,	O
621.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
linen	O
gowns	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
about	O
48	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Iverson	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
21	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Iverson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ratcliff	B-place
high-way	I-place
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
or	O
shovel-maker	O
;	O
Hail	O
is	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
my	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
;	O
Butler	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
a	O
shop	O
I	O
have	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
and	O
pawn	O
them	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
:	O
Hall	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
622.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
two	O
silver	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
one	O
g	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Cocket	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Limehouse	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
my	O
son	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
money	O
and	O
p	O
,	O
were	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
girl	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
my	O
son	O
's	O
wife	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
gone	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
my	O
son	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
we	O
found	O
every	O
thing	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
gardener	O
's	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
shirt	O
11	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
silver	O
buckle	O
belonging	O
to	O
my	O
son	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
first	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
garden	O
where	O
I	O
work	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
the	O
box	O
of	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
remove	O
his	O
quarters	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
then	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
watch	O
I	O
carried	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kennard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
witnesses	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
things	O
were	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
Kennard	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
while	O
dimity	O
gown	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pap-spoon	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
corals	O
with	O
bells	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
buckle	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
are	O
yours	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
thing	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
find	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
laid	O
there	O
together	O
a	O
night	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
serjeant	O
and	O
other	O
officers	O
in	O
the	O
army	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
623	O
,	O
624.	O
William	B-pers
Southey	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Ackman	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
on	O
Sonoves	B-pers
Mellek	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
diamond	O
rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sonoves	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Sept.	O
13	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
on	O
Sydro	B-pers
Meilek	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
ten	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Sept.	O
13	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prosecutors	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
other	O
witness	O
being	O
all	O
three	O
Muhomitans	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
admitted	O
to	O
swear	O
upon	O
the	O
New	O
Testament	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
witnesses	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
625.	O
Mary	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
spaterdashes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
626.	O
Edward	B-pers
Dunfield	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Blasfield	I-pers
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
on	O
foot	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Wales	O
,	O
Sept.	O
10.	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
miles	O
out	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
riding	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
;	O
we	O
fell	O
into	O
discourse	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
Welchman	O
from	O
Mongomeryshire	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
at	O
London	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
doing	O
there	O
?	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
paying	O
a	O
visit	O
to	O
a	O
brother	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
master	O
taylor	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
works	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
fond	O
of	O
his	O
company	O
;	O
he	O
complained	O
that	O
riding	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
very	O
sore	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
rode	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
as	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
hurt	O
by	O
riding	O
;	O
his	O
horse	O
had	O
sweat	O
very	O
much	O
:	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
,	O
two	O
Miles	O
beyond	O
Acton	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
love	O
I	O
bear	O
to	O
your	O
brother	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
you	O
drink	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
(	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
be	O
put	O
me	O
on	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
by	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
I	O
lik	O
'd	O
that	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
;	O
he	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
meaning	O
himself	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
master	O
robe-maker	O
.	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
brother	O
that	O
died	O
lately	O
,	O
near	O
Brook-street	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
your	O
brother	O
is	O
making	O
me	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
mourning	O
for	O
my	O
brother	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
pray	O
Sir	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
How	O
can	O
I	O
tell	O
that	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
frown	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
fore-man	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
journeymen	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
this	O
conversation	O
was	O
after	O
we	O
was	O
past	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
walking	O
by	O
him	O
on	O
foot	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
town	O
call	O
'd	O
Hays	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
3	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
receive	O
4000	O
l.	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
only	O
1000	O
l.	O
it	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
man	O
for	O
ever	O
.	O
So	O
it	O
would	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
furlong	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
Angel	O
in	O
Hay	O
's	O
parish	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
buy	O
these	O
rings	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
knowledge	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
one	O
is	O
a	O
diamond	O
ring	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
buy	O
them	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
horse	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
you	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
10	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lend	O
him	O
10	O
s	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
10	O
s.	O
of	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
9	O
s.	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
keep	O
the	O
other	O
5	O
;	O
he	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
,	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
silver	O
buckles	O
you	O
told	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
make	O
words	O
;	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
his	O
horse	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
wretch	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
in	O
spight	O
of	O
my	O
note	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
bought	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
in	O
our	O
conversation	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
these	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
down	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
shoe	O
and	O
knee	O
buckles	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
rode	O
off	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
take	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
thinking	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
heart	O
failed	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bid	O
me	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
eat	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
more	O
for	O
fear	O
than	O
good	O
will	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
your	O
heart	O
fail	O
you	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
fearful	O
he	O
had	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
gang	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Jibson	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
you	O
have	O
denied	O
your	O
name	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
your	O
name	O
now	O
:	O
hush	O
,	O
hush	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
eat	O
and	O
drank	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
forward	O
to	O
a	O
heath	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
considering	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
whether	O
to	O
go	O
forward	O
or	O
return	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
riding	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
jump	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
bridle	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
buckles	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
into	O
a	O
long-lane	O
.	O
I	O
still	O
held	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
reins	O
of	O
the	O
bridle	O
;	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
cutlass	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
right-side	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
me	O
cross	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
my	O
clothes	O
very	O
much	O
(	O
he	O
shewed	O
the	O
scar	O
about	O
an	O
inch	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
long	O
near	O
his	O
right	O
ear	O
)	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
hold	O
for	O
about	O
40	O
yards	O
,	O
the	O
horse	O
running	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
trampling	O
on	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
bleeding	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
some	O
people	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
fighting	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
people	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
I	O
might	O
ride	O
behind	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
granted	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
related	O
the	O
affair	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
and	O
my	O
conversation	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
had	O
mentioned	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
there	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
and	O
knee	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
he	O
died	O
the	O
Oxford-arms	O
in	O
Tyburn-old	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
step	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
assisted	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
saying	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
that	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
and	O
breeches	O
knees	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Questions	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
or	O
no	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
proposal	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
this	O
money	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
short	O
of	O
money	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
another	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
giving	O
me	O
the	O
9	O
shillings	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
pledge	O
a	O
gold-ring	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
the	O
rings	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
9	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
3	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
beer	O
and	O
victuals	O
at	O
one	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
d	O
before	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
pay	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
both	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
appoint	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King's-arms	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
appoint	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
strange	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
should	O
not	O
apprehend	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
should	O
attempt	O
it	O
alone	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
stood	O
a	O
better	O
chance	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
fearing	O
he	O
had	O
companions	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Henningway	I-pers
and	O
James	O
Price	O
the	O
constable	O
corroborated	O
what	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
owning	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
the	O
taking	O
and	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
care	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
safer	O
with	O
me	O
than	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
lent	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
money	O
again	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
or	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
Uxbridge	O
with	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
parted	O
good	O
friends	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
troop	O
of	O
Horse-guards	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
soldier	O
almost	O
all	O
my	O
life	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
627.	O
Phillis	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
late	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
's	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
fustian	O
frock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
damask	O
napkin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
hair	O
cap	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
four	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Proctor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
basket	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
June	O
17	O
.	O
These	O
were	O
clothes	O
delivered	O
to	O
a	O
washer-woman	O
,	O
who	O
intrusted	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
adding	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
628	O
,	O
629	O
,	O
630.	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Loyer	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Carmichal	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Maschal	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
did	O
put	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
against	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Maschal	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
St.	B-place
Gyles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mary	B-pers
Carmichal	I-pers
took	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
struck	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
mouth	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
murder	O
and	O
thieves	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
deliver	O
my	O
hat	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
held	O
her	O
fast	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
called	O
himself	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
deposed	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Carmichal	I-pers
and	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
such	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
lights	O
,	O
and	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
contradicted	O
what	O
Francis	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
the	O
watchman	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
jury	O
gave	O
no	O
credit	O
to	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
Burk	O
and	O
Loyer	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Carmichal	I-pers
,	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
631.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
late	B-place
of	I-place
Horsey	I-place
in	I-place
Norfolk	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
30	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
20th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
majesty	O
,	O
being	O
arm	O
'd	O
with	O
fire-arms	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
offensive	O
weapons	O
,	O
were	O
assembled	O
in	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
running	O
goods	O
,	O
liable	O
to	O
pay	O
duty	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
assistant	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
of	O
customs	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
1746	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Horsey	B-place
in	I-place
Norfolk	I-place
,	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
friends	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
's	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
smugglers	O
in	O
town	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
farmer	O
's	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
when	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
messenger	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
answer	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
was	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
Dick	O
Costings	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
wants	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
tiff	O
of	O
punch	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
stay	O
here	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Manning	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
you	O
silly	O
rogue	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
come	O
alone	O
,	O
for	O
here	O
are	O
many	O
rogues	O
in	O
town	O
now	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
there	O
came	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
men	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
some	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
were	O
strangers	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
farmer	O
kept	O
the	O
door	O
lock	O
'd	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
amongst	O
them	O
they	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fled	O
into	O
the	O
barn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
among	O
so	O
many	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
remarkably	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
being	O
stuck	O
out	O
with	O
pistols	O
and	O
other	O
arms	O
in	O
an	O
uncommon	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
barn	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
assembled	O
together	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Pearson	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
they	O
,	O
they	O
block	O
'd	O
my	O
face	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
across	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
their	O
member	O
of	O
parliament	O
;	O
they	O
kept	O
me	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
then	O
th	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
farmer	O
's	O
house	O
again	O
one	O
of	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
Yarmouth	O
man	O
;	O
we	O
smoak	O
'd	O
a	O
pi	O
ther	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
there	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
they	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
and	O
me	O
in	O
el	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
a	O
rope	O
about	O
me	O
and	O
hang	O
'd	O
me	O
across	O
a	O
tree	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
hung	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
much	O
pain	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Beech	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
upwards	O
of	O
forty	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
among	O
them	O
;	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
they	O
were	O
one	O
and	O
all	O
arm	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
particularly	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
arm	O
'd	O
;	O
some	O
had	O
blunderbusses	O
,	O
some	O
one	O
thing	O
and	O
some	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
that	O
way	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
load	O
there	O
goods	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cutter	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
smugglers	O
of	O
her	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
.	O
According	O
to	O
the	O
package	O
of	O
the	O
tea	O
and	O
casks	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
run	O
;	O
the	O
tea	O
was	O
in	O
oil-skin	O
bags	O
,	O
which	O
held	O
about	O
26	O
or	O
27	O
pounds	O
weight	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
casks	O
were	O
slung	O
with	O
ropes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
general	O
loading	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
off	O
in	O
form	O
,	O
two	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
towards	O
Winterton	O
side	O
.	O
Cross	O
examin	O
'd	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
faces	O
of	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
you	O
saw	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
now	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
arm	O
'd	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
particular	O
manner	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
me	O
remember	O
him	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
at	O
Horsey	O
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
these	O
people	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
,	O
and	O
with	O
an	O
oath	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
with	O
an	O
oath	O
again	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
wrong	O
person	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
Bailey	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
old	O
smuglers	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
drunk	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
dress	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
pistols	O
in	O
an	O
odd	O
manner	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
hardly	O
knew	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
cutter	O
coming	O
on	O
,	O
of	O
many	O
of	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
young	O
an	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
goods	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
arm	O
'd	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
arms	O
,	O
in	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
affair	O
at	O
Manning	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
632.	O
John	B-pers
Hutchings	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
squeeze	O
by	O
a	O
hogshead	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
alarm	O
the	O
people	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
described	O
him	O
so	O
near	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
brought	O
two	O
persons	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
such	O
like	O
clothes	O
,	O
neither	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
him	O
;	O
afterwards	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
633	O
,	O
634.	O
Diana	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bushel	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
walnuts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Lovet	I-pers
.	O
Sept.	O
17	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
635.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pewter	O
gallon	O
pot	O
wine	O
measure	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
636.	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Sergent	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
hood	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
case	O
of	O
fleams	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
large	O
silver	O
coat	O
button	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
.	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
6	O
weeks	O
or	O
2	O
months	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
beg	O
'd	O
the	O
savour	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
lie	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
on	O
my	O
own	O
bed	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
silver	O
tankard	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
then	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
little	O
walk	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
man	O
John	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
hours	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
next	O
morning	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
on	O
all	O
her	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
tea	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
emptied	O
into	O
a	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
inquiry	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
paper	O
to	O
read	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
curse	O
and	O
swear	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
or	O
child	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
surrender	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
stir	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
;	O
the	O
alderman	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
lodgings	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
sat	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
your	O
chest	O
or	O
clothes	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
box	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
brother-in-law	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
Tavern	O
,	O
Temple-bar	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
drawer	O
there	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
inquire	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
brother	O
told	O
us	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Sergent	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
that	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
sister	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
trunk	O
there	O
with	O
his	O
clothes	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
his	O
sister	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
be	O
easy	O
with	O
her	O
brother	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
help	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
tankard	O
again	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
nightman	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
down	O
the	O
vault	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
nightman	O
,	O
who	O
soon	O
brought	O
up	O
my	O
tankard	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
vault	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
found	O
his	O
trunk	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Truckel	I-pers
another	O
witness	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
tankard	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
637.	O
Lidia	B-pers
Whittmore	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
36	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
two	O
Moidores	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Mawley	I-pers
,	O
one	O
child	O
's	O
skirt	O
of	O
a	O
frock	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
Sept.	O
6	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
before	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
miss	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
her	O
son	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
belonging	O
to	O
James	O
White	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
never	O
confest	O
taking	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
638	O
,	O
639.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Constell	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Sugar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Froom	I-pers
.	O
Sept	O
24	O
.	O
Bristow	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Constell	O
,	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
640	O
,	O
641	O
,	O
642.	O
John	B-pers
Waine	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cumings	I-pers
and	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Oct	O
7	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
hosier	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoners	O
a	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hassall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
company	O
at	O
the	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
Holborn	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
Waine	O
and	O
Cumings	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
,	O
it	O
came	O
at	O
last	O
to	O
blows	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
turn	O
'd	O
one	O
out	O
at	O
one	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
at	O
another	O
;	O
they	O
met	O
and	O
fought	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
Sullivan	O
had	O
the	O
stockings	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
Waine	O
's	O
coat	O
:	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
Waine	O
's	O
,	O
adding	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
Sullivan	O
strip	O
'd	O
the	O
stockings	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
Comings	O
for	O
his	O
other	O
stockings	O
;	O
Comings	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
Sullivan	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
another	O
witness	O
has	O
got	O
those	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
such	O
as	O
the	O
others	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
.	O
George	O
Taylor	O
produc	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
as	O
above	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
Waine	O
and	O
Sullivan	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
stockings	O
,	O
Sullivan	O
stood	O
near	O
where	O
the	O
stockings	O
lay	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
7	O
pair	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Hassall	O
had	O
before	O
deposed	O
.	O
Waine	O
and	O
Sullivan	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Comings	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
643.	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Moles	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
counterpane	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shag	O
breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
644.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bowmaster	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Hendrick	B-pers
Bowmaster	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edmond	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
7	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
645.	O
Mary	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Blare	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mackey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
on	O
the	O
Trial	O
of	O
John	O
Godard	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
559.	O
and	O
likewise	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
,	O
as	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
concluded	O
that	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
646.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
late	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Andrew	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
for	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mary	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
,	O
alias	O
Blare	O
,	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
July	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
Mr	O
Hains	O
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
record	O
of	O
Sup	O
trial	O
.	O
Aug.	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
Mr	O
Adams	O
Wright	O
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
also	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
,	O
which	O
last	O
witness	O
proceeded	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
all	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
broke	O
up	O
three	O
such	O
rings	O
as	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
execute	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
jewels	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Holborn	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Leather	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
without	O
taking	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
door	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
joining	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
backwards	O
)	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
open	O
such	O
a	O
buroe	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
two	O
drops	O
of	O
ear-rings	O
in	O
a	O
pen-case	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
a	O
person	O
present	O
to	O
fetch	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
recollect	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
drop	O
may	O
be	O
like	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
the	O
middle	O
one	O
has	O
been	O
lately	O
mended	O
in	O
a	O
remarkable	O
clumsey	O
manner	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
having	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
her	O
seeing	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
oath	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
's	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
all	O
again	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
things	O
easy	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
above	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
law	O
would	O
permit	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Moll	O
Blare	O
;	O
two	O
days	O
afterwards	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
New-prison	O
,	O
and	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
bought	O
my	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
three	O
diamond	O
rings	O
,	O
two	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
all	O
together	O
for	O
24	O
l.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
commiserated	O
my	O
misfortune	O
,	O
(	O
from	O
whence	O
I	O
conclude	O
by	O
the	O
things	O
being	O
advertised	O
before	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
mine	O
)	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
calculation	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
pounds	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
stone	O
drops	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Bargae	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Summer-street	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Leather-lane	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
a	O
wax	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
to	O
stick	O
loose	O
diamonds	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
again	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
what	O
diamonds	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
heads	O
of	O
rings	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
stones	O
in	O
the	O
collets	O
without	O
the	O
rings	O
;	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
loose	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
collets	O
;	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
break	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
weighed	O
them	O
separately	O
,	O
the	O
roses	O
in	O
one	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
brilliant	O
in	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
down	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
they	O
weighed	O
;	O
it	O
amounted	O
to	O
8	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
and	O
my	O
partner	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
pounds	O
profit	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
15th	O
or	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
diamonds	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
profit	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
such	O
a	O
day	O
I	O
should	O
see	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
bring	O
my	O
partner	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
no	O
business	O
without	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
coming	O
without	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
back	O
room	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
broke	O
up	O
the	O
rings	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
12	O
l.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
6	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
about	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
break	O
them	O
up	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
too	O
good	O
to	O
be	O
broke	O
up	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
caution	O
not	O
to	O
tell	O
one	O
Robins	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
:	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Robins	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
ear-rings	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
bought	O
these	O
of	O
Johnson	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
but	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Robins	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
describe	O
these	O
ear-rings	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
worthy	O
gentleman	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
ear-rings	O
by	O
drawing	O
them	O
with	O
my	O
pencil	O
,	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Hughes	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
hers	O
;	O
she	O
particularly	O
described	O
the	O
three	O
rings	O
that	O
were	O
broke	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
these	O
ear-rings	O
must	O
be	O
yours	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
value	O
the	O
earrings	O
at	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
.	O
About	O
18	O
l.	O
James	B-pers
Price	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
those	O
things	O
for	O
26	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
about	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
or	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
profit	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hughes	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
again	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
647.	O
Ann	B-pers
Masterson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
fustian	O
breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Leonard	I-pers
,	O
Oct	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
lives	O
in	O
High-Holborn	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
hanging	O
at	O
his	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
648.	O
John	B-pers
Crosby	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
with	O
two	O
seals	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
July	O
5	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
come	O
upon	O
likeing	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
a	O
baker	O
at	O
Poplar	O
to	O
go	O
apprentice	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
hung	O
my	O
watch	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
bake-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
and	O
watch	O
were	O
missing	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
seals	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Barry	O
last	O
Thursday	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
his	O
confession	O
.	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
barber	O
at	O
Highgate	O
,	O
who	O
delivered	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
hands	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
649.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dancer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
falsely	O
forging	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
an	O
acceptance	O
to	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
Exchange	O
for	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
drawn	O
upon	O
Israel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
450.	O
James	B-pers
Hertford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Witts	I-pers
,	O
Oct	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
cast	O
upon	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
451.	O
Francis	B-pers
Forbes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
val	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gavin	I-pers
Sept.	O
12	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
at	O
the	O
Mr.	O
Gavin	O
was	O
turning	O
himself	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
him	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
652	O
,	O
653.	O
Francis	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
soles	O
for	O
shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hailey	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
21	O
.	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Butts	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Pennice	I-pers
,	O
being	O
an	O
accomplice	O
with	O
Francis	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
came	O
as	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
both	O
he	O
and	O
Brown	O
being	O
two	O
little	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
an	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Brown	O
both	O
declared	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Butts	O
for	O
one	O
shilling	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
two	O
starving	O
children	O
to	O
the	O
London	O
work-house	O
.	O
654.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Killegrew	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
pint	O
cup	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
waiter	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
widow	O
;	O
four	O
shifts	O
and	O
three	O
aprons	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Craxton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
March	O
5	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
offer	O
'd	O
a	O
silver	O
waiter	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
cup	O
to	O
pledge	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
some	O
years	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
appeared	O
not	O
so	O
credible	O
as	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
lend	O
her	O
any	O
money	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
them	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
repute	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
me	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
advance	O
any	O
money	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
interim	O
I	O
had	O
notice	O
sent	O
me	O
from	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
hall	O
about	O
these	O
things	O
being	O
stole	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
off	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
since	O
till	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
camblet	O
.	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
committed	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
found	O
the	O
waiter	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cup	O
he	O
had	O
melted	O
down	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Comington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Craxton	O
of	O
Tottenham-high-Cross	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
waiter	O
is	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
matron	O
of	O
the	O
work-house	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Craxton	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
horses	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
of	O
the	O
work	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
grey	O
of	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Clark	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
things	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
stair-foot	O
door	O
was	O
buttoned	O
fast	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
door	O
where	O
I	O
might	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
she	O
opened	O
a	O
little	O
cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
paper	O
to	O
be	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
distributed	O
from	O
Goldsmith's-hall	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
James	B-pers
Cessil	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
this	O
day	O
seven-night	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
voluntary	O
confession	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
sign	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
else	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
655.	O
William	B-pers
Gaskine	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Coffoy	O
seat	O
of	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
Oct.	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
656.	O
Judith	B-pers
Carneen	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Kelley	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Donoly	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
eleventh	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
majesty	O
,	O
did	O
marry	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
19th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
majesty	O
,	O
did	O
marry	O
one	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Donoly	I-pers
,	O
stationer	O
,	O
her	O
former	O
husband	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
Cornelius	B-pers
York	I-pers
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
wife	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
as	O
appears	O
by	O
Wm	O
Kelley	O
's	O
affidavit	O
,	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
chief	O
justice	O
Lee	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Donoly	I-pers
.	O
Here	O
is	O
an	O
affidavit	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
swore	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
read	O
as	O
not	O
being	O
evidence	O
.	O
York	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1738	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
prove	O
that	O
?	O
York	O
.	O
She	O
sued	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
husband	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
bishop	O
's	O
court	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
that	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
whore	O
,	O
to	O
an	O
excommunication	O
;	O
I	O
filed	O
a	O
bill	O
in	O
Chancery	O
to	O
be	O
relieved	O
,	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
several	O
complaints	O
in	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afterwards	O
obliged	O
to	O
pay	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
York	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
32	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
ever	O
married	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Donoly	I-pers
?	O
York	O
.	O
Her	O
husband	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
produce	O
two	O
men	O
-	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
answer	O
my	O
question	O
;	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
again	O
and	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
believed	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
-	O
Singleton	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
the	O
court	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
.	O
Singleton	O
.	O
About	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
years	O
ago	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Kelley	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
ever	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
657	O
,	O
658.	O
John	B-pers
Belson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
peg-awl	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Boxton	I-pers
;	O
one	O
iron	O
wedge	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
eight	O
iron	O
nails	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
:	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Mortimore	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
Oct.	O
11	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
659	O
,	O
660.	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
21	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
21	O
s.	O
seven	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
five	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
fourteen	O
napkins	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
:	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Rowland	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
four	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
April	O
16	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
661	O
,	O
662.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buttons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
live	O
in	O
Crown-court	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
they	O
keep	O
what	O
they	O
tell	O
me	O
is	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
bawdy-house	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
gin	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
one	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
dram	O
if	O
that	O
will	O
do	O
you	O
any	O
good	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
might	O
she	O
be	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
creature	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
me	O
into	O
these	O
people	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
nothing	O
but	O
gin	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
saw	O
me	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
lie	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lie	O
down	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
Yes	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
for	O
some	O
hours	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
Somebody	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
:	O
after	O
I	O
awak	O
'd	O
my	O
buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
above	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buttons	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
in	O
my	O
sleeves	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
these	O
things	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
heel	O
for	O
somebody	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
presently	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
hand	O
push	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
disappear	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
fasten	O
'd	O
in	O
before	O
)	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
my	O
buckles	O
again	O
;	O
after	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
talk	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
3	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
gin	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
buckles	O
again	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
relation	O
hard	O
by	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
some	O
,	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
somebody	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
call	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
my	O
buckles	O
again	O
I	O
would	O
prosecute	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
law	O
would	O
direct	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
that	O
you	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
cousin	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
name	O
:	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
wrong	O
woman	O
first	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
663	O
,	O
664.	O
Francis	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
dimity	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
and	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Macguire	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
665.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Venteres	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brandy	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Oct.	O
12	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
going	O
through	O
Aldgate	B-place
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
secur	O
'd	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
part	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
666.	O
John	B-pers
Feild	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
sack	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
8	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
667.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pewter	O
pint-pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Tessel	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
668.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cluney	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Badcock	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
12	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
his	O
compting-house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
hand	O
take	O
this	O
hat	O
off	O
from	O
many	O
others	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
but	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
steps	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
informed	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
669.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yalden	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
feloniously	O
forging	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
deed	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
from	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cousey	I-pers
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Chester	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
to	O
Patrick	B-pers
Cousins	I-pers
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Cousins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Drakeford	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
agent	O
for	O
the	O
Chester	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
's	O
prizes	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
last	O
January	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
power	O
of	O
an	O
attorney	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
agent	O
's	O
clerk	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yalden	I-pers
;	O
that	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
last	O
January	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
indict	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
)	O
then	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
last	O
Saturday	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
making	O
another	O
power	O
of	O
Attorney	O
;	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cousey	I-pers
;	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
Gosport	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
correspondent	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
wrote	O
if	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cousey	I-pers
should	O
come	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
correspondent	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Higenbottom	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Higenbottom	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
Power	O
of	O
an	O
Attorney	O
in	O
a	O
packet	O
from	O
Gosport	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
a	O
bill	O
to	O
pay	O
24	O
l.	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cousey	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
giving	O
me	O
a	O
receipt	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
next	O
day	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
for	O
it	O
from	O
Gosport	O
,	O
saying	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Cousey	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
confirm	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
a	O
letter	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
post	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Cousins	O
,	O
from	O
Gosport	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
me	O
mine	O
with	O
the	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
orders	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bill	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
in	O
six	O
days	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
for	O
24	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
He	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
none	O
,	O
being	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
trust	O
for	O
every	O
thing	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
till	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
he	O
returned	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
guinea	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
three	O
guineas	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
receipt	O
;	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
write	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
+	O
which	O
was	O
witnessed	O
by	O
one	O
here	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
Attorney	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
person	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Welister	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Higenbottom	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
step	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
witness	O
his	O
paying	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
receipt	O
was	O
read	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
Received	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
49	O
l.	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Cousins	I-pers
,	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
James	O
Higenbotton	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
for	O
Prize	O
Money	O
,	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
Thomas	O
Cousey	O
for	O
the	O
St.	O
Domingo	O
ship	O
,	O
taken	O
by	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Chester	O
.	O
The	O
mark	O
+	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cousey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
above	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
24	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
paid	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cousey	I-pers
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Swanson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
any	O
Letter	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cousey	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
certain	O
deed	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Letter	O
of	O
Attorney	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Baldwell	I-pers
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Chester	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
unto	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cadiwould	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yalden	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
office	O
(	O
my	O
master	O
keeps	O
a	O
public	O
office	O
,	O
he	O
transacts	O
by	O
commission	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
receiver	O
of	O
prize-money	O
and	O
wages	O
in	O
the	O
navy	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baldwell	I-pers
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
Power	O
of	O
an	O
Attorney	O
to	O
be	O
executed	O
in	O
that	O
name	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Chester	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
St.	O
Domingo	O
ship	O
;	O
this	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
to	O
receive	O
25	O
l.	O
My	O
master	O
being	O
busy	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
saying	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
leisure	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
at	O
leisure	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
office	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Baldwell	I-pers
;	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
a	O
land-corporal	O
on	O
board	O
;	O
accordingly	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
Power	O
of	O
Attorney	O
,	O
and	O
fill	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sign	O
the	O
name	O
John	B-pers
Baldwell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
our	O
other	O
clerk	O
witnessed	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
made	O
attorney	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
receive	O
25	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
and	O
on	O
sending	O
that	O
down	O
to	O
Gosport	O
he	O
would	O
receive	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Higenbottom	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
indictment	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
seal	O
taken	O
off	O
?	O
Cadiwould	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
we	O
always	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
re-executed	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
other	O
words	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
sealed	O
and	O
delivered	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
his	O
right	O
name	O
he	O
set	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Cadiwould	O
.	O
His	O
wife	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
office	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yalden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Higenbottom	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Couzens	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Higenbottom	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
24	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
to	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cousey	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
going	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
detected	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Higenbottom	O
came	O
in	O
?	O
Cadiwould	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Jowel	O
Swain	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sign	O
John	B-pers
Baldwell	I-pers
,	O
to	O
a	O
power	O
of	O
an	O
attorney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
filled	O
up	O
before	O
he	O
signed	O
that	O
name	O
?	O
Swain	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
sent	O
down	O
to	O
Gosport	O
to	O
have	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
by	O
our	O
agent	O
Mr.	O
Cousins	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
directed	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
letter	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
brought	O
in	O
their	O
Verdict	O
special	O
.	O
670.	O
Otho	B-pers
Hemingson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Doneholme	I-pers
,	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
18	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
man	O
's	O
trowsers	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Moses	B-pers
Jansen	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
10	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Doneholme	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
one	O
coat	O
,	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
from	O
me	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cabin	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
my	O
breeches	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
coat	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
house	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Doneholme	O
.	O
The	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sailed	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Dane	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
am	O
I	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
every	O
thing	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
on	O
board	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
fore-room	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
press-bed	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
lie	O
there	O
they	O
might	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
ever	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Captain	O
found	O
his	O
clothes	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
buckles	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
taking	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
English	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
shillings	O
in	O
Danish	O
money	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
opened	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
chest	O
in	O
a	O
ship	O
by	O
Irongate	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
examin	O
'd	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
clothes	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Ucopson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
captain	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
breeches	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coat	O
lay	O
under	O
the	O
pillow	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
Trials	O
being	O
ended	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
proceeded	O
to	O
give	O
Judgment	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Transported	O
for	O
7	O
years	O
,	O
25.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
599	O
Thomas	B-pers
Claiton	I-pers
600	O
Simon	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
601	O
John	B-pers
Napleton	I-pers
607	O
James	O
Needham	O
609	O
John	B-pers
Hutchens	I-pers
632	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
alias	O
Sergant	O
636	O
Lydia	B-pers
Whittmore	I-pers
637	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Venters	I-pers
665	O
Edward	O
Hill	O
667	O
Otho	B-pers
Hemingson	I-pers
670	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
604	O
Charles	B-pers
Mosley	I-pers
614	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
619	O
Henry	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
622	O
Edward	B-pers
Dunfield	I-pers
626	O
Philis	O
Jones	O
627	O
Mary	B-pers
Carmichel	I-pers
630	O
John	B-pers
Waine	I-pers
640	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
642	O
John	B-pers
Crosby	I-pers
648	O
James	B-pers
Hertford	I-pers
650	O
Francis	O
Forbes	O
651	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Killegrew	O
654	O
William	B-pers
Gunskine	I-pers
655	O
Whipped	O
,	O
10	O
.	O
Francis	O
Green	O
608	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
611	O
Susannah	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
635	O
Edward	B-pers
Cluney	I-pers
668	O
Gyles	O
Taylor	O
605	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
616	O
Henry	O
Hill	O
620	O
Joseph	B-pers
Buttler	I-pers
621	O
Thomas	B-pers
Caustel	I-pers
639	O
Ann	B-pers
Masterson	I-pers
647	O
Branded	O
1.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Scallock	I-pers
615	O
.	O
SHORT	O
HAND	O
taught	O
by	O
T.	O
Gurney	O
,	O
Watchmaker	O
,	O
in	O
Bennet	O
street	O
near	O
Christ	O
Church	O
,	O
Surrey	O
,	O
the	O
Writer	O
of	O
these	O
Proceedings	O
,	O
who	O
attends	O
every	O
Saturday	O
Evening	O
,	O
from	O
Five	O
till	O
Nine	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Last	O
and	O
Sugar-loaf	O
,	O
Water-lane	O
,	O
Black-fryars	O
.	O
Half	O
a	O
guinea	O
entrance	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
sum	O
when	O
the	O
scholar	O
is	O
compleated	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
takes	O
down	O
Trials	O
at	O
Law	O
.	O
