TOKEN	NE
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Deliver	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
22d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1749	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Public	O
may	O
be	O
assured	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
during	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CALVERT	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
)	O
the	O
Sessions-Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
Four-pence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
Sessions	O
shall	O
be	O
carefully	O
compriz	O
'd	O
in	O
One	O
such	O
Four-penny	O
Book	O
,	O
any	O
farther	O
Burthen	O
on	O
the	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
CALVERT	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DENNISON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLIVE	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BIRCH	O
,	O
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
Edward	B-pers
Shipman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Tookey	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Waite	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Whywall	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
Wyant	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Collard	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Luttman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Seccull	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Godfrey	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Stenton	I-pers
,	O
*	O
George	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Stenton	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Perrit	I-pers
were	O
sworn	O
in	O
their	O
room	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Caigow	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Torrane	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Greening	I-pers
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
318	O
,	O
319.	O
John	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
Sir	O
Geleius	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
Baronet	O
.	O
May	O
8	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
320.	O
Philip	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
skains	O
of	O
sowing	O
silk	O
,	O
18	O
yards	O
of	O
ribband	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
Things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Mertin	I-pers
.	O
April	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
321.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Oshorne	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Martin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
April	O
15	O
.	O
Martin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
kitchen	O
she	O
took	O
2	O
table	O
spoons	O
;	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Alderman	O
who	O
committed	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
after	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
at	O
Mr.	O
King	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
broke	O
the	O
handle	O
off	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
it	O
down	O
a	O
cellar	O
window	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
King	O
confirmed	O
the	O
stopping	O
the	O
spoon	O
at	O
her	O
House	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
322.	O
Henrietta	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
late	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Hanover	I-place
square	I-place
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
Holland	O
shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
Holland	O
aprons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
William	I-pers
Touyn	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knott	I-pers
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
Major	O
Touyn	B-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
my	O
family	O
;	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
Hare-street	B-place
,	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
,	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Knott	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
in	O
your	O
family	O
?	O
Touyn	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
weeks	O
before	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
when	O
we	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Marybone	O
street	O
;	O
we	O
discovered	O
eleven	O
parcels	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Maclean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
parish	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
to	O
the	O
Major	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Knott	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
two	O
shifts	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
in	O
Swallow	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
Major	O
has	O
sworn	O
belonged	O
to	O
his	O
daughter	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
can	O
inform	O
the	O
court	O
of	O
.	O
Nathanael	O
Brown	O
.	O
Upon	O
hearing	O
the	O
Major	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
servant	O
's	O
being	O
the	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
they	O
missed	O
any	O
spoons	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
examined	O
my	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
over	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
parcels	O
brought	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
2	O
clouts	O
,	O
2	O
napkins	O
,	O
one	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Major	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Major	O
Touyn	B-pers
.	O
Are	O
these	O
goods	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Major	O
Touyn	B-pers
.	O
They	O
are	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
persons	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
her	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
former	O
character	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Major	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hoped	O
she	O
would	O
meet	O
with	O
some	O
favour	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
323	O
,	O
324.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Delaport	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
near	B-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
Joha	O
Delaport	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
from	O
Cambridge	O
alone	O
,	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
lower	O
road	O
,	O
Islington	O
,	O
almost	O
opposite	O
Cambray	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
a	O
trott	O
,	O
I	O
overtook	O
an	O
ill-looking	O
fellow	O
on	O
foot	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
clapp	O
'd	O
spurs	O
to	O
my	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
perceived	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
some	O
word	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
stop	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
surprized	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
about	O
40	O
yards	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
directly	O
towards	O
my	O
horse	O
;	O
he	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
had	O
a	O
cutlass	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
snapp	O
'd	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stop	O
.	O
My	O
horse	O
went	O
from	O
under	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
;	O
they	O
pulled	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
silver	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
canvas	O
bag	O
with	O
some	O
French	O
sixpences	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
silver	O
or	O
gold	O
case	O
?	O
Delaport	O
.	O
Gold	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
interim	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
horseback	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
hopes	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
some	O
honest	O
countryman	O
,	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
n't	O
murder	O
me	O
.	O
Immediately	O
he	O
on	O
horseback	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
club	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
beat	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
another	O
word	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
go	O
over	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
[	O
This	O
by	O
their	O
own	O
confession	O
was	O
Murphy	O
on	O
my	O
horse	O
]	O
They	O
all	O
three	O
took	O
me	O
about	O
40	O
yards	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
that	O
pull	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
first	O
overtook	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
they	O
had	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
Murphy	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
examined	O
me	O
more	O
closely	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
private	O
pocket	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
rings	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
gold	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
gold	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
picture	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
.	O
They	O
also	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
wrought	O
buckles	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
tore	O
off	O
my	O
spurs	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
amazing	O
how	O
genteely	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
the	O
leather	O
was	O
torn	O
off	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
silver	O
spur	O
much	O
bent	O
.	O
]	O
They	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
buttons	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
cravat	O
from	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
underneath	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
green	O
velvet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
my	O
hanger	O
,	O
my	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
laced	O
hat	O
;	O
they	O
helped	O
me	O
on	O
with	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
afterwards	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
time	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
riding	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
once	O
had	O
thoughts	O
to	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
Murphy	O
in	O
his	O
confession	O
says	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
on	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
fearing	O
I	O
should	O
meet	O
with	O
assistance	O
,	O
he	O
rode	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
set	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
grass	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
both	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
feet	O
through	O
.	O
There	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
sitting	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
removed	O
from	O
thence	O
till	O
they	O
returned	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
continue	O
there	O
?	O
Delaport	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
endangering	O
my	O
health	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
my	O
breeches	O
was	O
unbuttoned	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
made	O
shift	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
safe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Delaport	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
industrious	O
in	O
advertising	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
Jew	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
and	O
belt	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
hanger	O
yours	O
?	O
Delaport	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry-Compter	O
where	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Lee	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
new	O
nothing	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
intelligence	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
an	O
Irishman	O
and	O
a	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
man	O
strive	O
to	O
avoid	O
us	O
,	O
ran	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
I	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
niece	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lee	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
after	O
some	O
threats	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
found	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
wig	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
powder-horns	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
implements	O
for	O
making	O
bullets	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
two	O
pistols	O
loaded	O
and	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
proposed	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
all	O
the	O
intelligence	O
she	O
could	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
had	O
play	O
'd	O
at	O
rob	O
thief	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
return	O
'd	O
to	O
Lee	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Counter	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
James	O
Wood	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
the	O
lace	O
waist-coat	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
girl	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
Wood	O
sent	O
her	O
for	O
sixpence	O
worth	O
of	O
salmon	O
to	O
White-chapel	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
interim	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
place	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
rings	O
and	O
two	O
watches	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
former	O
I	O
suppose	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
cap	O
'd	O
with	O
silver	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
rings	O
on	O
her	O
fingers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
one	O
was	O
the	O
picture	O
of	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
daughter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
diamond	O
ring	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Delaport	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
Sunday	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Lee	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
He	O
impeach	O
'd	O
thirteen	O
besides	O
himself	O
and	O
Murphy	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
list	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
several	O
other	O
robberies	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
hat	O
in	O
a	O
particular	O
position	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
observing	O
it	O
I	O
am	O
confident	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
every	O
thing	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
contains	O
three	O
sides	O
of	O
a	O
sheet	O
of	O
paper	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
Murphy	O
.	O
The	O
Saturday	O
before	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
absolutely	O
denied	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Lee	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry-Compter	O
for	O
further	O
examination	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
every	O
thing	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
on	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
before	O
related	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
gang	O
,	O
and	O
assisted	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
my	O
horse	O
up	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Thatch'd-house	O
,	O
Islington	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
witnesses	O
that	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
trouble	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
read	O
the	O
list	O
to	O
him	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Lee	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
robberies	O
with	O
eleven	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Nathan	B-pers
Ashur	I-pers
.	O
Lee	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
which	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
Lee	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
aside	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
sell	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
something	O
by	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
another	O
room	O
.	O
He	O
opened	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
there	O
a	O
green	O
double-breasted	O
velvet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
gold	O
tasts	O
,	O
and	O
laced	O
before	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
pockets	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
astonished	O
to	O
see	O
such	O
a	O
valuable	O
thing	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
above	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
gold	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
guess	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
two	O
rings	O
,	O
one	O
had	O
fourteen	O
little	O
diamonds	O
round	O
a	O
yellow	O
diamond	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Delaport	O
.	O
Did	O
that	O
ring	O
answer	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
yours	O
?	O
Delaport	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
exactly	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
picture	O
ring	O
with	O
shell	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
where	O
the	O
picture	O
was	O
set	O
in	O
.	O
Ashur	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
buttons	O
with	O
crystal	O
stones	O
.	O
Delaport	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sleeves	O
.	O
Ashur	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
these	O
things	O
are	O
valuable	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
on	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
Wood	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
Lee	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
rings	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
them	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
wet	O
?	O
Ashur	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
.	O
Delaport	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
fell	O
from	O
my	O
horse	O
I	O
fell	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
which	O
received	O
some	O
wet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
?	O
Ashur	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
this	O
hanger	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
not	O
under	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
hanger	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Constable	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Lisle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Constable	O
.	O
Ashur	O
the	O
Jew	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Saturday-night	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
,	O
Lee	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
something	O
for	O
sale	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
accordingly	O
on	O
Sunday	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eleven	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
assistance	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
hanger	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
Lee	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
girl	O
,	O
who	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
following	O
things	O
,	O
two	O
pistols	O
deeply	O
loaded	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Delaport	O
's	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
wig	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
cloak	O
and	O
a	O
hanger	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Lee	O
is	O
my	O
uncle	O
,	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
kept	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
took	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
to	O
pay	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
there	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
wer	O
e	O
very	O
private	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
ways	O
indeed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
James	O
Wood	O
burn	O
the	O
lace	O
belonging	O
to	O
this	O
velvet	O
waistcoat	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
hands	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Lee	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
's	O
custody	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
both	O
on	O
my	O
finger	O
;	O
the	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
picture	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
stones	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
one	O
was	O
the	O
picture	O
of	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
daughter	O
.	O
Lee	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
hanger	O
of	O
a	O
sailor	O
for	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
proof	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
witnesses	O
are	O
gone	O
down	O
into	O
Kent	O
last	O
week	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
says	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
swear	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
at	O
liberty	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
Murphy	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
take	O
a	O
farthing	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
325.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gorman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
April	O
19	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
declared	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
tankard	O
on	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
some	O
milk	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
near	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
before	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
his	O
maid-servant	O
remember	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
pan	O
to	O
take	O
in	O
milk	O
of	O
the	O
milk-woman	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
remember	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
326.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
hat	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
boxes	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	O
April	O
22	O
.	O
The	O
principal	O
evidence	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
who	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
hat	O
for	O
15	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
nine-pence	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
kept	O
the	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Bail-dock	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
cap	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
327.	O
James	B-pers
Foaley	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Curren	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Matthew	O
,	O
April	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
328.	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
late	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Buckworth	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
329.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
callicoe	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Rees	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
330.	O
William	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
yards	O
of	O
flanel	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
100	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hopley	I-pers
and	O
others	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hopley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
most	O
sorts	O
of	O
woolen	O
goods	O
;	O
this	O
parcel	O
of	O
goods	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Rochester-coach	O
,	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
their	O
coming	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
night	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
inn	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
brought	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
porter	O
of	O
the	O
inn	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stradwick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Rochester	O
coachman	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
with	O
the	O
coach	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
Spread-eagle	O
in	O
Grace-church-street	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Medcalf	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
porter	O
and	O
bookkeeper	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday-night	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
these	O
goods	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hopley	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
Hs	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
stooping	O
to	O
read	O
another	O
direction	O
,	O
this	O
parcel	O
was	O
lying	O
part	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
take	O
the	O
parcel	O
by	O
one	O
corner	O
I	O
was	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
power	O
to	O
call	O
out	O
for	O
help	O
;	O
he	O
drag	O
'd	O
it	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
some	O
persons	O
there	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
occasions	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
this	O
parcel	O
stood	O
up	O
on	O
one	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
thives	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
331.	O
John	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
April	O
30	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
332.	O
John	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
calf	O
skins	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
19	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Adamson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
currier	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
London-wall	B-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
Alderman-bury	I-place
.	O
On	O
Jan.	O
the	O
19th	O
I	O
lost	O
30	O
calf-skins	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
between	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
and	O
six	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
:	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
them	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
23	O
d	O
they	O
were	O
stopp	O
'd	O
upon	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
marks	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
parcel	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Wakefield	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Howel	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
my	O
master	O
some	O
skins	O
to	O
sell	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
20	O
s.	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
15	O
s	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
reason	O
Mr.	O
Howel	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
We	O
would	O
have	O
stopped	O
him	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
us	O
before	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
master-currier	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
six	O
men	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Attwood	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Walnut	O
tree	O
Alley	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
old	O
shoes	O
,	O
going	O
into	O
Rosemary-branch	O
alehouse	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
it	O
rain	O
'd	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
skin	O
or	O
two	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
he	O
seeing	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
many	O
shoemakers	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Attwood	O
;	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
skins	O
and	O
try	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
before	O
or	O
since	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
333.	O
John	B-pers
Cundict	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bane	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
334.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Leatherdale	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
Hen	O
Matthew	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
scourer	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Leatherdale	O
who	O
lives	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
coat	O
to	O
clean	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
going	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
doors	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witness	O
nor	O
he	O
either	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
335.	O
Robert	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
leather	O
hood	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
April	O
18	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
going	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
Exchange	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
on	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
my	O
great-coat	O
being	O
fasten	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
saddle	O
with	O
two	O
straps	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nail	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
cut	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bernard	O
took	O
a	O
post-chaise	O
and	O
I	O
rid	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
Threadneedle-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
horse	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
run	O
away	O
across	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
other	O
witnesses	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
upon	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
.	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
my	O
man	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
having	O
done	O
the	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
betwixt	O
the	O
Ship-tavern	O
behind	O
the	O
Exchange	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Winman	O
's	O
punch-house	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
on	O
horseback	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
off-side	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
that	O
cut	O
the	O
leather	O
straps	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
pushed	O
by	O
me	O
under	O
the	O
plazzas	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
Castle	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
Popes	O
head	O
tavern	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
tavern	O
and	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
coat	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
leather	O
hood	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hillier	I-pers
.	O
His	O
servant	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
336.	O
Martha	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
a	O
Pinchbeck	O
mettle	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
blood-stone	O
heart	O
,	O
and	O
philosopher	O
's	O
stone	O
egg	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Brooker	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
Sept.	O
15	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brooker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milliner	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
room	O
within	O
my	O
shop	O
where	O
this	O
watch	O
was	O
hanging	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
journey	O
woman	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
hanging	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
journeywoman	O
told	O
me	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
since	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
like	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
having	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
some	O
little	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
gentleman	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
to	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
Tooly-street	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
first	O
said	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
all	O
three	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
and	O
wrung	O
her	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
see	O
it	O
more	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
key	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
cap	O
;	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
three	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
two	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
jacket	O
and	O
trowsers	O
bring	O
a	O
light	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
three	O
guineas	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
beginning	O
at	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Simm	I-pers
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
September	O
15	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
step	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
hung	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
hour	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
by	O
herself	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
o'clock	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
337.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Emerson	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
gause	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
338.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
(	O
from	O
her	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodgings	O
)	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
339.	O
Charles	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Usher	I-pers
,	O
May	O
2	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Usher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
breeches	O
maker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
this	O
three	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
miss	O
'd	O
breeches	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
taxed	O
him	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
three	O
pair	O
more	O
than	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
before	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Timbril	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
more	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
340.	O
George	B-pers
Iberbeen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
for	O
proof	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
keeping	O
of	O
a	O
key	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
unlock	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
box	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
were	O
lost	O
from	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
341.	O
James	B-pers
Penoroy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Batty	I-pers
,	O
an	O
infant	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Mar	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Batty	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
mother	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
born	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
hard	O
frost	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
nine	O
years	O
old	O
last	O
January	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Crown	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
Vinegar	I-place
Merchant	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Worship	I-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Hog-lane	I-place
.	O
The	O
child	O
did	O
not	O
complain	O
of	O
any	O
hurt	O
till	O
the	O
Friday	O
after	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sore	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
complained	O
sadly	O
.	O
I	O
applied	O
fuller	O
's	O
earth	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
thinking	O
that	O
would	O
cool	O
her	O
,	O
looking	O
upon	O
the	O
disorder	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
scalding	O
of	O
her	O
water	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
inspect	O
the	O
parts	O
?	O
S.	O
Batty	O
.	O
She	O
appeared	O
very	O
red	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
something	O
ran	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
showed	O
me	O
a	O
cloth	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
to	O
her	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
;	O
her	O
shift	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
midwife	O
who	O
lived	O
near	O
me	O
that	O
afternoon	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
upon	O
seeing	O
her	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
feared	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
been	O
abused	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
foul	O
disease	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
believe	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
saying	O
the	O
child	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
two	O
men	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
thought	O
would	O
never	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
trust	O
my	O
life	O
with	O
either	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
hoped	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
better	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
easier	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
neighbour	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
worse	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
apply	O
to	O
a	O
proper	O
Doctor	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
applied	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Wathen	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Man-midwife	O
and	O
Doctor	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
child	O
had	O
over-strained	O
herself	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
her	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
child	O
is	O
foul	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
surprized	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
never	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
care	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
through	O
the	O
abuse	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
still	O
denied	O
that	O
ever	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
meddled	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
threaten	O
'd	O
her	O
life	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
tell	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Maclemara	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
many	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
laid	O
many	O
women	O
.	O
The	O
mother	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
child	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
running	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
her	O
shift	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
stiff	O
as	O
buckram	O
with	O
corrupted	O
matter	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
strain	O
.	O
A	O
strain	O
indeed	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
is	O
foul	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
through	O
the	O
abuse	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
:	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
trust	O
my	O
child	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
of	O
the	O
Sunday	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
Doctor	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
child	O
then	O
?	O
Maclemara	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
red	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
running	O
come	O
down	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
think	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Maclemara	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
really	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
the	O
abuse	O
of	O
some	O
man	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q.	O
Supposing	O
a	O
grown	O
man	O
had	O
laid	O
with	O
a	O
girl	O
about	O
nine	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
is	O
it	O
possible	O
it	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
shewn	O
by	O
her	O
walking	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Maclemara	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
it	O
must	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
swelling	O
?	O
Maclemara	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
torn	O
?	O
Maclemara	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
known	O
as	O
bad	O
symptoms	O
as	O
that	O
child	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
only	O
proceeded	O
from	O
heat	O
and	O
strains	O
?	O
Maclemara	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
strain	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
gross	O
humour	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
hear	O
of	O
children	O
being	O
so	O
without	O
the	O
abuse	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
?	O
Maclemara	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
talk	O
of	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
case	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
know	O
girls	O
at	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
that	O
have	O
had	O
gleetings	O
and	O
runnings	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
proceeded	O
from	O
strains	O
?	O
Maclemara	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
this	O
child	O
's	O
bedfellow	O
?	O
Maclemara	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
S.	O
Batty	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
son	O
about	O
15	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
?	O
S.	O
Batty	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
frequently	O
lie	O
along	O
with	O
this	O
girl	O
?	O
S.	O
Batty	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
large	O
family	O
,	O
have	O
laid	O
them	O
in	O
one	O
bed	O
sometimes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
?	O
S.	O
Batty	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
week	O
she	O
was	O
hurt	O
;	O
nor	O
can	O
I	O
say	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
.	O
They	O
being	O
brother	O
and	O
sister	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
any	O
harm	O
in	O
so	O
doing	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
court	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
if	O
required	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Maclemara	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
linen	O
?	O
Maclemara	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
colours	O
did	O
you	O
observe	O
there	O
?	O
Maclemara	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
mixed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
green	O
?	O
Maclemara	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wathen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
the	O
child	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
an	O
apprentice	O
?	O
Wathen	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
attended	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
foul	O
disease	O
?	O
Wathen	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
many	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
child	O
;	O
Wathen	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
parent	O
brought	O
the	O
child	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
talked	O
of	O
a	O
rape	O
committed	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
soul	O
distemper	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
clothes	O
that	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
matter	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
its	O
quantity	O
,	O
colour	O
,	O
and	O
malignity	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
really	O
the	O
foul	O
disease	O
in	O
both	O
our	O
opinions	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
prescribe	O
things	O
proper	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
the	O
child	O
now	O
?	O
Wathen	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
bad	O
symptoms	O
are	O
abated	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
of	O
recovery	O
;	O
I	O
attended	O
her	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
running	O
on	O
her	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
Wathen	O
.	O
White	O
;	O
which	O
is	O
what	O
we	O
apprehend	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
colour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
inspect	O
the	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
Wathen	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
inspected	O
her	O
last	O
Monday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
her	O
?	O
Wathen	O
.	O
The	O
external	O
lips	O
of	O
the	O
womb	O
are	O
extended	O
beyond	O
their	O
natural	O
dimensions	O
;	O
the	O
internal	O
parts	O
were	O
very	O
much	O
inflamed	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
from	O
the	O
acrimony	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
running	O
proceeding	O
from	O
the	O
womb	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
this	O
matter	O
?	O
Wathen	O
.	O
The	O
soul	O
disease	O
,	O
very	O
bad	O
indeed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
means	O
were	O
the	O
parts	O
extended	O
?	O
Wathen	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
by	O
carnal	O
copulation	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
there	O
could	O
be	O
the	O
foul	O
disease	O
given	O
to	O
any	O
child	O
without	O
penetration	O
?	O
Wathen	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
its	O
appearance	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
there	O
be	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
acted	O
on	O
a	O
child	O
of	O
that	O
age	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
penetration	O
without	O
being	O
lacerated	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
grown	O
up	O
?	O
Wathen	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
there	O
may	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
man	O
may	O
copulate	O
with	O
a	O
child	O
of	O
that	O
age	O
by	O
introducing	O
himself	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
without	O
a	O
laceration	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
?	O
Wathen	O
.	O
Far	O
enough	O
for	O
emissio	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
there	O
not	O
other	O
means	O
of	O
communicating	O
the	O
soul	O
disease	O
than	O
by	O
penetration	O
?	O
Wathen	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
its	O
appearance	O
in	O
this	O
kind	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
possible	O
that	O
a	O
small	O
degree	O
of	O
disorder	O
may	O
be	O
communicated	O
without	O
emissio	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
being	O
foul	O
?	O
Wathen	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
not	O
an	O
impossible	O
thing	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
who	O
catch	O
diseases	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
where	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
running	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
a	O
man	O
has	O
a	O
running	O
,	O
can	O
that	O
communicate	O
itself	O
to	O
a	O
child	O
without	O
emissio	O
?	O
Wathen	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
S.	O
Batty	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Herson	O
,	O
the	O
Attorney	O
?	O
S.	O
Batty	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
concerned	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
acted	O
by	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
and	O
my	O
advice	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
friends	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
husband	O
would	O
never	O
yield	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
offer	O
'd	O
us	O
ten	O
pounds	O
upon	O
the	O
nail	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
all	O
costs	O
and	O
charges	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Batty	I-pers
,	O
the	O
infant	O
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
hurt	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
coat	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
shift	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
tag	O
of	O
my	O
lace	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
lace	O
myself	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
below	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
lace	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
her	O
chamber	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
again	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
hither	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
ale	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
draw	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
owed	O
my	O
mother	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
bed	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
laid	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
one	O
hand	O
on	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
ran	O
his	O
double	O
fist	O
up	O
my	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
any	O
thing	O
wet	O
then	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
made	O
water	O
in	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
father	O
or	O
mother	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
them	O
half	O
murder	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
would	O
quite	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
mother	O
then	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
below	O
stairs	O
then	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
people	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
mouth	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
almost	O
strangled	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
threatened	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
tell	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
happened	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
my	O
mother	O
thought	O
I	O
walked	O
comically	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
sore	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
walk	O
.	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
make	O
a	O
plaister	O
of	O
fuller	O
's	O
earth	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
frightened	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
came	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
midwife	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
was	O
it	O
up	O
where	O
he	O
used	O
you	O
so	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
Two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
rooms	O
on	O
a	O
floor	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
two	O
rooms	O
on	O
a	O
floor	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
lodger	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
dressing	O
there	O
dinner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
laced	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
keep	O
your	O
bed	O
upon	O
this	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
once	O
so	O
bad	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
once	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
your	O
mother	O
called	O
you	O
away	O
;	O
telling	O
you	O
to	O
keep	O
private	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
swear	O
your	O
father	O
's	O
or	O
mother	O
's	O
life	O
away	O
instead	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Frances	B-pers
Bletsoe	I-pers
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
keep	O
your	O
bed	O
before	O
,	O
or	O
after	O
that	O
Friday	O
your	O
mother	O
searched	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
a	O
bed	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
was	O
it	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
cry	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
down	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
cold	O
day	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
my	O
mother	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
cried	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
cold	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
S.	O
Batty	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owe	O
you	O
any	O
money	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
S.	O
Batty	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
about	O
25	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
paid	O
me	O
since	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
victuals	O
,	O
drink	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q.	O
to	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
put	O
a	O
clean	O
shift	O
on	O
between	O
the	O
Sunday	O
and	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
?	O
M.	O
Batty	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
malicious	O
prosecution	O
;	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
spite	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Bletsoe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Batty	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
us	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
matter	O
?	O
Bletsoe	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Batty	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
come	O
upon	O
the	O
trial	O
,	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
wanted	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
of	O
eleven	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
bid	O
her	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
shift	O
herself	O
.	O
Then	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
mother	O
bid	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
worse	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
heard	O
to	O
speak	O
louder	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
her	O
mother	O
used	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
she	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
hang	O
her	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
instead	O
of	O
the	O
fellow	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
apprehend	O
was	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Bletsoe	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
was	O
kept	O
a	O
bed	O
on	O
purpose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
son	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Batty	O
fifteen	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
who	O
us	O
'd	O
frequently	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
this	O
child	O
?	O
Bletsoe	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
search	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
Bletsoe	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
once	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
swell	O
'd	O
nor	O
torn	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
nor	O
red	O
neither	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
a	O
running	O
?	O
Bletsoe	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
running	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
occasioned	O
by	O
a	O
strain	O
?	O
Bletsoe	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Batty	O
's	O
?	O
Bletsoe	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
warning	O
before	O
this	O
thing	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stayed	O
my	O
time	O
up	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
brother	O
very	O
orderly	O
?	O
Bletsoe	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
well	O
enough	O
while	O
near	O
his	O
parents	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
he	O
is	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
sight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
well-behaved	O
modest	O
man	O
?	O
Bletsoe	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
harm	O
in	O
him	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
in	O
any	O
one	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
not	O
addicted	O
to	O
women	O
?	O
Bletsoe	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
Knowledge	O
.	O
The	O
Court	O
made	O
enquiry	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
ever	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr	O
.	O
Guy	O
answered	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Guy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
business	O
?	O
Guy	O
.	O
Seven	O
years	O
for	O
myself	O
next	O
Midsummer	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Take	O
Mary	B-pers
Batty	I-pers
into	O
a	O
proper	O
place	O
and	O
inspect	O
the	O
parts	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
mother	O
,	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
together	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
returned	O
Guy	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
inspected	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Court	O
.	O
Pray	O
give	O
us	O
your	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
case	O
.	O
Guy	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
the	O
appearance	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
though	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
been	O
ravished	O
by	O
somebody	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
foul	O
disease	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
ready	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
running	O
she	O
has	O
is	O
only	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
the	O
lacerated	O
parts	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
a	O
certainty	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
children	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
usual	O
for	O
people	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
venereal	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
only	O
proceeds	O
from	O
an	O
inflammation	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
gentleman	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
first	O
inspection	O
on	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
certain	O
,	O
it	O
appears	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
child	O
has	O
been	O
lacerated	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
opinion	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
carnally	O
known	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
us	O
your	O
reasons	O
for	O
your	O
belief	O
?	O
Guy	O
.	O
The	O
part	O
is	O
distended	O
beyond	O
what	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
for	O
a	O
child	O
at	O
her	O
age	O
:	O
It	O
is	O
impossible	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
without	O
force	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
possible	O
,	O
if	O
a	O
full	O
grown	O
man	O
was	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
immediately	O
discovered	O
by	O
its	O
gate	O
?	O
Guy	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
must	O
:	O
The	O
child	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
much	O
inflamed	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
difficult	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
persons	O
who	O
spoke	O
well	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
former	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
342.	O
Bryan	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
clasps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hackney	B-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
March	O
19.	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawer	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
breeches	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Bell	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
paid	O
my	O
wife	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
an	O
old	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Horn	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
breeches	O
on	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
Deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
346.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
from	O
thence	O
one	O
linen	O
pocket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
three	O
iron	O
Keys	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
spectacles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jane	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Farnham-court	B-place
,	I-place
Pancrass	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
weekly	O
servant-man	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
away	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
farm	O
and	O
cows	O
;	O
they	O
broke	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
maid	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
screaming	O
out	O
awaken	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
seream	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
my	O
window	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
me	O
last	O
of	O
all	O
.	O
They	O
pull	O
'd	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
flung	O
me	O
down	O
in	O
another	O
room	O
and	O
trod	O
upon	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
then	O
their	O
cancle	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
man	O
's	O
candle	O
from	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
seed	O
the	O
cattle	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
confession	O
.	O
His	O
confession	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
others	O
a	O
night	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
thought	O
of	O
this	O
method	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
my	O
servant	O
man	O
goes	O
out	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
cows	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
my	O
servant	O
's	O
lanthorn	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Frances	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Give	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
J.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
lying	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
came	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
men	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
one	O
stood	O
by	O
my	O
side	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
:	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
my	O
mistress	O
and	O
her	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
frighten	O
'd	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
broke	O
my	O
three	O
boxes	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
?	O
J.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Peter	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
that	O
stood	O
with	O
the	O
candle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
by	O
the	O
bedside	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
tied	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
my	O
neck	O
and	O
drag	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
rooms	O
.	O
I	O
jump	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
thieves	O
;	O
then	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
me	O
sadly	O
;	O
they	O
beat	O
and	O
almost	O
choak	O
'd	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
under	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
hands	O
almost	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
They	O
found	O
my	O
mistress	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
left	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
guard	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
screamed	O
,	O
out	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
serv	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
worse	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
their	O
candle	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
at	O
next	O
door	O
were	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
so	O
a	O
man	O
below	O
whistled	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
hallowed	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
drag	O
my	O
mistress	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
lighted	O
till	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
put	O
her	O
down	O
and	O
tread	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
they	O
prevented	O
my	O
seeing	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
They	O
put	O
a	O
petticoat	O
about	O
my	O
head	O
to	O
hinder	O
me	O
from	O
seeing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
take	O
of	O
yours	O
?	O
J.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
9	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
four	O
caps	O
,	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
betwixt	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Ash-wednesday	O
morning	O
going	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
cattle	O
,	O
these	O
men	O
took	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
clap	O
'd	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
they	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
spring-lock	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
threatned	O
to	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
was	O
there	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
they	O
tied	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
post	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
guard	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
with	O
an	O
iron	O
paddle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
tied	O
to	O
the	O
post	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
some	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
some	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
They	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
clerk	O
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sign	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
freely	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Peter	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Luke	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Lame	O
Anthony	O
,	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Frances	O
,	O
Feb.	O
8.	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
;	O
that	O
Luke	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
and	O
Lame	O
Anthony	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
while	O
the	O
rest	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
he	O
now	O
is	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
innocent	O
young	O
fellow	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
and	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
sign	O
that	O
paper	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
made	O
me	O
stupified	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
foolish	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
lie	O
at	O
the	O
court	O
's	O
mercy	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
343.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bavin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
pint-mug	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Warwicker	I-pers
,	O
April	O
17	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Warwicker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
sign	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Nag's-head	I-place
in	I-place
Carnaby-market	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
pint-mug	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
fire-works	O
were	O
exhibited	O
in	O
the	O
Green	O
Park	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
serv	O
'd	O
with	O
threepenny	O
worth	O
of	O
bumbo	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
somewhat	O
like	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
person	O
had	O
a	O
green	O
cap	O
on	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Sun	O
and	O
Bull	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
:	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Winamill-street	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
loaded	O
pistol	O
and	O
a	O
green	O
cap	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
before	O
mentioned	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
houses	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
and	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
near	O
his	O
lodgings	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
West	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
he	O
wanted	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
walked	O
a	O
great	O
pace	O
;	O
we	O
followed	O
him	O
pretty	O
close	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Marybone	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurry	O
so	O
fast	O
:	O
we	O
still	O
kept	O
going	O
on	O
;	O
instead	O
of	O
keeping	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
stile	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
something	O
from	O
him	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
some	O
low	O
pales	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
rise	O
above	O
the	O
pales	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
up	O
much	O
like	O
a	O
silver-mug	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
ran	O
and	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
stile	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
still	O
by	O
a	O
pond	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
circles	O
in	O
the	O
water	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
thing	O
he	O
toss	O
'd	O
in	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
my	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
West	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
your	O
tankard	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
a	O
boy	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
water	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
sixpence	O
:	O
I	O
flung	O
a	O
stone	O
to	O
direct	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
the	O
motion	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
where	O
the	O
stone	O
fell	O
the	O
boy	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
pint-mug	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
this	O
is	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
flung	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
the	O
contrary	O
:	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
weight	O
on	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
and	O
letters	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
described	O
before	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
West	O
.	O
Depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
,	O
being	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Lyon	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
saw	O
only	O
bubles	O
in	O
the	O
water	O
:	O
he	O
also	O
advertis	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Warwicker	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Green	O
Park	O
that	O
day	O
from	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
'till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
344.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
April	O
17	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Ball	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
him	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
check	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
some	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
shirt	O
that	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
piece	O
the	O
shirt	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
from	O
;	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shift-sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
down	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
change	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
my	O
sister	O
saw	O
something	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
about	O
four	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
woman	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
bargained	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
my	O
sister	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
has	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
maid	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Minshaw	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
as	O
before-mentioned	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Vinegar-yard	O
;	O
by	O
that	O
time	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
crying	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
she	O
was	O
our	O
maid	O
,	O
my	O
sister	O
had	O
sent	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
courage	O
enough	O
to	O
call	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
two	O
bones	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
feet	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
run	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Minshaw	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
faster	O
than	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Peter's-street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
April	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
seven	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
rum	O
.	O
He	O
followed	O
me	O
and	O
drank	O
the	O
rum	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
glass	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
something	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
understand	O
,	O
took	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
rum	O
but	O
left	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
.	O
I	O
concluded	O
he	O
designed	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
rum	O
when	O
he	O
fetched	O
the	O
cloath	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
though	O
it	O
was	O
spoke	O
so	O
low	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
perfectly	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Ball	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
bundle	O
of	O
clothes	O
yours	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Ball	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
your	O
house	O
off	O
from	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Ball	O
's	O
shop	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
not	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Minshaw	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Mirshaw	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Vinegar-yard	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
crying	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
and	O
ran	O
into	O
an	O
ale-house	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
directly	O
through	O
the	O
house	O
into	O
the	O
ground	O
is	O
made	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
himself	O
behind	O
it	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
345.	O
John	B-pers
Darling	I-pers
,	O
late	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Hackney	I-place
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
37	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
May	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
not	O
being	O
laid	O
as	O
an	O
offence	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
346.	O
John	B-pers
Hoe	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Young	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Blackhorne	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Moulson	I-pers
,	O
April	O
26	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
347.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
wife	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
pint-mug	O
,	O
value	O
36s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
,	O
March	O
the	O
27th	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
348.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Toffe	I-pers
,	O
had	O
three	O
indictments	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
forgery	O
;	O
one	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
under	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stotten	I-pers
,	O
and	O
for	O
publishing	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forg	O
'd	O
:	O
a	O
second	O
note	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
under	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stotten	I-pers
,	O
and	O
also	O
for	O
publishing	O
it	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forg	O
'd	O
:	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
for	O
forging	O
the	O
last	O
will	O
and	O
testament	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
a	O
sailor	O
.	O
April	O
16	O
,	O
1736	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
defraud	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forg	O
'd	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
affect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
seemed	O
rather	O
the	O
artifice	O
of	O
Usher	B-pers
Gahagan	I-pers
and	O
Terence	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
(	O
against	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
principal	O
evidence	O
in	O
the	O
Jan	O
.	O
Sessions	O
last	O
)	O
either	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
way	O
or	O
invalidate	O
his	O
evidence	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
each	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
449.	O
Martha	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
5s	O
.	O
a	O
sette	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
cameo	O
petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Laninecre	I-pers
,	O
May	O
4	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
350.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
China	O
bowls	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
China	O
plate	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lardon	I-pers
,	O
April	O
16	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lardon	I-pers
.	O
My	O
parlour	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
April	O
16	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	I-place
King	I-place
's	I-place
head-court	I-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
things	O
than	O
are	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
By	O
making	O
some	O
complaint	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
China	O
,	O
saying	O
Mr.	O
Unwin	O
,	O
that	O
honest	O
man	O
a	O
thief	O
catcher	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye-tavern	O
without	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
will	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
drink	O
?	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
we	O
come	O
to	O
search	O
your	O
house	O
:	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
search	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
you	O
are	O
come	O
upon	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
fetch	O
you	O
the	O
China	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
;	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
four	O
bowls	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
kept	O
by	O
him	O
almost	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
advertiz	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Lardon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
them	O
without	O
giving	O
me	O
the	O
trouble	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
China	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
by	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
:	O
they	O
never	O
were	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
upon	O
sale	O
upon	O
any	O
account	O
whatsoever	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
were	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
?	O
Unwin	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
suspect	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
?	O
Unwin	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
chalanged	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
inquire	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Unwin	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
she	O
then	O
?	O
Unwin	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Magpye-tavern	O
without	O
Aldgate	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
them	O
'till	O
I	O
knew	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
sent	O
them	O
out	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
these	O
people	O
came	O
in	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
wanted	O
some	O
China	O
and	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
stop	O
'd	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Unwin	O
.	O
Three	O
nights	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Unwin	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
lie	O
two	O
nights	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
out	O
of	O
charity	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Thursday	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
see	O
counsel	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
this	O
prosecution	O
?	O
Unwin	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
any	O
harm	O
in	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Counsel	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
guinea	O
from	O
this	O
witness	O
to	O
plead	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
acquitted	O
and	O
Unwin	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
came	O
into	O
court	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
following	O
presentment	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
We	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
for	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
do	O
most	O
humbly	O
and	O
unanimously	O
present	O
,	O
that	O
Samuel	O
Unwin	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Botolp	O
,	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
vintner	O
,	O
now	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
two	O
months	O
last	O
past	O
,	O
has	O
kept	O
an	O
ill-govern	O
'd	O
and	O
disorderly	O
house	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
or	O
known	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
Magpye-tavern	O
,	O
situate	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
parish	O
without	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
that	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
wicked	O
lucre	O
and	O
gain	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
during	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
aforesaid	O
has	O
harboured	O
and	O
entertained	O
,	O
and	O
still	O
harbours	O
and	O
entertains	O
divers	O
rogues	O
,	O
thieves	O
,	O
vagabonds	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
loose	O
and	O
disorderly	O
persons	O
in	O
his	O
said	O
house	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
by	O
day	O
as	O
by	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
house	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
suppressed	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
to	O
us	O
that	O
the	O
said	O
Unwin	O
's	O
farther	O
continuance	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
must	O
greatly	O
tend	O
to	O
the	O
corruption	O
of	O
the	O
morals	O
of	O
youth	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
endangerment	O
of	O
the	O
publick	O
safety	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
terror	O
and	O
nusance	O
of	O
all	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
liege	O
subjects	O
inhabiting	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Signed	O
by	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
351.	O
William	B-pers
Chitty	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ashur	I-pers
;	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
,	O
May	O
4	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
352.	O
William	B-pers
Stoakes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
353.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
Nemark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Stracy	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Leydon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
one	O
damask	O
table-cloth	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
nine	O
napkins	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
streamer	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Leydon	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
26	O
.	O
The	O
only	O
evidence	O
here	O
was	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
an	O
accomplice	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
354.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pavet	I-pers
.	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
holland	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
lac	O
'd	O
mob	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Bine	I-pers
,	O
April	O
27	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
355.	O
George	B-pers
Jaques	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
damask	O
clouts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
silver	O
teaspoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
silver	O
correl	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
356.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hand	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Pletcher	I-pers
.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Macartey	I-pers
;	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
April	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stole	O
these	O
goods	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
and	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Note	O
:	O
this	O
edition	O
of	O
the	O
Proceedings	O
was	O
misdated	O
on	O
the	O
original	O
title	O
page	O
.	O
The	O
correct	O
dates	O
for	O
this	O
meeting	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
are	O
MAY	O
11	O
,	O
12	O
and	O
13	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
]	O
357.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
,	O
late	B-place
of	I-place
Dublin	I-place
in	I-place
Ireland	I-place
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Conway	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
uttering	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
will	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
.	O
One	O
day	O
last	O
summer	O
Mr.	O
Deverix	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
three	O
men	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deverix	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
talk	O
about	O
some	O
affairs	O
;	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
my	O
son	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
going	O
aboard	O
some	O
king	O
's	O
ship	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
now	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
will	O
and	O
power	O
before	O
he	O
goes	O
;	O
says	O
Deverix	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
will	O
do	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Paul's-head	O
tavern	O
near	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Commons	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
will	O
was	O
fill	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Deverix	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
likewise	O
I	O
filled	O
up	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
for	O
her	O
son	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
witnessed	O
by	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
besides	O
myself	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
said	O
son	O
sign	O
'd	O
both	O
will	O
and	O
power	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
name	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
son	O
by	O
?	O
Barry	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
mother	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
since	O
?	O
Barry	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
or	O
since	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
none	O
there	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Deverix	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Davis	O
that	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
since	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
discovered	O
the	O
fraud	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
discovery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
will	O
?	O
Barry	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Deverix	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
our	O
business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
since	O
?	O
Barry	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
pass	O
'd	O
and	O
repass	O
'd	O
the	O
navy	O
office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
coversation	O
with	O
her	O
since	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Barry	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
use	O
she	O
made	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Barry	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
remember	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Barry	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
mother	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
son	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
that	O
person	O
she	O
called	O
her	O
son	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Barry	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
original	O
will	O
is	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
hand-writing	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
fill	O
'd	O
in	O
?	O
Barry	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
whose	O
direction	O
did	O
you	O
write	O
it	O
?	O
Barry	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
was	O
her	O
end	O
in	O
having	O
it	O
done	O
?	O
Barry	O
.	O
Doubtless	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
obtain	O
what	O
wages	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
prick	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
*	O
R	O
and	O
if	O
Deverix	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
how	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
R	O
off	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
three	O
guineas	O
.	O
*	O
That	O
is	O
run	O
from	O
the	O
ship	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
receiving	O
any	O
money	O
