TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
24th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1749	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
John	B-pers
Blachford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1750	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BLACHFORD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
DENNISON	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLIVE	I-pers
,	O
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chidley	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Merryfield	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Mascall	I-pers
,	O
Lamper	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
,	O
Eleazar	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Wing	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Leightenhouse	I-pers
,	O
Nathaneal	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
Duncan	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cosh	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pudington	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pinchbeck	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bough	I-pers
.	O
369.	O
Joseph	B-pers
James	I-pers
Swaby	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
Finchly	B-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
William	B-pers
Rock	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
presenting	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
demanding	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
370.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
small	O
glass	O
bottles	O
with	O
flower	O
of	O
mustardseed	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
six	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
crown	O
soap	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
two	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
snuff	O
,	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
fig	O
blue	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
one	O
pound	O
of	O
powder	O
blue	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
,	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
Accquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
quart	O
bottle	O
of	O
rum	O
,	O
two	O
blacking	O
brushes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
rush	O
basket	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
371.	O
Benj	B-pers
.	I-pers
Chamberlayne	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
Abraham	B-pers
Maddocks	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
Pinchbeck-mettle	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
tortoise	O
shell	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Abraham	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
April	O
10	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Maddocks	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
being	O
met	O
by	O
five	O
persons	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
who	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
sware	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Applegate	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
in	O
company	O
in	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
amongst	O
the	O
last	O
malefactors	O
at	O
Tyburn	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
a	O
black	O
,	O
also	O
gave	O
a	O
particular	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
agreeable	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
testimony	O
not	O
being	O
confirm	O
'd	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
witness	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
372.	O
Charles	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Mecarty	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Desmond	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Earl	I-pers
of	I-pers
Desmond	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
the	I-place
martyr	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
subject	O
of	O
the	O
crown	O
of	O
Great	O
Britain	O
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
hire	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
subject	O
of	O
this	O
realm	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
intent	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
serve	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
as	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
without	O
leave	O
or	O
licence	O
from	O
his	O
Majesty	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
obtained	O
,	O
in	O
contempt	O
of	O
outsaid	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
laws	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plumber	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
below	O
the	O
church	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
home	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
servant	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
was	O
signed	O
Desmond	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
this	O
Desmond	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Desmond	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
my	O
service	O
to	O
his	O
lordship	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
wait	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
is	O
this	O
letter	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
purport	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
certain	O
lady	O
of	O
quality	O
that	O
had	O
some	O
business	O
to	O
do	O
to	O
some	O
houses	O
in	O
Wild-street	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
had	O
recommended	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
recommend	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Queen's-square	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
sitting	O
with	O
a	O
book	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
and	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
chair	O
to	O
me	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
or	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
lady	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
there	O
'till	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
expected	O
some	O
company	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
return	O
again	O
by	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
with	O
him	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
appointed	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
whom	O
he	O
called	O
my	O
Lady	O
Gunston	O
,	O
he	O
recommended	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
plumber	O
's	O
work	O
to	O
some	O
houses	O
of	O
hers	O
in	O
Wild-street	O
;	O
she	O
immediately	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
work	O
to	O
do	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
do	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
dine	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
accordingly	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
after	O
dinner	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
complain	O
of	O
the	O
hardship	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
from	O
the	O
present	O
government	O
,	O
and	O
especially	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Carrington	O
,	O
a	O
messenger	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
as	O
many	O
ill	O
names	O
as	O
possible	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
like	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
having	O
an	O
order	O
from	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
France	O
to	O
come	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
French	O
ambassador	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
above	O
150	O
l.	O
for	O
his	O
passage	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
debts	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
France	O
or	O
Ireland	O
this	O
summer	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
captain	O
's	O
commission	O
in	O
a	O
regiment	O
in	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
least	O
it	O
should	O
not	O
cost	O
me	O
above	O
100	O
l.	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
very	O
well	O
afford	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
began	O
to	O
drink	O
healths	O
,	O
he	O
drank	O
Prince	O
Charles	O
,	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
healths	O
I	O
drank	O
.	O
Late	O
at	O
night	O
he	O
drank	O
damnation	O
to	O
the	O
Protestant	O
succession	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
refus	O
'd	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
leave	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
900	O
l.	O
lay	O
in	O
Sir	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
's	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
going	O
there	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
and	O
two	O
servants	O
in	O
livery	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
their	O
livery	O
were	O
green	O
,	O
with	O
scarlet	O
waistcoats	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
silver	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
towards	O
dusk	O
,	O
when	O
there	O
I	O
waited	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
some	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
having	O
had	O
some	O
discourse	O
with	O
Sir	O
Daniel	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
Sir	O
Daniel	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
compting-house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
talk	O
with	O
Sir	O
Daniel	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
accordingly	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
'd	O
about	O
on	O
the	O
pavement	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
Sir	O
Daniel	O
expected	O
the	O
money	O
very	O
soon	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
drove	O
away	O
.	O
Coming	O
to	O
the	O
black	O
horse	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
dry	O
,	O
we	O
stop	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
servants	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
drove	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
servants	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
there	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
his	O
lordship	O
before	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Drummonds	O
,	O
were	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
waited	O
in	O
the	O
hall	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
sent	O
a	O
servant	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
din	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
discourse	O
went	O
on	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
insisting	O
on	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
captain	O
in	O
a	O
regiment	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
my	O
cloaths	O
should	O
not	O
cost	O
me	O
anything	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
himself	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
there	O
pretty	O
late	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Pearce	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
for	O
his	O
housekeeper	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
wife	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
during	O
this	O
we	O
had	O
continual	O
discourse	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
one	O
Isaac	B-pers
Osbridge	I-pers
came	O
to	O
take	O
measure	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
order	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
fashion	O
that	O
would	O
suit	O
the	O
French	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
any	O
directions	O
concerning	O
the	O
fashion	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
fashion	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
these	O
cloaths	O
paid	O
for	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
yet	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
suits	O
I	O
wore	O
for	O
upwards	O
of	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
suits	O
were	O
ordered	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
suits	O
order	O
'd	O
and	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
continually	O
together	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
still	O
holding	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
discourse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
are	O
the	O
cloaths	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
now	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lay	O
down	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
a	O
plumber	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
fore-man	O
who	O
did	O
that	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
nights	O
without	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
design	O
'd	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
my	O
agreeing	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
,	O
thinking	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
there	O
was	O
enough	O
at	O
home	O
to	O
supply	O
her	O
with	O
what	O
she	O
might	O
want	O
.	O
'T	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
last	O
earthquake	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
shock	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
breakfast	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
)	O
that	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Windsor	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
conceal	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
taking	O
me	O
abroad	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Windsor	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Ockingham	O
,	O
returning	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
from	O
London	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
to	O
Reading	O
;	O
and	O
whilst	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
messenger	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Windsor	O
,	O
upon	O
what	O
business	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Henley	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
Reading	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
,	O
a	O
plumber	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
short	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
too	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Nevel	O
,	O
a	O
silversmith	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
discourse	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
engag	O
'd	O
myself	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
captain	O
in	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
's	O
service	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
design	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
France	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
We	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
several	O
days	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
raise	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
cloaths	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
wore	O
them	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
my	O
key	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
consent	O
,	O
sent	O
them	O
by	O
his	O
servant	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
ten	O
guineas	O
to	O
one	O
Singleton	O
by	O
Red-lion-square	O
;	O
of	O
which	O
sum	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
kept	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Windfor	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
a	O
plumber	O
any	O
longer	O
.	O
[	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
coats	O
was	O
blue	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
rows	O
of	O
lace	O
round	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
lac	O
'd	O
with	O
silver	O
.	O
]	O
Isaac	B-pers
Osbridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
measure	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
,	O
by	O
and	O
for	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
orders	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
cloaths	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
recommendation	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
measure	O
,	O
directed	O
me	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
their	O
being	O
made	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
I	O
made	O
,	O
(	O
holding	O
the	O
coat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
are	O
made	O
in	O
a	O
richer	O
manner	O
than	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
expect	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
you	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
I	O
imagin	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
paid	O
yet	O
,	O
neither	O
have	O
I	O
demanded	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
he	O
has	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
bill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
before	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
:	O
but	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
these	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
one	O
day	O
went	O
,	O
who	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
his	O
having	O
got	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
customer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
fortune	O
too	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
quality	O
I	O
then	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
express	O
'd	O
my	O
obligation	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
kindness	O
:	O
He	O
then	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
who	O
happen	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
one	O
day	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
chanc	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
arrest	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
those	O
cloaths	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
such	O
cloaths	O
as	O
those	O
for	O
plumbers	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
plumber	O
then	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
fortune	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
they	O
are	O
regimentals	O
of	O
any	O
country	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
Really	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
in	O
that	O
form	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
as	O
rich	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
the	O
fashion	O
of	O
England	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
so	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
directed	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
lace	O
on	O
in	O
any	O
particular	O
form	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
particular	O
order	O
;	O
my	O
order	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
as	O
rich	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
lace	O
on	O
according	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
mind	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
do	O
you	O
look	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
debtor	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
I	O
enter	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
book	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
debtor	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
the	O
cloaths	O
were	O
pawned	O
for	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
;	O
the	O
reason	O
was	O
,	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
any	O
money	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
fortune	O
lately	O
left	O
you	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
is	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
yet	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
executor	O
's	O
hands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
receive	O
any	O
more	O
money	O
than	O
what	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
?	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
about	O
eight	O
guineas	O
at	O
Windsor	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Nevil	O
,	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
were	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
there	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
determined	O
to	O
go	O
when	O
these	O
cloaths	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
word	O
,	O
I	O
judg	O
'd	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
to	O
the	O
jubilee	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
fit	O
for	O
England	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
abroad	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
name	O
the	O
jubilee	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
nam	O
'd	O
among	O
the	O
servants	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
THEY	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
;	O
nor	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
expression	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
hear	O
Pearce	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
France	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Windsor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Mermaid	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
fuddled	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
school-fellows	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
fathers	O
were	O
partners	O
together	O
.	O
Their	O
discourse	O
was	O
upon	O
military	O
affairs	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
knew	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
out	O
on	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
paper	O
a	O
machine	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
invented	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
putting	O
the	O
infantry	O
and	O
cavalry	O
in	O
disorder	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
the	O
D	O
-	O
and	O
the	O
Protestant	O
Succession	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
asking	O
him	O
the	O
reason	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
unhappy	O
gentlemen	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
ship	O
coming	O
over	O
to	O
assist	O
P	O
-	O
C	O
-	O
in	O
recovering	O
his	O
right	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
delivered	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carrington	O
,	O
in	O
whose	O
hands	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
almost	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
whom	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
through	O
the	O
head	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
further	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
inlisted	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
in	O
the	O
foreign	O
service	O
as	O
a	O
captain	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
that	O
station	O
,	O
telling	O
as	O
an	O
encouragement	O
for	O
me	O
his	O
having	O
enlisted	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
suits	O
of	O
cloaths	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
captain	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
company	O
:	O
he	O
added	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
honour	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
joint-engineer	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
under	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
France	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
forty	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
for	O
my	O
machine	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
every	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
cloaths	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
riding-suit	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
enlisted	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
twenty	O
times	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
cloaths	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
likewise	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
the	O
Dauphin	O
of	O
France	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
bawdy-house	O
when	O
he	O
pleased	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Orleans	O
in	O
France	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
contradict	O
his	O
being	O
inlisted	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
actually	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
captain	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
this	O
discourse	O
between	O
us	O
at	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
stay	O
'd	O
till	O
about	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
smoak	O
'd	O
a	O
pipe	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
During	O
this	O
talk	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
but	O
us	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Mr.	O
White	O
there	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
for	O
aught	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
when	O
this	O
talk	O
was	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
there	O
but	O
us	O
three	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Your	O
doxy	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
's	O
doxy	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
us	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
this	O
discourse	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Mermaid	O
at	O
Windsor	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
ladies	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
staid	O
there	O
almost	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
near	O
ten	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
was	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
frequently	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
dining-room	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
a	O
scarlet	O
coat	O
,	O
trimmed	O
with	O
gold	O
.	O
One	O
evening	O
we	O
went	O
a	O
fishing	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
discourse	O
.	O
Indeed	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
talk	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Oxford	O
first	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
first	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
upon	O
a	O
letter	O
I	O
wrote	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
influence	O
of	O
Lady	O
Gunston	O
,	O
wife	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
chairman	O
at	O
Westminster	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
house	O
to	O
repair	O
in	O
Wild-street	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
my	O
business	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
expected	O
the	O
Lady	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
with	O
me	O
again	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
.	O
He	O
accordingly	O
came	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
Lady	O
Gunston	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
an	O
agreement	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
drink	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
punch	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
health	O
was	O
toasted	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
made	O
answer	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Rome	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
left	O
London	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
jubilee	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
added	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Pearce	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
at	O
an	O
equal	O
expence	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
too	O
:	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
telling	O
him	O
tradesmen	O
could	O
not	O
dispense	O
with	O
so	O
large	O
a	O
sum	O
,	O
he	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
his	O
father	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
20,000	O
l.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
spare	O
500	O
l.	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
tradesman	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
a	O
scarlet	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
well	O
made	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
who	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
Mr.	O
Osbridge	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Osbridge	O
came	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
measure	O
,	O
made	O
the	O
cloaths	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
desire	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
home	O
.	O
Early	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
miss	O
Williams	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
keeps	O
company	O
with	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
Windsor	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
four-wheele	O
chaise	O
with	O
two	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
saddle	O
horses	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
no	O
denial	O
,	O
but	O
oblig	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
about	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
without	O
more	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
mentioned	O
his	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
supply	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
should	O
return	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
there	O
very	O
late	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
prepar	O
'd	O
a	O
fishing-boat	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
diversion	O
of	O
fishing	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
it	O
was	O
inconsistent	O
with	O
our	O
interest	O
to	O
stay	O
here	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
naked	O
truth	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
debt	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
.	O
An	O
express	O
was	O
now	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
bail	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
town	O
in	O
a	O
limited	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
satisfied	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
Windsor	O
.	O
Pearce	O
insisted	O
on	O
my	O
returning	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
unwilling	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
sent	O
his	O
chaise	O
and	O
two	O
horses	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Upon	O
their	O
arrival	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
upon	O
earnest	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
defray	O
the	O
expences	O
;	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
cloaths	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
went	O
to	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
positively	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
return	O
home	O
.	O
He	O
wrote	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
bitch	O
of	O
a	O
whore	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
cohabit	O
with	O
her	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
loved	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
little	O
finger	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
better	O
than	O
he	O
did	O
her	O
whole	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
settle	O
something	O
agreeable	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
his	O
fortune	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
hands	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
intreaties	O
he	O
prevailed	O
on	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Reading	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
two	O
days	O
,	O
some	O
men	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
dinner	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
dine	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
dined	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
drink	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
dinner	O
,	O
he	O
entertained	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
machine	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
it	O
with	O
iron	O
graffles	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
a	O
thousand	O
men	O
should	O
beat	O
twenty	O
thousand	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
them	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
sword	O
in	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
impracticable	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
D	O
-	O
of	O
C	O
-	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
paid	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
h	O
-	O
was	O
too	O
thick	O
to	O
conceive	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
after	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
settle	O
my	O
affairs	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
I	O
never	O
inlisted	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
below	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Attorney-General	O
mov	O
'd	O
against	O
me	O
last	O
Sessions	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Carrington	O
took	O
the	O
most	O
disorderly	O
steps	O
that	O
man	O
could	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
was	O
so	O
punctual	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
our	O
return	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
return	O
in	O
six	O
months	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
my	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
inherit	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
fortune	O
,	O
and	O
improve	O
the	O
liberal	O
education	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
hoping	O
I	O
shall	O
turn	O
out	O
an	O
honour	O
to	O
my	O
country	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cennet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
inlisting	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
talk	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
jubilee	O
at	O
Rome	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
when	O
the	O
taylor	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
understood	O
those	O
cloaths	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
fitting	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
jubilee	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
mentioned	O
to	O
the	O
taylor	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
taylor	O
for	O
those	O
cloaths	O
?	O
Cennet	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
each	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
his	O
own	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
their	O
going	O
to	O
France	O
?	O
Cennet	O
.	O
They	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
going	O
through	O
France	O
to	O
Rome	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
inlisted	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
?	O
Cennet	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
nor	O
had	O
I	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
countryman	O
is	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Cennet	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
an	O
Irishman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Cennet	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
last	O
races	O
in	O
Tothill-fields	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
by	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
somebody	O
said	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Desmond	O
was	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
induc	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Queen-square	O
.	O
I	O
get	O
notes	O
discounted	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
's	O
,	O
of	O
54	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
which	O
I	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
distiller	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
would	O
take	O
10	O
or	O
20	O
gallons	O
of	O
rum	O
,	O
and	O
allow	O
the	O
discount	O
besides	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
distiller	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
some	O
enquiry	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
some	O
other	O
person	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
sham	O
note	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Queen-square	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
distiller	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
distiller	O
not	O
thinking	O
proper	O
to	O
discount	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Cennet	O
.	O
In	O
Round-court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
paid	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
trouble	O
in	O
going	O
with	O
this	O
note	O
?	O
Cennet	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
deal	O
in	O
?	O
Cennet	O
.	O
I	O
deal	O
sometimes	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
sometimes	O
in	O
Irish	O
linens	O
,	O
sometimes	O
in	O
Irish	O
stuffs	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
getting	O
notes	O
discounted	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
house-keeper	O
?	O
Cennet	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
second	O
floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
been	O
very	O
private	O
together	O
since	O
this	O
?	O
Cennet	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
together	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
inlisted	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
?	O
Cennet	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
own	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
prevail	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
to	O
Rome	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
Pearce	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
any	O
foreign	O
service	O
?	O
Cennet	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
please	O
you	O
may	O
ask	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
that	O
wrote	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
guard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Guard	O
!	O
for	O
what	O
?	O
Cennet	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
should	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
Pearce	O
to	O
the	O
question	O
.	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
sham	O
Lord	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
should	O
suffer	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Cennet	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
taylor	O
for	O
those	O
cloaths	O
?	O
Cennet	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
taylor	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
draught	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
these	O
cloaths	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
these	O
cloaths	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Novel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
February	O
there	O
was	O
wrote	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
book	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
wait	O
on	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Desmond	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
some	O
plate	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
departed	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
draught	O
upon	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
meaning	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Upon	O
enquiry	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
draught	O
was	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
therefore	O
went	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
accept	O
the	O
draught	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
deliver	O
'd	O
a	O
hundred	O
pound	O
's	O
worth	O
of	O
plate	O
at	O
his	O
Lordship	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
Did	O
Pearce	O
ever	O
employ	O
you	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
servant	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
livery	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
them	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
this	O
affair	O
has	O
stop	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
finished	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
they	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
shoulder-knot	O
,	O
scarlet	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q.	O
Supposing	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
bound	O
in	O
point	O
of	O
law	O
to	O
pay	O
you	O
for	O
these	O
cloaths	O
you	O
have	O
made	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
must	O
lose	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
you	O
not	O
demand	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
in	O
Queen's-square	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
house	O
keeper	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
house	O
or	O
a	O
lodging	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
whole	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
cook	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
servants	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
witness	O
was	O
always	O
in	O
my	O
company	O
when	O
gentlemen	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
great	O
obligations	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
supplied	O
me	O
with	O
money	O
to	O
see	O
counsel	O
last	O
November	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
talk	O
of	O
inlisting	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
into	O
the	O
French	O
King	O
's	O
service	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
Pearce	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
first	O
acquainted	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
My	O
lady	O
Gunston	O
wanted	O
a	O
plumber	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
,	O
they	O
talk	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
election	O
affairs	O
,	O
and	O
duke	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
name	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
see	O
him	O
soon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
could	O
afford	O
to	O
spend	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
tradesman	O
in	O
London	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
he	O
to	O
go	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
jubilee	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
bid	O
him	O
consider	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
expence	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
who	O
made	O
his	O
cloaths	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Osbridge	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
suits	O
of	O
cloaths	O
made	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
March	O
he	O
hired	O
a	O
black	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
ten	O
pounds	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
hear	O
mention	O
made	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
France	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
France	O
mentioned	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
taylor	O
brought	O
home	O
the	O
cloaths	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
they	O
brought	O
to	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
fitted	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
cloaths	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
lady	O
's	O
house	O
which	O
he	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
cloaths	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
return	O
in	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Pearce	O
said	O
that	O
would	O
just	O
suit	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
fortune	O
would	O
come	O
due	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
husband	O
living	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
Windsor	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
three	O
times	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
lady	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Her	O
name	O
is	O
Molly	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
married	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
trade	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
went	O
and	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
's	O
cloaths	O
tried	O
on	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
your	O
glady	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Windsor	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
without	O
my	O
company	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
had	O
a	O
four	O
wheel	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
rode	O
a	O
single	O
horse	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
footman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
husband	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Pearce	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
lady	O
Gunston	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
their	O
dining	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
their	O
going	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
together	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Cennet	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
frequently	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
long	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
Windsor	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
F.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hear	O
d	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
a	O
draught	O
of	O
his	O
machine	O
,	O
and	O
explain	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
D	O
-	O
of	O
C	O
-	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
D	O
-	O
of	O
C	O
-	O
,	O
his	O
h	O
-	O
was	O
too	O
thick	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Holmes	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
Cennet	O
was	O
his	O
attorney	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
373.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bradnam	I-pers
,	O
May	O
17	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bradnam	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
away	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
nineteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
into	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
purse	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
intending	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
afterwards	O
I	O
thought	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
pocket	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
it	O
?	O
Bradnam	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
pocket	O
had	O
been	O
mov	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
told	O
over	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
my	O
maid	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
some	O
body	O
had	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
on	O
searching	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
guinea	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
any	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Bradnam	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
then	O
owned	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
design	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
Ann	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	O
Archer	O
up	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
heard	O
her	O
own	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
her	O
testimony	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
acknowleged	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
374.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
one	O
diamond	O
ring	O
,	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
,	O
one	O
purse	O
and	O
ten	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Kirk	O
,	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Lillypot-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Aldersgate	I-place
without	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
maker	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
bound	O
,	O
come	O
August	O
next	O
,	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
seventeen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
when	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
came	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
directly	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
chamber	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
before	O
was	O
double	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
also	O
a	O
buroe	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
till	O
within	O
it	O
,	O
were	O
both	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
bank	O
note	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
read	O
,	O
he	O
denies	O
ever	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
Out	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
not	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
cupboard	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
lock	O
broke	O
of	O
a	O
cupboard	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
miss	O
'd	O
ten	O
guineas	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
by	O
the	O
buroe	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
every	O
thing	O
last	O
Friday	O
.	O
[	O
Martha	O
,	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
above	O
account	O
.	O
]	O
Mary	B-pers
Asgue	I-pers
.	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
at	O
past	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
man	O
rung	O
the	O
bell	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
fallen	O
down	O
over	O
an	O
iron	O
bar	O
,	O
where	O
also	O
lay	O
a	O
screw-driver	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
chamber	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
keys	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
buroe	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
said	O
.	O
Sampson	O
Fairbass	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Dover	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Law	O
,	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
letter	O
with	O
an	O
advertisement	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
who	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
answer	O
'd	O
that	O
advertisement	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
secure	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
body	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
used	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
sitting	O
there	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
Sir	O
George	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
again	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
from	O
Shropshire	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
name	O
John	O
Davis	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
deliver	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
to	O
France	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
,	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
375.	O
John	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
April	O
19	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
On	O
April	O
19.	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
Snow-hill	B-place
,	O
John	B-pers
Leaver	I-pers
and	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
absent	O
,	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
his	O
brother	O
was	O
fuddled	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
his	O
brother	O
.	O
All	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
John	B-pers
Leaver	I-pers
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
immediately	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Said	O
John	B-pers
Leaver	I-pers
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
drop	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
ran	O
above	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
yards	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
The	O
excuse	O
he	O
made	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
last	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
lost	O
it	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Holbourn-bridge	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
side	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
four	O
lamps	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
mob	O
,	O
I	O
cross	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
lying	O
by	O
a	O
post	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
376.	O
Dulick	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Kinnear	I-pers
,	O
April	O
19	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Kinnear	I-pers
.	O
On	O
April	O
19	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	B-place
St.	I-place
Magnus	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
bridge	I-place
foot	I-place
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Clapham	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
make	O
several	O
attempts	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
lad	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kinnear	I-pers
.	O
My	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
just	O
by	O
St.	O
Magnus	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
boy	O
popt	O
in	O
betwixt	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
judg	O
'd	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
make	O
several	O
attempts	O
at	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
pocket	O
lid	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
fling	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
came	O
against	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
flung	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
stoop	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Elick	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
has	O
pick	O
'd	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
ran	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
K.	O
No	O
1.	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
gentleman	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
pull	O
'd	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
sirrah	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
377.	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
yards	O
of	O
cord	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Giltspur-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
.	O
My	O
boy	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
cord	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wadkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
apprentice	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
cord	O
hung	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
I	O
see	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
throw	O
'd	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
own	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Wadkins	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
hanging	O
last	O
?	O
Wadkins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
number	O
I	O
put	O
upon	O
it	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
writing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
shop	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
to	O
change	O
six-pence	O
.	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
heal	O
upon	O
the	O
boards	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
cord	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
378.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
iron	O
weights	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boult	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
May	O
22	O
.	O
The	O
weights	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
porters	O
at	O
Dice	O
and	O
Drake	O
's	O
key	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
weights	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
mark	O
'd	O
W	O
K.	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
swore	O
too	O
as	O
their	O
property	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
379.	O
William	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seventy	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Brown	O
,	O
January	O
24	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
at	O
Harrow	B-place
,	O
from	O
whence	O
great	O
quantities	O
of	O
lead	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
advis	O
'd	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Quentery	I-pers
to	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
No	O
body	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Harrow	O
before	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
Quentery	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
selling	O
some	O
leaden	O
weights	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
sash	O
windows	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
evidence	O
will	O
give	O
a	O
further	O
account	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Parrow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Sarazen	O
's	O
head	O
at	O
Watford	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
of	O
lady	O
Essex	O
,	O
for	O
offenders	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
betwixt	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
but	O
two	O
plumbers	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
notice	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
all	O
weights	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
one	O
King	O
,	O
a	O
plumber	O
,	O
in	O
Washford	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
him	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Snoxal	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
and	O
Quentery	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
380.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Frances	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
one	O
stay	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
bib	O
and	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Frances	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
May	O
2	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
father	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
to	O
play	O
in	O
Leister-fields	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
's	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fraizer	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
child	O
from	O
Leicester-fields	B-place
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
her	O
own	O
confession	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bugdon	I-pers
.	O
My	O
neighbour	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
child	O
was	O
stripp	O
'd	O
by	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
left	O
hand	O
and	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
mother	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
bring	O
her	O
to	O
justice	O
,	O
for	O
few	O
mothers	O
strip	O
their	O
own	O
children	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
cried	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
it	O
what	O
she	O
cried	O
for	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
fling	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
pond	O
if	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
was	O
naked	O
all	O
to	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
shift	O
,	O
and	O
petticoat	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
bundle	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
stay	O
,	O
a	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
bib	O
,	O
and	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
She	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
child	O
from	O
near	O
Leicester-house	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
stockings	O
.	O
She	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
its	O
parents	O
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
court	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
the	O
things	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lead	O
the	O
child	O
by	O
a	O
pond	O
in	O
Mary-le-bon-fields	O
,	O
something	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Leicester-fields	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
place	O
herself	O
in	O
a	O
particular	O
place	O
,	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
corner	O
betwixt	O
two	O
banks	O
,	O
which	O
determin	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Accordingly	O
I	O
watch	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
bib	O
and	O
apron	O
off	O
,	O
then	O
her	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
on	O
to	O
her	O
smock	O
.	O
She	O
put	O
her	O
under	O
petticoat	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
gown	O
on	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pull	O
her	O
shoes	O
and	O
stockings	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
a	O
milk-woman	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
come	O
here	O
,	O
for	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
stripping	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
she	O
shuffled	O
on	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
leading	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
cried	O
bitterly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
mamma	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-Court	O
at	O
a	O
china-shop	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bundle	O
opened	O
.	O
[	O
There	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
said	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mary	O
le	O
bon	O
,	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
very	O
well	O
dress	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
mistress	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
let	O
this	O
child	O
be	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
go	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
two-pence	O
when	O
I	O
come	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
go	O
in	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
maid	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
hungry	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
.	O
Walking	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-court	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
women	O
put	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
child	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
pull	O
'd	O
and	O
haul	O
'd	O
me	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
child	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
upon	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
age	O
,	O
her	O
oath	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
taken	O
]	O
381.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pridex	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
pillow-bear	O
,	O
one	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
May	O
17	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
382.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bois	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
holland	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bartlay	I-pers
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
383.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huddle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
April	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
384.	O
Mary	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
lac	O
'd	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
May	O
25	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
385.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
iron	O
sugar	O
hatchets	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
April	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
386.	O
Esther	B-pers
Hoskings	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
May	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
387.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Islington	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Honnan	I-pers
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
388.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Coventry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
tumbler	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
mantilet	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Upshaw	I-pers
;	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Cewel	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Daniel	B-pers
Upshaw	I-pers
,	O
May	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
389	O
,	O
390.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Knapp	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Clancey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Heart	I-pers
,	O
May	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Buckmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
watchman	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
in	O
Catherine-street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
tower	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
4th	O
and	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
did	O
him	O
this	O
mischief	O
.	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
sailor	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
sailor	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
cut	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
sword	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
last	O
Friday	O
.	O
The	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
Knapp	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
their	O
directions	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
surrounded	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Knapp	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
before	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
who	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
him	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
cut	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
swore	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
chang	O
'd	O
his	O
cloaths	O
,	O
for	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
regimentals	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
was	O
really	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
at	O
times	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
ghts	O
,	O
as	O
once	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
before	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
separately	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
Clancey	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
not	O
there	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
also	O
separately	O
examin	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Goodman	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
abuses	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
Clancey	O
was	O
first	O
examined	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
once	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
cut	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
reply	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Knapp	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
Knapp	O
was	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
't	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
defence	O
.	O
-	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Knapp	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
about	O
300	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
hear	O
the	O
noise	O
made	O
there	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
Knapp	O
's	O
door	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
all	O
was	O
very	O
still	O
then	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
slumbered	O
a	O
little	O
between	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Knapp	O
's	O
being	O
brought	O
in	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Ditch	O
side	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
by	O
Knapp	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
headborough	O
sitting	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
man	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
surrounded	O
,	O
somebody	O
burst	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Knapp	O
just	O
getting	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
has	O
cut	O
you	O
?	O
He	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
eyes	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
hard	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
chang	O
'd	O
his	O
cloaths	O
,	O
for	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
soldier	O
's	O
cloaths	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
clean	O
trowsers	O
.	O
Clancey	O
was	O
then	O
very	O
soon	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
running	O
down	O
the	O
hill	O
,	O
Knapp	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
100	O
yards	O
with	O
a	O
cutlass	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
cut	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
Lord	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
n't	O
kill	O
me	O
,	O
struggling	O
from	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
about	O
10	O
yards	O
farther	O
;	O
but	O
Knapp	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
sla	O
you	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
Clancey	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
made	O
no	O
declaration	O
how	O
the	O
quarrel	O
began	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
within	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
cap	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
on	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
a	O
thick	O
worsted	O
cap	O
with	O
three	O
cuts	O
in	O
it	O
about	O
two	O
inches	O
long	O
each	O
.	O
]	O
Knapp	O
declared	O
he	O
cut	O
him	O
so	O
long	O
till	O
the	O
cutlass	O
flew	O
in	O
two	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross-examination	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
this	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
pretty	O
saint	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
sensible	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Maclane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
second	O
regiment	O
of	O
guards	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
was	O
upon	O
guard	O
in	O
the	O
tower	O
,	O
about	O
100	O
yards	O
from	O
Knapp	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
whence	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
disturbance	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
came	O
out	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
rob	O
my	O
house	O
?	O
another	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
to	O
me	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
quarrel	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
however	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
recovered	O
and	O
ran	O
about	O
40	O
yards	O
,	O
follow	O
'd	O
by	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
or	O
sword	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
who	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
struck	O
him	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
blows	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
fire	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
man	O
alone	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
to	O
them	O
because	O
the	O
ditch	O
was	O
between	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
strove	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
soldier	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
too	O
far	O
off	O
to	O
see	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
a	O
watchman	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
man	O
up	O
that	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
four	O
doors	O
of	O
Knapp	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
bed	O
and	O
asleep	O
,	O
but	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
of	O
fighting	O
with	O
sticks	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
struck	O
as	O
tho	O
'	O
against	O
a	O
stone	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
upon	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
at	O
what	O
distance	O
from	O
Knapp	O
's	O
house	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
positively	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
believe	O
't	O
was	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
century	O
call	O
and	O
tell	O
them	O
he	O
'd	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
some	O
persons	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
above	O
two	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
towards	O
Knapp	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
that	O
fighting	O
with	O
sticks	O
?	O
M.	O
Gray	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Heyley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
assist	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Knapp	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
We	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
man	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
man	O
.	O
They	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Clancey	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
under	O
a	O
bed	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
London	O
hospital	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
on	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
;	O
it	O
reached	O
almost	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
ear	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
wound	O
under	O
the	O
right	O
ear	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
beginning	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
thereof	O
,	O
and	O
reaching	O
down	O
about	O
two	O
inches	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
was	O
the	O
most	O
mortal	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
May	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
directions	O
of	O
the	O
surgeons	O
,	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
't	O
was	O
the	O
judgment	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
that	O
these	O
wounds	O
were	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
how	O
this	O
accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
ship-mate	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
going	O
a-cross	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
a	O
crowd	O
of	O
people	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
what	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
,	O
a	O
soldier	O
and	O
sailor	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
soldier	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
took	O
for	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
drew	O
his	O
hanger	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
cuts	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
several	O
times	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
way	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
so	O
closely	O
follow	O
'd	O
by	O
them	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
escape	O
,	O
for	O
at	O
Tower-ditch	O
the	O
soldier	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
him	O
again	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
soldier	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
century	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
heard	O
the	O
disturbance	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
fire	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
them	O
desist	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
lay	O
in	O
his	O
blood	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
whence	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
account	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
bruises	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wounds	O
were	O
made	O
by	O
some	O
cutting	O
instrument	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
account	O
how	O
the	O
quarrel	O
arose	O
?	O
Dobson	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
first	O
occasioned	O
the	O
mob	O
.	O
Knapp	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
High	O
German	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
upon	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
that	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
till	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
forgot	O
what	O
you	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
.	O
Some	O
people	O
gave	O
me	O
brandy	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Clancey	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
Knapp	O
's	O
door	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
Knapp	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
they	O
wanted	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
unseasonable	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
to	O
let	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
insisted	O
upon	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
would	O
break	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
they	O
were	O
no	O
watchmen	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
twice	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
defence	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
blow	O
with	O
my	O
fist	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
go	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
n't	O
make	O
any	O
more	O
noise	O
about	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
run	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
stay	O
'd	O
behind	O
,	O
crying	O
shame	O
on	O
the	O
others	O
for	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
throwing	O
stones	O
at	O
Knapp	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
which	O
made	O
Knapp	O
say	O
,	O
must	O
my	O
house	O
be	O
broke	O
open	O
by	O
those	O
three	O
villains	O
?	O
However	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
.	O
Knapp	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
afterwards	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Knapp	O
came	O
in	O
afterwards	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Osborne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
infirmary	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
have	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
mob	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
amongst	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
soldier	O
and	O
a	O
sailor	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
cut	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
Knapp	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
lives	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Knapp	O
guilty	O
of	O
manslaughter	O
,	O
and	O
Clancey	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
391.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harbottle	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
apron	O
,	O
seven	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
and	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
May	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
392.	O
John	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
signed	O
under	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Griffice	I-pers
,	O
and	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
sterling	O
;	O
one	O
other	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
,	O
drawn	O
upon	O
the	O
cashier	O
of	O
the	O
bank	O
of	O
England	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
uttering	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
bills	O
sent	O
me	O
from	O
Liverpool	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
post	O
there	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Crosby	I-pers
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
me	O
three	O
bills	O
,	O
value	O
200	O
l.	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
receiv	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
'd	O
stop	O
payment	O
if	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bank	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
to	O
stop	O
payment	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
to	O
bread-street	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
payment	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Exchange	O
after	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
clarke	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
demanded	O
payment	O
of	O
my	O
bill	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
the	O
bill	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
insist	O
upon	O
knowing	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
seemed	O
confus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
answer	O
not	O
being	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
afterwards	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
fact	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
bills	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
post-office	O
at	O
Liverpool	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
post-master	O
there	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
those	O
letters	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
letters	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
other	O
bills	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
now	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
50	O
l.	O
note	O
upon	O
the	O
bank	O
,	O
another	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
under	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
,	O
draughted	O
on	O
the	O
bank	O
of	O
Scotland	O
upon	O
our	O
bank	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
[	O
Andrew	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
]	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
393.	O
James	B-pers
Curd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
140	O
bullion	O
nails	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
394.	O
Richard	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
Benacre	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
armed	O
with	O
fire	O
arms	O
and	O
other	O
offensive	O
weapons	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
twenty	O
persons	O
and	O
upwards	O
;	O
being	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
,	O
in	O
landing	O
and	O
running	O
goods	O
liable	O
to	O
pay	O
custom	O
,	O
August	O
23	O
,	O
1746	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
offence	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
,	O
committed	O
at	O
Horsey	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Norfolk	I-place
,	O
February	O
24	O
,	O
1746	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lindow	I-pers
was	O
the	O
only	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
lay	O
his	O
hand	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
twice	O
to	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
an	O
offence	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
,	O
committed	O
at	O
Benacre	O
,	O
October	O
8	O
,	O
1746	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
395.	O
William	B-pers
Obrian	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Mote	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
hat	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
Ratcliff-high-way	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
May	O
10.	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
from	O
his	O
head	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
putting	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
any	O
surprise	O
,	O
or	O
bodily	O
fear	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
396.	O
Richard	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
beaver-hat	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
a	O
glass	O
mug	O
,	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
flannel	O
petticoats	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
April	O
,	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
397.	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
two	O
skirts	O
for	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
towel	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tapperall	I-pers
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
398	O
,	O
399.	O
William	B-pers
Lindley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Whiteman	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
harateen	O
bed-curtains	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
window	O
ditto	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
May	O
22	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
High-Holbourn	B-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dyer	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
the	O
twenty	O
second	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
shut	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Singleton	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Fetherstone	O
Buildings	O
,	O
to	O
inquire	O
if	O
any	O
such	O
things	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
apprentice	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
came	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
sooner	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
catched	O
the	O
men	O
pawning	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
knew	O
Lindley	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
apprehended	O
Lindley	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
that	O
Whiteman	O
Bailey	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
Bailey	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
curtains	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
require	O
.	O
He	O
much	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
tarry	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
without	O
committing	O
him	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Boucher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Singleton	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
twenty	O
second	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
betwixt	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
Lindley	O
brought	O
in	O
these	O
curtains	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
five	O
shillings	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
immediately	O
Whiteman	O
Bailey	O
stepped	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
six	O
shillings	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
Bailey	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
witness	O
.	O
[	O
Lindley	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
Bailey	O
and	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
judgment	O
on	O
the	O
curtains	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
taylor	O
;	O
that	O
Bailey	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Harris	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
neither	O
he	O
or	O
Bailey	O
had	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Bailey	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
says	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Bailey	O
called	O
Edward	B-pers
Tost	I-pers
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
pork	O
shop	O
in	O
Newport-market	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
miss	O
behaved	O
word	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
above	O
a	O
twelve	O
month	O
within	O
two	O
doors	O
of	O
Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Austine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
Bailey	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
257	O
.	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pennant	I-pers
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
400.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Egen	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Glass	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
401.	O
John	B-pers
Aston	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
spades	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Trimmer	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
402.	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
by	O
drawing	O
a	O
dray	O
over	O
his	O
leg	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
,	O
May	O
15	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
May	O
the	O
15th	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
dray	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
sharps	O
on	O
the	O
near	O
side	O
with	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
towards	O
the	O
church	O
,	O
the	O
beadle	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
silver	O
mace	O
home	O
he	O
had	O
borrowed	O
to	O
attend	O
at	O
the	O
Foundling-hospital	O
;	O
he	O
crost	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
belive	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
get	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
here	O
that	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
down	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
beadle	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
(	O
there	O
was	O
out	O
one	O
horse	O
)	O
and	O
turned	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
towards	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
were	O
then	O
both	O
upon	O
the	O
dray	O
:	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
mob	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
said	O
,	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
,	O
knock	O
the	O
beadle	O
down	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jumped	O
from	O
the	O
dray	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
he	O
hit	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
or	O
shoved	O
him	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
down	O
he	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
rather	O
think	O
he	O
pushed	O
him	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
and	O
turned	O
him	O
short	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
near	O
wheel	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
leg	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
he	O
lay	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
the	O
dray	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
gone	O
streight	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
wheel	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
touched	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
making	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
way	O
with	O
the	O
dray	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
words	O
pass	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
fifteenth	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
beadle	O
and	O
drayman	O
both	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
near	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
dray	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
off	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
then	O
towards	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
dray	O
,	O
the	O
beadle	O
let	O
his	O
staff	O
fall	O
in	O
the	O
struggle	O
,	O
the	O
dray	O
was	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
rather	O
standing	O
,	O
the	O
drayman	O
disengaged	O
himself	O
from	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
push	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
or	O
two	O
from	O
the	O
dray	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
drayman	O
turned	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
short	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
the	O
wheel	O
over	O
his	O
leg	O
which	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
prevented	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
gone	O
streight	O
on	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
avoided	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
within	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
lay	O
above	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
the	O
streight	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
dray	O
sideways	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Buckingham	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
south-side	O
.	O
[	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
a	O
short	O
trice	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
great	O
multitude	O
of	O
people	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
blows	O
pass	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
push	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
see	O
they	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
each	O
others	O
collar	O
.	O
]	O
Hugh	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
shop	O
within	O
seventy	O
yards	O
where	O
this	O
thing	O
happened	O
:	O
hearing	O
a	O
noice	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
fall	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
occasioned	O
it	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
interrupted	O
my	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
dray	O
run	O
over	O
his	O
legs	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Bowl-yard	O
,	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
the	O
beadle	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
parish	O
a	O
tusling	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pushed	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
drove	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
near	O
wheel	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
leg	O
.	O
He	O
drove	O
the	O
horse	O
streight	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pull	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
was	O
towards	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
church	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
twenty	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
wheel	O
run	O
over	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
coroner	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sa	O
y	O
the	O
same	O
there	O
you	O
do	O
now	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
let	O
the	O
horse	O
go	O
on	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
way	O
,	O
doubtless	O
the	O
wheel	O
might	O
have	O
escaped	O
the	O
old	O
gentleman	O
's	O
leg	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
flung	O
the	O
halter	O
over	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
when	O
he	O
hit	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
have	O
escaped	O
him	O
.	O
Darby	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
yards	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
shove	O
the	O
beadle	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
with	O
the	O
dray	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
about	O
,	O
the	O
horse	O
stood	O
still	O
when	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
pushed	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
might	O
have	O
avoided	O
running	O
over	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Windsor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
leg	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
close	O
by	O
the	O
ancle	O
,	O
both	O
the	O
bones	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
elderly	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
attended	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
when	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
The	O
wound	O
began	O
to	O
mortify	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Bridewel	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
Mr.	O
Burgess	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
advice	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
dray	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
hurt	O
the	O
deceased	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
examine	O
witnesses	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
