TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
24th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1749	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
John	B-pers
Blachford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1750	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BLACHFORD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
FOSTER	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BIRCH	O
,	O
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edmond	B-pers
Comyns	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Whitridge	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Reginald	B-pers
Trotter	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Heapes	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Des	I-pers
Champs	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huddle	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boozsher	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Manvell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Duck	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gaff	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
417.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
books	O
,	O
each	O
entitled	O
,	O
Letters	O
of	O
Cicero	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
June	O
11	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bookseller	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
More-fields	B-place
,	O
these	O
books	O
were	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
by	O
my	O
private	O
mark	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
two	O
doors	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
books	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
my	O
brother	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
again	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
my	O
brother	O
know	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Benn	O
,	O
before	O
whom	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
volumes	O
of	O
the	O
Athenian	O
Oracles	O
,	O
I	O
exchanged	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
above	O
two	O
months	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
418	O
,	O
419.	O
John	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
rooms	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
two	O
pillowbiers	O
,	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
towel	O
,	O
one	O
diaper	O
napkin	O
,	O
a	O
mahogony	O
waiter	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
the	O
statute	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
,	O
June	O
25	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
.	O
My	O
mother	O
Ann	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
lives	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
lodgings	O
of	O
my	O
mother	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
They	O
agreed	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
ready	O
furnished	O
for	O
seven	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
Rooms	O
might	O
be	O
got	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bed	O
sheeted	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
back	O
in	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
they	O
returned	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
pass	O
for	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
?	O
M.	O
Kirk	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
understood	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
rooms	O
,	O
they	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
keys	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
back	O
again	O
by	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
They	O
not	O
coming	O
back	O
at	O
eleven	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
the	O
bolt	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
till	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
smith	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
lock	O
off	O
.	O
We	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
specified	O
.	O
The	O
looking	O
glass	O
was	O
a	O
swinging	O
one	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
frame	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
the	O
lodgings	O
were	O
taken	O
?	O
M.	O
Kirk	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
drank	O
tea	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
offered	O
the	O
seven	O
shillings	O
per	O
week	O
?	O
M.	O
Kirk	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
stuff	O
shop	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
opposite	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
live	O
near	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
doors	O
distant	O
,	O
she	O
agreed	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
goods	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
55	O
s.	O
She	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
bill	O
and	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
aunt	O
's	O
in	O
Dean-street	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
through	O
Bartlet	O
's	O
buildings	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
goods	O
down	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
bill	O
and	O
receipt	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
run	O
him	O
up	O
a	O
long	O
bill	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
but	O
2	O
l.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
2	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
They	O
made	O
off	O
with	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
Black	O
fryar	O
's	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
in	O
a	O
boat	O
and	O
he	O
getting	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
bundles	O
besides	O
mine	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
:	O
my	O
goods	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
these	O
goods	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
be	O
it	O
at	O
their	O
peril	O
who	O
dare	O
touch	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Atubury	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
is	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
attend	O
here	O
with	O
this	O
bundle	O
,	O
[	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
swore	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
the	O
lodgings	O
as	O
his	O
sister	O
had	O
done	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
his	O
getting	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
things	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
[	O
pointing	O
to	O
her	O
fellow	O
prisoner	O
]	O
made	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
420.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lege	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cowell	I-pers
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
recognizance	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
421.	O
John	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
coffee	O
mill	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
June	O
13	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
Hyde	O
Park	O
corner	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
and	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
the	O
Friday	O
was	O
7	O
nights	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Lock	O
hospital	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
a	O
patient	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Cumberland	O
's	O
head	O
in	O
Ratclif	O
highway	O
who	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
having	O
such	O
things	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
gentlewoman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
brick-field	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
her	O
the	O
truth	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
a	O
hair	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
And	O
by	O
reason	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
place	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
me	O
away	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
said	O
somewhat	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
being	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
surprise	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
422.	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
nutmeg-grater	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
steel	O
cork	O
skrew	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Arthur	I-pers
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Eastwoff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
keeps	O
White	O
's	O
chocolate	O
house	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
Mr.	O
Warner	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
who	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
about	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
at	O
7	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Arthur	O
,	O
and	O
Eastwoff	O
came	O
,	O
[	O
the	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
witness	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
tried	O
about	O
them	O
at	O
Westminster	O
hall	O
and	O
was	O
cleared	O
.	O
Warner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Westminster-hall	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
bill	O
found	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
court	O
.	O
Warner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
lay	O
there	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
pay	O
my	O
fees	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
423.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
July	O
2	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Broad-way	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
perriwig	O
maker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
July	O
2	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
shave	O
a	O
customer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wig	O
too	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
above	O
four	O
hours	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
wig	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Peak	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
bob	O
cut	O
wig	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
a	O
painter	O
.	O
It	O
lay	O
in	O
buckle	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
absent	O
?	O
Peak	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Peak	O
.	O
Because	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
what	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
yesterday	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
waggoner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
next	O
return	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
for	O
three	O
shillings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
wig	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
all	O
day	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
soap	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
resented	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
hours	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
worth	O
my	O
while	O
to	O
return	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
scandalous	O
man	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
his	O
journeymen	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
work	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Morphet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
person	O
before	O
this	O
thing	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
424	O
,	O
425.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Tyler	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Darnell	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
puting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
perosn	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Darnel	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
Hackney	O
church	O
clock	O
struck	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
between	O
Dalston	O
and	O
Hackney	O
;	O
Tyler	O
came	O
up	O
first	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
two	O
keys	O
;	O
they	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
before	O
my	O
face	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
back	O
my	O
keys	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
to	O
drink	O
their	O
healths	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
by	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
fire-arms	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
resistance	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Tyler	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
with	O
a	O
brass-handle	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
frock	O
on	O
.	O
Cook	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
habit	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
green	O
apron	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
alone	O
?	O
Darnell	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
farm	O
which	O
I	O
occupy	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Hackney-cage	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
had	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
about	O
stealing	O
a	O
shirt	O
.	O
After	O
his	O
worship	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Tyler	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
man	O
who	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
cried	O
terribly	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Eglestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
(	O
Tyler	O
)	O
cried	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hanged	O
wrongfully	O
.	O
Tyler	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
with	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Cook	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Hackney	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
a	O
shirt	O
.	O
This	O
old	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
shook	O
hands	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
swore	O
wrongfully	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
426	O
,	O
427.	O
John	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
Hurdle	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
;	O
two	O
linen-shifts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
June	O
22	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hurdle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hackney	B-place
;	O
I	O
hung	O
out	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
Indictment	O
,	O
to	O
dry	O
in	O
my	O
garden	O
,	O
June	O
22	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
who	O
did	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
We	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
currant	O
bushes	O
trodden	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
witness	O
can	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
found	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Ecclestone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
about	O
1	O
o'clock	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Wright	O
go	O
by	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
much	O
affrighted	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
linen	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
signal	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
another	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
dropped	O
the	O
things	O
behind	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
owned	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hoxford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
rogues	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
stolen	O
some	O
linen	O
.	O
When	O
Wright	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
held	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
bit	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
got	O
his	O
liberty	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shear	I-pers
.	O
As	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
Wright	O
)	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
beckoned	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
flung	O
the	O
things	O
down	O
behind	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
people	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
Flying-horse-yard	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
taken	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tomline	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Wright	O
[	O
the	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
as	O
to	O
Wright	O
]	O
I	O
saw	O
Kingston	O
run	O
up	O
the	O
Flying-horse-yard	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
Wright	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Holley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
working	O
in	O
a	O
farrier	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
report	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
gone	O
by	O
with	O
something	O
not	O
his	O
own	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
then	O
taken	O
Wright	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
a	O
m	O
guilty	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
myself	O
.	O
Kingston	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
Hackney	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
cross	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
jump	O
over	O
the	O
hedge	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
companion	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
man	O
[	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Wright	O
]	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
otherwise	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
alehouse	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
.	O
Kingston	O
acquitted	O
;	O
Wright	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
428.	O
Charles	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Nudkins	I-pers
,	O
June	O
21	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
in	O
court	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
having	O
no	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
in	O
great	O
want	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
429.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
George	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
one	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
against	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
June	O
24	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Chancery-lane	B-place
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
gate	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
surrounded	O
by	O
four	O
men	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stop	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
me	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
stooped	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
light	O
night	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
darkish	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
in	O
company	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
shape	O
and	O
size	O
;	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
coat	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
risled	O
my	O
breeches-pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
pinchbeck	O
metal	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
enamel	O
'd	O
dial-plate	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
stood	O
by	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
held	O
the	O
pistol	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
his	O
Lodge	O
;	O
then	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Omit	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
taking	O
a	O
walk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
we	O
?	O
Omit	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
myself	O
;	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
bargain	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
robbing	O
about	O
Chancery-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
Chamberlain	O
)	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
mop-stick	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
it	O
in	O
two	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
one	O
half	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
kept	O
himself	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
a	O
house	O
that	O
harbours	O
all	O
whores	O
and	O
thieves	O
;	O
first	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Fleetditch	O
side	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
Chancery-lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
this	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
than	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
half	O
from	O
our	O
first	O
setting	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
about	O
from	O
gin-shop	O
to	O
gin-shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
Omit	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
almost	O
opposite	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
Robbery	O
.	O
Omit	O
.	O
I	O
clapp	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Chamberlain	O
flung	O
his	O
stick	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
clapp	O
'd	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
his	O
watch	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
Lodge	O
,	O
meaning	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
proffer	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
returned	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
one	O
way	O
and	O
he	O
another	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
towards	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
then	O
towards	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
Duke's-place	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
drank	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
The	O
Jew	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Alexander	B-pers
Minous	I-pers
;	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
together	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
sold	O
for	O
?	O
Omit	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
sold	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
shoes	O
lay	O
something	O
down	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
laid	O
something	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
hanger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
deliver	O
this	O
witness	O
some	O
halfpence	O
which	O
he	O
returned	O
again	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
some	O
halfpence	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
returned	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
This	O
Omit	O
is	O
a	O
cruel	O
man	O
to	O
say	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
death	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
371	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions-book	O
.	O
430	O
,	O
431.	O
Ely	B-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ely	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Horseface	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Ben	O
the	O
coal-heaver	O
,	O
on	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
steel	O
tobacco-box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
,	O
June	O
9	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
coming	O
from	O
thence	O
through	O
Breams-buildings	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
in	O
the	O
buildings	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
trip	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
turning	O
that	O
goes	O
to	O
Bond	O
's	O
stables	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
Smith	O
came	O
running	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
hollo	O
;	O
hollo	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Instantly	O
came	O
three	O
more	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
collar	O
.	O
Webb	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
Webb	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
cheek	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
fisk	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
set	O
to	O
rifling	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
steel	O
tobacco-box	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
stared	O
them	O
full	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
pulled	O
my	O
hat	O
over	O
my	O
eyes	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
old	O
one	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
there	O
till	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
mentioning	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
gentleman	O
robb	O
'd	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
chang	O
'd	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
left	O
him	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
hat	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
remarkable	O
slit	O
long	O
ways	O
in	O
the	O
brim	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
hat	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
so	O
they	O
finding	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
great	O
bargain	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
they	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
Constable	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
how	O
I	O
was	O
served	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
day	O
se'nnight	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
these	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
Smith	O
:	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
Webb	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
afterwards	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
surely	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
cheek	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
laughed	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
described	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
tender	O
in	O
swearing	O
;	O
I	O
swear	O
,	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
Webb	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
night	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
robbed	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
under	O
Castle-yard-gate	O
,	O
coming	O
into	O
Holborn	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
men	O
collared	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
;	O
my	O
hat	O
was	O
almost	O
new	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
of	O
theirs	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
hat	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
took	O
away	O
your	O
hat	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
Smith	O
came	O
up	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
covered	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
took	O
away	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
remember	O
something	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
faces	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Omit	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
in	O
Whitson	O
week	O
we	O
all	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
Bricklayer	O
's	O
arms	O
,	O
in	O
George-alley	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
Fleet-market	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Ben	O
.	O
the	O
coal-heaver	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
We	O
made	O
a	O
bargain	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
robbing	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
12	O
o'clock	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
from	O
George	O
alley	O
.	O
Near	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
gate	O
we	O
stopped	O
a	O
little	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
silver	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
then	O
we	O
turned	O
down	O
a	O
turning	O
that	O
went	O
back	O
into	O
Chancery-lane	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
saw	O
this	O
gentleman	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
we	O
followed	O
him	O
towards	O
Bond	O
's	O
stables	O
,	O
Smith	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
tobacco-box	O
,	O
and	O
exchanged	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Chancery-lane	O
towards	O
Southampton-buildings	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
gate-way	O
goes	O
into	O
some	O
buildings	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
stopped	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
took	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Smith	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
changed	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
thought	O
his	O
hat	O
better	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
's	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Plough-court	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Holborn-hill	O
,	O
a	O
thoroughfare	O
into	O
Field-lane	O
.	O
We	O
lay	O
down	O
there	O
till	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Duke's-place	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
watch	O
to	O
Alexander	B-pers
Minous	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
We	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
going	O
home	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
have	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
divers	O
street	O
robberies	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
sold	O
diamond-rings	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
cheated	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Parsons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Minous	O
the	O
Jew	O
?	O
Omit	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
arms	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
this	O
night	O
?	O
Omit	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
both	O
pistols	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Ben	O
.	O
Bennet	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
going	O
my	O
rounds	O
behind	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
,	O
out	O
started	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
horse-ride	O
by	O
the	O
Star-Inn	O
;	O
he	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
watch	O
and	O
thieves	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
drew	O
his	O
sword	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
bustling	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
towards	O
Chancery-lane	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Webb	O
.	O
And	O
we	O
took	O
Smith	O
also	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
swore	O
revenge	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
if	O
ever	O
they	O
got	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
'd	O
make	O
me	O
remember	O
taking	O
another	O
man	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
prison	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
watchmen	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
pistol	O
,	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
432.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shakespear	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
scarlet	O
hair-shag	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
and	O
company	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
June	O
13	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
,	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
hair-shag	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
dealt	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
dyed	O
any	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
quantity	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
stopped	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
your	O
servant	O
?	O
Farmer	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
about	O
eight	O
yards	O
in	O
all	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dickerson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
cannon	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
last	O
June	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
scarlet	O
shag	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
such	O
another	O
remnant	O
from	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
certain	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
money	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
escape	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
my	O
business	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
last	O
directed	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Farmer	O
and	O
company	O
's	O
dye	O
house	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Farmer	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
partners	O
in	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
Farmer	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
John	B-pers
Pippen	I-pers
and	O
Chamberlain	O
Goodwin	B-pers
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Gyles	O
Readhouse	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Abel	B-pers
Bingham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
wards	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
ever	O
broke	O
bread	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
careful	O
and	O
industrious	O
to	O
provide	O
for	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sober	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pearne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
sober	O
,	O
discreet	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
any	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
action	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
433.	O
Rachael	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Daniel	I-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bowston	I-pers
,	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
East	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
in	O
Stone-house	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
upwards	O
of	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
room	O
where	O
none	O
went	O
into	O
but	O
she	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
here	O
?	O
Bowston	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
put	O
me	O
to	O
charges	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
woman	O
your	O
servant	O
?	O
Bowston	O
.	O
She	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
cloth	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
another	O
woman	O
worked	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
did	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
employed	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
433.	O
William	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wiggington	I-pers
,	O
secretly	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wiggington	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Gohl	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
through	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
through	O
a	O
gentleman	O
asked	O
if	O
either	O
of	O
us	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
feet	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Stronginthearm	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
:	O
the	O
evidence	O
will	O
give	O
the	O
court	O
a	O
more	O
clear	O
account	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
Gohl	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stronginthearm	O
,	O
we	O
no	O
sooner	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Stronginthearm	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Then	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Wiggington	O
's	O
handkerchief	O
one	O
part	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
feet	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
corner	O
he	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
handkerchiefs	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stronginthearm	I-pers
.	O
The	O
last	O
witness	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
parted	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Winter	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
Shoemaker-row	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
partner	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
followed	O
them	O
close	O
under	O
the	O
arch	O
in	O
Aldgate	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
companion	O
close	O
almost	O
through	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
turned	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
prey	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
friends	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Gohl	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
replied	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
cast	O
my	O
eye	O
under	O
his	O
foot	O
and	O
there	O
lay	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
prosecute	O
him	O
cost	O
what	O
it	O
will	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
work	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
Aldgate	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
lad	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
drop	O
something	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
434.	O
John	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
just	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
quite	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Hunter	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
435	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
,	O
June	O
18	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bennington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
shirt	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
;	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Bonivel	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
H.	O
Bennington	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
shirt	O
the	O
minute	O
after	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hoy	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bonivel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
shirt	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
I	O
questioned	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
your	O
brother	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Petticoat	O
lane	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
my	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
thief	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
;	O
I	O
being	O
head	O
borough	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
this	O
shirt	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
shirt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
:	O
this	O
woman	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
shirt	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
either	O
black	O
or	O
blue	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
she	O
described	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
pawnbroker	O
takes	O
in	O
things	O
on	O
Sundays	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
436.	O
Hester	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hat	O
and	O
perriwig	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
kitchen	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
and	O
was	O
below	O
doing	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Rosemary	O
lane	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
request	O
,	O
if	O
such	O
things	O
should	O
be	O
brought	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
person	O
might	O
be	O
stopped	O
who	O
should	O
offer	O
them	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
afterwards	O
stopped	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
.	O
The	O
next	O
witness	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
fuller	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
lane	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
June	O
28	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
should	O
bring	O
such	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
wig	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
the	O
price	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
descriptions	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
wig	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
her	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Catharine	I-place
's	I-place
lane	I-place
,	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
437.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martial	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
438.	O
Edward	B-pers
Burguss	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
knives	O
with	O
silver	O
handles	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
seven	O
forks	O
ditto	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
butler	O
to	O
Admiral	O
Knowles	B-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
the	O
knives	O
in	O
the	O
usual	O
place	O
,	O
designing	O
to	O
clean	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
the	O
Admiral	O
,	O
to	O
solicit	O
his	O
interest	O
about	O
getting	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
charity	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
about	O
4	O
o'clock	O
I	O
had	O
intelligence	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
knives	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Chariot	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
silver	O
handle	O
knife	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
present	O
from	O
the	O
Admiral	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nevil	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Admiral	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
thirteen	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
stop	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
?	O
Chariot	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
knife	O
handle	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopt	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
fix	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nevil	O
deposed	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Admiral	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
to	O
Admiral	O
Knowles	B-pers
;	O
I	O
never	O
offered	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
wronged	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
or	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
dram	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
see	O
him	O
weigh	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
comes	O
to	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
thought	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
brass	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
drink	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
men	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
should	O
have	O
come	O
here	O
a	O
witness	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
439.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Valentine	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
periwig	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
July	O
5	O
.	O
Valentine	O
Harris	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dimer	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Sept	O
.	O
Sessions	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
paper	O
the	O
Reader	O
is	O
refered	O
No	O
.	O
582.	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
certain	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Dimer	I-pers
,	O
(	O
since	O
executed	O
)	O
did	O
commit	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
clear	O
view	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
trial	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dimer	I-pers
was	O
my	O
daughter	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
my	O
daughter	O
did	O
use	O
to	O
keep	O
company	O
together	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
house	O
they	O
lodged	O
together	O
,	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
him	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Dimer	I-pers
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
together	O
six	O
weeks	O
;	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
One	O
night	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
night	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
She	O
nor	O
he	O
ever	O
came	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
remarkable	O
*	O
mould	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
cheek	O
.	O
*	O
It	O
was	O
reported	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
his	O
trial	O
came	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
mould	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
off	O
by	O
art	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wolley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
last	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
your	O
play-fellow	O
gone	O
by	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lain	O
in	O
about	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
husband	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
mightily	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Islington	O
.	O
I	O
having	O
sent	O
my	O
child	O
to	O
the	O
church	O
to	O
be	O
baptized	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
reason	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
it	O
so	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
stay	O
with	O
you	O
any	O
time	O
?	O
Wolley	O
.	O
He	O
stayed	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
till	O
5	O
o'clock	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
child	O
baptized	O
?	O
Wolley	O
.	O
At	O
Cripplegate	O
church	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
hasten	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
christened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Wolley	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Golden-Lane	O
,	O
facing	O
the	O
hand	O
and	O
tipstaff	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Olifant	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wolley	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Crawford	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
stayed	O
till	O
the	O
company	O
broke	O
up	O
;	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
and	O
slept	O
till	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
awaking	O
him	O
at	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
morning	O
near	O
Cripplegate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
child	O
christened	O
that	O
day	O
your	O
mistress	O
speaks	O
of	O
?	O
Olifant	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
mistress	O
's	O
business	O
?	O
Olifant	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
fish-woman	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
a	O
carman	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
would	O
have	O
paid	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
my	O
month	O
being	O
up	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Wolley	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
bring	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
christening	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
register	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
?	O
Wolley	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
there	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
occasion	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
440.	O
Mary	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
Fulham	B-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
five	O
copper	O
sauce-pans	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
saucepan	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
kettle	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
.	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Fulham	O
.	O
On	O
Whitsun	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
my	O
servant	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
got	O
up	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
window-shutter	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
also	O
a	O
casement	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
thief	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
night	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
saying	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
some	O
sauce-pans	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
inquired	O
amongst	O
the	O
watermen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
my	O
man	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
Fulham	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
denied	O
it	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
confest	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
fellow	O
with	O
her	O
who	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
get	O
them	O
for	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Baniman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
sold	O
me	O
four	O
copper	O
sauce-pans	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
kettle	O
at	O
a	O
market	O
price	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
and	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
remove	O
farther	O
off	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
carriage	O
thither	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
10	O
d.	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
the	O
copper	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
brass	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
out	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
them	O
?	O
Baniman	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
me	O
whether	O
or	O
not	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
441.	O
William	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
sauce-pan	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Becket	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
June	O
21	O
.	O
Becket	O
Mitchel	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Faulcon	O
ale-house	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
.	O
The	O
sauce-pan	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
yard	O
June	O
21.	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
clear	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
I	O
would	O
fetch	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
him	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
,	O
also	O
he	O
did	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
sauce-pan	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
ground	O
playing	O
at	O
skettles	O
,	O
they	O
lost	O
a	O
sauce-pan	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
on	O
suspicion	O
.	O
Q	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
sauce-pan	O
was	O
pawned	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
here	O
without	O
I	O
subpoena	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
442.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
diaper	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
.	O
June	O
19	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
my	O
watchman	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
3	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
then	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Islington	B-place
road	I-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
linen	O
which	O
was	O
left	O
hanging	O
there	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
there	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
there	O
lying	O
upon	O
a	O
dray	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
side	O
the	O
buildings	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
another	O
watchman	O
stationed	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
pursue	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
ran	O
about	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
yards	O
off	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
flung	O
down	O
the	O
linen	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
apron	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purport	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
443.	O
William	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hat	O
and	O
one	O
periwig	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
Evan	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
taking	O
up	O
fustians	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
home	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
parcel	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
in	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
late	O
.	O
Going	O
from	O
thence	O
up	O
Holborn	O
,	O
just	O
beyond	O
the	O
bars	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
be	O
careful	O
how	O
you	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
dangerous	O
walking	O
the	O
streets	O
now	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
you	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
my	O
country	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
countryman	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Irishman	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
liquor	O
(	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
's	O
house	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
true	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
Queen	O
Court	O
with	O
me	O
under	O
the	O
middle	O
archway	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
running	O
faster	O
than	O
he	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
before	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
my	O
b	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
then	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
,	O
and	O
kick	O
'd	O
and	O
bruised	O
me	O
much	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
ill	O
usage	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
both	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
you	O
first	O
come	O
together	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
He	O
overtook	O
me	O
just	O
by	O
Holborn	O
Bars	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
apace	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Great	O
Wild-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
in	O
Great	O
Queen-street	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
both	O
bare-headed	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
of	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
down	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Then	O
another	O
watchman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
in	O
Great	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
hats	O
and	O
one	O
wig	O
under	O
the	O
archway	O
going	O
into	O
Queen	O
Court	O
;	O
they	O
lay	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
took	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
charged	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
both	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
then	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
overtook	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
hollo	O
!	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
together	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
black	O
eye	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
tied	O
round	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
countrymen	O
he	O
fought	O
with	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
along	O
together	O
to	O
Queen-street	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
you	O
drink	O
some	O
beer	O
before	O
you	O
go	O
home	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
drank	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
my	O
work	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
drink	O
none	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
treat	O
me	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
return	O
you	O
thanks	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
drink	O
none	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
scoundrel	O
fellow	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
upon	O
my	O
own	O
defence	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
wig	O
;	O
my	O
hat	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
also	O
my	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
cost	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
watchman	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
our	O
hats	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
wig	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knock	O
the	O
gentleman	O
down	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
meddling	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
444.	O
William	B-pers
Tankling	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
rape	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Collings	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
under	O
four	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
May	O
10	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
child	O
was	O
at	O
play	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
it	O
a	O
cake	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
her	O
from	O
home	O
till	O
9	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
bruised	O
very	O
much	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
her	O
nose	O
was	O
bruised	O
,	O
her	O
shift	O
,	O
coat	O
and	O
apron	O
were	O
very	O
bloody	O
.	O
We	O
thought	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
mouth	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
The	O
mother	O
after	O
this	O
found	O
the	O
child	O
very	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
persuaded	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Morton	O
;	O
he	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Infirmary	O
for	O
the	O
cure	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
foul	O
distemper	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
clean	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
foul	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
child	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
will	O
be	O
4	O
years	O
old	O
next	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
its	O
mother	O
?	O
C.	O
Higgins	O
.	O
The	O
mother	O
went	O
distracted	O
upon	O
this	O
account	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Morton	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
child	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
foul	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
hurt	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
with	O
his	O
cock	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
has	O
a	O
buboe	O
now	O
on	O
each	O
groin	O
.	O
The	O
infant	O
not	O
being	O
capable	O
of	O
giving	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
at	O
Hicks's-hall	O
,	O
for	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
commit	O
a	O
rape	O
,	O
and	O
giving	O
the	O
child	O
the	O
foul	O
disease	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
cast	O
to	O
be	O
confined	O
in	O
the	O
prison	O
of	O
Newgate	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
twice	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
the	O
pillory	O
in	O
one	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
more	O
at	O
the	O
three	O
years	O
end	O
;	O
and	O
find	O
such	O
security	O
for	O
his	O
good	O
behaviour	O
as	O
the	O
court	O
approves	O
on	O
for	O
four	O
years	O
more	O
.	O
445.	O
John	B-pers
Sellereat	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
23	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
June	O
15	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
abroad	O
in	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
vessel	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Robert	O
of	O
Lynn	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
at	O
Cotton's-wharf	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
my	O
money	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Lynn	O
;	O
we	O
failed	O
to	O
Tilbury	O
Fort	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
proposal	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
land	O
to	O
Lynn	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
wait	O
the	O
vessel	O
's	O
coming	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
consented	O
,	O
we	O
walked	O
about	O
two	O
miles	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
occasion	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
chare	O
for	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
walked	O
on	O
before	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
walked	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
quite	O
to	O
Lynn	O
,	O
and	O
waited	O
there	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
vessel	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
mate	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
chear	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
bad	O
chear	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
your	O
consort	O
has	O
taken	O
all	O
your	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
chest	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
46	O
guineas	O
in	O
my	O
chest	O
,	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
owner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
all	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
that	O
opportunity	O
to	O
slip	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
vessel	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
chest	O
of	O
the	O
owner	O
's	O
daughter	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
again	O
at	O
Lynn	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
money	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
23	O
guineas	O
to	O
keep	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
in	O
a	O
sloop	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
letter	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carr	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
hasten	O
'd	O
back	O
to	O
London	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
my	O
letter	O
which	O
I	O
sent	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
His	O
confession	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
feloniously	O
took	O
the	O
46	O
guineas	O
&	O
c.	O
Charles	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
delivered	O
23	O
guineas	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
Boston	O
,	O
in	O
Lincolnshire	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
then	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
swear	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
ship	O
's	O
company	O
as	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
robbery	O
being	O
committed	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
but	O
detained	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
proper	O
indictment	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
preferred	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
in	O
that	O
county	O
.	O
446.	O
John	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
tin	O
canisters	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Coxal	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Coxall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Featherstone-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
parish	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Withers	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
conveyed	O
tin	O
canisters	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
his	O
companions	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
concealed	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
value	O
the	O
three	O
canisters	O
at	O
?	O
Coxall	O
.	O
The	O
tea	O
and	O
all	O
we	O
valued	O
at	O
9	O
s.	O
Court	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
no	O
tea	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
canisters	O
themselves	O
worth	O
?	O
Coxall	O
.	O
The	O
three	O
canisters	O
together	O
cost	O
(	O
second-hand	O
)	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Coxall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
stepped	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
there	O
stood	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
canister	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
denied	O
he	O
touch	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
farthingworth	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
handed	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
his	O
companions	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
Henry	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
waiting	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Coxall	I-pers
.	O
We	O
were	O
after	O
these	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
could	O
hear	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
uncle	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
transported	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
with	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
canister	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
447	O
,	O
448.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Carrel	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Arthur	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
portmanteau	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
wastcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
six	O
shirts	O
,	O
six	O
cravats	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stocking	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
six	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
three	O
razors	O
,	O
one	O
penknife	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Arthur	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
June	O
21	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
portmanteau	O
carrying	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
coming	O
through	O
Stepney	B-place
church-yard	I-place
a	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
three	O
fellows	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
stop	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
hanger	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
surprise	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
(	O
this	O
witness	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
sighted	O
)	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
guarded	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
murder	O
,	O
they	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
speak	O
they	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
directly	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
deliver	O
two	O
penknives	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
assistance	O
and	O
pursued	O
them	O
to	O
Rag	O
fair	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
each	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
a	O
warrant	O
he	O
refused	O
going	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
got	O
money	O
for	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
got	O
one	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
searched	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
portmanteau	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
that	O
night	O
and	O
left	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stephen	O
Row	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
this	O
witness	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
forward	O
with	O
my	O
portmanteau	O
while	O
I	O
discharged	O
the	O
waterman	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
after	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
White	O
Horse	O
street	O
,	O
within	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
church-yard	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
outcry	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
robbery	O
committed	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
cross	O
,	O
making	O
his	O
complaint	O
to	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
men	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
pursue	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
yours	O
?	O
Row	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
6	O
shirts	O
,	O
6	O
cravats	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
;	O
three	O
razors	O
,	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
one	O
penknife	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
myself	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
found	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
who	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
wig	O
of	O
mine	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
accomplice	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
as	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
apprehended	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
John	O
,	O
Wapping	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
confessed	O
robbing	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
robberies	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Manwaring	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
last	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
sent	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
beadle	O
,	O
that	O
Dawson	O
,	O
then	O
in	O
Clerkenwel	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
informed	O
against	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pledged	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
the	O
beadle	O
after	O
her	O
she	O
was	O
easy	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
servant	O
talking	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
them	O
that	O
Dawson	O
had	O
then	O
my	O
wig	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Carrel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
wig	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
portmanteau	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
this	O
first	O
witness	O
in	O
Stepney	O
churchyard	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
towards	O
Limehouse	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
Rag	O
fair	O
together	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
to	O
Stepney	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
footman	O
in	O
White	O
Horse	O
street	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
the	O
church-yard	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
church-yard	O
we	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
Wallis	O
held	O
a	O
hanger	O
to	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
fall	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Gardner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
they	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
your	O
shoulder	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
surprised	O
.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
two	O
penknives	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Gardner	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
penny	O
.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
were	O
dodged	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
Stitchburn	O
's	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
lodg	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
divided	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
and	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
for	O
my	O
share	O
.	O
The	O
wig	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Carrel	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Carrel	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
shoes	O
;	O
Wallis	O
had	O
a	O
new	O
Holland	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
The	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
breeches	O
were	O
pawned	O
for	O
nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
girl	O
who	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
;	O
some	O
things	O
we	O
lost	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
lodged	O
was	O
searched	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
Carrel	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
wall	O
into	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
or	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Penney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
St.	O
John	O
,	O
Wapping	O
.	O
Since	O
the	O
prisoners	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
twenty	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Dawson	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
new	O
silver	O
buckle	O
,	O
the	O
knife	O
and	O
buckle	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Row	O
.	O
The	O
buckle	O
is	O
not	O
mine	O
.	O
But	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
know	O
a	O
knife	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
knife	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
make	O
pens	O
with	O
.	O
Gardner	O
deposed	O
the	O
knife	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
Wallis	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Rag	O
fair	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Dawson	O
that	O
night	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
fleet	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
do	O
you	O
lodge	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
in	O
Wapping	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
that	O
first	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Carrel	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
had	O
my	O
health	O
these	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
lodgings	O
and	O
going	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
mild	O
porter	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
his	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
quietly	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
449.	O
Shedrick	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
siver	O
spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
,	O
June	O
16	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Abercromby	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
sweep	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
(	O
Francis	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
)	O
chimney	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
maid	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
Fulham	O
again	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
lives	O
there	O
.	O
My	O
fellow	O
servant	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
swept	O
the	O
chimney	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
in	O
Peter	O
's	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
sweep	O
our	O
chimney	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
up	O
the	O
chimney	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
for	O
sweeping	O
the	O
chimney	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Anson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
as	O
before	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
bag	O
of	O
sut	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
450	O
,	O
451.	O
John	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Possey	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
iron	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
and	O
sixteen	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
June	O
11	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
in	O
Stepney	B-place
fields	I-place
I	O
was	O
attacked	O
by	O
four	O
persons	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
stick	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
much	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
searched	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
four-pence	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
Bailey	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
from	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fine	O
moon-light	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
box	O
and	O
gloves	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Frazier	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
four	O
again	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
them	O
accidentally	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
near	O
the	O
Maypole	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
there	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
and	O
inquired	O
for	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
these	O
four	O
watchmen	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
near	O
home	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
talking	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
proper	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
watch	O
and	O
thieves	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
,	O
Bailey	O
ran	O
to	O
Cock-alley	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
my	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
;	O
Frazier	O
was	O
taken	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
I	O
live	O
pretty	O
near	O
the	O
officer	O
that	O
took	O
John	B-pers
Frazier	I-pers
,	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
owning	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
Stepney	O
fields	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
he	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
And	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
either	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
or	O
a	O
tobacco	O
box	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Medows	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Bailey	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Airton	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Hyson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
Frazier	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
his	O
confession	O
.	O
Frazier	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
14	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
Bailey	O
about	O
16	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
452.	O
James	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
20	O
other	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
being	O
armed	O
with	O
fire-arms	O
and	O
other	O
offensive	O
weapons	O
,	O
from	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
1746	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
to	O
say	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1746	O
,	O
)	O
were	O
feloniously	O
assembled	O
at	O
Broom	O
hill	O
in	O
Sussex	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
aiding	O
in	O
the	O
running	O
uncustomed	O
goods	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
liable	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
duties	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
paid	O
,	O
or	O
secured	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
diminution	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
revenue	O
,	O
against	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
peace	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
the	O
statute	O
in	O
that	O
behalf	O
made	O
and	O
provided	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
In	O
October	O
,	O
1746	O
,	O
I	O
lived	O
hostler	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
at	O
Lydd	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
smugglers	O
coming	O
there	O
,	O
about	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
of	O
them	O
lodged	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
(	O
as	O
many	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
stables	O
for	O
)	O
the	O
town	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
in	O
Broomhill-house	O
,	O
those	O
people	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
George	B-pers
I	I-pers
had	O
seen	O
there	O
before	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
Hawkhurst	O
gang	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
tarry	O
there	O
any	O
time	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
there	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
waiting	O
for	O
a	O
cutter	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
the	O
19th	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
advice	O
of	O
a	O
cutter	O
being	O
arrived	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
the	O
horses	O
out	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
follow	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
compelled	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
shoemaker	O
Tom	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
my	O
master	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
.	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
then	O
Dixon	O
took	O
me	O
several	O
blows	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
with	O
the	O
great	O
end	O
of	O
his	O
whip	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
alone	O
.	O
The	O
cutter	O
was	O
come	O
into	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
the	O
Jew	O
's	O
Gutt	O
,	O
in	O
Sussex	O
,	O
five	O
miles	O
from	O
Lydd	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
horse	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
saddle	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
in	O
the	O
holsters	O
on	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Beech	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
moon	O
shun	O
very	O
bright	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
several	O
times	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
company	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
leading	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
shoemaker	O
Tom	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
John	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
shoemaker	O
Tom	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
all	O
on	O
shore	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
tea	O
was	O
in	O
oil-skin	O
bags	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
away	O
five	O
half	O
anchors	O
of	O
brandy	O
on	O
my	O
own	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
away	O
towards	O
Rye	O
with	O
two	O
bags	O
of	O
tea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
armed	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
armed	O
,	O
some	O
with	O
pistols	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
some	O
with	O
carbines	O
slung	O
to	O
their	O
shoulders	O
,	O
some	O
with	O
hangers	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
carbine	O
,	O
and	O
pistol	O
too	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
many	O
horses	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
horses	O
than	O
men	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
went	O
from	O
Lydd	O
to	O
the	O
Jew	O
's	O
Gutt	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Jew	O
's	O
Gutt	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
1746	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Lydd	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
Romney	O
parish	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
little	O
miles	O
from	O
New	O
Romney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
county	O
is	O
Lydd	O
in	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Kent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
Broom-hill	O
house	O
from	O
Lydd	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
five	O
miles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
been	O
at	O
Winchester	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
Lydd	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
computed	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
72	O
miles	O
from	O
hence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
miles	O
was	O
it	O
from	O
where	O
you	O
was	O
then	O
landing	O
these	O
goods	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
These	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
sometimes	O
at	O
one	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
at	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
resided	O
some	O
time	O
at	O
Winchester	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
large	O
family	O
there	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
Winchester	O
in	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
that	O
ago	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
long	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
has	O
served	O
any	O
Officer	O
in	O
Winchester	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
hath	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Jew	O
's	O
Gutt	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
distinguish	O
one	O
person	O
's	O
face	O
from	O
another	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
was	O
this	O
horse	O
the	O
person	O
was	O
leading	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
grey	O
horse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
to	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
towards	O
Rye	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
time	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
gangs	O
met	O
together	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
300	O
horses	O
,	O
they	O
staid	O
at	O
Lydd	O
till	O
the	O
cutter	O
came	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
at	O
Jew	O
's	O
Gutt	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
loaded	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
help	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
load	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
?	O
