TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
and	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
In	O
the	O
23d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pennant	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
1750	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Pu	O
may	O
be	O
assured	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
during	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	O
PENNANT	O
,	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
)	O
the	O
Sessions-Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
Four-pence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
hole	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
Sessions	O
shall	O
be	O
carefully	O
compriz	O
'd	O
in	O
The	O
such	O
Four-penny	O
Book	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
other	O
Burthen	O
on	O
the	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PENNANT	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
LEE	O
,	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
ABNEY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLARKE	I-pers
,	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Cuney	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Attley	I-pers
Sanders	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
John	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bedham	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wilbourne	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bramley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Wetherley	I-pers
James	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
Simeon	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Goadman	I-pers
Benj	B-pers
Ormered	I-pers
290.	O
Mary	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
19	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
and	O
linnen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
291.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jarret	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
Cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Combs	I-pers
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Combs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Holborn-bridge	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
Hosier	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
my	O
man	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
ware-house	O
to	O
set	O
it	O
to	O
rights	O
.	O
We	O
bid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
mind	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
after	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
boy	O
had	O
been	O
taking	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
parcels	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
apprehended	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
boy	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
candle	O
to	O
serch	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
bundle	O
he	O
had	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
chared	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confest	O
the	O
fact	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
air	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Two	O
pair	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
at	O
parcel	O
my	O
wife	O
shewed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
off	O
my	O
counter	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
returned	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
breach	O
ear	O
the	O
top	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
changed	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
breaches	O
was	O
shewed	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
,	O
the	O
servant	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prison	O
came	O
well	O
recommended	O
,	O
do	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
,	O
therefore	O
do	O
beg	O
that	O
he	O
may	O
have	O
some	O
corporal	O
punishment	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
be	O
sent	O
abd	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
292.	O
Frances	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s	O
five	O
linnen	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
diaper	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
two	O
linnen	O
caps	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
O	I-pers
Hara	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
293.	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
late	B-place
of	I-place
Enfield	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
with	O
force	O
and	O
arms	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Oliver	B-pers
Driver	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
eleven	O
linnen	O
napkins	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Oliver	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
294	O
,	O
295.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Job	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Richard	B-pers
Goldington	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
seven	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Goldington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Victualler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Hendon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Barnet	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
duty	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
bridle	O
,	O
near	B-place
a	I-place
wood	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
a	I-place
place	I-place
called	I-place
Holder	I-place
's	I-place
hill	I-place
;	O
one	O
got	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
wanted	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
then	O
Job	O
Savage	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
Carey	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
for	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
other	O
five	O
to	O
Savage	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
silver	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
only	O
about	O
a	O
shilling	O
or	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
hoped	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
cord	O
to	O
bind	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
We	O
rais	O
'd	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
doing	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
stone	O
's	O
throw	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
run	O
into	O
the	O
wood	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoners	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
company	O
sufficient	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
past	O
me	O
before	O
they	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
Job	O
Savage	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
ockey	O
?	O
Joseph	B-pers
Love	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
Carey	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Group-Lane	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
search	O
them	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
dropp	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
leaden	O
square	O
balls	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
gun-powder	O
;	O
we	O
also	O
found	O
a	O
pistol	O
charged	O
with	O
slugs	O
under	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
Savage	O
had	O
sat	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
taken	O
him	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
taken	O
from	O
Savage	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
having	O
good	O
sight	O
of	O
it	O
when	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
also	O
of	O
my	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
Savage	O
one	O
shilling	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ederidge	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Love	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Love	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
Savage	O
's	O
mouth	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
chew	O
of	O
Tobacco	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hooked	O
them	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
mohock	O
knife	O
.	O
Savage	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
out	O
that	O
day	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
labouring	O
work	O
;	O
this	O
Money	O
we	O
brought	O
out	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
This	O
young	O
fellow	O
(	O
meaning	O
Carey	O
)	O
designed	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pig	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
returning	O
we	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
witness	O
to	O
shew	O
how	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
have	O
that	O
money	O
about	O
us	O
.	O
Lidia	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Carey	O
lodges	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
rooms	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
that	O
morning	O
take	O
five	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
trunk	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
little	O
pig	O
and	O
bring	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Savage	O
is	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
brother	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
last	O
monday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
296	O
,	O
297	O
,	O
298.	O
James	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Bambrick	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
shift	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Varse	I-pers
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
shift	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
March	O
2	O
.	O
Each	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
299.	O
Richard	B-pers
Sweetman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
pistol	O
,	O
on	O
Mary	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Whitmarsh	I-pers
,	O
feloniously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
intending	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Whitmarsh	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Arnold	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
about	O
30	B-place
or	I-place
40	I-place
yards	I-place
from	I-place
Powis-wells	I-place
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
April	O
22	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
cross	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
towards	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
us	O
not	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
saying	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
immediately	O
ran	O
back	O
screaming	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
pursued	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
found	O
by	O
our	O
noise	O
we	O
had	O
alarmed	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
,	O
until	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
by	O
his	O
turning	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
upon	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
salute	O
us	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Arnold	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
is	O
my	O
sister	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
Powis-wells	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
my	O
sister	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Arnold	O
scream	O
out	O
;	O
my	O
sister	O
came	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
some	O
gentleman	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Story	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Story	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
right-side	O
pocket	O
,	O
a	O
pistol	O
loaded	O
and	O
cock	O
'd	O
.	O
Janus	O
Story	O
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
account	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
an	O
affair	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
away	O
with	O
myself	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
extremity	O
and	O
want	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
wife	O
in	O
a	O
starving	O
condition	O
,	O
but	O
thinking	O
about	O
my	O
soul	O
,	O
hindered	O
me	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
300.	O
John	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Chester	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
March	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
301.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
housing	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
saddle	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
a	O
leopard	O
's	O
skin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
April	O
30	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
again	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
302.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
303.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Darlow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
304	O
,	O
305.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
five	O
linnen	O
caps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Morpher	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Ann	O
Guilty	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
569	O
,	O
570	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
306.	O
William	B-pers
Rollett	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
horsewhip	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
March	O
15	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
horsewhip	O
were	O
hanging	O
on	O
two	O
pins	O
near	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
observed	O
by	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
dropt	O
the	O
whip	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
hat	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
throwed	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
307	O
,	O
308.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
penknife	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
three-pence	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
March	O
22	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	B-place
the	I-place
halfway	I-place
house	I-place
on	I-place
this	I-place
side	I-place
Hampstead	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
foot	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
bridge	I-place
that	I-place
leads	I-place
to	I-place
Pancras	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
where	O
were	O
four	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
person	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
running	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
Blast	O
your	O
eyes	O
and	O
limbs	O
,	O
keep	O
down	O
your	O
hat	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Lewis	O
jobb	O
'd	O
his	O
pistol	O
against	O
my	O
teeth	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
my	O
gums	O
bleed	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
s	O
tood	O
with	O
his	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
ear	O
.	O
They	O
rifled	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
one	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
six-pences	O
,	O
one	O
penknife	O
,	O
and	O
three-pence	O
in	O
halfpence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
met	O
them	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
robbed	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pentelow	O
,	O
the	O
headborough	O
of	O
our	O
parish	O
,	O
who	O
assisted	O
in	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pentelow	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
That	O
upon	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
describing	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
,	O
having	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
took	O
Lewis	O
on	O
my	O
Lady	O
Albemarle	O
's	O
account	O
.	O
(	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
200	O
,	O
201.	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
paper	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
Lewis	O
snapt	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
his	O
breast	O
twice	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
Lewis	O
in	O
bed	O
in	O
Newtoner	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
May	O
at	O
infamous	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Cannon	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
he	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
rings	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
espcially	O
May	O
,	O
much	O
abused	O
this	O
headborough	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
would	O
swear	O
away	O
any	O
person	O
's	O
life	O
for	O
a	O
trifle	O
.	O
But	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
upon	O
oath	O
declared	O
,	O
he	O
sincerely	O
believed	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
an	O
honestr	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
braver	O
man	O
than	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
dominion	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
May	O
talked	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
though	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
James	B-pers
Cissel	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
two	O
officers	O
,	O
and	O
Andrew	O
Campbel	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
Pentelow	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
309.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Blacketer	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
d.	O
and	O
5	O
d.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
May	O
22	O
.	O
Lewis	O
and	O
Hambleton	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
May	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Pancras-Fields	B-place
,	O
March	O
21	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Lewis	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
'd	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
May	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
repeated	O
the	O
same	O
Words	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
pray	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
use	O
me	O
well	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
Hambleton	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
terrible	O
threatening	O
words	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
rob	O
Mr.	O
Matevae	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Matevae	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
of	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
ten	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Hambleton	O
and	O
Lewis	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Hambleton	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
very	O
ill	O
with	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
22d	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
parched	O
oats	O
put	O
to	O
my	O
side	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
blooded	O
,	O
when	O
these	O
people	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
The	O
Truth	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
to	O
prove	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
a	O
blundering	O
account	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
ill	O
;	O
being	O
asked	O
how	O
see	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
Day	O
of	O
the	O
Month	O
,	O
her	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
apt	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
church	O
to	O
the	O
evening-prayers	O
,	O
makes	O
me	O
remember	O
it	O
.	O
Lewis	O
,	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
and	O
May	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
a	O
4th	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Matevae	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
ten	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
were	O
those	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
Trial	O
.	O
Lewis	O
and	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
May	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
310.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Stitchbury	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Phaling	I-pers
,	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
311.	O
Mary	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Eccles	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pound	O
6	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pound	O
ten	O
ounces	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jefferson	I-pers
,	O
April	O
17	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jefferson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
Grocer's-shop	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
then	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
the	O
two	O
washerwomen	O
were	O
eating	O
their	O
suppers	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Jefferson	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
some	O
tea	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
We	O
felt	O
about	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
our	O
hands	O
to	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Colbech	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
she	O
would	O
acknowledge	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Mrs.	O
Jefferson	O
falling	O
into	O
a	O
fit	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
attend	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
at	O
last	O
and	O
untied	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
tea	O
from	O
above	O
her	O
knee	O
,	O
which	O
hung	O
in	O
her	O
ham	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
searched	O
her	O
other	O
leg	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
sugar	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
another	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
ham	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
.	O
We	O
were	O
sitting	O
at	O
dinner	O
;	O
the	O
Cat	O
got	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
meat	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
under	O
the	O
cellar	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
parcel	O
of	O
tea	O
in	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
it	O
to	O
our	O
apprentice	O
and	O
maid-servant	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
concluded	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
to	O
watch	O
which	O
way	O
it	O
would	O
go	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
upon	O
its	O
being	O
gone	O
from	O
this	O
place	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
washerwoman	O
insisted	O
upon	O
both	O
being	O
searched	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
312.	O
Peter	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
sheet	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Bodington	I-pers
.	O
March	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
313	O
,	O
314.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Carel	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
James	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
peruke	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
April	O
18	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
peruke	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Talby	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
peruke	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Upon	O
these	O
four	O
Indictments	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
evidence	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
more	O
like	O
drunken	O
quarrelling	O
than	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
315.	O
Edward	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Innes	I-pers
,	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
And	O
likewise	O
standing	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
:	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Capt	O
.	O
Innes	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
about	O
eight	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Welton	O
,	O
a	O
Painter	O
,	O
in	O
Green	O
street	O
,	O
Leicester-fields	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Captain	O
Clark	O
at	O
the	O
dining-room	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
Capt	O
.	O
Innes	O
was	O
up	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
dining-room	O
the	O
time	O
:	O
my	O
master	O
got	O
up	O
very	O
soon	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
After	O
my	O
master	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
dining-room	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
say	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Innes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
discourse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
distinctly	O
hear	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
speak	O
,	O
insisting	O
on	O
his	O
fighting	O
sword	O
and	O
pistol	O
(	O
the	O
voice	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
voice	O
;	O
)	O
after	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
words	O
passed	O
,	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Innes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
understood	O
him	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
:	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Capt	O
Clark	O
has	O
been	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
challenged	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Hyde-park	B-place
,	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Innes	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
from	O
Grosvenor's-Gate	O
;	O
Capt	O
.	O
Innes	O
was	O
on	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
from	O
where	O
the	O
Duel	O
was	O
fought	O
;	O
at	O
my	O
first	O
seeing	O
him	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
500	O
yards	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
just	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
park	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
they	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
the	O
grove	O
,	O
but	O
turned	O
more	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
seemed	O
to	O
walk	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
servant	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
They	O
walked	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
duel	O
was	O
fought	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
very	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
within	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
clear	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
parted	O
,	O
the	O
trees	O
hindered	O
me	O
from	O
seeing	O
the	O
position	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
I	O
moved	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
was	O
standing	O
with	O
his	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Innes	O
was	O
getting	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
posture	O
to	O
be	O
ready	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
yards	O
asunder	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
report	O
Capt	O
.	O
Innes	O
was	O
then	O
lifting	O
up	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
the	O
pistol	O
pois	O
'd	O
in	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
stock	O
still	O
;	O
as	O
Capt	O
.	O
Innes	O
was	O
reaching	O
out	O
his	O
arm	O
towards	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
fir	O
'd	O
his	O
pistol	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
servant	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
turned	O
round	O
at	O
the	O
explosion	O
of	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
knee	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Innes	O
did	O
not	O
fire	O
at	O
all	O
(	O
his	O
pistols	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
both	O
charged	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ball	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Capt	O
.	O
Innes	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
)	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
servant	O
took	O
the	O
pistols	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
my	O
master	O
to	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
He	O
bade	O
me	O
tell	O
every	O
body	O
that	O
should	O
enquire	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
honourable	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
took	O
full	O
aim	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
fired	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
ready	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
about	O
eleven	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
several	O
times	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
forgave	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
God	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
These	O
words	O
were	O
spoke	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
pistols	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
cocks	O
were	O
let	O
down	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
Pans	O
fallen	O
back	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
pistols	O
were	O
very	O
large	O
screw-barrel	O
pistols	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hurdman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Abercromby	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Captain	O
Innes	B-pers
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
when	O
Captain	O
Clark	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
desire	O
Captain	O
Innes	B-pers
to	O
call	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
stairs	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
when	O
he	O
spoke	O
these	O
words	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Welton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
about	O
eight	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
somebody	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
walking	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
talking	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
about	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
door	O
clap	O
again	O
.	O
Newman	O
come	O
up	O
stairs	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
fright	O
(	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
)	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
Captain	O
Clark	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
challenged	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
be	O
sure	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
when	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
will	O
;	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
shall	O
go	O
without	O
shoes	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
At	O
night	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
black	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
them	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
to-morrow	O
morning	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
captain	O
walking	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
clap	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
Castle-street	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
door	O
shut	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
run	O
towards	O
Leicester-fields	O
.	O
I	O
make	O
haste	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Montague-house	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
about	O
on	O
every	O
spot	O
of	O
high	O
ground	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
;	O
I	O
not	O
finding	O
them	O
,	O
made	O
haste	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
hang	O
up	O
my	O
hat	O
before	O
Newman	O
came	O
running	O
home	O
with	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
sword	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
captain	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
wounded	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
his	O
hands	O
in	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
six	O
hours	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
cold	O
,	O
seeming	O
almost	O
dead	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
he	O
asked	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
how	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
declare	O
it	O
when	O
asked	O
by	O
any	O
:	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dying	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
forgave	O
Captain	O
Clark	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
heart	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
like	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
fired	O
too	O
soon	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
go	O
to	O
fight	O
such	O
a	O
gentleman	O
as	O
Captain	O
Clark	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
's	O
will	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
strove	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
my	O
life	O
at	O
the	O
Court	O
Martial	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
done	O
now	O
.	O
The	O
reason	O
she	O
had	O
for	O
asking	O
that	O
question	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
heard	O
from	O
Captain	O
Innes	B-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
Captain	O
Clark	O
had	O
swore	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
Court	O
Martial	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
against	O
several	O
other	O
captains	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Welton	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
extracted	O
the	O
ball	O
.	O
It	O
entered	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
false	O
ribs	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
hand	O
's	O
breadth	O
from	O
the	O
pit	O
of	O
the	O
stomach	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
had	O
broke	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
false	O
ribs	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
This	O
wound	O
,	O
no	O
doubt	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
asking	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
wound	O
in	O
a	O
duel	O
with	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
in	O
Hyde-park	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
stood	O
about	O
four	O
yards	O
from	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
murder	O
to	O
stand	O
so	O
close	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
my	O
pistols	O
were	O
small	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
fault	O
to	O
find	O
with	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
honourable	O
enough	O
.	O
Lord	O
Southwell	O
,	O
Admiral	O
Martin	O
,	O
Admiral	O
Byng	B-pers
,	O
Admiral	O
Faukes	B-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Montague	B-pers
Bertie	I-pers
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
West	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Wickham	O
,	O
Colonel	O
Lee	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Dent	O
,	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Dr.	O
Hale	O
,	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Horton	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stanley	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Forrest	O
,	O
Col.	O
Durand	O
,	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
gave	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
an	O
exceeding	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
behaviour	O
,	O
not	O
easily	O
mov	O
'd	O
to	O
passion	O
,	O
willing	O
to	O
reconcile	O
differences	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
peaceable	O
disposition	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
But	O
recommended	O
to	O
Mercy	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
brought	O
into	O
court	O
to	O
receive	O
judgment	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
convicts	O
,	O
addressed	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
MY	B-pers
LORDS	I-pers
,	O
I	O
Am	O
very	O
sensible	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
indulgence	O
of	O
your	O
lordships	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
early	O
passing	O
the	O
sentence	O
of	O
the	O
law	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
though	O
't	O
is	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
all	O
human	O
favours	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
hoped	O
to	O
have	O
received	O
from	O
your	O
lordships	O
hands	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
my	O
lords	O
,	O
were	O
pleased	O
to	O
shew	O
their	O
compassion	O
to	O
the	O
failings	O
of	O
human	O
nature	O
,	O
in	O
recommending	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
royal	O
mercy	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
there	O
have	O
appeared	O
some	O
circumstances	O
in	O
my	O
case	O
,	O
which	O
may	O
not	O
render	O
me	O
altogether	O
unworthy	O
the	O
recommendations	O
of	O
your	O
lordships	O
also	O
.	O
N.	O
B.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
were	O
horse	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
Ca	O
pt	O
.	O
Innes	O
's	O
very	O
small	O
pocket	O
pistols	O
.	O
Far	O
,	O
my	O
lords	O
,	O
shall	O
it	O
be	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
endeavour	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
rules	O
of	O
law	O
,	O
to	O
justify	O
the	O
crime	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
convicted	O
of	O
,	O
nor	O
can	O
I	O
express	O
the	O
affliction	O
I	O
am	O
under	O
for	O
that	O
unfortunate	O
Gentleman	O
whose	O
death	O
has	O
occasioned	O
this	O
trouble	O
to	O
your	O
lordships	O
,	O
and	O
misfortune	O
to	O
myself	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
through	O
the	O
mediation	O
of	O
your	O
lordships	O
,	O
the	O
royal	O
mercy	O
should	O
be	O
extended	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
shall	O
be	O
employed	O
in	O
preventing	O
other	O
gentlemen	O
from	O
falling	O
into	O
those	O
unhappy	O
circumstances	O
I	O
now	O
appear	O
in	O
.	O
[	O
As	O
the	O
above	O
trial	O
is	O
obliged	O
to	O
be	O
abridged	O
to	O
make	O
room	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
trials	O
,	O
by	O
permission	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
this	O
trial	O
will	O
be	O
published	O
at	O
large	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
,	O
by	O
itself	O
]	O
316.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
seaman	O
's	O
ticket	O
,	O
dated	O
March	O
29	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stockwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wapping	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
about	O
18	O
l.	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
this	O
ticket	O
,	O
(	O
both	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
good	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
by	O
Johanna	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
forgery	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Player	O
.	O
This	O
ticket	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Johanna	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
bring	O
Perry	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
clerk	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Sommerset	O
,	O
for	O
wages	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
signed	O
on	O
the	O
wrong	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
printing	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
mistakes	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
captain	O
's	O
clerk	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
Sommerset	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Strutton	O
,	O
captain	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
gave	O
him	O
this	O
ticket	O
,	O
nor	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
Scruthon	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
wrong	O
.	O
The	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
;	O
this	O
here	O
is	O
wrote	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
James	O
Butler	O
Moore	O
,	O
is	O
purser	O
;	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
;	O
also	O
here	O
is	O
Robert	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
put	O
for	O
John	O
Davis	O
,	O
Boatswain	O
.	O
The	O
time	O
this	O
was	O
made	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
entitled	O
to	O
any	O
wages	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
made	O
out	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
from	O
the	O
ship	O
the	O
5th	O
.	O
He	O
entered	O
July	O
16th	O
,	O
1749.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
boatswain	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
nor	O
my	O
name	O
;	O
neither	O
is	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
my	O
writing	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
last	O
witnesses	O
had	O
the	O
ticket	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
when	O
examined	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
317.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
pistol	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunsdon	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
intent	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
intending	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunsdon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Savage-gardens	O
,	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
addressed	O
me	O
in	O
these	O
words	O
:	O
Sir	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
,	O
by	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
spring	O
to	O
a	O
watchman	O
that	O
was	O
near	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Poor	O
Jury-lane	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
another	O
man	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
accomplice	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
perfect	O
view	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
at	O
a	O
lamp	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
watchmen	O
that	O
took	O
him	O
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
,	O
one	O
hearing	O
the	O
very	O
words	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
318.	O
Ann	B-pers
Mann	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloath	O
coat	O
,	O
one	O
leghorn	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Overy	I-pers
,	O
March	O
26	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
319.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linning	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
April	O
17	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
320.	O
William	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
gun	O
loaded	O
with	O
powder	O
and	O
shot	O
,	O
wilfully	O
,	O
feloniously	O
and	O
of	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
did	O
shoot	O
off	O
at	O
Anthony	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
with	O
an	O
Intent	O
the	O
said	O
Anthony	O
to	O
kill	O
or	O
murder	O
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
these	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dwells	O
almost	O
opposite	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
looking	O
on	O
my	O
meat	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
sudden	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
head	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
report	O
of	O
a	O
gun	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
who	O
shot	O
.	O
A	O
surgeon	O
was	O
fetch	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
above	O
100	O
shot	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
neck	O
behind	O
;	O
(	O
He	O
shewed	O
the	O
part	O
,	O
which	O
looked	O
much	O
like	O
a	O
person	O
recovered	O
from	O
the	O
small-pox	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hat	O
also	O
which	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
hundred	O
holes	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
holding	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
light	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
days	O
under	O
the	O
surgeon	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
now	O
walk	O
or	O
drink	O
much	O
,	O
or	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
hastily	O
,	O
it	O
puts	O
me	O
in	O
very	O
great	O
pain	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
shot	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
flesh	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
were	O
the	O
third	O
size	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Nelson	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
gun	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
He	O
held	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
shop-window	O
towards	O
Mr.	O
Higgins	O
's	O
shop	O
which	O
is	O
almost	O
opposite	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Higgins	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Higgins	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
street	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
.	O
Being	O
cross	O
examined	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
no	O
words	O
between	O
them	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
sometimes	O
,	O
once	O
tied	O
down	O
in	O
bea	O
.	O
He	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
without	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
followed	O
the	O
trade	O
of	O
a	O
butcher	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
once	O
saw	O
him	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
ago	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
naked	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
thought	O
had	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
madness	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
facing	O
Mr.	O
Higgins	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
report	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
gun	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Higgins	O
clap	O
his	O
anos	O
to	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
rogue	O
Archer	O
had	O
killed	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Higgins	O
's	O
back	O
was	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
staid	O
about	O
5	O
minutes	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
crossed	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
eyes	O
he	O
had	O
hit	O
his	O
mark	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
eyes	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
to	O
several	O
people	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
Higgins	O
an	O
informer	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Higgins	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
twelve	O
years	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
years	O
ago	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
fever	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bill	O
found	O
against	O
him	O
that	O
day	O
he	O
shot	O
Mr.	O
Higgins	O
,	O
for	O
selling	O
meat	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deane	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
being	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
,	O
by	O
Archer	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
piece	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
upon	O
the	O
noise	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
to	O
look	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Higgins	O
clap	O
his	O
two	O
hands	O
to	O
the	O
sides	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Archer	O
say	O
,	O
never	O
fear	O
but	O
I	O
hit	O
my	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
eyes	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
:	O
He	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
I	O
am	O
I	O
'll	O
surrender	O
myself	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
before	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
Fellow	O
Servant	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
Witness	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barber	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
years	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
this	O
misfortune	O
happened	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
out	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Master	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
indicted	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
seeming	O
extasy	O
,	O
for	O
selling	O
meat	O
on	O
the	O
sabbath-day	O
,	O
that	O
villian	O
Higgins	O
has	O
done	O
it	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
be	O
misinformed	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
tip	O
it	O
him	O
before	O
night	O
;	O
when	O
in	O
liquor	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
passionate	O
creature	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
sober	O
,	O
very	O
quiet	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
only	O
words	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
gun	O
go	O
off	O
about	O
3-qrs	O
.	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
shave	O
Mr.	O
Higgins	O
,	O
his	O
hair	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
inches	O
long	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
The	O
blood	O
spouted	O
out	O
as	O
water	O
does	O
through	O
a	O
cuilender	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
much	O
ado	O
to	O
shave	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
could	O
exhist	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
looked	O
upon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
madman	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Daws	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
say	O
that	O
day	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
the	O
Rogue	O
(	O
meaning	O
Mr.	O
Higgings	O
)	O
I	O
'll	O
kill	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
week	O
is	O
out	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
gun-powder	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
shot	O
,	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
pretty	O
large	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ketly	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
two	O
boys	O
fighting	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
gun	O
pointed	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Archer	O
's	O
Window	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
shot	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
aimed	O
at	O
a	O
mark	O
but	O
I	O
always	O
hit	O
it	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
Eyes	O
:	O
His	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
all	O
the	O
week	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
have	O
killed	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
a	O
bitch	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
killed	O
another	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
had	O
his	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
srantick	O
?	O
Kelley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apothecary	O
,	O
I	O
once	O
attended	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
ten	O
years	O
since	O
;	O
Dr.	O
Barrowby	O
was	O
his	O
physician	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
several	O
days	O
and	O
nights	O
bound	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
bed	O
with	O
a	O
madman	O
's	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
's	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
restored	O
to	O
his	O
senses	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
or	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
this	O
madness	O
arise	O
from	O
a	O
fever	O
?	O
Wells	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
high	O
fever	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Metherington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
16	O
or	O
17	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
dressed	O
six	O
blisters	O
for	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
Dr.	O
Barrowby	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
about	O
this	O
time	O
twelve	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
Dr.	O
Barrowby	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
times	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
for	O
seventeen	O
years	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
ago	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
bleed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
delicious	O
way	O
;	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
known	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
ventered	O
high	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
within	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
talked	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
a	O
raving	O
and	O
swearing	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
a	O
hole	O
big	O
enough	O
,	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
come	O
through	O
,	O
come	O
thro	O
'	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
thus	O
for	O
several	O
days	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Privinix	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
nurse	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
any	O
thing	O
ailed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
mad	O
about	O
nine	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
corded	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
mad	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
in	O
Bedlam	O
,	O
three	O
times	O
within	O
this	O
Twelvemonth	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
321.	O
Mary	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
York	I-pers
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
April	O
17	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
322.	O
Richard	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
iron	O
hoops	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
March	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
323.	O
James	B-pers
Paria	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pistol	O
mounted	O
with	O
steel	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pistol	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
and	O
brass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Malise	I-pers
.	O
April	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
324.	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
counterfeiting	O
the	O
silver	O
coin	O
of	O
this	O
realm	O
,	O
called	O
shillings	O
.	O
December	O
21	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Pye-street	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
serjeant	O
Sage	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Davenport	O
,	O
make	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
Davenport	O
held	O
the	O
mould	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
poured	O
the	O
pewter	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
shewed	O
me	O
about	O
15	O
,	O
or	O
16	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
appeared	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
other	O
shillings	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
in	O
Gardner's-lane	O
at	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
About	O
December	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
one	O
Willis	O
,	O
make	O
three	O
of	O
these	O
;	O
there	O
lay	O
15	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
all	O
cast	O
.	O
They	O
sist	O
a	O
wooden	O
square	O
frame	O
full	O
of	O
whiting	O
,	O
then	O
cram	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
scrape	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
on	O
a	O
shilling	O
with	O
a	O
sheet	O
of	O
white	O
paper	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
frame	O
were	O
there	O
are	O
four	O
holes	O
and	O
four	O
pegs	O
to	O
fit	O
in	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
those	O
two	O
frames	O
lie	O
true	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
before	O
cut	O
away	O
the	O
paper	O
over	O
,	O
the	O
shilling	O
,	O
they	O
then	O
fill	O
the	O
other	O
frame	O
with	O
this	O
whiting	O
,	O
then	O
take	O
them	O
asunder	O
,	O
the	O
paper	O
being	O
between	O
,	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
shilling	O
:	O
They	O
made	O
a	O
gutter	O
for	O
the	O
mettle	O
to	O
run	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
generally	O
used	O
to	O
melt	O
their	O
pewter	O
in	O
a	O
tobacco	O
pipe	O
to	O
pour	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
mould	O
;	O
there	O
would	O
appear	O
a	O
little	O
roughness	O
upon	O
the	O
edge	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
finished	O
up	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
prince	O
Eugene	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
we	O
once	O
put	O
off	O
some	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
wanted	O
to	O
pass	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
quarrel	O
amongst	O
ourselves	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
quarrel	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
so	O
twice	O
that	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
time	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Green-man	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
gave	O
the	O
boy	O
a	O
shilling	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
change	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
mouth	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
change	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Stratton's-ground	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mistrust	O
he	O
carried	O
on	O
this	O
business	O
then	O
,	O
till	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ind	I-pers
came	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
putting	O
off	O
bad	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
,	O
searched	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
wooden	O
flasks	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
inches	O
square	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
powdered	O
whiting	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
quicksilver	O
.	O
Ward	O
.	O
The	O
quicksilver	O
was	O
to	O
rub	O
over	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
like	O
silver	O
.	O
Fisher	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
three	O
corner	O
'd	O
file	O
.	O
Ward	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
to	O
mill	O
the	O
edges	O
with	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
Testimony	O
of	O
Fisher	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ind	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
tools	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
Gardner	O
's	O
Lane	O
at	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
half	O
a	O
sheet	O
of	O
paper	O
on	O
the	O
teaster	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
print	O
of	O
a	O
shilling	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
four	O
peg	O
holes	O
that	O
shewed	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
pegg	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
flask	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gardner	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
logged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
pewter	O
spoons	O
.	O
Ward	O
hired	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
all	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Vere	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Prince	O
Eugene	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
came	O
intomy	O
house	O
along	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Lampler	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Wolsington	I-pers
,	O
they	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
betwixt	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
reckoning	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
Andrews	O
and	O
Wolfington	O
began	O
to	O
quarrel	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
quarrel	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Lampler	O
and	O
Macdonald	O
threw	O
down	O
sixpence	O
a	O
piece	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
presently	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
draw	O
'd	O
them	O
one	O
;	O
then	O
when	O
that	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
drew	O
them	O
another	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
six-pence	O
,	O
then	O
Andrews	O
began	O
to	O
quarrel	O
with	O
Wolfington	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
desired	O
Mary	O
Jenneson	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
some	O
college	O
loaf	O
and	O
cheese	O
;	O
when	O
Wolfington	O
and	O
Macdonald	O
had	O
done	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
paid	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
t	O
wo	O
bad	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jenneson	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
them	O
soldiers	O
had	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
bad	O
shillings	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
and	O
fetched	O
some	O
beer	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
six-pence	O
is	O
gone	O
for	O
that	O
beer	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
fetch	O
that	O
withal	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Firnasses	O
's	O
house	O
were	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
Mrs.	O
Jenneson	O
had	O
not	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
bad	O
shilling	O
,	O
which	O
upon	O
enquiry	O
was	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
men	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Ward	O
there	O
owned	O
giving	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
bad	O
:	O
Andrews	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
hang	O
us	O
?	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
141.	O
of	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jenneson	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
account	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Curless	I-pers
.	O
About	O
Christmas	O
day	O
Mrs.	O
Jenneson	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
Nine-pence	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
shilling	O
but	O
that	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
received	O
bad	O
money	O
of	O
Mrs	O
Jenneson	O
for	O
that	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jenneson	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
Ward	O
owned	O
the	O
bad	O
money	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
quarters	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
Andrews	O
slew	O
in	O
a	O
passion	O
,	O
he	O
knocked	O
my	O
son	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
away	O
the	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Curless	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Jenneson	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
witness	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
shilling	O
drop	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
hair	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Colonel	O
upon	O
guard	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
bad	O
shillings	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
a	O
justice	O
of	O
peace	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
engaged	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
there	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
identity	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
another	O
hand	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
325.	O
John	B-pers
Thrift	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Faris	I-pers
,	O
March	O
11	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Faris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
widow	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	O
Garvy	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
were	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Door	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
Patrick	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
said	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
David	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
Man	O
?	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
door	O
)	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
overheard	O
the	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
pack	O
of	O
Thieves	O
,	O
suppose	O
it	O
is	O
Jack	B-pers
Ketch	I-pers
,	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
?	O
Said	O
Patrick	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
offence	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
this	O
Farrel	O
in	O
the	O
Face	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
satisfied	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
without	O
sleeves	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
Cutlass	O
,	O
drawed	O
it	O
,	O
delivered	O
the	O
scaboard	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
then	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
Cole	O
yard	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Faris	I-pers
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
they	O
three	O
ran	O
;	O
he	O
pursued	O
them	O
cross	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
into	O
an	O
Arch-way	O
,	O
going	O
under	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
deceased	O
ran	O
forward	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
Side	O
of	O
his	O
Head	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
stick	O
and	O
kept	O
off	O
several	O
blows	O
from	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
till	O
his	O
foot	O
slipp	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Dung	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
cuts	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
about	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
confined	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Enoch	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
my	O
crying	O
out	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
which	O
hit	O
the	O
infant	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
stunn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
witness	O
was	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
loath	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Reb	O
.	O
Faris	O
.	O
They	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
book	O
to	O
swear	O
before	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
any	O
Questions	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
Justice	O
if	O
she	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
commit	O
her	O
directly	O
:	O
Then	O
I	O
swore	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
cutlass	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
examined	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
?	O
Reb	O
.	O
Faris	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
there	O
you	O
do	O
now	O
?	O
Reb	O
.	O
Faris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
consulted	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
you	O
do	O
now	O
?	O
Reb	O
.	O
Faris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
gave	O
my	O
husband	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
difference	O
between	O
what	O
you	O
said	O
then	O
and	O
now	O
?	O
Reb	O
.	O
Faris	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
struck	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
one	O
word	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
you	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
?	O
Reb	O
.	O
Faris	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
hear	O
something	O
like	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
reason	O
that	O
for	O
what	O
another	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
should	O
lose	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Garvey	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
Farrel	O
,	O
Farrel	O
said	O
something	O
about	O
Jack	B-pers
Ketch	I-pers
,	O
whose	O
wife	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
overheard	O
us	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
Thieves	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
murder	O
,	O
or	O
rob	O
us	O
?	O
She	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
towards	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
fell	O
a	O
beating	O
the	O
Man	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
blows	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Thrift	O
do	O
n't	O
strike	O
the	O
man	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
perhaps	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Then	O
somebody	O
hollowed	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
with	O
a	O
Hanger	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
striped	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
without	O
sleeves	O
I	O
stood	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
under	O
the	O
Arch-way	O
at	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
the	O
deceased	O
a	O
cut	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
or	O
cutlass	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
Faris	O
had	O
a	O
cane	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
keep	O
off	O
the	O
blows	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
struck	O
the	O
first	O
blow	O
?	O
Garvey	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
blow	O
struck	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
never	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
what	O
words	O
did	O
this	O
squabble	O
begin	O
?	O
Garvey	O
.	O
Farrel	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Jack	B-pers
Ketch	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
overheard	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
Newgate	O
?	O
Garvey	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
stood	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
attempted	O
to	O
strike	O
,	O
or	O
lift	O
up	O
his	O
Hand	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
I	O
'll	O
strike	O
you	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
Thrist	O
away	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
I	O
was	O
present	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Cole-yard	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
blackguard	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
look	O
at	O
me	O
for	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
had	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
do	O
look	O
at	O
you	O
,	O
Mistress	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
not	O
looking	O
at	O
you	O
for	O
any	O
harm	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
You	O
lie	O
,	O
you	O
Teague	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
do	O
n't	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
we	O
work	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
our	O
bread	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
behind	O
,	O
near	O
his	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
He	O
takes	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
fails	O
a	O
poking	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
:	O
Then	O
said	O
Timothy	B-pers
Garvey	I-pers
to	O
him	O
,	O
pray	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
young	O
Man	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
perhaps	O
he	O
may	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
Garvey	O
went	O
on	O
:	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
gone	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
,	O
we	O
looked	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
running	O
with	O
a	O
naked	O
Hanger	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
on	O
fast	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
coming	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
Gateway	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
overtook	O
us	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
Cane	O
to	O
save	O
himself	O
from	O
damage	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
several	O
blows	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
blow	O
over	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
cut	O
him	O
down	O
under	O
the	O
Gateway	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
two	O
blows	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
hanger	O
:	O
I	O
held	O
my	O
stick	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
middle	O
to	O
keep	O
off	O
the	O
blows	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
any	O
blows	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
words	O
did	O
this	O
fray	O
begin	O
upon	O
?	O
Farrel	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
words	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
told	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
nothing	O
said	O
by	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
spoke	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Farrel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
blackguard	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
look	O
at	O
me	O
for	O
?	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
words	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
mention	O
made	O
about	O
Newgate	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
?	O
Farrel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Without	O
any	O
provocation	O
at	O
all	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Recollect	O
yourself	O
whether	O
some	O
of	O
your	O
company	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
something	O
first	O
.	O
Farrel	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
as	O
thus	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
woman	O
?	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
is	O
Jack	B-pers
Ketch	I-pers
.	O
Then	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Jack	B-pers
Ketch	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
stolen	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
?	O
Farrel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
nobody	O
else	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clutton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Nine-pin	O
house	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
time	O
these	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
woman	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
last	O
Witness	O
call	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
whore	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
eternal	O
whore	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
He	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
a	O
scabbard	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Strutton	O
,	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
bring	O
such	O
a	O
weapon	O
out	O
to	O
naked	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
it	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
stripped	O
into	O
a	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
fight	O
them	O
manfully	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
overtook	O
these	O
men	O
,	O
he	O
that	O
hanged	O
the	O
last	O
prisoners	O
was	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
men	O
was	O
engaged	O
one	O
with	O
another	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
chopp	O
'd	O
one	O
over	O
the	O
Forehead	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
ran	O
fighting	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
Farrel	O
was	O
one	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
sticks	O
going	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
they	O
could	O
go	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Farrel	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
any	O
blows	O
?	O
you	O
hear	O
what	O
this	O
witness	O
says	O
.	O
Farrel	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
his	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
a	O
fighting	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
Farrel	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
who	O
began	O
the	O
quarrel	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
widow	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
fighting	O
?	O
Widow	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Waring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
men	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
just	O
pass	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
mob	O
about	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
was	O
off	O
before	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
and	O
unbuttoned	O
the	O
neck	O
of	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
men	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
the	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
thousand	O
People	O
about	O
them	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Enoch	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
bleeding	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
deceased	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
engaged	O
in	O
fighting	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
hanger	O
?	O
Waring	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Lisle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
facing	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Scymiter	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
follow	O
those	O
people	O
into	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
he	O
overtook	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
Gateway	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
three	O
cuts	O
at	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
is	O
dead	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
named	O
Farrel	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
white	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
crowd	O
of	O
people	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Farrel	O
making	O
strokes	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
man	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
first	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
arm	O
,	O
which	O
falling	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
got	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
bleedy	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
besieged	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
cut	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
heads	O
off	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Heastfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
of	O
Westminster	O
Infarmary	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
surgeon	O
dressed	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
cut	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
first	O
table	O
,	O
flesh	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
other	O
wounds	O
on	O
different	O
parts	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
wound	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
wrist	O
;	O
I	O
imagined	O
they	O
were	O
from	O
some	O
cutting	O
instrument	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
came	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
hurt	O
your	O
husband	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
hope	O
for	O
salvation	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dying	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
soon	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
eternity	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
wound	O
but	O
John	B-pers
Ketch	I-pers
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
die	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
my	O
friends	O
will	O
do	O
me	O
justice	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
wound	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
Enoch	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
owned	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
very	O
extraordinary	O
.	O
Two	O
days	O
before	O
the	O
deceased	O
died	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
seeing	O
him	O
speechless	O
,	O
Consider	O
,	O
hold	O
up	O
your	O
right	O
hand	O
if	O
Jack	B-pers
Thrist	I-pers
did	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
strange	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
side	O
.	O
Then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
consider	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
hold	O
up	O
your	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
shook	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
the	O
blow	O
.	O
Enoch	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
did	O
take	O
the	O
hanger	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
this	O
man	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
witnesses	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
prosecution	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sailor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
cut	O
the	O
deceased	O
several	O
strokes	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carrier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
strike	O
the	O
deceased	O
one	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
yards	O
distance	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
directly	O
opposite	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
stannel	O
waistcoat	O
without	O
sleeves	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
opposite	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
persons	O
engaged	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Thrist	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
deceased	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Boseen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
give	O
a	O
blow	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
Ann	B-pers
Boseen	I-pers
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
croud	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
strike	O
the	O
deceased	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
five	O
yards	O
off	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
strike	O
the	O
deceased	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
twice	O
at	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
church	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
through	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
Farrel	O
began	O
the	O
quarrel	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
wife	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
Coal-yard	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
.	O
Blood	O
and	O
ounds	O
,	O
said	O
Farrel	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
this	O
is	O
coming	O
along	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
Jack	B-pers
Ketch	I-pers
,	O
he	O
stole	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
go	O
along	O
,	O
you	O
black-guard	O
dog	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
ten	O
guineas	O
reward	O
for	O
taking	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Farrel	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
strove	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
stick	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
me	O
another	O
blow	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
hanger	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
declare	O
it	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
scabbard	O
,	O
till	O
Enoch	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Elliet	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Coal-yard	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
men	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
there	O
.	O
One	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
man	O
?	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
answered	O
,	O
no	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
Jack	B-pers
Ketch	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
Thrift	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
want	O
him	O
,	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
stick	O
by	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
intending	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
fetched	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hands	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
put	O
down	O
your	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
fight	O
me	O
like	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
Then	O
Enoch	O
Stock	O
coming	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
help	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
killed	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
snatch	O
'd	O
the	O
hanger	O
out	O
of	O
Thrift	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
fought	O
his	O
way	O
through	O
the	O
mob	O
to	O
Short's-gardens	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
fighting	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
fight	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
hanger	O
from	O
Enoch	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Enoch	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
bleeding	O
in	O
a	O
sad	O
manner	O
,	O
which	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
sticks	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
washed	O
his	O
wounds	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
reek	O
go	O
against	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
fighting	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
trouble	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
business	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Enoch	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
wig	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
lost	O
it	O
then	O
.	O
Patience	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
this	O
squabble	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
men	O
with	O
sticks	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
;	O
they	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
knock	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
brains	O
out	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
ran	O
behind	O
some	O
women	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
killed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
hanger	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
out	O
not	O
drawn	O
.	O
They	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
down	O
,	O
then	O
Enoch	O
Stock	O
snatched	O
the	O
hanger	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
under	O
the	O
gate-way	O
at	O
Short	O
's	O
gardens	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
cutting	O
at	O
some	O
body	O
,	O
they	O
with	O
sticks	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
changed	O
three	O
words	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Collison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
three	O
men	O
fighting	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
Enoch	O
Stock	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
they	O
fought	O
with	O
sticks	O
blow	O
for	O
blow	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
Enoch	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
Enoch	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Irishmen	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
Stock	O
pulled	O
his	O
coat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Garbey	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
at	O
,	O
you	O
fool	O
?	O
He	O
then	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
the	O
deceased	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
behind	O
Enoch	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
croud	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
some	O
men	O
fighting	O
with	O
sticks	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
hanger	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
swear	O
he	O
'd	O
cut	O
Jack	O
Ketch	O
's	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
Short's-gardens	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Call	O
Enoch	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
call	O
him	O
for	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
knows	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
owned	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
We	O
shall	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
that	O
question	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
'll	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
here	O
.	O
Enoch	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
standing	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
mob	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
gate-way	O
near	O
Short's-gardens	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
thieves	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
murder	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
beating	O
him	O
with	O
sticks	O
,	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
help	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
these	O
rogues	O
will	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
nineteen	O
or	O
twenty	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
hit	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
stood	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
They	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
my	O
head	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
also	O
my	O
little	O
finger	O
in	O
defending	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
stunned	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
my	O
senses	O
;	O
I	O
strove	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
hanging	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
shoulder	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
his	O
shirt	O
all	O
bloody	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
hanger	O
?	O
Stock	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
I	O
got	O
way	O
,	O
they	O
beat	O
me	O
so	O
unmercifully	O
.	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
night	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
below	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
had	O
received	O
his	O
death	O
's	O
wound	O
,	O
all	O
over	O
blood	O
:	O
I	O
offered	O
the	O
woman	O
the	O
book	O
to	O
swear	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
was	O
sworn	O
;	O
all	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
,	O
A	O
man	O
,	O
whom	O
they	O
call	O
Jack	B-pers
Ketch	I-pers
,	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
husband	O
this	O
wound	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
over	O
and	O
over	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
repeating	O
that	O
often	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
told	O
it	O
was	O
Jack	B-pers
Ketch	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
himself	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
grant	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
a	O
violent	O
assault	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
granted	O
a	O
warrant	O
on	O
that	O
occasion	O
already	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
grant	O
cross	O
warrants	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
best	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
himself	O
bail	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
surrender	O
himself	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
surgeon	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
not	O
likely	O
to	O
recover	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
refused	O
bail	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
positive	O
oath	O
against	O
Enoch	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
committed	O
him	O
too	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
surrender	O
himself	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
surrender	O
himself	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
walk	O
before	O
me	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
amob	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
walk	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
326.	O
Jane	B-pers
Stow	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
35	O
ells	O
of	O
linnen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
327.	O
Silver	B-pers
Strice	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
March	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
328	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
329.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clory	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
54	O
yards	O
of	O
paduasuoy	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Haycock	I-pers
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
20	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
330.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
upon	O
Samuel	B-pers
Fancourt	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
stick	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
331.	O
James	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Mar	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
332.	O
John	B-pers
Copless	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
:	O
He	O
also	O
stood	O
charged	O
upon	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
Accidental	O
Death	O
.	O
333	O
.	O
334	O
.	O
335.	O
John	B-pers
Giddis	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beesley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Hudd	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
two-pence	O
half-penny	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hudd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Sawyer	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
,	O
a	O
Coach-maker	O
in	O
Long-acre	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
sawing	O
at	O
Aberstock-fields	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
half-way	B-place
house	I-place
and	O
Pancras-church	B-place
:	O
John	B-pers
Giddis	I-pers
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
moved	O
or	O
stir	O
'd	O
he	O
'd	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
man	O
Smith	O
unbuttoned	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
all	O
my	O
pockets	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
two-pence	O
half	O
penny	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
Giddis	O
said	O
take	O
him	O
out	O
below	O
,	O
meaning	O
my	O
buckles	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
but	O
white	O
metal	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
Beesley	O
was	O
a	O
distance	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
turned	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
saw	O
the	O
thing	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
running	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
are	O
you	O
come	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
pursue	O
them	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
follow	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
stout	O
man	O
but	O
lame	O
)	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
fight	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Hen	O
.	O
James	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
ditching	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Brill	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
coming	O
along	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
Carpenter	O
the	O
other	O
night	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
and	O
whistled	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
sat	O
down	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
woman	O
asked	O
them	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
point	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
then	O
we	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
robbing	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
assist	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
said	O
my	O
partner	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
very	O
near	O
them	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
coming	O
away	O
unconcerned	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
are	O
you	O
coming	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
