TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
24th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1749	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
John	B-pers
Blachford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1750	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	B-pers
BLACHFORD	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
LEE	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLIVE	I-pers
,	O
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Erick	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Shamalt	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lerkin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Longden	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Skert	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Howse	I-pers
,	O
Gerviss	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Both	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Ashworth	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hugget	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
*	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
*	O
William	O
King	O
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Woolridge	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Vanleat	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sugar	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Roby	I-pers
.	O
617	O
,	O
618.	O
Edward	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
ginger	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
October	O
1	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Gangs-man	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
landing	O
goods	O
at	O
Wigins	O
's	O
Key	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
goods	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Sugars	O
and	O
ginger	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
constables	O
,	O
Emerson	O
and	O
Clark	O
,	O
each	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
ginger	O
from	O
each	O
man	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
the	O
prisoners	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
like	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
subpoena	O
'd	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
two	O
sorts	O
of	O
ginger	O
,	O
black	O
and	O
white	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
black	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
landing	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
;	O
the	O
bags	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
ginger	O
came	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
an	O
indifferent	O
condition	O
,	O
having	O
holes	O
in	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Emerson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
the	O
stations	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Evans	O
standing	O
pretty	O
near	O
the	O
bags	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
partner	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Evans	O
set	O
himself	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
pilfering	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
some	O
ginger	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
Potts	O
came	O
and	O
did	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
directly	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
common	O
way	O
of	O
such	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
about	O
a	O
pound	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
and	O
unload	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
again	O
may	O
be	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
times	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
black	O
ginger	O
from	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
bag	O
was	O
whole	O
before	O
;	O
we	O
observed	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
where	O
the	O
ginger	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
Potts	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
there	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Emerson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
landing	O
goods	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
each	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
on	O
this	O
bag	O
by	O
turns	O
,	O
and	O
filling	O
their	O
pockets	O
with	O
ginger	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
begged	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
sent	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
way	O
of	O
living	O
than	O
this	O
.	O
Evans	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
ginger	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Potts	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Clark	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
ginger	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
take	O
ginger	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
some	O
planks	O
very	O
near	O
them	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
619.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wellam	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
September	O
17	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
last	O
September	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
breeches	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
betwixt	O
sleep	O
and	O
awake	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
.	O
He	O
disturbed	O
me	O
by	O
taking	O
the	O
breeches	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
breeches	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
nothing	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Turk	B-place
's	I-place
Bagnio	I-place
,	I-place
Charing	I-place
Cross	I-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
he	O
;	O
we	O
lay	O
both	O
in	O
one	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
two	O
different	O
beds	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
money	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
four	O
shillings	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
just	O
made	O
up	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Sophia	B-pers
Lennoy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
bring	O
the	O
prisoner	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
of	O
the	O
porter	O
that	O
afternoon	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
being	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
stuff	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
away	O
about	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
burning	O
at	O
his	O
bed	O
's	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
telling	O
it	O
over	O
;	O
he	O
jumped	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
picking	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
of	O
yours	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
purse	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
over	O
some	O
gold	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
beat	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
beating	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
me	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
books	O
,	O
and	O
attend	O
in	O
the	O
Bagnio	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
under	O
porter	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
620.	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brown	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Demock	I-pers
,	O
February	O
11	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Demock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
horse	O
of	O
a	O
brown	O
colour	O
,	O
about	O
14	O
hands	O
and	O
an	O
inch	O
,	O
at	O
grass	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Glasby	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Rosemary	B-place
Branch	I-place
,	I-place
Islington	I-place
;	O
he	O
was	O
missing	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
February	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Glasby	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Rosemary	O
Branch	O
,	O
Islington	O
.	O
This	O
horse	O
was	O
at	O
grass	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
ground	O
either	O
the	O
10th	O
or	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
the	O
10th	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
corn	O
scattered	O
about	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
we	O
supposed	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
catch	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
hard	O
to	O
be	O
catched	O
.	O
Q.	O
Whhat	O
colour	O
was	O
he	O
?	O
Glasby	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
mouse-brown	O
colour	O
,	O
about	O
14	O
hands	O
and	O
an	O
inch	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
better	O
;	O
comes	O
five	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
gelding	O
?	O
Glasby	O
.	O
A	O
gelding	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
ground	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Glasby	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
there	O
owned	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Punnet	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
offered	O
to	O
sale	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Bell	O
,	O
near	O
Rochester	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
horse	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Punnet	O
,	O
an	O
attorney	O
at	O
law	O
,	O
at	O
Maidstone	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
for	O
seven	O
guineas	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Punnet	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
horse	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
[	O
he	O
answers	O
to	O
the	O
description	O
before	O
given	O
]	O
for	O
seven	O
guineas	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
liked	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
another	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Punnet	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
name	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
horse	O
once	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Welchman	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
travel	O
that	O
way	O
with	O
bullocks	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
him	O
?	O
Punnet	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
Mr.	O
Glasby	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
demand	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
such	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
mayor	O
of	O
Rochester	O
,	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
his	O
six	O
months	O
before	O
.	O
But	O
this	O
seems	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
mistake	O
,	O
not	O
done	O
with	O
any	O
design	O
;	O
it	O
appears	O
this	O
horse	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Demock	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Glasby	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
horse	O
you	O
say	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Demock	O
's	O
property	O
?	O
Glasby	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Demock	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
ground	O
now	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Demock	O
,	O
Was	O
that	O
your	O
horse	O
Mr.	O
Glasby	O
brought	O
to	O
your	O
door	O
?	O
Demock	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Glasby	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
swear	O
this	O
horse	O
was	O
yours	O
?	O
Glasby	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
read	O
the	O
affidavit	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
7	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
for	O
this	O
horse	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
:	O
Richard	B-pers
Ribalt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
inn-keeper	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
coming	O
with	O
Welch	O
cattle	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
into	O
Kent	O
.	O
His	O
brother	O
is	O
a	O
drover	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
have	O
dealt	O
in	O
horses	O
;	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
up	O
with	O
their	O
beasts	O
often	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
,	O
or	O
heard	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
621.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Robert	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
buttons	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
salt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
five	O
large	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
one	O
quart	O
silver	O
cup	O
,	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
two	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
one	O
Alapeen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
strainer	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
spurs	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
sheets	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Garnet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
September	O
21	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Garnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
cup	O
,	O
five	O
large	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
four	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
strainer	O
and	O
tongs	O
,	O
a	O
marrow	O
spoon	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
buttons	O
,	O
one	O
garnet	O
ring	O
,	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
spurs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
sheets	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
other	O
new	O
flaxen	O
sheets	O
,	O
six	O
damask	O
napkins	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
three	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
some	O
pillow-biers	O
,	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
cloaths	O
of	O
my	O
son	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
Alapeen	O
waistcoat	O
besides	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
all	O
these	O
goods	O
?	O
Garnet	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Woodstreet	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
The	O
silver	O
is	O
all	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
cypher	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
your	O
servant	O
?	O
Garnet	O
.	O
Between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
wife	O
?	O
Garnet	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
other	O
servant	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
My	O
son	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Russel-court	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
several	O
things	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
to	O
pledge	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Garnet	O
.	O
The	O
silver	O
cup	O
,	O
gold	O
buttons	O
,	O
several	O
spoons	O
,	O
the	O
rings	O
and	O
cloaths	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
rings	O
and	O
buttons	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
had	O
them	O
before	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
rings	O
and	O
buttons	O
?	O
Garnet	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
.	O
Alison	O
.	O
The	O
cloaths	O
she	O
pawned	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Alison	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
in	O
Lambeth	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Garnet	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
had	O
pledged	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Garnet	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Holland	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
flaxen	O
sheets	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
gold	O
buttons	O
several	O
times	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
spurs	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Garnet	I-pers
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
daughter	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
daughter	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
,	O
my	O
daughter	O
has	O
been	O
married	O
seven	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Fell	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
her	O
divers	O
questions	O
about	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
once	O
she	O
must	O
bring	O
a	O
quart	O
mug	O
.	O
We	O
said	O
we	O
must	O
go	O
and	O
ask	O
her	O
master	O
first	O
about	O
that	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
master	O
had	O
done	O
without	O
sending	O
that	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
suspected	O
her	O
she	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
?	O
Fell	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Fell	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Haslewood	O
street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
,	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rawlings	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
buttons	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
away	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
brought	O
several	O
things	O
since	O
;	O
she	O
once	O
brought	O
some	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
redeemed	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
shirt	O
;	O
she	O
also	O
brought	O
,	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
,	O
a	O
marrow-spoon	O
,	O
two	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
strainer	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Garnet	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
care	O
?	O
Garnet	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
the	O
keeping	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
.	O
I	O
once	O
missed	O
the	O
cup	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
once	O
missed	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
put	O
before	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
Thus	O
I	O
was	O
deceived	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
three	O
pawnbrokers	O
houses	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
pawned	O
was	O
for	O
money	O
for	O
housekeeping	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
say	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
you	O
had	O
before	O
?	O
when	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
say	O
,	O
why	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
money	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
money	O
's	O
worth	O
in	O
your	O
hands	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
give	O
these	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
?	O
Garnet	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
are	O
people	O
now	O
in	O
court	O
know	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
better	O
reputation	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
622	O
,	O
623.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
and	O
Phillis	B-pers
Baird	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
cotton	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
ruffled	O
,	O
one	O
dowlas	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
huckaback	O
tablecloth	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
October	O
6	O
.	O
John	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Queen-street	B-place
,	I-place
Wapping	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coal-heaver	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
my	O
own	O
chest	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Joshua	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Baird	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
under	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
left	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
iron	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Nichols	O
swore	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
small	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
in	O
John	O
Brown	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
Phillis	B-pers
Baird	I-pers
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
things	O
away	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
things	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
these	O
things	O
mentioned	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
betwixt	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
his	O
chest	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
candle	O
burning	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
up	O
;	O
they	O
never	O
owned	O
to	O
their	O
having	O
the	O
goods	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
then	O
Hannah	O
Nichols	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Phillis	B-pers
Baird	I-pers
took	O
them	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
accordingly	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
caps	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
cotton	O
shirts	O
belong	O
to	O
Joshua	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
he	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
are	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
two	O
aprons	O
found	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
they	O
worth	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
about	O
2	O
s.	O
John	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
to	O
Nichols	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
before-mentioned	O
.	O
Baird	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
some	O
things	O
at	O
my	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
wash	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
by	O
mistake	O
,	O
took	O
more	O
than	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
J	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
not	O
left	O
a	O
stitch	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
wash.	O
Nichols	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Phillis	B-pers
Baird	I-pers
to	O
take	O
a	O
lodging	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
things	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
three	O
caps	O
to	O
iron	O
.	O
I	O
get	O
my	O
bread	O
by	O
washing	O
and	O
ironing	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
624.	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Scarr	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
pillow	O
bier	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodgings	O
,	O
September	O
24	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Denmark-street	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
away	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pillow-bier	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
then	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
;	O
she	O
never	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
pillow-bier	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sheets	O
was	O
marked	O
with	O
S.	O
Both	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
is	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
in	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
she	O
remained	O
there	O
but	O
a	O
week	O
and	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
day	O
my	O
mother	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
sheets	O
were	O
gone	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
directions	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Holms	O
's	O
Ratcliff	O
Highway	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
in	O
Bell-yard	O
,	O
White-chapel	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
husband	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
fetched	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
625.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thursel	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Layland	I-pers
,	O
September	O
30	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Layland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
go	O
with	O
milk	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
our	O
child	O
;	O
coming	O
home	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
her	O
mother	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
;	O
her	O
mother	O
had	O
got	O
information	O
she	O
was	O
met	O
going	O
towards	O
Newington	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
child	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
put	O
in	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
garret	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
child	O
crying	O
,	O
all	O
black	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
weakened	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
lies	O
in	O
a	O
dangerous	O
way	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
drawer	O
to	O
examine	O
my	O
cow-keeper	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
but	O
23	O
s.	O
instead	O
of	O
45	O
or	O
46	O
s.	O
I	O
pay	O
my	O
cow-man	O
every	O
Monday	O
morning	O
.	O
Besides	O
this	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
7	O
l.	O
all	O
but	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
15	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cow-keeper	O
's	O
money	O
she	O
took	O
upwards	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
again	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
told	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
with	O
two	O
girls	O
to	O
Cold	O
Bath-fields	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
meet	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
her	O
towards	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
gate	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
all	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
reckon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
wrapt	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
step	O
that	O
goes	O
up	O
into	O
Faulcon-court	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
place	O
near	O
our	O
own	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
something	O
above	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
about	O
14	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
my	O
own	O
fire	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
hear	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
the	O
girl	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
very	O
much	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
thought	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
where	O
to	O
have	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
girl	O
away	O
towards	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
much	O
desired	O
her	O
mother	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
still	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
quite	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Her	O
mother	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
girl	O
tell	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Bridewell-gate	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
master	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
put	O
me	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
confess	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
drew	O
the	O
staple	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
a	O
post	O
at	O
the	O
steps	O
going	O
down	O
Faulcon-court	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Woodward	O
Harlow	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
girl	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
threatning	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
persuading	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
confess	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
from	O
Bridewell-gate	O
to	O
our	O
shuffleboard-room	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
girl	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
step	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
in	O
coming	O
back	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
good-natured	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
trouble	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
now	O
would	O
put	O
me	O
to	O
trouble	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
her	O
master	O
had	O
ravished	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
foul	O
disease	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
our	O
bed	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
once	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
pulled	O
her	O
into	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
ravishing	O
her	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
time	O
the	O
girl	O
indeed	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
her	O
master	O
promised	O
not	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
gaol	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
;	O
this	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
face	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
girl	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
Isabella	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
drawers	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
open	O
where	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
money	O
out	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
so	O
inclined	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
above	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
half-pence	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
declared	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
likewise	O
her	O
master	O
had	O
used	O
her	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
this	O
money	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
her	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
distemper	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
say	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
House	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
often	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
her	O
nor	O
heard	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Alcock	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
these	O
five	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Acquit	O
.	O
626.	O
Sarah	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
10	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
North	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
this	O
spoon	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
husband	O
works	O
with	O
mine	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
few	O
broth	O
in	O
a	O
bason	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
and	O
eat	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
wooden	O
spoon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
the	O
bason	O
down	O
and	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
silver	O
spoon	O
that	O
lay	O
near	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
tuesday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
detect	O
her	O
?	O
George	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
North	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
North	O
came	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
rout	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
she	O
was	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
pluck	O
out	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
my	O
story	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
North	O
's	O
mending	O
her	O
servant	O
's	O
gown	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
broth	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
eaten	O
them	O
a	O
few	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
eat	O
them	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
bason	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
wooden	O
spoon	O
down	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
other	O
;	O
that	O
last	O
witness	O
stood	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
room	O
and	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
why	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
follow	O
me	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
when	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
that	O
witness	O
says	O
;	O
I	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
North	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
money	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
talks	O
of	O
?	O
Grace	B-pers
North	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
but	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
627.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Duglass	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
promissory	O
note	O
for	O
108	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
bearing	O
date	O
Jan.	O
3	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
purses	O
,	O
one	O
with	O
three	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matth.ias	B-pers
Palling	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Matthias	O
,	O
Sep.	O
24	O
.	O
Matthias	B-pers
Palling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
oil	O
way	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
hand	O
desk	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
compting-house	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
supper	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
servant	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
desk	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
a	O
yearly	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
inquiry	O
possible	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
two	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
draught	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
drawn	O
upon	O
Freame	O
and	O
Barcley	O
,	O
bankers	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Steven	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
payable	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
or	O
bearer	O
,	O
that	O
bore	O
date	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
stopped	O
payment	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
filed	O
it	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
papers	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
o'clock	O
they	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
they	O
got	O
my	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
believed	O
my	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Describe	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
desk	O
when	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Palling	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
this	O
note	O
for	O
108	O
l.	O
13	O
s.	O
payable	O
to	O
me	O
ten	O
months	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
dated	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Jan.	O
1750	O
,	O
witness	O
John	B-pers
Dodbonel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dupree	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
purses	O
with	O
money	O
in	O
each	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
much	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
other	O
bills	O
and	O
notes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
justly	O
what	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
purse	O
with	O
three	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
halfpence	O
in	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
the	O
two	O
purses	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
compting	O
house	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
dwelling	O
house	O
?	O
Palling	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
under	O
the	O
same	O
roof	O
with	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
the	O
court	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Palling	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
Mess	O
.	O
Freame	O
and	O
Barcley	O
's	O
sending	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
telling	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
believed	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
me	O
;	O
immediately	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
draught	O
:	O
they	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
Unless	O
you	O
show	O
me	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
gave	O
you	O
this	O
draught	O
I	O
'll	O
prosecute	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
ship	O
at	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
witness	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
note	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
ale-house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
neither	O
a	O
warrant	O
or	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
let	O
us	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
he	O
refus	O
'd	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
let	O
the	O
porter	O
go	O
up	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
detected	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fly	O
for	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
people	O
out	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
struggle	O
with	O
the	O
landlord	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
over	O
the	O
houses	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
dock	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
some	O
coal	O
lighters	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
wharf	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
By	O
that	O
time	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
whom	O
we	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
without	O
that	O
he	O
delivered	O
me	O
up	O
one	O
purse	O
with	O
three	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
draught	O
upon	O
Freame	O
and	O
Bercley	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
These	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
notes	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
bills	O
and	O
other	O
papers	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
wrap	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
sew	O
'd	O
together	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
writing	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
with	O
the	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
The	O
note	O
John	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Duperee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
were	O
he	O
lay	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
many	O
more	O
papers	O
all	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
desk	O
had	O
nothing	O
on	O
it	O
but	O
the	O
two	O
locks	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
directed	O
that	O
parcel	O
?	O
Palling	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Richards	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
an	O
indorsement	O
on	O
the	O
note	O
?	O
Palling	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Palling	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
banker	O
since	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hartshorne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Palling	O
's	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
by	O
his	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
above	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
before	O
Mess	O
.	O
Freame	O
and	O
Barcley	O
's	O
servant	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Palling	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
watchman	O
we	O
were	O
inform	O
'd	O
afterwards	O
;	O
we	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
he	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Palling	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Newman	O
I	O
believe	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
,	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
ship	O
alehouse	O
by	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
bridge	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
we	O
imagin	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
below	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
refused	O
us	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Hartshorne	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
I	O
think	O
is	O
Bercley	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
and	O
would	O
do	O
as	O
he	O
pleas	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
watchman	O
go	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
fetch	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
had	O
the	O
note	O
then	O
;	O
we	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
constable	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
enquiring	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
backwards	O
,	O
so	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
coal	O
barges	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
another	O
publick	O
house	O
just	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
arms	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
deliver	O
'd	O
up	O
two	O
purses	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Palling	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
guineas	O
in	O
one	O
green	O
purse	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
there	O
were	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
silver	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
crooked	O
shilling	O
amongst	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
where	O
we	O
first	O
went	O
to	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
little	O
desk	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
papers	O
sow	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
108	O
l.	O
odd	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
joint	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
.	O
Twice	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
stole	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Palling	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
persuaded	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
a	O
soldier	O
that	O
lives	O
in	O
Charles-street	O
Westminster	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
brother	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
this	O
thing	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
after	O
that	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
whom	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Cannan	O
,	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
who	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
was	O
easily	O
persuaded	O
,	O
brought	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
shut	O
too	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
again	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
brought	O
a	O
hammer	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Galway	O
in	O
Scotland	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
that	O
lad	O
from	O
his	O
Infancy	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
lad	O
,	O
a	O
fair	O
character	O
till	O
this	O
unfortunate	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
here	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
this	O
summer	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
Waite	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Blowbladder-street	O
at	O
the	O
Acorn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
woollen-draper	O
,	O
he	O
served	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
a	O
porter	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
extreme	O
well	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
trusted	O
him	O
frequently	O
with	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
fellow	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-le-grand	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
me	O
through	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
a	O
brother	O
of	O
his	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
Jamaica	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Waite	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Galway	O
in	O
Scotland	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
have	O
staid	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Curry	O
of	O
that	O
town	O
sent	O
up	O
his	O
son	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
into	O
some	O
business	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
about	O
last	O
April	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
628.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Boswel	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	I-pers
widow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
fustian	O
,	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
one	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mullings	I-pers
,	O
October	O
4	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mullings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Crown-court	B-place
,	I-place
Butcher-hall	I-place
lane	I-place
.	O
The	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
some	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
this	O
woman	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
you	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
giving	O
her	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Mullings	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
3	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
stop	O
to	O
drink	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
?	O
Mullings	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
She	O
began	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
she	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
more	O
till	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
and	O
knocked	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
seven	O
,	O
[	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
]	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
her	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
return	O
for	O
running	O
away	O
with	O
my	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
might	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
dram	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
never	O
drank	O
a	O
dram	O
in	O
a	O
morning	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
you	O
shall	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
dressed	O
myself	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Mullings	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
nursing	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
that	O
was	O
sick	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
ten	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
that	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
says	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
double	O
locked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
the	O
whole	O
house	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Mullings	O
.	O
Only	O
a	O
lower	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
let	O
out	O
in	O
tenements	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
staple	O
burst	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
was	O
broke	O
with	O
forcing	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
my	O
neighbour	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
naming	O
her	O
name	O
)	O
had	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
gown	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
before	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Mention	O
what	O
goods	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Mullings	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
blue	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
short	O
cloak	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
which	O
she	O
has	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
four	O
caps	O
(	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
brandy	O
shop	O
near	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
out	O
there	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
room	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
he	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Mullings	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
Lime-street	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
to	O
Newington-green	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
porter	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
again	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
Goldsmith's-hall	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
at	O
Harris	O
's	O
in	O
St.	O
Bride's-lane	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
white	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
St.	O
Bride's-lane	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
blue	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
fustian	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
linen	O
apron	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Mullings	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Crown-court	O
,	O
Butcher-hall-lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
fourth	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Mullings	O
go	O
out	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
red	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
she	O
carried	O
it	O
before	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
of	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
betwixt	O
Mr.	O
Mullings	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
going	O
out	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Nichols	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
full	O
half	O
hour	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
of	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
barber	O
and	O
perriwig-maker	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
unfortunate	O
girl	O
;	O
he	O
carried	O
me	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
white	O
gown	O
;	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
dagged	O
at	O
the	O
tail	O
[	O
she	O
takes	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
looks	O
on	O
it	O
]	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
fustian	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
carried	O
me	O
home	O
nights	O
after	O
nights	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
lain	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Bride's-lane	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
That	O
milk-woman	O
saw	O
me	O
carry	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gown	O
he	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
.	O
He	O
broke	O
a	O
glass	O
in	O
pulling	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
locked	O
me	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
four	O
hours	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
poker	O
and	O
drew	O
the	O
staple	O
and	O
let	O
myself	O
out	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
no	O
witnesses	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
or	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
looking-glass	O
was	O
hanging	O
up	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
629.	O
Anne	B-pers
Burgamy	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Anne	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Simms	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
necklace	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
punch-ladle	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Darker	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
September	O
19	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hosier-lane	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Hannah	B-pers
Darker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
two	O
persons	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
our	O
house	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
lodger	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
means	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
away	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Darker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
lodger	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
missed	O
7	O
s.	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
character	O
of	O
her	O
since	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
she	O
confessed	O
taking	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
She	O
sold	O
the	O
necklace	O
to	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
20th	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Anna	B-pers
Maria	I-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
(	O
mentioning	O
each	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
necklace	O
and	O
seal	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Merry	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Merry	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
by	O
Smithfield-bars	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
gold	O
necklace	O
weighed	O
five	O
pennyweights	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
19	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
seal	O
weighed	O
18	O
grains	O
stone	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
3	O
s	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
ladle	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
but	O
sent	O
his	O
affidavit	O
concerning	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
confederate	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
gold	O
necklace	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
told	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
gold	O
seal	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
confederate	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
many	O
things	O
while	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
drawers	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
630.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
tea	O
and	O
a	O
diaper	O
napkin	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
631.	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Bedkey	I-pers
,	O
October	O
2	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Bedkey	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Augustus	B-pers
Shoot	I-pers
,	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
Rolls	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
this	O
summer	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
from	O
my	O
neighbours	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
taken	O
in	O
my	O
rooms	O
in	O
Grosvenor-square	O
,	O
Chandler's-street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
spoons	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
bosom	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Coals	I-pers
.	O
October	O
the	O
second	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
her	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
these	O
spoons	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
One	O
Mary	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
spoons	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
hunted	O
about	O
for	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
husband	O
lived	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
632.	O
Matth.ias	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foscue	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
one	O
linen	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
twelve	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
September	O
22	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
each	O
witness	O
might	O
be	O
examined	O
apart	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
accordingly	O
done	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foscue	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
turnips	O
;	O
about	O
half	B-place
a	I-place
mile	I-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
other	I-place
side	I-place
Paddington	I-place
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
stopped	O
me	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
stopped	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
halfpence	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
turnpike	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
stirred	O
an	O
inch	O
he	O
'd	O
shoot	O
me	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
stick	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
bag	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
your	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
with	O
this	O
mop-stick	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
witness	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
purse	O
?	O
Foscue	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
twelve	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
half-pence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
discern	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Foscue	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
above	O
a	O
pole	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
stick	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
head	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struck	O
so	O
fierce	O
at	O
me	O
his	O
stick	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
that	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
Robert	O
Hargood	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
we	O
bound	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
hands	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
away	O
to	O
Paddington	O
:	O
there	O
we	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
o'clock	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
time	O
two	O
milkmen	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
has	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hargood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
cart	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
drove	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
Foscue	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
half-pence	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
your	O
coat	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
shoot	O
you	O
dead	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
shoot	O
him	O
dead	O
three	O
times	O
over	O
)	O
then	O
Foscue	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
was	O
uppermost	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
underneath	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Paddington	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
daunted	O
him	O
more	O
than	O
when	O
Foscue	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
the	O
bag	O
nor	O
money	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
witness	O
here	O
who	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
a	O
vial	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
stuff	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
black	O
the	O
stick	O
and	O
make	O
it	O
shine	O
like	O
a	O
gun	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
up	O
without	O
carrying	O
him	O
any	O
farther	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hanged	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
?	O
Hargood	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
too	O
dark	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
that	O
blow	O
had	O
hit	O
Foscue	O
he	O
'd	O
never	O
have	O
known	O
who	O
hurted	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
lanthorn	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
Paddington	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
flower	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
for	O
by	O
tumbling	O
about	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
near	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
purse	O
and	O
four-pence	O
halfpenny	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
farthings	O
among	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
likewise	O
a	O
vial	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
kept	O
oil	O
for	O
his	O
piece	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
The	O
purse	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
purse	O
open	O
?	O
Foscue	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Price	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
the	O
three	O
mile	O
stone	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
dust	O
and	O
gravel	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
more	O
money	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Quinn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
at	O
Paddington	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
in	O
Marybone	O
parish	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
long	O
case-knif	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
he	O
had	O
stopped	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
with	O
a	O
nod	O
towards	O
his	O
stick	O
,	O
his	O
hands	O
being	O
tied	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
gun	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
go	O
and	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
find	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
money	O
too	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
Paddington	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
complaining	O
how	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
strike	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
blow	O
had	O
hit	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
here	O
to	O
have	O
told	O
who	O
hurted	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
bag	O
was	O
shewn	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
cows	O
that	O
lie	O
at	O
grass	O
at	O
Kilbourne	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
dog	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cart	O
stop	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
hearing	O
some	O
words	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
cart	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
heard	O
words	O
increase	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
either	O
a	O
cart	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
or	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
say	O
get	O
down	O
,	O
get	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
'll	O
shoot	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
ran	O
on	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
the	O
soldier	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
crying	O
out	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
the	O
countryman	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
has	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
them	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
Paddington	O
,	O
and	O
charge	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
soldier	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
little	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
use	O
him	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hanged	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
them	O
to	O
hang	O
him	O
up	O
then	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
life	O
was	O
a	O
misery	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Turk's-head	O
near	O
Clerkenwell-green	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
lives	O
at	O
Kingsbury-green	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
matter	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
link	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
light	O
myself	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Marybone	O
,	O
there	O
it	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
Paddington	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
that	O
and	O
Kilbourne	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
return	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
that	O
mop-stick	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
keep	O
me	O
from	O
falling	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
fight	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
bottle	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
robbing	O
the	O
man	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
beat	O
and	O
abus	O
'd	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
hang	O
me	O
outright	O
,	O
than	O
use	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
fear	O
hanging	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
bears	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
633.	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matth.ias	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
2	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
634.	O
Ann	B-pers
Standing	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
635.	O
Judith	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
gloves	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
hood	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cambrick	O
ruffles	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bisben	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
10	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bisben	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	B-place
of	I-place
Wild-street	I-place
in	I-place
Steward	I-place
's	I-place
Rents	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
on	O
wednesday	O
last	O
about	O
3	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
shifts	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
yard	O
hanging	O
upon	O
a	O
line	O
,	O
two	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
horse	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
trunk	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
hood	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
Fox	O
Lane	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
last	O
wednesday	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
trunk	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
facing	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
by	O
sight	O
;	O
we	O
enquir	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
directed	O
us	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
gave	O
her	O
them	O
in	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
things	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
these	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
tax	O
'd	O
me	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
need	O
not	O
break	O
open	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
636.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Hore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
11	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barber	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Lickapon-street	B-place
,	I-place
one	I-place
end	I-place
of	I-place
it	I-place
comes	I-place
into	I-place
Leather-lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
shaving	O
a	O
gentleman	O
last	O
thursday	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
my	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
trip	O
along	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
pretty	O
suddenly	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
after	O
some	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
now	O
remember	O
,	O
whether	O
they	O
d	O
id	O
not	O
live	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
know	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
here	O
.	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
under	O
your	O
cloak	O
;	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
new	O
shoes	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sparks	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
was	O
shaving	O
,	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
as	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
engag	O
'd	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
forgive	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
other	O
people	O
's	O
apartments	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
necessity	O
that	O
drove	O
her	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
child	O
wanting	O
bread	O
.	O
She	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
her	O
father	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Young	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
above	O
stairs	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
shoes	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
were	O
hanging	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
fuddled	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
months	O
gone	O
with	O
child	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
husband	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
637.	O
George	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
ribon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
good	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Thwaites	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
8	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Thwaites	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Portland-street	B-place
by	I-place
Soho	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
and	O
sell	O
stockings	O
,	O
ribons	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
Aug.	O
8th	O
.	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
figur	O
'd	O
ribons	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
sell	O
such	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
allow	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
more	O
fashionable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
behind	O
my	O
counter	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
many	O
others	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
pause	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
I	O
may	O
buy	O
some	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
chose	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
belonging	O
to	O
him	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
John	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
one	O
drawer	O
,	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
difficult	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
another	O
,	O
still	O
he	O
was	O
difficult	O
in	O
the	O
colour	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
some	O
look	O
'd	O
watery	O
,	O
some	O
were	O
flimsy	O
.	O
Thus	O
I	O
had	O
five	O
drawers	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
satin	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
of	O
paduasoy	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
dress	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
mistrust	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
dress	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
trim	O
'd	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
other	O
things	O
answerable	O
:	O
he	O
bought	O
4	O
single	O
yards	O
of	O
paduasoy	O
,	O
at	O
7	O
d.	O
halfpeny	O
per	O
yard	O
,	O
of	O
three	O
different	O
colours	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
at	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
change	O
his	O
money	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
third	O
yard	O
was	O
not	O
paid	O
for	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
quite	O
right	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
to	O
John	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
well	O
John	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
shall	O
ruin	O
myself	O
in	O
buying	O
ribbons	O
;	O
no	O
sir	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
ribbons	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
that	O
;	O
no	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
master	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
lay	O
out	O
that	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
get	O
more	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
now	O
my	O
hand	O
is	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
buy	O
you	O
a	O
ribbon	O
John	O
for	O
your	O
wife	O
;	O
master	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
joaking	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
should	O
she	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
?	O
There	O
lay	O
a	O
white	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
by	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
you	O
'd	O
buy	O
me	O
such	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
disputing	O
what	O
colour	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
brown	O
,	O
scarlet	O
,	O
one	O
colour	O
after	O
another	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
chuse	O
what	O
colour	O
to	O
buy	O
for	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
some	O
ribbons	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
ribbon	O
you	O
have	O
put	O
into	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
your	O
own	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
villain	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
but	O
what	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
these	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbon	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
scarlet	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
green	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
yards	O
long	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
18	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
doubling	O
up	O
the	O
4	O
yards	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
strove	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
from	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
he	O
draw	O
'd	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
swore	O
d	O
-	O
mn	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
villain	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
kill	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
spot	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
long	O
knife	O
from	O
his	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
over	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
Christ	O
's	O
sake	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
He	O
cut	O
my	O
husband	O
over	O
the	O
eye	O
,	O
and	O
cross	O
the	O
nose	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
affrighted	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
neighbours	O
pursu	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
these	O
ribbons	O
worth	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Thwaites	I-pers
.	O
They	O
cost	O
me	O
5	O
d.	O
halfpeny	O
per	O
yard	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
27	O
yards	O
.	O
The	O
ribbons	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
also	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
when	O
open	O
'd	O
about	O
18	O
inches	O
long	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
this	O
ribbon	O
is	O
yours	O
?	O
Jane	O
Thwaites	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
given	O
him	O
one	O
piece	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
such	O
a	O
piece	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
for	O
colour	O
and	O
quantity	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
figures	O
for	O
the	O
selling	O
mark	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Thwaites	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
about	O
2	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
coat	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
imagine	O
I	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
through	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
faces	O
the	O
compter	O
.	O
At	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
sight	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
putting	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
green	O
ribbon	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
his	O
coat	O
under	O
his	O
right	O
arm	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
compter	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
bow	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
villain	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
servant	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
pieces	O
from	O
that	O
pocket	O
,	O
one	O
green	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
scarlet	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
while	O
we	O
scuffled	O
together	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
more	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
last	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
cut	O
on	O
my	O
forehead	O
;	O
the	O
scar	O
was	O
just	O
above	O
the	O
eyebrows	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
inches	O
long	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
blind	O
for	O
5	O
days	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
then	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
cut	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
and	O
disabled	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
cut	O
down	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
scar	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
as	O
though	O
it	O
had	O
went	O
through	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
palm	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
hualing	O
,	O
the	O
palm	O
was	O
draw	O
'd	O
together	O
.	O
My	O
surgeon	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
who	O
computed	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
blood	O
from	O
these	O
wounds	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
army	O
,	O
but	O
now	O
am	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
doing	O
duty	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
neighbours	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examin	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
these	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
ribbons	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Thwaites	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
directly	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
has	O
had	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
William	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
about	O
300	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
without	O
hat	O
or	O
wig	O
making	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
running	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
take	O
care	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
the	O
bailiffs	O
are	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
bailiffs	O
are	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
waving	O
the	O
knife	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
surrender	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
his	O
knife	O
through	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
offered	O
to	O
lay	O
hands	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
surrender	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
receive	O
damage	O
by	O
stones	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
people	O
flung	O
stones	O
at	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
crying	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
)	O
I	O
looked	O
back	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
borrowed	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
hit	O
him	O
a	O
knock	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
he	O
staggered	O
15	O
or	O
16	O
yards	O
,	O
then	O
fell	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
run	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
hit	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
wrist	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
knife	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
knife	O
up	O
again	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
a	O
brick-bat	O
hit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
temple	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
threw	O
it	O
tumbled	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
to	O
seize	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
narrowly	O
escaped	O
falling	O
into	O
a	O
pond	O
by	O
the	O
ditch	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
hit	O
him	O
and	O
knocked	O
the	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
a	O
stone	O
hit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
christening	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
requisite	O
to	O
make	O
presents	O
to	O
the	O
women	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
ribbons	O
;	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
every	O
yard	O
I	O
bought	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
says	O
he	O
took	O
these	O
ribbons	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
justice	O
Trent	B-pers
Mr	I-pers
.	O
Salt	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Salt	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
to	O
alledge	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
she	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
husband	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
green	O
ribbon	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Salt	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
what	O
quantity	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
she	O
there	O
swore	O
to	O
but	O
3	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
she	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
was	O
only	O
transportation	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
that	O
would	O
hang	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
scarlet	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
more	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
the	O
ribbon	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
?	O
Thwaites	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Thwaites	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
husband	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
I	O
desire	O
Mr.	O
Salt	O
may	O
be	O
called	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Salt	O
sworn	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
agreed	O
in	O
what	O
they	O
there	O
swore	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
they	O
have	O
done	O
now	O
;	O
she	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
8	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
they	O
swore	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
green	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
scarlet	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
638.	O
John	B-pers
Coppinger	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Flannigin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
,	O
October	O
12	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Flannigin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Hampshire	B-place
Hog	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
in-the-fields	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
others	O
go	O
in	O
a	O
gang	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
resorted	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
one	O
O'Brian	B-pers
and	O
a	O
fighting	O
man	O
,	O
named	O
Maine	B-pers
;	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
this	O
box	O
to	O
change	O
money	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
morning	O
he	O
breakfasted	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
close	O
in	O
all	O
day	O
;	O
his	O
partners	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
quarrel	O
;	O
they	O
knocked	O
one	O
another	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
one	O
another	O
about	O
.	O
Coppinger	O
,	O
it	O
seems	O
,	O
had	O
got	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
this	O
box	O
and	O
money	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
watchman	O
without	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
knocked	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
Flannigin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
out	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
3	O
d.	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
fell	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
he	O
ever	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
piece	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Rose-and-Crown	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Church-lane	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
see	O
O'Brian	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
gang	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Flannigin	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
swear	O
under	O
the	O
sum	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Flannigin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
silver	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
drop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
it	O
to	O
wear	O
about	O
my	O
child	O
's	O
neck	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
money	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
E.	O
Flannigin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
there	O
were	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
it	O
used	O
always	O
to	O
be	O
locked	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
then	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
O'Brian	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
removed	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
some	O
men	O
had	O
bred	O
a	O
great	O
disturbance	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
catched	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
O'Brian	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
the	O
chamber	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
wood	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
big	O
was	O
this	O
box	O
?	O
E.	O
Flannigin	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
long	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Bull	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
all	O
day	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
bolted	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
undoing	O
the	O
bolt	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
doing	O
so	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
speaking	O
to	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
there	O
stood	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
O'Brian	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
all	O
day	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
opened	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
11	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
my	O
master	O
called	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
found	O
,	O
it	O
dropped	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
searching	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
made	O
a	O
3	O
or	O
a	O
4	O
upon	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
pin	O
because	O
she	O
would	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
neck	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
this	O
3	O
d.	O
from	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
once	O
in	O
Denmark-street	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
King	O
William	O
and	O
Queen	O
Mary	O
's	O
3	O
d.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
with	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
my	O
mistress	O
said	O
,	O
go	O
back	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
3	O
d.	O
I	O
'll	O
keep	O
that	O
for	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
neck	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
O'Brian	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
because	O
we	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Flannigin	O
in	O
doing	O
plain	O
work	O
.	O
About	O
10	O
o'clock	O
that	O
Friday	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
against	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
then	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
box	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
found	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Leveridge	I-pers
.	O
That	O
very	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
assistance	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
him	O
this	O
3	O
d.	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
amongst	O
ten	O
thousand	O
.	O
The	O
3	O
d.	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Flannigin	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
3	O
d.	O
?	O
E.	O
Flannigin	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
5	O
s	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
this	O
with	O
the	O
halfpence	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
maid	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
marked	O
the	O
figure	O
of	O
4	O
with	O
a	O
pin	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
4	O
marked	O
on	O
it	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
never	O
fell	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
[	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
desired	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
might	O
be	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
once	O
committed	O
for	O
giving	O
false	O
evidence	O
in	O
this	O
court	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
in	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
gave	O
evidence	O
in	O
that	O
court	O
in	O
her	O
life	O
.	O
]	O
Court	O
.	O
Does	O
any	O
person	O
here	O
know	O
this	O
woman	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Newfoundland	O
Dog-alehouse	O
Charterhouse-lane	O
.	O
He	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
desire	O
,	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
court	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
sessions	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
give	O
evidence	O
in	O
favour	O
of	O
a	O
prisoner	O
who	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
fact	O
cast	O
and	O
executed	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bought	O
the	O
tankard	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
trying	O
for	O
somewhere	O
down	O
in	O
Walbrook	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
trial	O
was	O
over	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
perjury	O
;	O
(	O
for	O
which	O
see	O
No	O
.	O
34	O
in	O
Sir	O
Samuel	O
Pennant	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
,	O
the	O
witness	O
Margaret	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
)	O
He	O
said	O
likewise	O
he	O
knew	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
[	O
the	O
witness	O
being	O
a	O
drummer	O
now	O
in	O
general	O
Onslow	O
's	O
company	O
of	O
horse	O
grenadiers	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
foot	O
in	O
lord	O
Ancram	O
's	O
company	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
her	O
husband	O
belonged	O
]	O
being	O
asked	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
immediately	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Thompson	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
lately	O
tried	O
in	O
this	O
court	O
for	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
transported	O
.	O
(	O
For	O
which	O
see	O
No	O
.	O
25	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
344	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
Sir	O
William	O
Calvert	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
)	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
639.	O
James	B-pers
Currall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
,	O
October	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
lad	O
there	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
near	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
hat	O
away	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
and	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
640.	O
George	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
77	O
ells	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
tabby	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Delamare	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
3	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Delamare	I-pers
.	O
My	O
elder	O
and	O
younger	O
brothers	O
are	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
deal	O
in	O
merchandizing	O
silk	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
journeyman	O
Rottenbury	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
my	O
foreman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
the	O
man	O
when	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
his	O
face	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
my	O
man	O
take	O
care	O
;	O
they	O
pass	O
'd	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
turn	O
his	O
face	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
Freemont	O
had	O
the	O
goods	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
paper	O
of	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
care	O
,	O
or	O
this	O
man	O
would	O
trick	O
him	O
I	O
fear	O
'd	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
depend	O
upon	O
it	O
the	O
goods	O
are	O
safe	O
.	O
