TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
24th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1749	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
John	B-pers
Blachford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1750	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
JOHN	O
BLACHFORD	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
and	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Spearich	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Phene	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Peepover	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hool	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Heart	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tibson	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Luttman	I-pers
,	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Stenton	I-pers
,	O
*	O
Richard	O
Stenton	O
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Perrett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Seccul	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Morgen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Blacksley	I-pers
.	O
501.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
for	O
45	O
l.	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
also	O
an	O
acquittance	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
:	O
Being	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
court	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
his	O
so	O
pleading	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
unhappy	O
enough	O
to	O
stand	O
here	O
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
fact	O
which	O
my	O
prosecutor	O
can	O
so	O
easily	O
prove	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
therefore	O
from	O
a	O
consciousness	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
prevent	O
giving	O
the	O
court	O
any	O
unnecessary	O
trouble	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
confess	O
my	O
guilt	O
,	O
and	O
submissively	O
rely	O
on	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
to	O
intercede	O
for	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
-	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
thus	O
much	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
alleviation	O
of	O
my	O
crime	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
ever	O
appear	O
'd	O
before	O
a	O
court	O
of	O
Justice	O
in	O
an	O
ignominious	O
manner	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
necessity	O
urged	O
me	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
fact	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
my	O
heart	O
is	O
full	O
of	O
sorrow	O
and	O
contrition	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
If	O
therefore	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
or	O
Mr	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
pleased	O
to	O
report	O
me	O
in	O
this	O
favourable	O
light	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
Lords	O
in	O
power	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
be	O
the	O
happy	O
means	O
of	O
inducing	O
them	O
to	O
extend	O
their	O
clemency	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
unfortunate	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
thought	O
an	O
object	O
worthy	O
their	O
compassion	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
that	O
the	O
Lord	O
of	O
Heaven	O
and	O
Earth	O
will	O
have	O
mercy	O
on	O
my	O
soul	O
.	O
502	O
,	O
503	O
,	O
504.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Best	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
double	O
laced	O
mob	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
August	O
9	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
505.	O
Susannah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Francis	I-pers
Deadman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pilkington	I-pers
in	O
her	O
ready	O
furnish	O
'd	O
lodgings	O
,	O
let	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Susannah	O
,	O
July	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
506.	O
James	B-pers
Hawes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
eight	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
five	O
linen	O
mobs	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cambrick	O
ruffles	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
four	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
was	O
an	O
inmate	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
open	O
'd	O
a	O
door	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
fastened	O
up	O
from	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
enter	O
'd	O
her	O
apartment	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
directions	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
507.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
2	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
muslin	O
stocks	O
,	O
6	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
1	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
3	O
towels	O
,	O
one	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
July	O
14	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Old-Street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
supper	O
with	O
my	O
lodger	O
above	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
with	O
assistance	O
had	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
forgiveness	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
entry	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Gotoe	I-pers
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
Crosby-square	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
gave	O
her	O
them	O
to	O
hold	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
some	O
place	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
three	O
halfpence	O
for	O
holding	O
them	O
.	O
First	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Susannah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Baily	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gotoe	I-pers
confirmed	O
Mrs.	O
Smith	O
's	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Old-street	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
harvesting	O
.	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
condition	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
for	O
mine	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
husband	O
.	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
hold	O
this	O
bundle	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
three	O
halfpence	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
will	O
pay	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
trouble	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
408.	O
Jane	B-pers
Service	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Christopher-Stephen	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
August	O
4	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
we	O
mist	O
these	O
spoons	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
name	O
at	O
full	O
length	O
engrav	O
'd	O
upon	O
them	O
(	O
they	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
as	O
a	O
charewoman	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
these	O
two	O
spoons	O
at	O
two	O
different	O
times	O
to	O
pawn	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
each	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
from	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Solomon	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Headborough	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
spoons	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
broken	O
victuals	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
509.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
George	I-pers
Trussin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
three	O
moidores	O
,	O
one	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lawton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
August	O
25	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Swanson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Esquire	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
receive	O
his	O
rents	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Ratcliff-high-way	B-place
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
bag	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
into	O
a	O
sore	O
room	O
;	O
that	O
afternoon	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
employed	O
by	O
the	O
maid	O
the	O
fore	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
reported	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
affair	O
she	O
had	O
expended	O
3	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
We	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
before	O
justice	O
Burry	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
shook	O
the	O
scrutore	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Lawton	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
scrutore	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
fell	O
down	O
behind	O
from	O
a	O
hole	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
whether	O
this	O
hole	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
name	O
any	O
particular	O
pieces	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
certificate	O
,	O
coming	O
back	O
from	O
being	O
married	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
a	O
servant	O
with	O
Esquire	O
Lawton	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
chare-woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
510.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
August	O
13	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
is	O
a	O
carpenter	B-pers
,	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
in	O
Skinner's-street	B-place
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
a	O
brother	O
carpenter	O
and	O
left	O
his	O
saw	O
upon	O
the	O
work	O
bench	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
likewise	O
,	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
511.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Codosa	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Batison	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Batison	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
three	O
gowns	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
ground	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
hung	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
neither	O
acknowledge	O
or	O
deny	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
Mrs.	O
Holland	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
dropp	O
'd	O
them	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Winn	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
woman	O
or	O
what	O
she	O
is	O
talking	O
of	O
.	O
Fra	O
.	O
Holland	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
two	O
gowns	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
turning	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
keep	O
a	O
bawdy	O
house	O
well	O
enough	O
.	O
F.	O
Holland	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
two	O
gowns	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
in	O
confinement	O
in	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
spare	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
wanted	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
one	O
would	O
fit	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
my	O
daughter	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
that	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
pay	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
borrow	O
'd	O
6	O
s.	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
remainder	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
but	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
512.	O
John	B-pers
Taphouse	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
quart	O
mug	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
11	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
(	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Elbow-lane	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
three	O
cranes	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
drinking	O
and	O
singing	O
.	O
One	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
missed	O
a	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
search	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
none	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
all	O
the	O
company	O
very	O
well	O
except	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
knowing	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Dowgate-hill	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
behind	O
a	O
spur	O
of	O
a	O
door	O
to	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Lazure	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
We	O
found	O
it	O
according	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
lavender	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
testimony	O
was	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Samuel	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Lazure	I-pers
;	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Room	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
for	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
513.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
upon	O
Charles	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbred	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
sen'night	O
in	O
the	O
Morning	O
I	O
was	O
coming	B-place
from	I-place
Moorfields	I-place
,	I-place
facing	I-place
Bedlam	I-place
gate	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stop	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
and	O
toss	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
put	O
my	O
wig	O
before	O
my	O
eyes	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
blind	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
shilling	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
ten	O
times	O
as	O
much	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
come	O
or	O
look	O
back	O
.	O
Then	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
watchman	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
another	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
came	O
Mr.	O
Chennery	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
robb	O
'd	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
across	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
some	O
more	O
watchmen	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
jacket	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
men	O
might	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
lent	O
me	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
would	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
staff	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chennery	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchmen	O
followed	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
betwixt	O
the	O
posts	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
sitting	O
upon	O
the	O
Wall	O
that	O
parts	O
the	O
middle	O
fields	O
from	O
the	O
quarters	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
jacket	O
by	O
the	O
fore	O
parts	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
close	O
round	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
my	O
head	O
down	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
us	O
what	O
we	O
wanted	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Chennery	O
said	O
money	O
and	O
manners	O
;	O
he	O
repeated	O
it	O
twice	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stood	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
ca	O
n't	O
we	O
sit	O
here	O
upon	O
the	O
wall	O
for	O
all	O
you	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chennery	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
we	O
stand	O
here	O
for	O
all	O
you	O
.	O
They	O
began	O
then	O
to	O
whistle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
jump	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
wall	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Then	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
go	O
if	O
the	O
others	O
do	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Chinnery	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
together	O
,	O
having	O
had	O
a	O
Scuffle	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Watchmen	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
moon	O
light	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
lamps	O
round	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
single	O
shilling	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
arms	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Chennery	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
of	O
their	O
taking	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Grubstreet	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
a	O
gentleman	O
like	O
man	O
that	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
wrong	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
much	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Skinner-street	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
four	O
full	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
together	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
betwixt	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
under	O
the	O
wall	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Men	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
up	O
came	O
my	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
wanted	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
money	O
and	O
manners	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
insisted	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pistol	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
5	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
514.	O
James	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Aug.	O
5	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Hammond	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Kirby-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
money	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
My	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket-apron	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
20	O
s.	O
at	O
least	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pail	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
my	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
26	O
s.	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Manby	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
White	I-pers
confirmed	O
that	O
of	O
his	O
confession	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
this	O
honourable	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
515	O
,	O
516	O
,	O
517.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ben	I-pers
the	I-pers
Coleheaver	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Harsel	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
lac	O
'd	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
hatband	O
buckle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harsell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
Red-Lion-street	B-place
,	O
Holborn	O
,	O
at	O
past	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Aug	O
.	O
I.	O
of	O
a	O
gold	O
lac	O
'd	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
hat	O
buckle	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
One	O
person	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
another	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
or	O
a	O
cutlass	O
.	O
They	O
damn	O
'd	O
my	O
eyes	O
and	O
limbs	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
javelin	O
screwed	O
on	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
my	O
walking	O
stick	O
(	O
it	O
went	O
on	O
with	O
a	O
socket	O
,	O
the	O
blade	O
about	O
nine	O
inches	O
long	O
)	O
but	O
the	O
scabbard	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
resistance	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
them	O
one	O
shilling	O
.	O
Then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
Fisk	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
preserved	O
my	O
watch	O
the	O
string	O
being	O
withinside	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
ring	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
charge	O
this	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
or	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Harsell	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
Hutton	O
and	O
Rowland	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
.	O
We	O
met	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
King's-head	O
,	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Red-Lion-street	O
.	O
Ben	O
the	O
Coalheaver	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
it	O
up	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
Rowland	O
had	O
another	O
and	O
fired	O
it	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
missed	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Harsell	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
pistol	O
fired	O
?	O
Harsell	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
snapp	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
missed	O
fire	O
.	O
Ball	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
to	O
Ben	O
the	O
Coalheaver	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
fire	O
?	O
mine	O
has	O
missed	O
.	O
Hutton	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
took	O
two	O
Shillings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
nose	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
cut	O
his	O
nose	O
off	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Harsell	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
Harsell	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
thieves	O
directly	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
nose	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
cut	O
my	O
nose	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
watchmen	O
were	O
very	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
big	O
rogues	O
as	O
these	O
;	O
had	O
they	O
come	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
taken	O
them	O
then	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Ball	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
hat	O
?	O
Ball	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Harsell	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
Ball	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
believe	O
two	O
of	O
these	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
or	O
from	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
?	O
Harsel	O
.	O
From	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
alamp	O
within	O
two	O
doors	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
green	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
with	O
gold	O
button-holes	O
(	O
such	O
as	O
Rowland	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
judge	O
by	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
Ball	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
hat	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
who	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Ball	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
an	O
information	O
against	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
three	O
prisoners	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Ball	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
To	O
their	O
characters	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hutton	O
five	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wells	O
's	O
and	O
Loe	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
trust	O
of	O
several	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
goods	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Hutton	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
cloth	O
drawer	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
much	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
robbing	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Hutton	O
,	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
crime	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Hutton	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
family	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Brumley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Rowland	O
from	O
two	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
ever	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
malt-distiller	O
;	O
I	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
every	O
thing	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
a	O
man	O
can	O
mention	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
for	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
took	O
money	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
30	O
,	O
40	O
,	O
50	O
pounds	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
he	O
wronged	O
or	O
cheated	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
farthing	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
ever	O
robb	O
'd	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
or	O
child	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bilson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
partner	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Brumley	O
.	O
Rowland	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
in	O
our	O
service	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Vernon	O
I	O
know	O
Rowland	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
ever	O
defrauded	O
any	O
person	O
of	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
wicked	O
man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
Mason	O
before	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
70.	O
in	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pennant	I-pers
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
518.	O
Diana	B-pers
Reves	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
flaxen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Basset	I-pers
,	O
July	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
519	O
,	O
520.	O
James	B-pers
Theobalds	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Dangerfield	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Aug.	O
12	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
about	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
and	O
three	O
women	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
four	O
wheel	O
chaise	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
back	O
seat	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
drove	O
it	O
.	O
Coming	O
along	O
Bethnal	B-place
Green	I-place
back	I-place
road	I-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
horseback	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
After	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
pass	O
'd	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
and	O
rainy	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
three	O
farthings	O
.	O
He	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
for	O
?	O
He	O
demanded	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
on	O
horseback	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
mind	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
other	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Then	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
horse	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
next	O
coach	O
,	O
calling	O
him	O
Thomas	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
horse	O
about	O
,	O
the	O
coachman	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
body	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
almost	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
called	O
out	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
hold	O
his	O
tongue	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
lost	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
coachman	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Mile-end	O
turnpike	O
to	O
Bethnal	O
Green	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
rode	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
off-side	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
bid	O
me	O
stop	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
rode	O
round	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
who	O
bid	O
me	O
stop	O
,	O
bid	O
me	O
hold	O
my	O
head	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
he	O
'd	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
:	O
(	O
then	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
voice	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cave	O
,	O
and	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
towards	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
ask	O
him	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
money	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
my	O
head	O
round	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
money	O
chink	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
.	O
Then	O
there	O
came	O
by	O
a	O
coach	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
one	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
stop	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stopp	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
Snow	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
face	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
or	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
voice	O
and	O
his	O
face	O
at	O
that	O
very	O
time	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Dangerfield	I-pers
;	O
I	O
have	O
drank	O
also	O
with	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
I	O
caused	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
book-keeper	O
to	O
a	O
Waggon	O
on	O
that	O
comes	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Sarazen	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Theobald	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Dangerfield	O
's	O
own	O
words	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Theobald	O
's	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
On	O
thursday	O
was	O
sen'night	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Half-moon	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Dangerfield	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
one	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
tapp	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
remember	O
'd	O
last	O
Sunday-night	O
,	O
about	O
stopping	O
a	O
four-wheel	O
'd	O
chaise	O
near	O
Mile-end	O
turnpike	O
.	O
And	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
drive	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
Then	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
My	O
dear	O
eyes	O
,	O
be	O
righteous	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
life	O
lies	O
in	O
your	O
hands	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Cave	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
living	O
in	O
this	O
place	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
rainy	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hat	O
was	O
not	O
put	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
neat	O
coat	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
blow	O
it	O
,	O
though	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
taking	O
him	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
believes	O
Dangerfield	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Dangerfield	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
which	O
this	O
man	O
charges	O
me	O
with	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
printer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
once	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
time	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
at	O
Holloway	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
7	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
off	O
their	O
horses	O
;	O
whether	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
or	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
thither	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
fuddled	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
out	O
some	O
cold	O
sowl	O
,	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
wine	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
discourse	O
with	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
Foundling-Hospital	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
christening	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
from	O
thence	O
17	O
minutes	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
clock	O
,	O
wanting	O
of	O
8	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
when	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
chaise	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
within	O
10	O
minutes	O
of	O
8	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
horses	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Walker	O
confirms	O
this	O
account	O
.	O
Joseph	O
Cooper	O
I	O
live	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Dangerfield	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
candles	O
lighted	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
milk	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
heavy	O
shower	O
of	O
rain	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
they	O
staid	O
drinking	O
their	O
liquor	O
;	O
how	O
long	O
they	O
stay	O
'd	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Christiana	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
a	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoners	O
coming	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
alighted	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
their	O
horses	O
up	O
themselves	O
;	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
sixpeny	O
worth	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
milk	O
;	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
wanted	O
10	O
minutes	O
of	O
9	O
,	O
it	O
rained	O
then	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
before	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
till	O
after	O
9	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Snow	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
breakfast	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Half-Moon	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
:	O
Hammond	O
is	O
a	O
coachman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
with	O
Cave	O
;	O
Snow	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
in	O
swearing	O
against	O
Dangerfield	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
advised	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
master	O
coachman	O
.	O
Job	O
Selby	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Page	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Norton	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Pepworth	I-pers
,	O
all	O
gave	O
Dangerfield	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
521.	O
George	B-pers
Otterton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Richard	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
coat	O
for	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
August	O
26	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
my	O
family	O
live	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
;	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
London	O
late	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
betwixt	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
soldier	O
's	O
coat	O
turn	O
'd	O
inside	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
deserter	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
betwixt	O
the	O
half	O
way	O
house	O
and	O
Kensington	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
in	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
ale-house	O
at	O
Kensington	O
and	O
drank	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
forward	O
towards	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
cross	O
Turnham-green	B-place
,	I-place
there	I-place
is	I-place
a	I-place
lane	I-place
leads	I-place
from	I-place
that	I-place
green	I-place
to	I-place
Branford	I-place
,	O
in	O
that	O
lane	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
attack	O
upon	O
me	O
sword	O
in	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
clapt	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
and	O
collar	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
change	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
shilling	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
dry	O
ditch	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
thieves	O
,	O
murder	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
I	O
judg	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
throatled	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
outright	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
me	O
and	O
got	O
my	O
knife	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
his	O
business	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
stuck	O
him	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
places	O
of	O
his	O
body	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
me	O
down	O
once	O
more	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
murder	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
notwithstanding	O
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
held	O
a	O
sixpence	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
scussle	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
coat	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
on	O
my	O
arm	O
was	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
that	O
also	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
on	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
.	O
I	O
imagined	O
he	O
would	O
drop	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
with	O
the	O
wounds	O
he	O
received	O
,	O
and	O
reported	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
his	O
comrade	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
together	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
would	O
be	O
upon	O
guard	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
instructions	O
were	O
false	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Captain	O
Salter	O
's	O
and	O
left	O
word	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
soldier	O
who	O
had	O
attack	O
'd	O
me	O
was	O
dangerously	O
wounded	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
pains	O
to	O
over-hale	O
his	O
men	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
was	O
wounded	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
blown	O
abroad	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
Richard	O
Nixon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
regiment	O
of	O
guards	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
declar	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
a	O
deserter	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
wounded	O
in	O
two	O
parts	O
of	O
his	O
body	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
coming	O
and	O
making	O
complaint	O
to	O
the	O
Adjutant	O
of	O
the	O
regiment	O
,	O
and	O
describing	O
the	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
body	O
he	O
had	O
wounded	O
the	O
soldier	O
in	O
who	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
Adjutant	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
wounded	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
highway	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
wounded	O
in	O
a	O
scuffle	O
with	O
a	O
deserter	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
man	O
.	O
This	O
coat	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
another	O
soldier	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
wound	O
the	O
person	O
you	O
say	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
breast	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
places	O
.	O
Nixon	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
scratch	O
with	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
pin	O
near	O
his	O
right	O
breast	O
,	O
I	O
examined	O
him	O
no	O
farther	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
just	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
little	O
cuts	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
breast	O
,	O
as	O
large	O
as	O
a	O
knife	O
might	O
be	O
imagined	O
to	O
cut	O
.	O
The	O
little	O
coat	O
is	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
very	O
lovingly	O
on	O
together	O
till	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
thief-taker	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
for	O
20	O
s.	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
deserter	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
doing	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
duty	O
;	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
knife	O
and	O
stuck	O
me	O
,	O
than	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
back	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Nixon	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
522.	O
George	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
chimney	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
27	O
India	O
prints	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Powers	I-pers
,	O
August	O
2	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Powers	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
keeps	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prince	O
's	O
cup	O
was	O
fail	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
our	O
dogs	O
made	O
a	O
prodigous	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
gallery	O
room	O
that	O
does	O
not	O
join	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
place	O
built	O
for	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
fit	O
in	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
pleasure	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
About	O
noon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
it	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
The	O
India	O
prints	O
were	O
nail	O
'd	O
up	O
with	O
brass	O
nails	O
,	O
every	O
one	O
was	O
drawn	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
guinea	O
reward	O
and	O
no	O
questions	O
ask	O
'd	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
is	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
attend	O
business	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
His	O
voluntary	O
confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
wherein	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
and	O
how	O
,	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
hand	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Boice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sign	O
this	O
confession	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
and	O
did	O
it	O
voluntary	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Powers	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
523.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Burrel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cow	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
8	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
cow	O
stole	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
field	O
near	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
a	O
butcher	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
one	O
Lewit	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
Lewit	O
live	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Near	O
White-chappel-mount	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
lost	O
her	O
;	O
Lewit	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
her	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
50	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
Brick-lane	O
,	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
lost	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
other	O
cows	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
certificate	O
for	O
this	O
cow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
value	O
her	O
at	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
is	O
worth	O
about	O
3	O
l.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
this	O
twelve	O
month	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
these	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
for	O
whatever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
524.	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
Punnet	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dolman	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
3	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dolman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Black	B-place
Baer	I-place
Inn	I-place
in	I-place
Pickadilly	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
last	O
monday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
with	O
pretence	O
to	O
sell	O
pincushions	O
and	O
huffeys	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
offering	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
maid	O
in	O
the	O
kitchin	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
of	O
mine	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Kitchin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
lay	O
her	O
box	O
down	O
on	O
this	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
servants	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
with	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
things	O
I	O
carry	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
525.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
fustian	O
frock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Nottingham	B-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
King-street	I-place
,	I-place
Seven	I-place
Dials	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
cloaths	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
hanging	O
upon	O
the	O
closet	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
latch	O
.	O
My	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
16	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Ma	I-pers
.	I-pers
Farley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
High-Holborn	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
brandy-shop	O
there	O
.	O
About	O
8	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
this	O
frock	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
his	O
cloths	O
away	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
all	O
her	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
proffer	O
'd	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
her	O
whether	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
or	O
pawn	O
them	O
for	O
that	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
cloaths	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
him	O
advertised	O
on	O
the	O
wed	O
nesday	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
and	O
received	O
a	O
guinea	O
of	O
a	O
master	O
of	O
mine	O
at	O
Brumpton	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
these	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pig	O
in	O
a	O
poke	O
;	O
so	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Then	O
a	O
soldier	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
bitch	O
,	O
come	O
and	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
gin	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
cloaths	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
constable	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
recompence	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
brought	O
another	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
526.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Badge	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
muslin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
cambric	O
mob	O
,	O
one	O
cambric	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
3	O
yards	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
holland	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
Aug.	O
29	O
.	O
James	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
East	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
several	O
rooms	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
brother	O
serv	O
'd	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
first	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
service	O
;	O
The	O
maid	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
persuaded	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
cleared	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
bundle	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
things	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cap	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
amongst	O
her	O
things	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
upon	O
that	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
robb	O
'd	O
my	O
till	O
of	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
three	O
farthings	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
amongst	O
her	O
friends	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
she	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
confessed	O
every	O
thing	O
and	O
cleared	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
pinned	O
the	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
strip	O
'd	O
muslin	O
to	O
her	O
shift-tail	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
former	O
testimony	O
confirmed	O
by	O
Dan	O
.	O
Hall	O
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Rumsey	I-pers
,	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
pawning	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
her	O
confession	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
fifteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
527.	O
James	B-pers
Macleane	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
on	O
Josiah	B-pers
Higden	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
five	O
holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
stocks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
spurs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
tea	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
June	O
26	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Higden	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
passenger	O
in	O
the	O
Salisbury	O
flying	O
coach	O
,	O
going	O
thither	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
gentlemen	O
and	O
one	O
gentlewoman	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Betwixt	O
Turnham	O
Green	O
and	O
Brentford	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
mile	O
stone	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Chiswick	O
,	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
pistol	O
in	O
,	O
demanding	O
our	O
money	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
calling	O
to	O
his	O
companion	O
who	O
lagg	O
'd	O
behind	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
.	O
Then	O
came	O
up	O
another	O
person	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
arm	O
'd	O
and	O
mask	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
acted	O
but	O
little	O
;	O
he	O
rather	O
sat	O
on	O
horseback	O
as	O
a	O
guard	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
about	O
twelve	O
or	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
first	O
.	O
They	O
declared	O
that	O
should	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
us	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
into	O
the	O
high-way	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
six	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
pocket	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
threaten	O
'd	O
to	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
for	O
concealing	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
on	O
horseback	O
I	O
believe	O
threaten	O
'd	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
declared	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
boot	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
jump	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
cloak	O
bags	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
the	O
coachman	O
help	O
them	O
up	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
each	O
rode	O
off	O
with	O
one	O
.	O
He	O
mentions	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
this	O
cloak	O
bag	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
a	O
light	O
perriwig	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
double	O
channel	O
pumps	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
cannisters	O
without	O
tea	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
trunk	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
cloakbag	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
also	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Loader	O
's	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
lace	O
stripp	O
'd	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
portmanteau	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
Kensington	O
Gravel-pits	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
also	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
also	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
the	O
robbery	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
,	O
did	O
commit	O
that	O
robbery	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
they	O
divided	O
the	O
cloaths	O
;	O
he	O
wrote	O
his	O
confession	O
down	O
himself	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
sign	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
that	O
witness	O
ever	O
saw	O
me	O
?	O
Higden	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
pass	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
hear	O
me	O
make	O
any	O
confession	O
?	O
Higden	O
.	O
Yes	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Hidgen	O
declare	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
me	O
before	O
?	O
Higden	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Higden	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
voice	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
did	O
not	O
agree	O
with	O
mine	O
?	O
Higden	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
voice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
never	O
declare	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
man	O
?	O
Higden	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
declared	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
through	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
duty	O
to	O
my	O
country	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Loader	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
himself	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Dunn	O
in	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
;	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
light	O
colour	O
'd	O
cloth	O
coat	O
and	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
with	O
the	O
lace	O
ripped	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Higden	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Macleane	O
,	O
the	O
name	O
he	O
left	O
with	O
me	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
hand	O
writing	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
direction	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
cloaths	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
taking	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Higden	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
were	O
advertised	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
papers	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
perriwig	O
maker	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
wig	O
now	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Justice	O
Lidiard	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
any	O
service	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
a	O
confession	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
admit	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
voluntary	O
confession	O
I	O
would	O
hear	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
press	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
this	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
robberies	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
one	O
Plunket	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
recollect	O
,	O
as	O
nearly	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
robberies	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
him	O
to	O
sign	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
read	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
that	O
paper	O
were	O
true	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
paper	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
and	O
never	O
ask	O
'd	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
two	O
portmanteaus	O
,	O
and	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
lay	O
then	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
confess	O
'd	O
this	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
by	O
me	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
the	O
court	O
would	O
indulge	O
him	O
to	O
read	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
``	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
persuaded	O
from	O
the	O
candour	O
and	O
indulgence	O
shewn	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
my	O
trial	O
,	O
that	O
your	O
lordship	O
will	O
hear	O
me	O
with	O
patience	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
allowance	O
for	O
the	O
confusion	O
I	O
may	O
shew	O
before	O
an	O
awful	O
assembly	O
,	O
upon	O
so	O
solemn	O
an	O
occasion	O
.	O
Your	O
lordship	O
will	O
not	O
construe	O
it	O
vanity	O
in	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
a	O
divine	O
of	O
the	O
kingdom	O
of	O
Ireland	O
,	O
well	O
known	O
for	O
his	O
zeal	O
and	O
affection	O
to	O
the	O
present	O
royal	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
happy	O
government	O
;	O
who	O
bestowed	O
an	O
education	O
upon	O
me	O
becoming	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
a	O
certificate	O
from	O
a	O
noble	O
lord	O
,	O
four	O
members	O
of	O
parliament	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
justices	O
of	O
peace	O
for	O
the	O
country	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
my	O
education	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
late	O
French	O
war	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
enter	O
into	O
the	O
military	O
service	O
of	O
my	O
king	O
and	O
country	O
;	O
but	O
unexpected	O
disappointments	O
obliged	O
me	O
to	O
change	O
my	O
resolution	O
;	O
and	O
having	O
married	O
the	O
daughter	O
of	O
a	O
reputable	O
trademan	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
fortune	O
I	O
added	O
what	O
little	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
entered	O
into	O
trade	O
in	O
the	O
grocery	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
therein	O
till	O
my	O
wife	O
died	O
.	O
I	O
very	O
quickly	O
after	O
her	O
death	O
found	O
a	O
decay	O
in	O
trade	O
,	O
arising	O
from	O
an	O
unavoidable	O
trust	O
reposed	O
in	O
servants	O
;	O
and	O
fearing	O
the	O
consequence	O
,	O
I	O
candidly	O
consulted	O
some	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
their	O
advice	O
,	O
sold	O
off	O
my	O
stock	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
honestly	O
discharged	O
my	O
debts	O
,	O
and	O
proposed	O
to	O
apply	O
the	O
residue	O
of	O
my	O
fortune	O
in	O
the	O
purchase	O
of	O
some	O
military	O
employment	O
,	O
agreeable	O
to	O
my	O
first	O
design	O
.	O
During	O
my	O
application	O
to	O
trade	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
unhappily	O
became	O
acquainted	O
with	O
one	O
Plunket	O
,	O
an	O
apothecary	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
,	O
induced	O
me	O
to	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
travelled	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
possessed	O
of	O
cloaths	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
suitable	O
thereto	O
,	O
and	O
prevailed	O
on	O
me	O
to	O
employ	O
him	O
in	O
attending	O
on	O
my	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
left	O
off	O
trade	O
,	O
I	O
pressed	O
Plunket	O
for	O
payment	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
receiving	O
,	O
by	O
degrees	O
,	O
several	O
sums	O
,	O
he	O
proposed	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
earnestly	O
insisting	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
call	O
in	O
all	O
debts	O
owing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
part	O
in	O
goods	O
and	O
part	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
These	O
very	O
cloaths	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
charged	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
were	O
cloaths	O
he	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
sale	O
of	O
,	O
towards	O
payment	O
of	O
my	O
debt	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
very	O
unfortunately	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
now	O
appears	O
;	O
little	O
thinking	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
by	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Higden	O
hath	O
been	O
pleased	O
to	O
express	O
,	O
whose	O
word	O
and	O
honour	O
are	O
too	O
well	O
known	O
to	O
doubt	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
contracting	O
this	O
debt	O
between	O
Plunket	O
and	O
myself	O
was	O
a	O
matter	O
of	O
a	O
private	O
nature	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
therefore	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
any	O
one	O
single	O
witness	O
to	O
these	O
facts	O
,	O
which	O
(	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
unavoidable	O
misfortune	O
)	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
and	O
doubt	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
that	O
your	O
lordship	O
and	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
will	O
duly	O
weigh	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
avoid	O
observing	O
to	O
your	O
lordship	O
,	O
Is	O
it	O
probable	O
,	O
nay	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
possible	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
come	O
by	O
those	O
cloaths	O
by	O
dishonest	O
means	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
imprudent	O
as	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
at	O
noon-day	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
my	O
name	O
and	O
place	O
of	O
residence	O
,	O
and	O
even	O
write	O
that	O
name	O
and	O
residence	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
Salesman	O
's	O
book	O
?	O
It	O
seems	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
must	O
to	O
every	O
man	O
,	O
a	O
madness	O
that	O
no	O
one	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
least	O
share	O
of	O
sense	O
,	O
could	O
be	O
capable	O
of	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
observed	O
in	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Higden	O
's	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
hath	O
declared	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
either	O
to	O
my	O
face	O
or	O
person	O
,	O
the	O
defect	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
humbly	O
presume	O
,	O
leaves	O
a	O
doubt	O
of	O
the	O
certainty	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
persons	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
true	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
first	O
apprehended	O
,	O
the	O
surprize	O
confounded	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
most	O
extraordinary	O
shock	O
;	O
it	O
caused	O
a	O
delirium	O
and	O
confusion	O
in	O
my	O
brain	O
,	O
which	O
rendered	O
me	O
incapable	O
of	O
being	O
myself	O
,	O
or	O
knowing	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
or	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
talked	O
of	O
robberies	O
as	O
another	O
man	O
would	O
do	O
in	O
talking	O
of	O
stories	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
friends	O
had	O
visited	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
some	O
new	O
spirits	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
re	O
examined	O
before	O
justice	O
Lediard	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
any	O
discovery	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
alledged	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
recovered	O
my	O
surprize	O
,	O
that	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
talked	O
of	O
before	O
concerning	O
robberies	O
was	O
false	O
and	O
wrong	O
,	O
and	O
entirely	O
owing	O
to	O
a	O
confused	O
head	O
and	O
brain	O
.	O
This	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
being	O
my	O
unhappy	O
fate	O
;	O
but	O
unhappy	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
as	O
your	O
lordship	O
is	O
my	O
judge	O
and	O
presumptive	O
council	O
,	O
I	O
submit	O
it	O
,	O
whether	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
other	O
evidence	O
against	O
me	O
than	O
circumstantial	O
.	O
First	O
,	O
the	O
selling	O
of	O
the	O
lace	O
and	O
cloaths	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
agree	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
account	O
.	O
Second	O
,	O
the	O
verbal	O
confession	O
of	O
a	O
confused	O
brain	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
account	O
.	O
All	O
this	O
evidence	O
I	O
humbly	O
apprehend	O
is	O
but	O
circumstantial	O
evidence	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
shew	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
answer	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Higden	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
juncture	O
,	O
to	O
recollect	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
more	O
to	O
bring	O
any	O
testimony	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
in	O
cases	O
where	O
a	O
prisoner	O
lies	O
under	O
these	O
impossibilities	O
of	O
proof	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
hard	O
,	O
nay	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
if	O
presumption	O
and	O
intendment	O
may	O
not	O
have	O
some	O
weight	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
humbly	O
hope	O
,	O
and	O
doubt	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
doctrine	O
will	O
not	O
escape	O
your	O
lordship	O
's	O
memory	O
to	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
credit	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
dealings	O
with	O
manking	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
humbly	O
beg	O
leave	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
to	O
call	O
about	O
a	O
score	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
,	O
if	O
your	O
lordship	O
pleases	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
if	O
in	O
your	O
lordship	O
's	O
opinion	O
the	O
evidence	O
against	O
me	O
should	O
be	O
by	O
law	O
only	O
circumstantial	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
character	O
given	O
of	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
witnesses	O
should	O
be	O
so	O
far	O
satisfactory	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
have	O
equal	O
weight	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
most	O
willingly	O
and	O
readily	O
submit	O
to	O
the	O
jury	O
's	O
verdict	O
.	O
''	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
nine	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
528.	O
Henry	B-pers
James	I-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Charles	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Curson	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
metal	O
watch	O
gilt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Curson	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
July	O
,	O
22	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Curson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Hampstead	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
landau	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
of	O
us	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
three	O
gentlewomen	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sherard	O
the	O
attorney	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
We	O
insisted	O
that	O
our	O
coachman	O
should	O
keep	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
yet	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
reason	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
divided	O
;	O
the	O
one	O
went	O
to	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
Hanover	O
Square	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
latter	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
stopp	O
'd	O
near	B-place
Fig	I-place
Lane	I-place
;	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
opposite	O
side	O
to	O
where	O
I	O
sat	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
each	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
They	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
their	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
our	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
di	O
d	O
not	O
deliver	O
our	O
watches	O
and	O
money	O
directly	O
.	O
One	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
metal	O
one	O
gilt	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
enamell	O
'd	O
dial	O
plate	O
,	O
made	O
by	O
Delander	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
enough	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
discern	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
clear	O
night	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
spent	O
that	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
took	O
none	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
evidence	O
I	O
believe	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
lying	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
heap	O
of	O
gravel	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ecklin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
committed	O
several	O
robberies	O
together	O
;	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
we	O
lay	O
in	O
weight	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Fig	O
Lane	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
rattling	O
of	O
coaches	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
do	O
you	O
lie	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
stones	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
landau	O
came	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
landau	O
turned	O
round	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
near	O
my	O
legs	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
which	O
shall	O
we	O
follow	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
best	O
to	O
follow	O
this	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
the	O
fewest	O
people	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
landau	O
.	O
Then	O
Henry	O
Saunders	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
watch	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
diamond	O
ring	O
and	O
another	O
plain	O
one	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
finger	O
;	O
and	O
Campbel	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
about	O
fourteen	O
of	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
pistols	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
brace	O
,	O
and	O
Campbel	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
529.	O
Adolphus	B-pers
James	I-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
ounces	O
of	O
hair	O
,	O
2	O
combs	O
,	O
one	O
awl	O
,	O
one	O
pasteboard	O
wig	O
box	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Leather	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
journeyman	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
trial	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
given	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
530.	O
James	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Simpson	B-pers
Levi	I-pers
.	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
coming	O
through	O
Ludgate	B-place
;	O
he	O
was	O
detected	O
in	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
he	O
flung	O
down	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
531.	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Clement	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
George	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
husband	O
being	O
living	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
marriage	O
was	O
laid	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
11th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
majesty	O
.	O
And	O
there	O
being	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
Grace	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
20th	O
year	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
court	O
thought	O
it	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
to	O
enquire	O
into	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
the	O
offence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
532.	O
George	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Aug.	O
21	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	B-place
Change	I-place
,	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
his	O
jacket	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wyat	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
train	O
bands	O
;	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
ragged	O
young	O
fellow	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
wig	O
near	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
touch	O
'd	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
my	O
days	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
found	O
betwixt	O
me	O
and	O
another	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
533.	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Cockram	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Cockram	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
on	O
Sunday	O
July	O
29.	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
New	B-place
Market	I-place
just	I-place
below	I-place
the	I-place
houses	I-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
pavement	I-place
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
sudden	O
outcry	O
of	O
murder	O
and	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
perceived	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
it	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
round	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shops	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Cockram	I-pers
,	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
person	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
shook	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Ah	O
!	O
is	O
it	O
you	O
?	O
and	O
left	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lad	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
.	O
The	O
bundle	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
hand	O
by	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
father	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cockram	I-pers
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
next	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
taking	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
answered	O
well	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
the	O
court	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
happened	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Cockram	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
watchman	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Fleet	O
Lane	O
,	O
on	O
this	O
Sunday	O
night	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
bundle	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
go	O
but	O
struggl	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
lamp	O
just	O
behind	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
moon	O
shined	O
too	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sensible	O
when	O
you	O
fell	O
down	O
?	O
Cockram	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
murder	O
and	O
thieves	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
witness	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
clasp	O
'd	O
him	O
round	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
round	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
houses	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
place	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
bundle	O
fall	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
bundle	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lie	O
long	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
Cockram	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
fight	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Cooper	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
This	O
lad	O
brought	O
this	O
bundle	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
his	O
stand	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Fleet	O
Lane	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
with	O
his	O
son	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
stick	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
also	O
the	O
bundle	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
which	O
Jones	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
father	O
deposed	O
to	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
two	O
to	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
over	O
the	O
stick	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
lad	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
somebody	O
had	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
fellow	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
534.	O
John	B-pers
Linsey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
commiting	O
a	O
rape	O
upon	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lacey	I-pers
,	O
an	O
infant	O
of	O
seven	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
was	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
being	O
admitted	O
to	O
give	O
its	O
evidence	O
upon	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
no	O
other	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
535.	O
Ben	B-pers
the	I-pers
Coleheaver	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Eli	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Web	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Henry	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
steel	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
12	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
who	O
gave	O
their	O
evidence	O
against	O
Smith	O
and	O
Web	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Mason	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
430.	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
paper	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Omit	I-pers
the	O
accomplice	O
deposited	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
536	O
,	O
537	O
,	O
538.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blakeway	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Hopton	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
for	O
that	O
William	B-pers
Hopton	I-pers
on	O
Henry	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
stick	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
neck	O
,	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
back	O
did	O
,	O
strike	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
giving	O
him	O
divers	O
mortal	O
bruises	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
did	O
die	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
,	O
compassing	O
,	O
and	O
assisting	O
therein	O
,	O
December	O
10	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
131.	O
in	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pennant	I-pers
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bradly	I-pers
deposed	O
as	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lantley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
about	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
His	O
head	O
was	O
black	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purport	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
John	O
Greenwood	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Anlicker	I-pers
.	O
The	O
night	O
before	O
the	O
deceased	O
died	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
lay	O
his	O
death	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
to	O
one	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
apothecary	O
the	O
corrupted	O
blood	O
which	O
came	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
made	O
water	O
;	O
it	O
looked	O
like	O
blood	O
itself	O
.	O
The	O
apothecary	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
bruises	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
And	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lift	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
coffin	O
,	O
the	O
blood	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
from	O
a	O
hole	O
between	O
his	O
shoulders	O
.	O
Before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
he	O
complained	O
of	O
pains	O
all	O
over	O
his	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
by	O
when	O
you	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
apothecary	O
this	O
bloody	O
water	O
?	O
Anlicker	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bradley	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Greenwod	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
there	O
was	O
never	O
such	O
a	O
word	O
past	O
.	O
I	O
view	O
'd	O
the	O
body	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
such	O
place	O
as	O
is	O
mentioned	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
.	O
I	O
applied	O
four	O
blisters	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
two	O
on	O
his	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
arm	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
blood	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
foreman	O
upon	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
jury	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
no	O
particular	O
bruises	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
all	O
the	O
fore	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
by	O
my	O
inspection	O
that	O
any	O
bruises	O
were	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
The	O
body	O
was	O
putrify	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
by	O
lying	O
too	O
long	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jinks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bradley	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
jury	O
had	O
sat	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
how	O
they	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
accidental	O
Death	O
.	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
I	O
believe	O
were	O
not	O
concern	O
'd	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
539.	O
William	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Loveless	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Sept.	O
7	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Loveless	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
night	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Ratliff	O
Cross	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
at	O
a	O
boat-builder	O
's	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
dog	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
myself	O
round	O
to	O
drive	O
him	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
voice	O
say	O
your	O
money	O
this	O
moment	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
got	O
above	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
steps	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
and	O
star	O
'd	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
;	O
and	O
thought	O
somebody	O
joak	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
being	O
pretty	O
well	O
known	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
plain	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
taken	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
started	O
back	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
hanger	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
an	O
offer	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
stirr	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
paper	O
which	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
direction	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Red	O
Lion	O
Square	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
off	O
quietly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
recovering	O
my	O
spirits	O
,	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
open	O
'd	O
;	O
they	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
there	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
pointed	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Tanner	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
push	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
ale-house	O
,	O
the	O
duke	O
of	O
Cumberland	O
's	O
head	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Said	O
they	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
run	O
to	O
the	O
d	O
-	O
l	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
have	O
him	O
.	O
Turning	O
down	O
at	O
a	O
corner	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
heels	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
view	O
then	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
wrench	O
'd	O
the	O
cutlass	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
drawn	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Tanner	O
to	O
take	O
particular	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
We	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
watch	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
sheath	O
of	O
the	O
hanger	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
night	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
stop	O
thief	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
now	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
me	O
about	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
running	O
by	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
head	O
there	O
came	O
out	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
tired	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
run	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
once	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
Mr.	O
Loveless	O
)	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
the	O
hanger	O
was	O
then	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
persons	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fitzer	I-pers
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Service	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Duke	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
Thomas	O
Fitzer	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
voice	O
cry	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fitzer	I-pers
was	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
a	O
stroak	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
cutlass	O
,	O
and	O
Fitzer	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
hanger	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Loveless	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Loveless	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
glass	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
by	O
some	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
who	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Blackwall	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
that	O
gentleman	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
lane	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
so	O
one	O
person	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
justice	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
did	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Loveless	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
ancient	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
troubled	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
should	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
not	O
possible	O
one	O
man	O
should	O
be	O
like	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
?	O
a	O
body	O
may	O
be	O
mistaken	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
nine	O
witnesses	O
spoke	O
well	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
in	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
observed	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
since	O
he	O
returned	O
from	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
with	O
Admiral	O
Boscawen	B-pers
's	O
fleet	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
540.	O
Francis	B-pers
Crocket	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
excise	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
from	O
my	O
first	O
course	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
down	O
Virginia-street	B-place
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
standing	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
row	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
passed	O
them	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
round	O
my	O
neck	O
and	O
throw	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
expression	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
waiting	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
thieves	O
,	O
murder	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
do	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
immediately	O
run	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
calling	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
bit	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
thumb	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
job	O
on	O
the	O
temples	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
scar	O
of	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blood	O
ran	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
with	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
I	O
flew	O
at	O
him	O
as	O
I	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
and	O
tore	O
off	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
only	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
neighbours	O
got	O
to	O
their	O
windows	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
fled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
off	O
before	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
