TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
23d	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pennant	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
1749	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Public	O
may	O
be	O
assured	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
during	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PENNANT	I-pers
,	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
)	O
the	O
Sessions-Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
Four-pence	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
Sessions	O
shall	O
be	O
carefully	O
compris	O
'd	O
in	O
One	O
such	O
Four-penny	O
Book	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
further	O
Burthen	O
on	O
the	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PENNANT	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	O
BURNET	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
MICHAEL	O
FOSTER	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Coverly	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Fellows	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Noxon	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Messenger	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
George	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Alien	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Herritage	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bracket	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlings	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Foyster	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Broadhead	I-pers
,	O
Harwood	B-pers
Lassiter	I-pers
,	O
Leonard	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
109.	O
John	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gwinn	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
,	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
linnen	O
cheque	O
,	O
thirty	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
seventy	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
stripe	O
cotton	O
,	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Gwinn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
after	O
his	O
confession	O
,	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mackelly	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
517	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Mayoralty	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
against	O
him	O
but	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
who	O
gave	O
evidence	O
against	O
Garret	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
in	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
110	O
,	O
111.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Heyden	I-pers
,	O
late	B-place
of	I-place
Fulham	I-place
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eighteen	O
iron	O
bars	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Jan.	O
9	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
stopped	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
with	O
nine	O
of	O
the	O
bars	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
confessed	O
the	O
other	O
nine	O
they	O
had	O
carried	O
and	O
hid	O
in	O
a	O
lane	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
112.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
single	O
channel	O
pumps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
where	O
a	O
shoe-blacker	O
used	O
to	O
stand	O
:	O
knowing	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
shoe-blacker	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
pumps	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
name	O
William	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
wrote	O
within	O
the	O
pumps	O
:	O
but	O
William	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
property	O
not	O
being	O
fully	O
proved	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
113.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wanless	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Newbey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
ruffles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
shift	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
diaper	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
.	O
October	O
25	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
away	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
same	O
pawned	O
,	O
which	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
it	O
before	O
Abraham	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
114	O
,	O
115.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
widows	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
rug	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ezekiel	B-pers
Wolse	I-pers
,	O
being	O
goods	O
lent	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
in	O
their	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
.	O
Dec.	O
20	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
116	O
,	O
117.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Darvel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
bushels	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Nov.	O
14	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
for	O
an	O
offence	O
committed	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Michael	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
tried	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
42	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
13	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
118.	O
Jane	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
val	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
16	O
s	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Warding	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
;	O
some	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
others	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
119.	O
George	B-pers
Fear	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
portmanteau	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
l.	O
one	O
petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
sack	O
and	O
petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
l.	O
one	O
linnen	O
sack	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Rigby	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
3	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Martha	B-pers
Rigby	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Stow	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
her	O
apartment	O
.	O
William	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carman	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
portmanteau	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
other	O
parcels	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
cart	O
,	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
Spread	O
Eagle	O
in	O
Grace-Church-Street	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
lady	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Cavendish-Square	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
,	I-place
I	I-place
stopped	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
One	I-place
Tun	I-place
alehouse	I-place
to	O
give	O
my	O
horses	O
some	O
water	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
tail	O
rope	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
flung	O
it	O
off	O
backwards	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
followed	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
with	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
Forster	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
to	O
justice	O
Frazer	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
servant	O
came	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
direction	O
on	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
cart	O
with	O
William	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
We	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
One-Tun	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
curtain	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
on	O
William	B-pers
May	I-pers
:	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
within	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Round	O
Court	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
night	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
May	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
very	O
dark	O
?	O
May	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
many	O
lamps	O
about	O
where	O
the	O
cart	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
very	O
plain	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
120.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chessam	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
iron	O
hoops	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
December	O
15	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sevil	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
yard	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
hoops	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
two	O
there	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
121.	O
Henry	B-pers
Shuter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Jervice	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
3	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
one	O
or	O
more	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
servant	O
there	O
,	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
shewing	O
goods	O
to	O
another	O
customer	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
Baker	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
122.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cheese	O
10	O
lb	O
.	O
10	O
oz	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Dente	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Crawforth	I-pers
.	O
January	O
1	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Martine	I-pers
,	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
work	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
cheese	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cheese	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
cheese	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
123.	O
John	B-pers
Emory	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
twenty	O
four	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
one	O
Spanish	O
piece	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Kempster	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
December	O
17	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
.	O
Dec.	O
17	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
stockings	O
upon	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
;	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
marked	O
on	O
the	O
heel	O
within	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
swore	O
,	O
also	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
124	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
flannel	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
green	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
scarlet	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
towel	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
facing	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
take	O
away	O
these	O
goods	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
he	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
hid	O
herself	O
in	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
's	O
cellar	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
125.	O
William	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
locks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
300	O
pounds	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
January	O
11	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Dickman	I-pers
,	O
servant	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Manley	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
empty	O
house	O
from	O
whence	O
these	O
goods	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
others	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
got	O
two	O
watchmen	O
,	O
with	O
whose	O
assistance	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dillimore	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
by	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
jumped	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
two	O
locks	O
fell	O
from	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
an	O
inside	O
and	O
an	O
outside	O
door	O
belonging	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
they	O
took	O
some	O
small	O
screws	O
belonging	O
thereto	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
handle	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
locks	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
below	O
there	O
lay	O
two	O
bags	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tinderbox	O
and	O
steel	O
on	O
a	O
shelf	O
just	O
over	O
it	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
watchman	O
,	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hormey	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
empty	O
house	O
from	O
whence	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
belongs	O
to	O
Mr	O
Henley	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
coming	O
by	O
him	O
had	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
from	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
126.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Kennish	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Isaac	B-pers
Kennish	I-pers
.	O
December	O
11	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Kennish	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Hampshire	I-place
Hog	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
parish	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Judith	B-pers
Dyke	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
I	O
having	O
but	O
two	O
silver	O
tankards	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
in	O
use	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
draw	O
them	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
club	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
my	O
company	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
that	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
towards	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
company	O
were	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
the	O
windows	O
were	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
room	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
my	O
girl	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
your	O
tankard	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
witness	O
(	O
Warwick	O
)	O
staid	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
has	O
took	O
away	O
something	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
either	O
pewter	O
or	O
silver	O
,	O
like	O
a	O
tankard	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
Judith	B-pers
Dyke	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
she	O
should	O
come	O
into	O
trouble	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
pish	O
at	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
young	O
man	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
Warwick	O
still	O
abode	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
stay	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
heart	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
Warwick	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
woman	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
gave	O
me	O
intelligence	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
made	O
answer	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
(	O
we	O
could	O
hear	O
her	O
whisper	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
Warwick	O
to	O
New-prison	O
;	O
my	O
lodger	O
said	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
hid	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
fear	O
the	O
woman	O
has	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knocked	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
immediately	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
admit	O
her	O
to	O
bail	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
tankard	O
since	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
Warwick	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
knife	O
,	O
or	O
such	O
instruments	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
tankard	O
about	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
justice	O
admitted	O
Warwick	O
to	O
bail	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
Thursday	O
evening	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
between	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Phillip	B-pers
Warwick	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
shall	O
we	O
not	O
drink	O
together	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Hercules	O
and	O
Pillars	O
,	O
in	O
Bow-lane	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Bread-street	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Dyke	O
rapp	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
sash	O
window	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bull's-head	O
:	O
We	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
Tankards	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
money	O
to	O
receive	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
is	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Hampshire-hog	O
,	O
in	O
Goswell-street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
o'clock	O
;	O
they	O
pretended	O
to	O
play	O
at	O
cards	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
whom	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
money	O
of	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Hosier	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
person	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
mentioned	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
talked	O
to	O
themselves	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
company	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
mov	O
'd	O
from	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
who	O
kept	O
his	O
place	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
beer	O
came	O
about	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
by	O
and	O
bye	O
I	O
heard	O
liquor	O
spill	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
and	O
saw	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
tankard	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cover	O
'd	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
flap	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
cover	O
'd	O
:	O
Presently	O
I	O
heard	O
liquor	O
spill	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
betwixt	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
whom	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
receive	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
whisper	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
feared	O
we	O
should	O
come	O
into	O
trouble	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
steel	O
away	O
a	O
tankard	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
pshaw	O
,	O
pshaw	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
At	O
going	O
away	O
the	O
woman	O
went	O
first	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
second	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
with	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
pot	O
or	O
a	O
tankard	O
in	O
that	O
hand	O
:	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
speak	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
meaning	O
Hosier	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
skirt	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
business	O
with	O
that	O
man	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Hosier	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
tankard	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
Said	O
Hosier	O
to	O
the	O
Girl	O
,	O
see	O
if	O
there	O
be	O
any	O
thing	O
missing	O
?	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
Constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
thinking	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
deny	O
what	O
I	O
whisper	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
of	O
my	O
suspicion	O
about	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
Friday	O
following	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Bedford-court	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
to	O
Covent-garden	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
thing	O
then	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
Character	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ansey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
Warwick	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
some	O
great	O
concern	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
was	O
not	O
domin	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
if	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
very	O
likely	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
tankard	O
might	O
be	O
met	O
with	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
likewise	O
mentioned	O
his	O
whispering	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
as	O
mentioned	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
of	O
Stevens	O
's	O
spilling	O
the	O
beer	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Slackman	I-pers
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
the	O
constable	O
said	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
the	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
paid	O
13	O
d.	O
half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
three	O
half-pence	O
to	O
pay	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
told	O
me	O
Mr.	O
Hosier	O
would	O
do	O
that	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
box	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
Warwick	O
,	O
Hosier	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
where	O
he	O
did	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
tankard	O
close	O
behind	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
away	O
without	O
another	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
draw	O
it	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
was	O
then	O
for	O
going	O
without	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
drew	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
I	O
am	O
drunk	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
drink	O
any	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
adding	O
he	O
was	O
sick	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
my	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
something	O
spill	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
somebody	O
had	O
been	O
spewing	O
,	O
or	O
there	O
was	O
water	O
running	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
tankard	O
then	O
,	O
nor	O
have	O
I	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
standing	O
behind	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
hard	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
another	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
beer	O
spill	O
again	O
:	O
then	O
there	O
were	O
7	O
d.	O
half	O
penny	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
her	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Warwick	O
whisper	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
head	O
a	O
shake	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
back	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
:	O
And	O
likewise	O
heard	O
Warwick	O
tell	O
Hosier	O
as	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
beer	O
in	O
the	O
tankard	O
when	O
it	O
stood	O
behind	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
127	O
,	O
128.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Joyner	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
ten	O
Foot	O
double	O
Deals	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
ten	O
Deal	O
Battins	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Riggs	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
landed	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
the	O
mate	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
will	O
give	O
the	O
Court	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Eley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
my	O
bear	O
,	O
crying	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
my	O
Brother	O
Watchman	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
step	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
Taylor	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
this	O
came	O
William	B-pers
Joyner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Taylor	O
,	O
how	O
many	O
have	O
you	O
carried	O
;	O
Taylor	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
Joyner	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
?	O
for	O
looking	O
for	O
the	O
bitch	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
;	O
Joyner	O
asked	O
which	O
wife	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
Jenny	B-pers
Joyner	I-pers
said	O
these	O
deals	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
up	O
a-drift	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
have	O
had	O
as	O
many	O
more	O
at	O
Ratcliff	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sunk	O
one	O
boat	O
in	O
bringing	O
them	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
.	O
The	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
after	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
my	O
Round	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
deals	O
lying	O
in	O
George	O
Alley	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Hour	O
of	O
11	O
I	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
12	O
deals	O
about	O
10	O
feet	O
long	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
watchman	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
'd	O
make	O
haste	O
round	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Lunn	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
said	O
all	O
these	O
were	O
brought	O
on	O
shore	O
since	O
10	O
o'Clock	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ludwell	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Lunn	O
asked	O
them	O
whose	O
Property	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
a	O
drift	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
sunk	O
a	O
boat	O
near	O
Ratcliff	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
up	O
many	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
wet	O
?	O
Herbert	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
but	O
two	O
that	O
was	O
so	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lunn	O
deposed	O
as	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Luddwell	I-pers
the	O
same	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
Addition	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
near	O
King	O
and	O
Queen	O
stairs	O
,	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
do	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
tide	O
running	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
;	O
the	O
deals	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
barge	O
at	O
Rotherhive	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
deals	O
in	O
a	O
position	O
ready	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
away	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
deals	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
barge	O
there	O
wanted	O
22	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bedlington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
mate	O
of	O
the	O
William	O
and	O
Jane	O
belonging	O
to	O
Whitby	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
these	O
deals	O
were	O
landed	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
were	O
deals	O
and	O
battens	O
gone	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
barge	O
.	O
I	O
hearing	O
there	O
were	O
deals	O
landed	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Riggs	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
cargo	O
which	O
I	O
brought	O
from	O
Christiana	O
in	O
Norway	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
at	O
the	O
ends	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
with	O
red	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
stroaks	O
downwards	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
their	O
thickness	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
yellow	O
wood	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
had	O
they	O
been	O
over-board	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
they	O
mention	O
,	O
the	O
tide	O
then	O
running	O
the	O
wrong	O
way	O
;	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
barge	O
without	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
hands	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
129	O
,	O
130.	O
Dennes	B-pers
Brannam	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Purcel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whiffin	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Dec.	O
13	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whiffin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shore-ditch	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
near	B-place
the	I-place
Unicorn	I-place
publick	I-place
house	I-place
in	I-place
Shore-ditch	I-place
,	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
an	O
evidence	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
dodg	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
minutes	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
skull	O
was	O
crack	O
'd	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
who	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
so	O
suddenly	O
;	O
(	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
hug	O
scar	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
)	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
3	O
minutes	O
before	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wigg	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
being	O
near	O
and	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
.	O
While	O
they	O
were	O
following	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
one	O
's	O
eyes	O
and	O
another	O
's	O
limbs	O
.	O
Brannam	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
sold	O
my	O
hat	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
my	O
wig	O
they	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
himself	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
before	O
George	B-pers
St	I-pers
.	O
Lawrence	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
George	B-pers
St	I-pers
.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
last	O
Sessions	O
,	O
Brannam	O
being	O
just	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Webb-Square	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Purcel	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
Purcel	O
drink	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
pawn	O
your	O
ha	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
said	O
Purcel	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
pawn	O
my	O
shuttle	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
shall	O
get	O
more	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
three-pence	O
half-penny	O
left	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
dram	O
for	O
each	O
to	O
put	O
us	O
in	O
spirits	O
:	O
said	O
Dennes	O
Brannam	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
hammer	O
and	O
chissel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
either	O
have	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
where	O
I	O
come	O
from	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
Purcel	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Webb-Square	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
a	O
Man	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
hit	O
him	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Purcel	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
Alehouse	O
in	O
Webb	O
Square	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
which	O
cost	O
6	O
d.	O
Brannam	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
two	O
young	O
fellows	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
drank	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
six-pence	O
out	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
(	O
either	O
to	O
get	O
money	O
by	O
house-breaking	O
,	O
or	O
knocking	O
people	O
down	O
and	O
robbing	O
them	O
)	O
we	O
went	O
along	O
Shore-ditch	O
,	O
and	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Black	O
Dog	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sellar	O
open	O
,	O
said	O
Brannam	O
,	O
stay	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
can	O
buy	O
a	O
shirt	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
seller	O
said	O
,	O
Brannam	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
?	O
Brannam	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
struck	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
he	O
let	O
Brannam	O
go	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Whiffin	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
were	O
walking	O
before	O
us	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Whiffin	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
man	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Whiffin	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
uncle	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
walked	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
Brannam	O
took	O
the	O
hammer	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
he	O
hit	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
with	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
but	O
Brannam	O
's	O
blow	O
fetched	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
much	O
;	O
then	O
Brannam	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
take	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
people	O
,	O
came	O
making	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
were	O
obliged	O
to	O
run	O
;	O
Brannam	O
delivered	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
wig	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
hat	O
to	O
Purcel	O
,	O
we	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
Brannam	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
Magpye	O
Alley	O
to	O
his	O
brother-in-law	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Phenix-street	O
;	O
presently	O
up	O
comes	O
Purcel	O
,	O
said	O
Brannam	O
,	O
what	O
signifies	O
staying	O
here	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
some	O
more	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
hat	O
we	O
left	O
there	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Wheeler-street	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
did	O
;	O
Brannam	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
last	O
blow	O
with	O
the	O
hammer	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
place	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
an	O
uproat	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
White	O
Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
a	O
man	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
staggered	O
against	O
a	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Dugley	O
Macanley	O
.	O
Brannam	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
knocked	O
down	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
knocked	O
down	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
White-Chapel	O
:	O
He	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
was	O
so	O
hurt	O
by	O
the	O
blow	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
blood	O
comes	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
ears	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
last	O
Sun-day	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
another	O
in	O
Wheeler-street	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Butts	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Brannam	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
evidence	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
near	O
the	O
Black	O
Dog	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
journeymen	O
:	O
The	O
man	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
?	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
for	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
alarmed	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
Mr.	O
Whiffin	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
gore	O
blood	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Whiffin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
uncle	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
before	O
him	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
rising	O
without	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bloody	O
condition	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
about	O
three	O
stones	O
cast	O
from	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Unicorn	O
Brew-house	O
,	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
131.	O
William	B-pers
Hopton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Piercy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Gents	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
on	O
Henry	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
against	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
Sovereign	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	O
did	O
kill	O
or	O
murder	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
widow	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
Henry	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
;	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
of	O
the	O
blows	O
and	O
wounds	O
he	O
received	O
of	O
those	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
road	O
near	O
Chelsea	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
was	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
a	O
publick-house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
side	O
:	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
these	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
violently	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
please	O
to	O
have	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
son	O
of	O
a	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
soon	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
want	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
:	O
My	O
husband	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
strong	O
man	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
resent	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
2d	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
altogether	O
,	O
beating	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
with	O
sticks	O
,	O
some	O
with	O
their	O
fists	O
,	O
and	O
treading	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
They	O
had	O
all	O
sticks	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
murder	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
mud	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
rail	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
strike	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
call	O
help	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
then	O
had	O
scuffled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mud	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
by	O
intreaties	O
they	O
became	O
a	O
little	O
easy	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
and	O
'Squire	O
Martin	O
came	O
with	O
his	O
pistols	O
and	O
some	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
surrounded	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
civil	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
went	O
to	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
being	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
to	O
bed	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
Coach	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
his	O
eyes	O
was	O
almost	O
torn	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
face	O
,	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
breast	O
was	O
bruis	O
'd	O
and	O
very	O
black	O
;	O
he	O
complained	O
much	O
of	O
inward	O
pain	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
spot	O
on	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
suppose	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
trod	O
upon	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
attended	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Greenwood	O
,	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
.	O
He	O
began	O
complaining	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
was	O
well	O
afterwards	O
;	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
healthy	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
all	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
crve	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
,	O
illness	O
,	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
really	O
believe	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
the	O
wounds	O
and	O
bruises	O
he	O
received	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Mary	O
Bradley	O
I	O
really	O
do	O
believe	O
it	O
;	O
his	O
head	O
was	O
swell	O
'd	O
almost	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
eye	O
tore	O
in	O
a	O
terrible	O
manner	O
:	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
one	O
Philip	B-pers
Lumpley	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
declare	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
?	O
My	O
husband	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
never	O
worse	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
better	O
soon	O
:	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
this	O
is	O
owing	O
to	O
the	O
blows	O
you	O
got	O
from	O
those	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dying	O
man	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
lay	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
one	O
in	O
particular	O
?	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
and	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
pray	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
brought	O
to	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
be	O
righted	O
.	O
About	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
himself	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
spit	O
any	O
blood	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
.	O
He	O
began	O
to	O
spit	O
blood	O
on	O
the	O
wednesday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
it	O
became	O
like	O
a	O
spungy	O
matter	O
,	O
of	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
colours	O
:	O
I	O
shewed	O
the	O
pot	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Greenwood	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
spit	O
such	O
like	O
before	O
.	O
His	O
belly	O
was	O
swell	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
complained	O
of	O
pains	O
and	O
aches	O
all	O
over	O
him	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
spitting	O
of	O
blood	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
apothecary	O
where	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
where	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
?	O
but	O
from	O
the	O
bruises	O
your	O
husband	O
has	O
receiv	O
'd	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Gains	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
smoaking	O
his	O
pipe	O
below	O
;	O
those	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
,	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
break	O
it	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
I	O
was	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
behind	O
his	O
back	O
:	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
fellow	O
(	O
a	O
Baker	O
)	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
son	O
of	O
a	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
instantly	O
knock	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
his	O
stick	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
other	O
five	O
men	O
behind	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
recovered	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
strong	O
,	O
hail	O
,	O
haroy	O
man	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
man	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
come	O
up	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
sticks	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
:	O
They	O
all	O
struck	O
him	O
I	O
know	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Candle	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
one	O
by	O
one	O
,	O
after	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
tall	O
fellow	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
,	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
they	O
were	O
dead	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
surrounded	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
They	O
put	O
about	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
Candles	O
in	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
for	O
fighting	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
every	O
day	O
after	O
this	O
.	O
She	O
described	O
his	O
branks	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
or	O
worse	O
than	O
the	O
former	O
Witness	O
,	O
sash	O
his	O
head	O
would	O
hardly	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
peck	O
measure	O
,	O
his	O
spitting	O
,	O
corruption	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
was	O
the	O
civilest	O
of	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Jemmy	O
Parkinson	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Baker	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
Death	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
you	O
do	O
now	O
?	O
Gains	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
Coroner	O
would	O
not	O
hear	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
see	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
laughing	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
that	O
sat	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Lantley	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
his	O
Illness	O
,	O
and	O
confirm	O
'd	O
what	O
the	O
Widow	O
had	O
sworn	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
dying	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
complained	O
much	O
about	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
stomach	O
,	O
and	O
head	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
black	O
about	O
his	O
shoulders	O
,	O
head	O
,	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
neck	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
behaved	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
the	O
six	O
persons	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Ridley	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
those	O
six	O
persons	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
:	O
we	O
let	O
them	O
all	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
we	O
stood	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
heard	O
murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
Red	O
Lyon	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
heard	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
heap	O
of	O
young	O
men	O
beating	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
his	O
head	O
was	O
swelled	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
terribly	O
bruised	O
about	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
extream	O
bad	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
eat	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
illness	O
I	O
believe	O
ten	O
times	O
;	O
sometimes	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
recover	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
live	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
heave	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
hardly	O
fetch	O
his	O
breath	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
from	O
an	O
inward	O
bruise	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
his	O
spitting	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Gains	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
husband	O
to	O
the	O
witness	O
Dorothy	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
going	O
;	O
with	O
'Squire	O
Martin	O
towards	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
condition	O
,	O
his	O
eye	O
almost	O
torn	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
complained	O
always	O
after	O
of	O
inwards	O
pains	O
,	O
and	O
spit	O
blood	O
and	O
corruption	O
;	O
afterwards	O
,	O
this	O
I	O
observed	O
till	O
within	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
his	O
death	O
proceeded	O
from	O
those	O
six	O
men	O
beating	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
make	O
yourself	O
easy	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
in	O
God	O
those	O
fellows	O
will	O
be	O
made	O
to	O
suffer	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
conjealed	O
blood	O
round	O
his	O
neck	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
breast	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
heard	O
before	O
the	O
coroner	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
gentleman	O
belonging	O
to	O
him	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
beat	O
by	O
those	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
time	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
frightned	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
enough	O
him	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
well	O
afterwards	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
beat	O
about	O
the	O
head	O
and	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
very	O
bad	O
marks	O
appeared	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
others	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
say	O
something	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
townsman	O
;	O
hearing	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
for	O
this	O
unhappy	O
affair	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
proofs	O
were	O
made	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
woman	O
Gains	O
was	O
examined	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
the	O
least	O
obstruction	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
coroner	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
witness	O
came	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
the	O
coroner	O
was	O
summing	O
up	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
person	O
was	O
refused	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross-examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
coroner	O
laugh	O
'd	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
a	O
trifling	O
affair	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
surgeon	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
on	O
monday	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pain	O
over	O
his	O
shoulders	O
,	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
head	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
evident	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
sad	O
blows	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
swelled	O
;	O
his	O
pulse	O
was	O
very	O
quick	O
;	O
I	O
bled	O
him	O
very	O
largely	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
prodigiously	O
better	O
,	O
but	O
still	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
pain	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
people	O
at	O
a	O
boxing-match	O
beat	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
done	O
well	O
again	O
;	O
his	O
eye	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
common	O
black	O
eye	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
swelled	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
his	O
Life	O
was	O
in	O
danger	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
affair	O
was	O
made	O
up	O
:	O
(	O
to	O
another	O
Q.	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
him	O
in	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
danger	O
)	O
adding	O
,	O
his	O
head	O
was	O
swelled	O
about	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
half	O
my	O
fist	O
about	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
when	O
dead	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
coroner	O
attended	O
his	O
body	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
particular	O
appeared	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
neither	O
do	O
I	O
think	O
his	O
death	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
what	O
he	O
received	O
this	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
after	O
this	O
action	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
8	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
beat	O
;	O
he	O
complained	O
of	O
pains	O
all	O
over	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
short	O
breath	O
'd	O
and	O
severish	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
great	O
cold	O
,	O
by	O
being	O
carried	O
about	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bled	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
your	O
husband	O
complain	O
of	O
getting	O
cold	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Greenwood	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
blood	O
in	O
the	O
pot	O
,	O
or	O
corruption	O
?	O
Greenwood	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
pot	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
rough	O
matter	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
appearance	O
of	O
blood	O
;	O
his	O
head	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
eye	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
needed	O
any	O
surgeon	O
's	O
business	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
fullness	O
on	O
one	O
eye	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
examine	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
two	O
blisters	O
on	O
his	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
bruised	O
,	O
as	O
mentioned	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
stripp	O
'd	O
down	O
his	O
cloathes	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
bruises	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
black	O
in	O
those	O
parts	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
one	O
side	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
common	O
to	O
persons	O
who	O
die	O
a	O
natural	O
death	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
in	O
children	O
and	O
grown	O
persons	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
catching	O
of	O
cold	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
his	O
being	O
beat	O
;	O
he	O
complained	O
of	O
very	O
short	O
breath	O
;	O
I	O
talked	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
in	O
conversation	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
beat	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
worse	O
than	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
well	O
sooner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
at	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
leaning	O
with	O
his	O
head	O
upon	O
a	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
wet	O
through	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
rainy	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
surgeon	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
danger	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
take	O
six	O
guineas	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Ten	O
Persons	O
gave	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
the	O
foreman	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Coroner	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
witness	O
Gains	O
met	O
with	O
no	O
obstruction	O
at	O
all	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
coroner	O
took	O
much	O
pains	O
to	O
explain	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
wilful	O
murder	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
132.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Alcon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Jan.	O
10	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
Devonshire	O
Square	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
Night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Houndsditch	I-place
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
brought	O
us	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
:	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
10	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
watch	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
about	O
10	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
however	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
evening	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
or	O
two	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
Constable	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
at	O
Guild-hall	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
Watch	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Solomon	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wardling	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
confirmed	O
this	O
confession	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
133.	O
Rebeccah	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
capuchin	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Lenox	B-pers
Ryder	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
134.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
8	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whitelock	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
-	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Whitelock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
upwards	O
of	O
14	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	B-place
Paterson	I-place
's	I-place
shop	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Cloysters	I-place
;	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
his	O
looks	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
none	O
under	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
others	O
lay	O
to	O
publick	O
view	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
4	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
4	O
s.	O
Upon	O
which	O
,	O
they	O
stood	O
pausing	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
bid	O
4	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
told	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
'bate	O
a	O
farthing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
many	O
there	O
were	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
counted	O
seven	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
very	O
well	O
pleased	O
with	O
her	O
counting	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
opened	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
second	O
or	O
third	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
counted	O
seven	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
all	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
desired	O
she	O
might	O
sold	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
trouble	O
herself	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
whipp	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
ran	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
trailed	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
running	O
after	O
stepped	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
gathered	O
them	O
all	O
up	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Riley	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
arm	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
ran	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
.	O
Master	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
mob	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
witness	O
will	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
confirmed	O
this	O
evidence	O
in	O
every	O
particular	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
former	O
witness	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Riley	O
,	O
are	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
bringing	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Riley	O
deposed	O
,	O
concerning	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
bringing	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Paterson	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
135.	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
George	B-pers
Merryman	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
one	O
peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
monies	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
136.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
Lead	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Christopher	O
's	O
Lestocks	O
,	O
Dec.	O
22	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
137.	O
John	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
half-inch	O
wainscot	O
boards	O
,	O
5	O
inch	O
wainscot	O
boards	O
,	O
one	O
3	O
qrs	O
.	O
and	O
half	O
board	O
,	O
one	O
foot	O
of	O
mahogany	O
,	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
fineer	O
,	O
10	O
walnut-tree	O
fineers	O
,	O
three	O
tin	O
cannisters	O
,	O
one	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
four	O
sets	O
of	O
brass	O
work	O
for	O
knife	O
cases	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
hinges	O
,	O
50	O
escutcheons	O
,	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
,	O
desk	O
hinges	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
all	O
valued	O
at	O
15	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
13	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
Cabinet-maker	O
,	O
lives	O
in	O
Fenchurch	B-place
street	I-place
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
Journeyman	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
his	O
practice	O
,	O
at	O
times	O
,	O
to	O
cut	O
the	O
wood	O
,	O
and	O
convey	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
as	O
likewise	O
brass-work	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
also	O
drawn	O
Robert	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
affair	O
,	O
by	O
hiring	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
carry	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
fully	O
prov	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
Apprentice	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
Likewise	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
confest	O
taking	O
away	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
brass	O
work	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
138.	O
Margaret	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Lanskill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tricket	I-pers
;	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
3	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
139.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Backwell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Tho	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
Dec.	O
14	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Eliz	B-pers
.	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
.	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
cloath	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Anderson	O
.	O
On	O
Dec.	O
14	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	B-place
from	I-place
Carnaby-market	I-place
,	I-place
into	I-place
Silver-street	I-place
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
my	O
Cloak	O
;	O
they	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
dragg	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
They	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
moonlight	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
;	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Benj	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
140.	O
John	B-pers
Kible	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Hannah	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Geo	I-pers
Warfoot	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
one	O
linnen	O
pocket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
monies	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hannah	O
,	O
Dec.	O
14	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
141.	O
Henry	B-pers
Woolfington	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
five	O
Guineas	O
in	O
Gold	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
;	O
at	O
my	O
entrance	O
into	O
the	O
first	O
Five	O
Fields	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
Mr.	O
Hans	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
and	O
stayed	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
Hans	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
;	O
accordingly	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
slowly	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
and	I-place
Thistle	I-place
,	O
and	O
passed	O
the	O
Fountain	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
are	O
some	O
posts	O
to	O
pass	O
through	O
to	O
enter	O
into	O
another	O
field	O
,	O
but	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
through	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
second	O
field	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
Hans	O
again	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
slowly	O
after	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Footsteps	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
;	O
the	O
Ground	O
being	O
very	O
wet	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
them	O
step	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Thistle	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
again	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
Hans	O
,	O
I	O
hear	O
some	O
people	O
coming	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
common	O
path-way	O
was	O
ancle-deep	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
upon	O
higher	O
ground	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
kept	O
the	O
path	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
dirt	O
;	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
yards	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
blows	O
struck	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
words	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
say	O
,	O
pray	O
do	O
n't	O
murder	O
a	O
poor	O
distressed	O
Sailor	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
with	O
large	O
sticks	O
,	O
beating	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
:	O
Two	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
On	O
my	O
turning	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
his	O
particular	O
voice	O
I	O
well	O
know	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
raseal	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
your	O
watch	O
and	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
cut	O
you	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
large	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
mop	O
or	O
broom-stick	O
,	O
swinging	O
it	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
attempting	O
to	O
strike	O
at	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
myself	O
in	O
a	O
posture	O
of	O
defence	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
touch	O
'd	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
having	O
a	O
slight	O
oak-stick	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
kept	O
him	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
easy	O
;	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
to	O
the	O
low	O
ground	O
,	O
so	O
got	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
swearing	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
cut	O
me	O
to	O
pieces	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
surrender	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
escape	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
close	O
quarters	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
either	O
a	O
sword	O
or	O
a	O
bayonnet	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
which	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
prick	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
forehead	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
fell	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
chink	O
:	O
He	O
held	O
fast	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
trembling	O
he	O
seemed	O
as	O
much	O
afraid	O
of	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
five	O
Guineas	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
Silver	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
sling	O
down	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
Guineas	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
knowing	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
easily	O
find	O
them	O
again	O
till	O
the	O
morrow	O
;	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
my	O
hand	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
five	O
Guineas	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
The	O
others	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
friend	O
all	O
along	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
let	O
my	O
friend	O
be	O
murder	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
watch	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
walk	O
'd	O
as	O
contentedly	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
could	O
do	O
by	O
my	O
side	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
my	O
friend	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
my	O
friend	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
heard	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
five	O
Guineas	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
My	O
friend	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
dirt	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
into	O
the	O
Robin-hood	O
and	O
Little-john	O
,	O
being	O
robb	O
'd	O
within	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Invalids	O
drinking	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
make	O
haste	O
and	O
get	O
help	O
,	O
we	O
might	O
take	O
them	O
before	O
they	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
seeing	O
the	O
wound	O
on	O
my	O
forehead	O
,	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
a	O
bayonnet	O
:	O
His	O
wife	O
fetch	O
'd	O
down	O
a	O
gun	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
go	O
without	O
my	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
bitch	O
to	O
call	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
his	O
Candle	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
's	O
stick	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
entring	O
of	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
College	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
Luke	B-pers
Lidier	I-pers
who	O
knew	O
my	O
tongue	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
person	O
in	O
so	O
particular	O
a	O
manner	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
quite	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
after	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
that	O
evening	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
foot	O
soldiers	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
put	O
off	O
bad	O
money	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
at	O
the	O
Robin-hood	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
satisfied	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Lidier	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
near	O
eight	O
o'Clock	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
's	O
Tongue	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
's	O
that	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
?	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
advis	O
'd	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
see	O
how	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
used	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
very	O
dirtily	O
;	O
he	O
stood	O
upon	O
the	O
Titter-Totter	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
to	O
Harp-alley	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
7-night	O
,	O
going	O
by	O
Somerset-house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
stood	O
century	O
;	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Men	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Babb	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
acquaint	O
Mr	O
Miller	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
saw	O
a	O
Man	O
whom	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
said	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
:	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Babb	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
's	O
.	O
We	O
four	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Parade	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
guards	O
reliev	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
saw	O
upon	O
guard	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
was	O
talking	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
you	O
describ	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
'd	O
round	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
well	O
satisfied	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
Man	O
.	O
Babb	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
Lodging	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
an	O
ale-house	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
almost	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
Ligonier	O
's	O
Horse	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
four	O
soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
trumpeter	O
's	O
wife	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
from	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
,	O
till	O
seven	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
reckoning	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
began	O
to	O
quarrel	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
desist	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
,	O
had	O
a	O
short	O
sword	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
drink	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
Chelsea	O
Clock	O
struck	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
.	O
Said	O
Swinney	O
to	O
Macdonald	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
stay	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
to-night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
bed	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
so	O
both	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
took	O
the	O
reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
two	O
bad	O
Shillings	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
took	O
up	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
I	O
hearing	O
Mr.	O
Miller	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
soldier	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
soldiers	O
in	O
company	O
that	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
abused	O
his	O
friend	O
;	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
thus	O
-	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
lusty	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
was	O
inclin	O
'd	O
to	O
sat	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
full	O
fat	O
hand	O
,	O
black	O
shock	O
hair	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
wigg	O
answerable	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
his	O
hand	O
warm	O
withal	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
coarse	O
voice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Thistle	O
and	O
Crown	O
-	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
about	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
very	O
good	O
Evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Collonboon	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Thistle	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
the	O
Five	O
Fields	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
Christmass	O
,	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
seven	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
living	O
soul	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
stagger	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
remain	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
'till	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
nine	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
but	O
my	O
own	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
threshold	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
at	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
children	O
to-bed	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
staid	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Colloxhoon	I-pers
,	O
his	O
young	O
daughter	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
this	O
same	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
her	O
uncle	O
Henry	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
leave	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
her	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
works	O
at	O
Farmer	O
Batt	B-pers
's	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
John	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
;	O
that	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
children	O
to	O
bed	O
as	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
seven	O
.	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Thistle	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
Christmas	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
from	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
'till	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to-bed	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
any	O
farther	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
than	O
to	O
the	O
threshold	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
there	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Worterbridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Thistle	O
and	O
Crown	O
this	O
very	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
regiment	O
of	O
guards	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
eight	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
brother-in-law	O
,	O
all	O
drinking	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
with	O
them	O
'till	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
nine	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Captain	O
Waling	B-pers
,	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
soldier	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
regiment	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
request	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
made	O
master	O
at	O
arms	O
on	O
board	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
vessels	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Toose	I-pers
,	O
a	O
green-grocer	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
months	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Courtley	I-pers
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Lewis	B-pers
Longfield	I-pers
,	O
has	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
upright	O
man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lampier	I-pers
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
lov	O
'd	O
and	O
caress	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
his	O
officers	O
,	O
and	O
esteem	O
'd	O
by	O
all	O
his	O
brother	O
soldiers	O
.	O
This	O
being	O
the	O
soldier	O
who	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
on	O
the	O
affair	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
told	O
been	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
such	O
people	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
person	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
;	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
description	O
given	O
,	O
it	O
seemed	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
.	O
This	O
Witness	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
guilty	O
;	O
for	O
they	O
looked	O
very	O
blank	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
soldier	O
)	O
and	O
this	O
witness	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
that	O
night	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Lidier	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
Lampler	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Macdonald	O
were	O
guilty	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Robin-hood	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
sprinkle	O
of	O
blood	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
eye	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
five	O
Guineas	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
slipshoe	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
shoes	O
and	O
pursue	O
them	O
?	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
much	O
matter	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
cane	O
or	O
stick	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
servant	O
my	O
Dog	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Gun	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
twopenny	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
my	O
man	O
twopence	O
;	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
about	O
fifty	O
or	O
sixty	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
impossible	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
should	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
there	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
my	O
window	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
place	O
where	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
stick	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
was	O
about	O
half-way	O
between	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
being	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Fowler	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
142.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Delaval	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Dec.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
143.	O
Philip	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Solomon	B-pers
Gibard	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
;	O
3	O
iron	O
vices	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
goose	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15.	O
one	O
rasp	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Solomon	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Jan	O
2d	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
144.	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
22d	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
145.	O
Ann	B-pers
Collings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
seal	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
six	O
Shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
146.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
seven	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mordicai	B-pers
Pates	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
13	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confest	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
four	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
147.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Iron	O
half	O
hundred	O
weight	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Halfhead	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
8	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
weight	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
Gate	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
148.	O
John	B-pers
Leminghau	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
large	O
book	O
,	O
entitled	O
,	O
A	O
Collection	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
Statues	O
now	O
in	O
Use	O
,	O
with	O
Notes	O
in	O
the	O
Margin	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Manby	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
of	O
Lincoln's-Inn	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
12	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Book	O
was	O
his	O
Property	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
books	O
in	O
Mr.	O
King	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
and	O
walked	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
posts	O
,	O
near	O
little	O
Moorgate	O
;	O
he	O
throw	O
'd	O
the	O
book	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
King	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
brought	O
back	O
the	O
book	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Lockyer	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
Russian	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
very	O
frequently	O
with	O
his	O
Father	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
priest	O
to	O
the	O
Russian	O
Chapel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Last	O
summer	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
Henley	O
upon	O
Thames	O
,	O
for	O
his	O
education	O
:	O
His	O
appearance	O
,	O
education	O
,	O
and	O
behaviour	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
for	O
real	O
want	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
Years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
first	O
coming	O
into	O
England	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
himself	O
always	O
like	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
express	O
'd	O
great	O
duty	O
to	O
his	O
Father	O
upon	O
all	O
occasions	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
short	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
moral	O
man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
capable	O
of	O
judging	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
's	O
opinion	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
real	O
necessity	O
that	O
drove	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
his	O
own	O
Father	O
is	O
chaplain	O
to	O
her	O
Imperial	O
Majesty	O
of	O
Russia	O
;	O
his	O
Father	O
was	O
recalled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
person	O
unfortunately	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
Country	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Cavanah	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
Father	O
in	O
Russia	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
Man	O
of	O
great	O
Character	O
in	O
the	O
Russian	O
Church	O
:	O
His	O
Father	O
left	O
him	O
here	O
for	O
his	O
Education	O
,	O
and	O
furnish	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
apparel	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
some	O
extravagancies	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Father	O
left	O
him	O
without	O
letting	O
him	O
know	O
of	O
his	O
departure	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
thing	O
was	O
merely	O
out	O
of	O
necessity	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
tried	O
at	O
his	O
request	O
by	O
a	O
Jury	O
of	O
half	O
Foreigners	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
privately	O
whipped	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
messenger	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Russian	O
Embassador	O
,	O
to	O
assure	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
his	O
crime	O
would	O
admit	O
of	O
corporal	O
Punishment	O
,	O
the	O
Ambassador	O
would	O
order	O
him	O
a	O
safe	O
passage	O
to	O
Russia	O
.	O
149.	O
Constantine	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
3	O
copper	O
japan	O
tea-kettles	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Shag-breeches	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hipkiss	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
15	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Hipkiss	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Birmingham	O
Waggon	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Yard	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sarazen	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
,	I-place
on	I-place
Snow-hill	I-place
;	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
Waggon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
tumbled	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
struggle	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
Hostler	O
came	O
and	O
assisted	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Tap-house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
Waggon	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
,	O
with	O
these	O
Goods	O
all	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
the	O
Things	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tyson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Hostler	O
at	O
the	O
Sarazen's-head	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Edward	B-pers
Hipkiss	I-pers
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struggling	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
assist	O
Hipkiss	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
jump	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
.	O
I	O
helped	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
tap-house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kerby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
at	O
this	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Waggon	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Waggon	O
scewer	O
'd	O
up	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Plastow	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
evening	O
last	O
,	O
bet	O
ween	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Edward	B-pers
Hipkiss	I-pers
bring	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
Collar	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
Tyson	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Longly	I-pers
with	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
box	O
marked	O
I.	O
W.	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
tea-kettles	O
and	O
stands	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
a	O
bulk	O
that	O
was	O
four	O
foot	O
high	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
lying	O
a	O
new	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
the	O
tops	O
of	O
them	O
lined	O
with	O
red	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shag	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hat	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
another	O
time	O
:	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
upon	O
the	O
bulk	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
struggle	O
with	O
Hipkiss	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
thing	O
impossible	O
.	O
The	O
hat	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Guild-hall	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Hipkiss	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
these	O
goods	O
last	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
waggon	O
?	O
Hipkiss	O
.	O
I	O
loaded	O
the	O
waggon	O
at	O
Birmingham	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
loading	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
at	O
7	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Longly	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Plastow	I-pers
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Bownel	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
principally	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
lading	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
mentioned	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
150.	O
William	B-pers
Courne	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
14	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
drawn	O
into	O
a	O
confession	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
accuse	O
himself	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
promise	O
to	O
interceed	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
discharge	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
151.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Dawsey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Cachae	I-pers
;	O
one	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jentee	I-pers
,	O
January	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
152.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cornelous	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
table	O
cloaths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Elwood	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
2	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
153.	O
James	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
gray	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Eliot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
Jan.	O
16	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
:	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
Jan.	O
16.	O
and	O
stole	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
:	O
They	O
are	O
here	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Plaxton	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Jan.	O
16	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
stockings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
what	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
for	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Plaxton	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
told	O
me	O
,	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
Bull's-alley	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
run	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
almost	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stockings	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
Davenport	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
stockings	O
down	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Eliot	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
confirmed	O
what	O
this	O
last	O
Witness	O
said	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
was	O
but	O
that	O
very	O
morning	O
clear	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
Gate	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
so	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
behave	O
so	O
in	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
handcuff	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
threatened	O
to	O
shoot	O
the	O
Justice	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
to	O
run	O
a	O
knife	O
into	O
his	O
heart	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
odd	O
names	O
he	O
could	O
think	O
on	O
.	O
Davenport	O
and	O
Plaxton	O
confirmed	O
the	O
said	O
account	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
154	O
155.	O
Richard	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Jane	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
Iron	O
pottage-pots	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s	O
2	O
Iron	O
heaters	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
frying-pan	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodgings	O
,	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
Both	O
Acq	O
.	O
156.	O
Peter	B-pers
Cruse	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
