TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
.	O
On	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
THURSDAY	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
FRIDAY	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
SATURDAY	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
MONDAY	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
TUESDAY	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
and	O
WEDNESDAY	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
23rd	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Rt	O
.	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pennant	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
1750	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
N.B	O
.	O
The	O
Public	O
may	O
be	O
assured	O
,	O
that	O
(	O
during	O
the	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
.	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PENNANT	I-pers
,	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
this	O
City	O
)	O
the	O
Sessions-Book	O
will	O
be	O
constantly	O
sold	O
for	O
Four-pence	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
Account	O
of	O
every	O
Sessions	O
shall	O
be	O
carefully	O
compriz	O
'd	O
in	O
Exe	O
such	O
Four-penny	O
Book	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
farther	O
Burthen	O
on	O
the	O
Purchasers	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
PENNANT	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
MARTIN	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Sir	B-pers
THOMAS	I-pers
BIRCH	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Baron	B-pers
LEGGE	I-pers
,	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Angel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stebbing	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
,	O
Martin	B-pers
Capron	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Grundy	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Mosely	I-pers
,	O
Nevil	B-pers
Feather	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chilshohm	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Deschampus	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jaumard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Greening	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Aynge	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Asby	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Meyow	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lowry	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Griscome	I-pers
.	O
178.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Richley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
William	B-pers
More	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
dined	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
missed	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Goldsmiths	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
advertisements	O
sent	O
about	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Goldsmith	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
deposed	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
the	O
31st	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
sent	O
him	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
done	O
:	O
He	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
More	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Geary	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
Alderman	O
.	O
Phoebe	B-pers
Goodfellow	I-pers
produced	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
beat	O
togegether	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
engrav	O
'd	O
round	O
it	O
,	O
answering	O
to	O
the	O
advertisement	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
179.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
Fork	O
,	O
one	O
pewter	O
Dish	O
,	O
two	O
pewter	O
Plates	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8	O
,	O
1749	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
180.	O
James	B-pers
Burr	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
hempen	O
Sacks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Colenet	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
181.	O
John	B-pers
Hinks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
together	O
with	O
Christopher	B-pers
Jinks	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
wire	O
Sieves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Murrell	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
5	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
182.	O
Casper	B-pers
Dunlap	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
before	O
him	O
and	O
Dennes	O
Richolate	O
,	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Tankard	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
his	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
constable	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
183.	O
John	B-pers
Chilton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
old	O
Iron	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
gates	O
,	O
carts	O
,	O
and	O
ploughs	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
Feb.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
184.	O
William	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Gelding	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Langton	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
29	O
.	O
Nathan	B-pers
Gunnel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Langton	O
.	O
This	O
horse	O
was	O
stolen	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
stable	O
at	O
Cockham	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Berkshire	I-place
,	O
Nov.	O
26	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
team	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Although	O
he	O
is	O
blind	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
place	O
,	O
we	O
value	O
him	O
at	O
about	O
5	O
l.	O
William	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Collar-maker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
sold	O
me	O
the	O
horse	O
without	O
shoes	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
bridle	O
,	O
saddle	O
,	O
and	O
collar	O
,	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
lives	O
near	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
stand	O
in	O
his	O
stable	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
work	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
pleas	O
'd	O
:	O
So	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
his	O
cart	O
by	O
the	O
former	O
witness	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
object	O
indeed	O
,	O
blind	O
,	O
swell	O
'd	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
pole-evil	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
horses	O
in	O
Swan-yard	O
,	O
facing	O
Somerset-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
horse	O
to	O
my	O
stable	O
about	O
the	O
26th	O
or	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
two	O
Nights	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
29th	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
agree	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
return	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
horse	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
his	O
keeping	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
horse	O
but	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
about	O
8	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
horse	O
and	O
himself	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
chang	O
'd	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
change	O
,	O
pay	O
the	O
prisoner	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
185.	O
Margaret	B-pers
the	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
George	I-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
two	O
quart	O
pewter	O
pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Billings	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
186.	O
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
diaper	O
tablecloths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
cap	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
five	O
linnen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
damask	O
night-gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Hazard	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
Jan.	O
19	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
187	O
,	O
188.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Cribb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
Nov.	O
18	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Beaumont	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
only	O
Evidence	O
was	O
Charles	B-pers
Speckman	I-pers
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
of	O
about	O
fifteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Who	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
himself	O
had	O
followed	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
thieving	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
back	O
'd	O
by	O
evidence	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
189.	O
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
d	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Feb.	O
10	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
190.	O
Bryan	B-pers
Gwinn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
cheshire	O
cheese	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Co.	O
Feb.	O
5	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
191.	O
William	B-pers
Beverley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Feb.	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
192.	O
William	B-pers
Windsor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Adrian	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
193.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
vessel	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
half-hogshead	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
194.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
l.	O
one	O
gold	O
chain	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
three	O
stone	O
seals	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
,	O
1748	O
.	O
General	O
St.	O
Clair	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
the	O
Birth-day	O
of	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
duty	O
to	O
his	O
Royal	O
Highness	O
.	O
Returning	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
place	O
being	O
crowded	O
with	O
chairs	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
great	O
gate	O
.	O
Turning	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
little	O
shops	O
,	O
a	O
prodigious	O
crowd	O
of	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
thrust	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
suspected	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
pocket	O
pick	O
'd	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
down	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
felt	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
that	O
whoever	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
at	O
any	O
distance	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
collar	O
'd	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
dragged	O
them	O
along	O
to	O
the	O
centinel	O
;	O
the	O
centinel	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
dragg	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
under	O
the	O
gateway	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
guard	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
that	O
,	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
who	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
came	O
running	O
up	O
with	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
old	O
Fellow	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
had	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
Serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
guard	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
my	O
Lord	O
Carpenter	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
met	O
him	O
going	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Edward	B-pers
Linn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Provost	O
's	O
Marshal-man	O
.	O
Telling	O
him	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
both	O
searched	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
was	O
found	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
spurs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
book	O
of	O
the	O
records	O
of	O
England	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
honour	O
and	O
conscience	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
which	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shorthouse	I-pers
said	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
drop	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
then	O
cloath	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
if	O
it	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
)	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
darkish	O
wigg	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
Shorthouse	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
while	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
General	O
one	O
question	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
what	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
General	O
reply	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shorthouse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
's	O
Court	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
General	O
St.	O
Clair	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crowd	O
of	O
people	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
.	O
He	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
press	O
'd	O
forward	O
,	O
leaning	O
over	O
the	O
General	O
's	O
right	O
shoulder	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
decline	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
General	O
almost	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
either	O
of	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
seeming	O
in	O
a	O
consternation	O
,	O
as	O
not	O
knowing	O
which	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
slip	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
General	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
Sir	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
Sir	O
,	O
have	O
I	O
got	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
Sir	O
?	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
looked	O
about	O
seemingly	O
as	O
though	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
amongst	O
the	O
chairs	O
and	O
coaches	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
General	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
has	O
got	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
meaning	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
.	O
The	O
General	O
had	O
quitted	O
his	O
hold	O
;	O
but	O
immediately	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
lugg	O
'd	O
him	O
forward	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
deliver	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
centinel	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
man	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
either	O
his	O
coat	O
or	O
waistcoat-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
chain	O
hang	O
out	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
drop	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
General	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
time	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
General	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
that	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
pocket	O
?	O
Shorthouse	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
Remark	O
the	O
General	O
made	O
then	O
,	O
was	O
(	O
in	O
that	O
Hurry	O
)	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
old	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
being	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
so	O
big	O
.	O
To	O
me	O
now	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seems	O
younger	O
than	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
that	O
man	O
cloath	O
'd	O
?	O
Shorthouse	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
grizzle	O
wigg	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Linn	I-pers
,	O
the	O
provosi	O
's	O
marshal	O
man	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
waiting	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Gen	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
blue-grey	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
darkish	O
wigg	O
,	O
for	O
picking	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
General	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Varne	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
Westminister	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
file	O
of	O
mujketteers	O
,	O
conducted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
him	O
safe	O
there	O
.	O
Not	O
seeing	O
him	O
since	O
,	O
or	O
knowing	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
commitment	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
mentioned	O
in	O
that	O
commitment	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
1748	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
rescued	O
from	O
the	O
prison	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Patrick	O
Henley	O
,	O
the	O
Deputy-turnkey	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
commitment	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
well	O
in	O
Dublin	O
.	O
Before	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
blue-grey	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
darkish	O
wigg	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
asked	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Name	O
of	O
Banbidge	O
,	O
the	O
pickpocket	O
,	O
in	O
Dublin	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
195	O
,	O
196.	O
James	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
Rachel	B-pers
Angue	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Rachel	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
197.	O
Judith	B-pers
Dyke	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Kennish	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Isaac	O
,	O
Dec.	O
11	O
.	O
The	O
witnesses	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
tryal	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
126	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
addition	O
of	O
Hosier	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
seemed	O
to	O
agree	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
by	O
Stevens	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
198.	O
James	B-pers
Blanthorn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
l.	O
one	O
alapeen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Bouger	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Ling	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
199.	O
John	B-pers
Duckett	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Slugh	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Feb.	O
5	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Slugh	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
an	O
ale-house	O
,	O
in	O
Mansfield-street	O
,	O
Goodmans-fields	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
two	O
fellows	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
pass	O
.	O
He	O
penn	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
shelf	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
arms	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
,	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wigg	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
towards	O
Rosemary-branch-alley	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
Watch	O
!	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
&	O
c.	O
He	O
,	O
finding	O
himself	O
pursued	O
,	O
flung	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wigg	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
about	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
took	O
him	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
George	O
ale-house	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Ricards	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
another	O
robbery	O
that	O
same	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
person	O
I	O
saw	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Being	O
cross-examined	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
ever	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
them	O
halfpence	O
you	O
snatch	O
'd	O
from	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
.	O
He	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
no	O
such	O
word	O
was	O
ever	O
mentioned	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
how	O
old	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sixteen	O
,	O
last	O
December	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Buckmaster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
George	O
ale-house	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
a	O
knock	O
on	O
the	O
pate	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wigg	O
.	O
Cross-Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
constable	O
by	O
at	O
this	O
confession	O
?	O
Buckmaster	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
talk	O
of	O
140	O
l.	O
on	O
his	O
Conviction	O
?	O
Buckmaster	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
afraid	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
penn	O
'd	O
you	O
up	O
?	O
Slugh	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
fellow	O
stood	O
by	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
afraid	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
alone	O
?	O
Slugh	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
or	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
older	O
.	O
A	O
Watchman	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
Watch	O
!	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
seeing	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
bare-headed	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
do	O
n't	O
abuse	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
stand	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
stand	O
still	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
witness	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Whitechapel	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
Justice	O
Ricards	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Golden	O
lyon	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
Clerk	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
struck	O
the	O
lad	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wigg	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
committed	O
another	O
robbery	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Randolph	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gun-stock-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
within	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
coming	O
home	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Mansfield-street	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
50	O
yards	O
farther	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
directly	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
moon-light	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
close	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
third	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Buckmaster	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
there	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
a	O
knock	O
on	O
the	O
pate	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wigg	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
have	O
play	O
'd	O
together	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
once	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
halfpence	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
Doctor	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
keep	O
your	O
hat	O
and	O
wigg	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Watch	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Prescot-street	O
.	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
one	O
night	O
,	O
past	O
11	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
boys	O
quarrelling	O
about	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
you	O
snatch	O
'd	O
from	O
me	O
?	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
nor	O
none	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
keep	O
your	O
hat	O
and	O
wigg	O
till	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
accordingly	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
boy	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
with	O
a	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
lame	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
boys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Dunn	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Sherbourn-lane	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
ticket	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
ply	O
at	O
Change	O
alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
tryal	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
your	O
Evidence	O
?	O
Dunn	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
night	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
telling	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
committed	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
come	O
through	O
the	O
place	O
by	O
Goodman's-fields	O
wells	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
taphouse-yard	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
smoaking	O
a	O
pipe	O
,	O
have	O
seen	O
these	O
two	O
boys	O
at	O
play	O
together	O
at	O
marbles	O
,	O
and	O
tossing	O
up	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
ride	O
horses	O
there	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
had	O
a	O
horse	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Slugh	I-pers
.	O
What	O
this	O
witness	O
says	O
is	O
absolutely	O
false	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
bound	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
rid	O
a	O
horse	O
but	O
once	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
on	O
my	O
own	O
business	O
to	O
Tottenham	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
that	O
yard	O
this	O
two	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
above	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
this	O
twelve-month	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
only	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
that	O
way	O
on	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
business	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
toss	O
up	O
for	O
a	O
farthing	O
or	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
Oath	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
swore	O
is	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
,	O
being	O
accidentally	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
heard	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Bradshaw	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
Dunn	O
's	O
Licence	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
for	O
keeping	O
a	O
disorderly	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
within	O
six	O
doors	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
witness	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
general	O
Character	O
was	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
gambler	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
really	O
did	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
credited	O
upon	O
oath	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
200	O
,	O
201.	O
John	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Ann	O
,	O
Countess	B-pers
of	I-pers
Albemarle	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Albemarle	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Countess	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
Lord	O
Bury	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
Lady	O
Albemarle	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Lady	O
were	O
stopped	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
on	O
the	O
top	B-place
of	I-place
Great	I-place
Russel	I-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
by	O
several	O
persons	O
.	O
His	O
Lordship	O
saw	O
three	O
pistols	O
pointed	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
he	O
sat	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
particular	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
fix	O
it	O
on	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
rainy	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stambeans	O
blown	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
violence	O
of	O
the	O
wind	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dauford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
footman	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
discern	O
the	O
persons	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Lewis	O
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
Stanton	O
,	O
Webster	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Eckley	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
committed	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
prov	O
'd	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
demonstration	O
,	O
himself	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cordosa	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
three	O
gold	O
watches	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
metal	O
one	O
,	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sent	O
them	O
abroad	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
by	O
a	O
kinsman	O
;	O
and	O
although	O
he	O
agreed	O
with	O
Lewis	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
from	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
yet	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
,	O
except	O
Lewis	O
.	O
The	O
witness	O
Lewis	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
back	O
'd	O
by	O
any	O
creditable	O
witnesses	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
identity	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
202.	O
John	B-pers
Carbold	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Giffling	I-pers
Jack	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Great	B-place
Yarmouth	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
not	O
surrendering	O
himself	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
order	O
in	O
Council	O
.	O
To	O
prove	O
that	O
proper	O
steps	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
render	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
felon	O
already	O
convicted	O
,	O
Justice	O
Kellett	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Leader	I-pers
came	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
,	O
1747	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
information	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
assembled	O
together	O
at	O
Benacre	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
30	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
landing	O
and	O
running	O
goods	O
,	O
liable	O
to	O
pay	O
custom	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
he	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Principal	O
Secretaries	O
of	O
State	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
post	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sharpe	O
,	O
Clerk	O
to	O
the	O
Council	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
laid	O
before	O
his	O
Majesty	O
in	O
Council	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22nd	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1747	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Duke	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
issue	O
out	O
an	O
Order	O
of	O
Council	O
,	O
requiring	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
information	O
,	O
to	O
surrender	O
themselves	O
within	O
forty	O
days	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
which	O
order	O
was	O
issued	O
the	O
22d	O
from	O
the	O
court	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
Printer	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
Gazette	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
two	O
copies	O
of	O
this	O
order	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Sharpe	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
next	O
Gts	O
,	O
to	O
wit	O
,	O
the	O
22nd	O
and	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
order	O
of	O
council	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lamb	O
Barry	O
,	O
the	O
Sheriff	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Suffolk	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
1748.	O
Richard	B-pers
Growper	I-pers
Under	O
sheriff	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
received	O
this	O
order	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Barry	O
,	O
and	O
caus	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
copy	O
'd	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
clerk	O
to	O
declare	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Mr.	O
Swackman	O
,	O
his	O
clerk	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
copy	O
'd	O
it	O
true	O
,	O
and	O
proclaim	O
'd	O
it	O
at	O
Beccles	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
twelve	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Southwold	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
fix	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
true	O
copy	O
on	O
each	O
market-cross	O
.	O
The	O
Jury	O
found	O
the	O
Issues	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
203.	O
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
uttering	O
a	O
certain	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
Will	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hughs	O
,	O
the	O
proctor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
to	O
prove	O
a	O
will	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
testator	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
,	O
holding	O
a	O
will	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
was	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
prov	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
Dr.	O
Paul	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
sole	O
executor	O
of	O
that	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
will	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
ingross	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
into	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
a	O
case	O
was	O
depending	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
father	O
and	O
one	O
Knox	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
off	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
could	O
send	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
father	O
.	O
The	O
father	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
this	O
pretended	O
executor	O
,	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
told	O
the	O
father	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
will	O
made	O
by	O
his	O
son	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
brother	O
of	O
his	O
was	O
left	O
executor	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
son	O
living	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
father	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
Guild-hall	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
made	O
the	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
wrote	O
the	O
witnesses	O
names	O
to	O
the	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
somewhere	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Crooked-billet	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
something	O
like	O
Blackman	O
.	O
The	O
father	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
will	O
being	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
James	O
Young	O
The	O
will	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
the	O
purport	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
James	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
pretended	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
testator	O
,	O
was	O
sole	O
executor	O
;	O
which	O
said	O
name	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
by	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
under	O
the	O
commissioners	O
of	O
the	O
navy	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
books	O
of	O
the	O
Boyne	O
and	O
the	O
Guernzey	O
's	O
prize	O
here	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
due	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
from	O
August	O
8	O
,	O
1743	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
September	O
8	O
,	O
1746	O
,	O
35	O
l.	O
He	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Guernzey	O
's	O
prize	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
there	O
till	O
he	O
fell	O
over	O
board	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
drowned	O
,	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
1746	O
.	O
Due	O
on	O
board	O
her	O
,	O
2	O
l.	O
At	O
his	O
death	O
there	O
was	O
37	O
l.	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
father	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
William	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Proctor	O
's	O
office	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hughs	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Paul	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
your	O
son	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
a	O
son	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
confus	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
retain	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
law	O
should	O
take	O
its	O
course	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Guild-hall	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
my	O
son	O
could	O
write	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
will	O
having	O
a	O
mark	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
)	O
There	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
forg	O
'd	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Brockman	I-pers
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Johnson's-change	O
,	O
in	O
Ragg-fair	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Crooked-billet	O
,	O
that	O
wrote	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
other	O
persons	O
wrote	O
other	O
names	O
,	O
not	O
their	O
own	O
,	O
to	O
witness	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
this	O
Crooked-billet	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Brockman	I-pers
liv	O
'd	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
ticket	O
?	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
merchant	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
business	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
tickets	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
intoxicated	O
with	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Brockman	I-pers
owed	O
me	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
will	O
I	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
real	O
executor	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
arrested	O
at	O
the	O
commons	O
for	O
debt	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
execute	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
bid	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
was	O
the	O
testator	O
's	O
brother	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sensible	O
whether	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
that	O
Brockman	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
one	O
who	O
takes	O
Rs	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Crooked-billet	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pointer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
married	O
my	O
daughter	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
unhappily	O
drawn	O
into	O
this	O
by	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Brockman	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Irishman	O
,	O
who	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
seeking	O
for	O
him	O
night	O
and	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
harmless	O
,	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
204.	O
John	B-pers
Clement	I-pers
Eastmead	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
82	O
yards	O
of	O
linnen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
Jan.	O
25	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
205.	O
Peter	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
sheep	O
's	O
carcass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
15	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
206	O
,	O
207.	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Spillage	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
returning	O
home	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
in	B-place
a	I-place
path	I-place
that	I-place
comes	I-place
from	I-place
Hide-park-hospital	I-place
,	I-place
into	I-place
the	I-place
road	I-place
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
rainy	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
pull	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
plucked	O
off	O
my	O
horse	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
a	O
Scymiter	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
held	O
it	O
over	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
low	O
tone	O
.	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pull	O
my	O
gloves	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Another	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
either	O
a	O
stick	O
or	O
a	O
sword	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
wav	O
'd	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
all	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
s.	O
I	O
saw	O
but	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Spillage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
affair	O
happen	O
'd	O
near	O
a	O
house	O
call	O
'd	O
Bloody-bridge-house	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
100	O
yards	O
before	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
near	O
a	O
stile	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
seemingly	O
coming	O
over	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
turn	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
King's-road	O
to	O
St.	O
George's-hospital	O
.	O
I	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
heard	O
a	O
horse	O
galloping	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
this	O
gate	O
,	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
Crompton	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
much	O
concern	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
back	O
up	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
riding	O
about	O
150	O
yards	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
terrible	O
fright	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
mentioned	O
before	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Armour	I-pers
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Crompton	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Blake	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Hog	O
in	O
armour	O
,	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
;	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
one	O
John	O
,	O
a	O
Countryman	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
news-paper	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
'em	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
use	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
paper	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
their	O
heads	O
together	O
over	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
North	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
suddenly	O
snatch	O
'd	O
away	O
upon	O
my	O
approach	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Wilkinson	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
shewing	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
his	O
uncle	O
died	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
thirty	O
guineas	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
fifteen	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
paid	O
for	O
three	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
their	O
ways	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Hog	O
in	O
armour	O
,	O
in	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
North	O
,	O
and	O
Blake	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
another	O
box	O
;	O
North	O
had	O
his	O
sword	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
soldiers	O
)	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
John	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
mentioned	O
before	O
,	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
sell	O
it	O
?	O
John	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
watch	O
maker	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
myself	O
)	O
may-be	O
he	O
'll	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
help	O
you	O
to	O
a	O
chapman	O
.	O
Then	O
Wilkinson	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
gold	O
one	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
enamell	O
'd	O
dial-plate	O
.	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
stone	O
upon	O
the	O
cock	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
jewel	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
;	O
but	O
the	O
number	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Advertiser	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
guineas	O
reward	O
offer	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
he	O
lost	O
was	O
as	O
describ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fennel	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
his	O
servant	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
Wilkinson	O
having	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
to	O
the	O
former	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Corporal	O
Day	B-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
Wilkinson	O
having	O
such	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
shewing	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
his	O
uncle	O
left	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
cost	O
30	O
guineas	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Holbridge	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
to	O
guard	O
Wilkinson	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
confess	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
House	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Blake	O
,	O
and	O
North	O
,	O
and	O
himself	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
designed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
advantage	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
confess	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
.	O
The	O
five	O
last	O
witnesses	O
being	O
cross	O
examined	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
North	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
when	O
Wilkinson	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
Hog	O
in	O
Armour	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
208.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Damask	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
Rev	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Butts	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Butts	O
,	O
Jan.	O
18	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
209.	O
John	B-pers
Oldham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Buckskin	O
Breeches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sam	B-pers
.	I-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
The	O
principal	O
Evidence	O
not	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
210.	O
James	B-pers
Sandiland	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
James	I-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
assembled	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
ten	O
or	O
more	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Parish	B-place
of	I-place
Lidd	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
County	I-place
of	I-place
Kent	I-place
,	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
landing	O
and	O
running	O
goods	O
liable	O
to	O
pay	O
duty	O
.	O
Aug.	O
13	O
.	O
1746	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Pelham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Lidd	O
in	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
Kent	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
the	O
fishing	O
trade	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Person	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
Years	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
fishing	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
1746.	O
off	O
of	O
Dungenness	O
,	O
coming	O
to	O
land	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
Cutter	O
working	O
,	O
she	O
lay	O
about	O
40	O
yards	O
from	O
shore	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
boat	O
land	O
there	O
some	O
people	O
on	O
shore	O
?	O
there	O
was	O
Authur	O
Gray	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
in	O
all	O
or	O
more	O
,	O
we	O
row	O
'd	O
betwixt	O
the	O
cutter	O
and	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
all	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
shore	O
came	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
arm	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
Carbine	O
or	O
Blunderduss	O
,	O
on	O
horse	O
back	O
with	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
tea	O
behind	O
him	O
in	O
an	O
oil-skin	O
bag	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
most	O
or	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
drove	O
horses	O
loaded	O
with	O
casks	O
and	O
oilskin	O
bags	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
many	O
times	O
amongst	O
the	O
smugglers	O
but	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
working	O
goods	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
sizeable	O
Bay	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
old	O
blue	O
Butcher	O
's	O
frack	O
on	O
under	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
which	O
was	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
,	O
'	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Hawkhurst	O
Gang	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Maidstone	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Goal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
seeing	O
him	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Hatton	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Lidd	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Aug.	O
1746	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
same	O
gang	O
in	O
the	O
Town	O
with	O
their	O
baggage	O
,	O
arm	O
'd	O
with	O
some	O
Pistols	O
,	O
Carbines	O
or	O
Blunderbusses	O
with	O
Horses	O
loaded	O
with	O
oil-skin	O
bags	O
and	O
half	O
anchors	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
in	O
number	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
this	O
number	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
Carbine	O
or	O
Blunderbus	O
flung	O
to	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
oil-skin	O
bag	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
betwixt	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
Ostler	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Lidd	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
this	O
7	O
years	O
,	O
the	O
smuglers	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
call	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
day	O
and	O
night	O
,	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
lay	O
them	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
Hawkhurst	O
gang	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
Arthur	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
he	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
rode	O
a	O
middle	O
size	O
bay	O
Horse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
loose	O
great	O
coat	O
of	O
a	O
lightish	O
colour	O
,	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
under	O
that	O
coat	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
enough	O
to	O
do	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
way	O
;	O
being	O
then	O
driving	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
corn	O
cut	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
by	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
smuglers	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
town	O
of	O
Lidd	O
,	O
about	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
in	O
number	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
1746	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
they	O
had	O
half	O
anchors	O
and	O
oil-skin	O
bags	O
and	O
fire	O
arms	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Polhil	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
smugglers	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
town	O
of	O
Lidd	O
,	O
Aug.	O
13th	O
,	O
1746	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
by	O
my	O
Journal	O
which	O
I	O
keep	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
them	O
nor	O
daring	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
Westraham	O
in	O
Kent	O
was	O
about	O
fourscore	O
miles	O
from	O
Lidd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
these	O
people	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
except	O
when	O
in	O
Maidstone	O
Goal	O
,	O
some	O
people	O
came	O
round	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
cat	O
stroking	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ran	O
up	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
they	O
mark	O
'd	O
me	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
Lidd	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kellet	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bignall	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waldon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
own	O
Mother	O
,	O
to	O
prove	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Butcher	O
in	O
Westerham	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
had	O
good	O
business	O
,	O
was	O
never	O
known	O
to	O
neglect	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
killed	O
his	O
beast	O
himself	O
against	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
market	O
day	O
,	O
(	O
on	O
which	O
day	O
the	O
witnesses	O
for	O
the	O
crown	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
Lidd	O
)	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
missing	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
on	O
market	O
days	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
apprentice	O
or	O
journeyman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
family	O
of	O
small	O
children	O
to	O
engross	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
her	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
bore	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
smuggler	O
to	O
their	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Then	O
John	O
Potter	O
,	O
at	O
Seven-oakes	O
within	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
miles	O
of	O
Westerham	O
in	O
Kent	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
near	O
2	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
smuggler	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
6	O
years	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
always	O
was	O
looked	O
upon	O
all	O
over	O
the	O
country	O
as	O
a	O
smuggler	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
go	O
with	O
fire	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Hawkburst	O
gang	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
211.	O
Charles	B-pers
Gaven	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
the	I-pers
Papist	I-pers
of	I-pers
Beckles	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
not	O
surrendering	O
himself	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
order	O
in	O
council	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
same	O
information	O
with	O
that	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cobold	I-pers
N.	O
202	O
.	O
Advertised	O
in	O
the	O
London	O
Gazette	O
,	O
and	O
proclaim	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
reader	O
is	O
referr	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
issues	O
were	O
found	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
212.	O
John	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
,	O
late	B-place
of	I-place
Norwich	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
not	O
surrendering	O
himself	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
order	O
in	O
council	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
Cobold	B-pers
.	O
The	O
issues	O
were	O
found	O
for	O
the	O
King	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
213	O
,	O
214	O
,	O
215	O
,	O
216.	O
John	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Oldfield	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
Charles	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
esq	O
;	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Feb.	O
13th	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
near	B-place
Burlington	I-place
Gardens	I-place
of	O
my	O
gold	O
watch	O
with	O
three	O
seals	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
,	O
by	O
four	O
men	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
seals	O
had	O
my	O
arms	O
cut	O
in	O
a	O
stone	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
another	O
little	O
cornelian	O
stone	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Burry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wittingbury	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
men	O
more	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
apprehend	O
Stanton	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
we	O
were	O
directed	O
to	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
there	O
was	O
Stanton	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Wittingbury	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
swore	O
to	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Stanton	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Wittingbury	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
friend	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
accepted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
adding	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
were	O
more	O
of	O
his	O
company	O
was	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wittingbury	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
near	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
take	O
them	O
immediately	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
fastened	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
surrounded	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
Busby	O
strove	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
surrounded	O
we	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
chamber	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Oldfield	I-pers
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
pistols	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
slugs	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Clarkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
Stanton	O
took	O
a	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wittingbury	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
sword	O
under	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
then	O
Stanton	O
told	O
us	O
of	O
Russel	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
who	O
lodged	O
some	O
where	O
in	O
Hockley	O
in	O
the	O
hole	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
rightly	O
know	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Russel	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
that	O
fore-noon	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
so	O
three	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
were	O
we	O
took	O
Stanton	O
in	O
Alien-street	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
staid	O
in	O
St.	O
John-street	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
pistols	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
five	O
pistols	O
were	O
loaded	O
,	O
some	O
with	O
bullets	O
and	O
one	O
with	O
slugs	O
.	O
Russel	O
gave	O
us	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
coachmen	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
sign	O
'd	O
their	O
confessions	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hain	I-pers
.	O
Stanton	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
information	O
and	O
likewise	O
where	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
door	O
and	O
looked	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
key	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
coat	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
burst	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
confirm	O
'd	O
swhat	O
was	O
deposed	O
by	O
the	O
former	O
Witness	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wittingbury	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ind	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
Joshua	B-pers
Brogdon	I-pers
clark	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
produc	O
'd	O
each	O
prisoners	O
confession	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
voluntary	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
each	O
prisoner	O
,	O
giving	O
a	O
particular	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
All	O
four	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
217.	O
Mary	B-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
her	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Larendine	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
13	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
child	O
's	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
tongs	O
,	O
one	O
large	O
common	O
prayer	O
book	O
,	O
three	O
coloured	O
handkerchiefs	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Jan.	O
19	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
218	O
,	O
219.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Roney	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bastow	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
together	O
with	O
J.	O
Norman	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Kings	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
Joseph	B-pers
Norfield	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
blue	O
cloth	O
coat	O
lac	O
'd	O
with	O
gold	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
one	O
scarlet	O
coat	O
value	O
3l	O
.	O
a	O
blue	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
value	O
10s	O
.	O
one	O
white	O
sattin	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
six	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foley	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
27	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Norfield	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
lieutenant	O
Thomas	B-pers
Foley	I-pers
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
Westminister	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
portmanteau	O
.	O
Jan.	O
27	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
near	I-place
Exeter	I-place
change	I-place
,	O
Roney	O
ran	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
flung	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
ask	O
'd	O
my	O
pardon	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
talking	O
together	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
coming	O
through	O
Temple-bar	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
carry	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
down	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
near	O
to	O
Fleet-ditch	O
,	O
then	O
a	O
sailor	O
went	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
sixpence	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
shall	O
go	O
as	O
easy	O
as	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
Patrick	B-pers
Roney	I-pers
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
so	O
to	O
the	O
Falstaff's-head	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
;	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
two	O
men	O
both	O
in	O
light	O
colour	O
'd	O
cloths	O
;	O
Bastow	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
there	O
these	O
fourteen	O
nights	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
perhaps	O
I	O
lik	O
'd	O
that	O
better	O
than	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
have	O
any	O
hot	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
once	O
round	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
portmanteau	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bastow	I-pers
went	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
Going	O
to	O
turn	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
Roney	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
carry	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
heavy	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
Bastow	O
laid	O
hold	O
round	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
squeeze	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
my	O
head	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
,	O
while	O
Roney	O
took	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
from	O
my	O
shoulder	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Thieves	O
!	O
and	O
a	O
mob	O
got	O
all	O
round	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
fright	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
up	O
a	O
tradesman	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
search	O
the	O
King's-arms	O
,	O
thinking	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
into	O
another	O
house	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
run	O
up	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
boy	O
came	O
running	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
people	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
Temple-stairs	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
watermen	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
saw	O
any	O
such	O
persons	O
with	O
a	O
portmanteau	O
?	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
White-fryars	O
,	O
pointed	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
boat	O
in	O
the	O
river	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
that	O
portmanteau	O
.	O
Two	O
boats	O
put	O
off	O
immediately	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
boat	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
landed	O
at	O
Moulston	O
's	O
dock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
;	O
we	O
ran	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
by	O
the	O
water-side	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
boat	O
kept	O
down	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
to	O
Bank-end	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
causeway	O
.	O
Constantine	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
water-men	O
who	O
was	O
landed	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Roney	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
took	O
Bastow	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
taken	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Fitz	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Foley	O
's	O
father-in-law	O
;	O
I	O
help	O
'd	O
pack	O
up	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
;	O
(	O
mentioning	O
each	O
thing	O
separately	O
.	O
)	O
Constantine	B-pers
Higgins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
water-man	O
;	O
I	O
ply	O
at	O
Temple-stairs	O
;	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Temple-lane	O
,	O
looking	O
out	O
for	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
Two	O
boys	O
came	O
running	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
fright	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
power	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
an	O
answer	O
when	O
I	O
ply	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
recover	O
'd	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
describing	O
their	O
dress	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
portmanteau	O
,	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
boat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
.	O
A	O
water-man	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
just	O
landed	O
his	O
boat	O
from	O
White-fryars	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
in	O
that	O
sculler	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
river	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
put	O
off	O
two	O
boats	O
;	O
two	O
men	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
into	O
one	O
boat	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
boat	O
had	O
three	O
men	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
the	O
boys	O
to	O
sit	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
seen	O
by	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
We	O
push	O
'd	O
on	O
shore	O
at	O
Moulston's-dock	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
boat	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
men	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
kept	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
down	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
We	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
turning	O
round	O
by	O
Horse-shoe-alley	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
landed	O
at	O
Bank-end	O
;	O
who	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
corner	O
talking	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Roney	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
then	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Bastow	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
heels	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
consorts	O
pursued	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Deadman's-place	O
.	O
Patrick	O
Roney	O
made	O
a	O
push	O
to	O
get	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
prevented	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
such	O
cloths	O
on	O
as	O
the	O
boy	O
described	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
little	O
boy	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
on	O
Patrick	B-pers
Roney	I-pers
's	O
back	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Joseph	O
Norfield	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
portmanteau	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
Fleet-street	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
water	O
as	O
beforementioned	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
and	O
ply	O
at	O
Temple-stairs	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
Higgin	O
's	O
account	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
manning	O
out	O
two	O
boats	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
when	O
Higgins	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Roney	O
,	O
Bastow	O
ran	O
away	O
up	O
towards	O
Deadman's-place	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Christopher	O
Armorer	O
ran	O
after	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
declared	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
colour	O
'd	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
blue-grey	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
boy	O
had	O
described	O
them	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Armorrer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
with	O
Higgins	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
all	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
said	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
watermen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Burkett	I-pers
;	O
we	O
landed	O
within	O
four	O
minutes	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
relation	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Roney	O
made	O
a	O
push	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
after	O
Higgins	O
had	O
taken	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
Burkett	O
and	O
himself	O
prevented	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Burkett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
a	O
fare	O
from	O
the	O
Old	O
Bargehouse	O
to	O
White-fryars	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
should	O
stay	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
rowed	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
had	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
get	O
another	O
fare	O
before	O
they	O
returned	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
White-friars	O
causeway	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Temple-stairs	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
white	O
coat	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
a	O
blue-grey	O
coat	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
portmanteau	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
came	O
down	O
asking	O
after	O
two	O
such	O
men	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
hanged	O
if	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
mann	O
'd	O
two	O
boats	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ingram	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
and	O
ply	O
at	O
White-sriars	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
down	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
plyed	O
them	O
Jan	O
27	O
.	O
Bastow	O
answered	O
when	O
I	O
plyed	O
,	O
taking	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
boat	O
.	O
Said	O
Bastow	O
,	O
pray	O
lend	O
my	O
servant	O
a	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
Roney	O
with	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
)	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
would	O
land	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
row	O
downwards	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
whereabouts	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
Pull	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
side	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
against	O
Horseshoe-alley	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
pull	O
in	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
farther	O
down	O
towards	O
Bank-end	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
landed	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
Bastow	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
must	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
boat	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
watermen	O
put	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
landed	O
.	O
Roney	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Market	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
boy	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
boat	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
portmanteau	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Norfield	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
direction	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Warwick-lane	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoners	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
off	O
.	O
Bastow	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
set	O
eyes	O
on	O
Roney	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
boat	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cooper	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
boat	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
220	O
,	O
221.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lucy	B-pers
Gypsey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
knife	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
two	O
damask	O
napkins	O
,	O
one	O
pillow-bier	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Standard	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Byfield	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
23	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
damask	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
two	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
cap	O
,	O
two	O
towels	O
,	O
one	O
coffeemill	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Theodore	B-pers
Ecclestone	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
222	O
,	O
223	O
,	O
224.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Cribb	I-pers
,	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Campbel	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Schriven	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jonathan	O
,	O
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
Dec.	O
10	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Schriven	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
witness	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
how	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Speckman	I-pers
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Cribb	I-pers
,	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
stole	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
watch	O
hang	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
inward	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
essays	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
till	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
half-penny	O
worth	O
of	O
sugar	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
half-pence	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
one	O
,	O
gave	O
it	O
a	O
trundle	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
hanging	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
it	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
was	O
weighing	O
my	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
asked	O
his	O
leave	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
my	O
money	O
which	O
had	O
fell	O
on	O
one	O
edge	O
and	O
run	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
,	O
nor	O
would	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
flung	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
others	O
stood	O
without	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
three	O
lodge	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Catherine	O
Hall	O
's	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
many	O
robberies	O
together	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Catherine	O
Hall	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
mother	O
to	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
we	O
took	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
we	O
put	O
up	O
to	O
buy	O
cloaths	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
witness	O
as	O
in	O
No	O
.	O
187	O
,	O
188	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
225	O
,	O
226.	O
Mordecai	B-pers
Wale	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Blee	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hartwell	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
227.	O
John	B-pers
Ruttey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
128.	O
Richard	B-pers
Manlove	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
February	O
20	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
229.	O
Mary	B-pers
Maschal	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
Mary	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
one	O
pocket-apron	O
,	O
no	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
18	O
shillings	O
in	O
moneys	O
numbered	O
,	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
February	O
25	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
at	B-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
Suffolk	I-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Hay-market	I-place
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
knocked	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
pocket-apron	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Sailor	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
affrighted	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
about	O
for	O
near	O
2	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
watchman	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Milbourne	I-pers
,	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
court	O
accidentally	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
common	O
street-walker	O
,	O
and	O
new	O
keeps	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
ill	O
fame	O
in	O
Prince	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
Hedge	O
Lane	O
,	O
the	O
regulator	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
had	O
before	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
prostitute	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Milbourne	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
know	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
this	O
regulator	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
justly	O
blamed	O
by	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
230	O
,	O
231	O
,	O
232	O
,	O
233	O
,	O
234	O
,	O
235	O
,	O
236	O
,	O
237.	O
John	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Mullins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Carmitchell	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Uptebacke	I-pers
,	O
Garret	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dowdle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Salt	I-pers
and	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
rescuing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
otherwise	O
Harper	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Gatehouse	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
January	O
20	O
,	O
1748	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Salt	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
Westminister	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
1748	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Harper	O
,	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
by	O
Gwyn	O
Vaughan	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
honourable	O
General	O
St.	O
Clair	O
's	O
Pocket	O
of	O
a	O
Gold	O
Watch	O
,	O
in	O
Company	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
Commitment	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
nearer	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
than	O
seven	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
prison	O
door	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
doors	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
folding	O
doors	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
upper	O
and	O
lower	O
bolt	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
doors	O
is	O
always	O
shut	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
cross	O
bar	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
lock	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
shut	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
folding	O
part	O
,	O
usually	O
opened	O
,	O
the	O
turnkey	O
was	O
prevented	O
closing	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
thrust	O
in	O
betwixt	O
the	O
post	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
instant	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
rushing	O
to	O
force	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
of	O
us	O
within	O
;	O
we	O
guessed	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
thus	O
we	O
shov	O
'd	O
force	O
against	O
force	O
;	O
at	O
length	O
we	O
closed	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
but	O
betwixt	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
closing	O
it	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
pistols	O
shot	O
off	O
from	O
without	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
fired	O
the	O
moment	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
which	O
almost	O
blinded	O
us	O
;	O
the	O
balls	O
and	O
shot	O
stick	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
wood	O
within	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
also	O
a	O
little	O
wicket	O
with	O
four	O
small	O
iron	O
bars	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
peep	O
through	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Mullins	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
been	O
with	O
Jones	O
in	O
the	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
this	O
wicket	O
was	O
that	O
evening	O
forced	O
away	O
and	O
lost	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
without	O
could	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
us	O
within	O
through	O
this	O
hole	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
opened	O
;	O
two	O
persons	O
within	O
were	O
stabbed	O
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
a	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
assisted	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
was	O
run	O
quite	O
through	O
the	O
elbow	O
.	O
No	O
ball	O
or	O
shot	O
touched	O
any	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
made	O
himself	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
nobody	O
but	O
he	O
and	O
some	O
circumstances	O
corresponding	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
identity	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
almost	O
blinded	O
with	O
their	O
powder	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
Jones	O
crept	O
out	O
in	O
this	O
struggle	O
at	O
the	O
door-way	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
ff	O
in	O
triumph	O
,	O
and	O
great	O
shouting	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
soldiers	O
(	O
which	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
guard	O
the	O
prison	O
)	O
found	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
burst	O
in	O
the	O
string	O
near	O
the	O
prison	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Bowen	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Brian	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
salivation	O
.	O
Salt	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Brian	O
said	O
Bowen	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
walking	O
fall	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
at	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
happened	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
often	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
together	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
was	O
twelve-months	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
news	O
brought	O
to	O
Field	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Angel-Court	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Folley	I-pers
,	O
to	O
Tom	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
's	O
companions	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
for	O
picking	O
the	O
pocket	O
of	O
General	O
St.	O
Clair	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
then	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
Garret	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dowdle	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
myself	O
in	O
company	O
;	O
George	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
gin	O
and	O
beer	O
;	O
we	O
concluded	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
rescue	O
Jones	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Field	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
York-buildings	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
Fox	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
four	O
,	O
Norton	O
otherwise	O
Smith	O
,	O
Uptebacke	O
otherwise	O
Mills	O
,	O
Bob	B-pers
Carmitchell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
;	O
we	O
told	O
them	O
what	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
about	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
broomstick	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
instrument	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
met	O
Edward	B-pers
Mullings	I-pers
;	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
Jones	O
;	O
we	O
talked	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
,	O
Mullings	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
turnkey	O
knew	O
me	O
and	O
himself	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
Jones	O
for	O
better	O
than	O
an	O
hour	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
concluded	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
stick	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
then	O
fire	O
and	O
cut	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
our	O
heads	O
were	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
concluded	O
on	O
;	O
says	O
Bowen	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
cutlass	O
;	O
says	O
a	O
second	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
on	O
.	O
Dowdle	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
a	O
hanger	O
by	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
Bowen	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
Garret	B-pers
Lawler	I-pers
,	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
Mullins	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
burst	O
in	O
the	O
barrel	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
it	O
hurt	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
Carmitchell	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
the	O
short	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
broomstick	O
;	O
Smith	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
and	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
Bowen	O
first	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
stick	O
between	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
the	O
post	O
;	O
we	O
strove	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Chain	O
being	O
fastened	O
across	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
strong	O
resistance	O
from	O
within	O
,	O
Harper	O
got	O
his	O
body	O
between	O
the	O
gate	O
and	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
squeezed	O
;	O
Bowen	O
stabbed	O
somebody	O
within	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
with	O
his	O
hanger	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
gate	O
and	O
gate-post	O
,	O
over	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
Harper	O
's	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
within	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
behind	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
pulled	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Man	O
cry	O
out	O
he	O
was	O
stabb	O
'd	O
;	O
afterwards	O
the	O
gate	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
three	O
pistols	O
fired	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
much	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
number	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Jones	O
otherwise	O
Harper	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
King-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
all	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
;	O
about	O
Whitehall	O
we	O
dispersed	O
,	O
some	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
another	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Bowen	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
a	O
sallivation	O
?	O
Brian	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
walking	O
fall	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Dowdle	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
I	O
arm	O
'd	O
?	O
Brian	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
cutlass	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Smith	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Norton	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
I	O
armed	O
?	O
Brian	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
hanger	O
and	O
an	O
oaken	O
stick	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
this	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
privateer	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
retook	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
England	O
.	O
Bowen	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
Brian	O
would	O
never	O
have	O
discovered	O
any	O
thing	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
my	O
information	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Henley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
under	O
turnkey	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Salt	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
:	O
when	O
Jones	O
was	O
brought	O
prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
day	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
Mullins	O
came	O
to	O
visit	O
him	O
;	O
about	O
five	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
the	O
yard	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
by	O
themselves	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
seven	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
seven	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
blood	O
and	O
ouns	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
time	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
fray	O
happened	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
somebody	O
come	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
opened	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
stick	O
put	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
shut	O
too	O
to	O
lock	O
;	O
the	O
chain	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
rushed	O
in	O
;	O
they	O
forced	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
we	O
for	O
our	O
shoulders	O
to	O
force	O
within	O
against	O
them	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
Harper	O
got	O
some	O
way	O
betwixt	O
our	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
pulled	O
away	O
from	O
us	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pushing	O
without	O
,	O
Harper	O
bounced	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
powder	O
hurt	O
our	O
eyes	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
pistols	O
fired	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
many	O
there	O
were	O
without	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
by	O
their	O
thrusting	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
strong	O
,	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
.	O
Allen	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
Jones	O
,	O
was	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
pulled	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
wounded	O
with	O
a	O
stab	O
on	O
my	O
forehead	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
shewed	O
the	O
scar	O
)	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
through	O
the	O
wicket	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
Jones	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
terrible	O
huzzaing	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
back	O
and	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
goal	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pistol	O
burst	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
next	O
morning	O
under	O
our	O
gateway	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
soldiers	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Diamond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
turnkey	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Salt	O
,	O
in	O
January	O
,	O
1748	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
confirmed	O
the	O
last	O
two	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Steven	B-pers
Macdaniel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
know	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
fray	O
happened	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
that	O
house	O
harboured	O
nothing	O
but	O
thieves	O
and	O
highwaymen	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
plough	O
;	O
I	O
dined	O
along	O
with	O
Mullins	O
,	O
Lawler	O
,	O
and	O
Brian	O
the	O
witness	O
,	O
once	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
Week	O
after	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
belong	O
to	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
themselves	O
the	O
Royal	O
Family	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Officer	O
(	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
Carter	O
and	O
Dowdle	O
,	O
stopped	O
me	O
one	O
night	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
deliver	O
my	O
Money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
take	O
very	O
easy	O
;	O
I	O
drew	O
my	O
hanger	O
,	O
and	O
pinned	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
Cheesemonger	O
's	O
pop	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Maycroft	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Mullings	O
came	O
in	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
dinner	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
tied	O
up	O
,	O
his	O
thumb	O
being	O
hurt	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
quarrelling	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
Brian	O
stagging	O
dog	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
English	O
of	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
took	O
Brian	O
;	O
Jones	O
took	O
a	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
use	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
myself	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
this	O
affair	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
conversation	O
about	O
this	O
with	O
Bowen	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Press-yard	O
in	O
Newgate	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
two	O
letters	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
were	O
Brian	O
then	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
as	O
an	O
evidence	O
about	O
this	O
rescue	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
your	O
first	O
Information	O
,	O
then	O
there	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
some	O
credit	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Jones	O
who	O
was	O
rescued	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
along	O
with	O
Quin	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Maycrost	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
generally	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
people	O
that	O
will	O
answer	O
our	O
purposes	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
once	O
treating	O
Brian	O
with	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
Mullins	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
quarrelling	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
imagined	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
tied	O
about	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tie	O
one	O
hand	O
and	O
fight	O
Brian	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
injury	O
done	O
to	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
advertisement	O
of	O
the	O
rescue	O
.	O
Bowen	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Merrychurch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Kent-street	O
,	O
Surrey	O
;	O
Bowen	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
till	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
1748	O
,	O
being	O
ill	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
salivation	O
.	O
Cross-Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
to	O
lay	O
people	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
salivation	O
,	O
when	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
you	O
yourself	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Lock	O
to	O
be	O
laid	O
down	O
yourself	O
?	O
Merrychurch	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Mullin	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
always	O
served	O
the	O
King	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
disabled	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
now	O
got	O
a	O
Pension	O
.	O
Smith	O
otherwise	O
Norton	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
Norton	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
at	O
his	O
uncle	O
Jackson	O
's	O
chambers	O
,	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
fever	O
,	O
which	O
took	O
him	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
January	O
1748.	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
above	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
:	O
his	O
uncle	O
is	O
an	O
attorney	O
in	O
Barnard's-Inn	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
:	O
his	O
uncle	O
is	O
now	O
confined	O
to	O
his	O
chamber	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
this	O
morning	O
very	O
ill.	O
On	O
her	O
cross-examination	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
coming	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
blister	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
green	O
cheney	O
curtains	O
to	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
raised	O
Tester	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
small	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
chair	O
by	O
his	O
bed	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
Smith	O
was	O
a	O
patient	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
4th	O
or	O
5th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
February	O
after	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
fever	O
,	O
I	O
bleeded	O
and	O
blistered	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
attendances	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
