TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
24th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Francis	B-pers
Cokayne	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1750	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Francis	B-pers
Cokayne	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Willes	O
*	O
,	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+Richard	O
Adams	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
++	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Arthur	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Steed	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Scull	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Owen	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hanks	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Peachey	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Knott	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Dobbinson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Merryman	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Beckett	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Hensby	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Walsh	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Mynett	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
,	O
Gislingham	B-pers
Arrowsmith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
1	O
,	O
2	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
hempen	O
sacks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
12	O
bushels	O
of	O
soot	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Abraham	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Newpark-bury	O
,	O
in	O
Hartfordshire	O
.	O
The	O
soot	O
and	O
sacks	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
evidences	O
can	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
six	O
score	O
bushels	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
24	O
sacks	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
loaded	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
waggon	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
with	O
24	O
sacks	O
of	O
soot	O
;	O
the	O
waggon	O
was	O
then	O
drawn	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	B-place
Inn	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
church	I-place
.	O
Next	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
sore	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
tilt	O
was	O
thrown	O
up	O
;	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
sacks	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
into	O
Plumtree	O
street	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoners	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
lay	O
the	O
soot	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
Blake	O
looking	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
Williams	O
had	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Blake	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
sacks	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
slung	O
them	O
away	O
at	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
stocks	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
are	O
chimney	O
sweepers	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
loaded	O
the	O
waggon	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
.	O
-	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
sold	O
the	O
soot	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
these	O
two	O
witnesses	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
soot	O
as	O
it	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
swept	O
a	O
smith	O
's	O
chimney	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
is	O
quite	O
different	O
soot	O
from	O
others	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
dust	O
of	O
a	O
corkcutter	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
I	O
saw	O
of	O
these	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
soot	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
,	O
and	O
Blake	O
there	O
said	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
gave-them	O
some	O
gin	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
deep	O
in	O
it	O
as	O
Williams	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
rolled	O
the	O
sacks	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
waggon	O
upon	O
Williams	O
's	O
back	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
Both	O
Acq	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gelding	O
of	O
a	O
chesnut	O
colour	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Hore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
gelding	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
)	O
by	O
his	O
order	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
him	O
to	O
Knightsbridge	O
from	O
Brook	O
street	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
linen	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
to	O
old	O
Mr.	O
Shacksby	O
's	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
I	O
fastened	O
my	O
horse	O
's	O
bridle	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
rail	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
turned	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
a	O
post	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
inches	O
above	O
the	O
rail	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
footmen	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
no	O
footmen	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
delivered	O
my	O
message	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
little	O
jobb	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
minute	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Kensington	O
,	O
a	O
sentinel	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
rode	O
through	O
the	O
town	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
his	O
horse	O
could	O
go	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
About	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
this	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
Inn	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
up	O
this	O
horse	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
people	O
coming	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
family	O
coming	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
fire	O
made	O
and	O
a	O
bed	O
sheeted	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
landlady	O
,	O
pray	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
that	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
landlord	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlady	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
had	O
took	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
change	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
change	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
till	O
his	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
came	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
returned	O
the	O
three	O
half	O
crowns	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
horse	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tilbury	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
hostler	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
in	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
chesnut	O
coloured	O
gelding	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
Nov.	O
4	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
more	O
a	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
stay	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
Head	O
and	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
in	O
Kensington	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Nov.	O
4	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
my	O
landlady	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
lodge	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
three	O
halfpennyworth	O
of	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
pay	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
swore	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ruined	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
instead	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
take	O
lodging	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
turned	O
himself	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
two	O
balls	O
and	O
prim	O
'd	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Kensington	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
lodging	O
?	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
to	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
late	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
to	O
night	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
tired	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Reading	O
to	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Thistle	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
their	O
beds	O
were	O
all	O
full	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
Head	O
and	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Bath	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
service	O
(	O
Esq	O
;	O
Carter	O
)	O
he	O
there	O
hired	O
a	O
servant	O
who	O
could	O
talk	O
French	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Paris	O
;	O
I	O
served	O
him	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
eight	O
months	O
,	O
part	O
in	O
Ireland	O
and	O
part	O
here	O
.	O
This	O
pistol	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
perquisite	O
.	O
Coming	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
horse	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
Kensington	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
soul	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
waited	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
nobody	O
did	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
this	O
Inn	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
hostler	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
post	O
chaises	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
drank	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
haste	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
ride	O
behind	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
chaises	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
advertise	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
lodging	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
ride	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
that	O
soldier	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
one	O
house	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Brandy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
tin	O
burners	O
to	O
lamps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bowles	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
*	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
bays	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Simpson	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
is	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
Rosemary	B-place
lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
was	O
backwards	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rumbling	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
Nov.	O
26	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
let	O
them	O
fall	O
on	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
want	O
occasioned	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
*	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
27	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
7	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Herman	B-pers
Milla	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
25	O
*	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Elgar	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sample	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Nov.	O
21	O
*	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sample	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Vine-street	B-place
,	I-place
by	I-place
Round	I-place
Court	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
coach-wheel	O
maker	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
prove	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Sample	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Davison	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
14	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
just	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
cloaths	O
and	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
room	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
lanthorn	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
broke	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Nov.	O
William	B-pers
Bonwick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Sample	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
two	O
doors	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
knock	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
from	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
sixpence	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
forc	O
'd	O
me	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
were	O
thieves	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
like	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Bonwick	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
Ann	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
cry	O
out	O
,	O
thieves	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
facing	O
the	O
door	O
run	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
fight	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
:	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
he	O
threw	O
away	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hanger	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
men	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
sling	O
away	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
turn	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
into	O
Chandos-street	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
tankard	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
towards	O
the	O
houses	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Nov.	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
butcher	O
's	O
door	O
in	O
Chandos-street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
also	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
this	O
tankard	O
thrown	O
by	O
some	O
body	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
yards	O
from	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
slung	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
Chandos-street	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
speed	O
;	O
we	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
came	O
;	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
flung	O
by	O
some	O
body	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
who	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
yards	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
fall	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
Chandos-street	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
running	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
tankard	O
fall	O
about	O
12	O
yards	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
Depos	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
9	O
,	O
10	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Leeman	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Kingston	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
secretly	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
*	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Billingsgate	B-place
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
about	O
5	O
minutes	O
after	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
pickpocket	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Leeman	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
constable	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wiseham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Billingsgate	O
market	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
pickpocket	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Leeman	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
cry	O
'd	O
duck	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
apron	O
was	O
tied	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
two	O
Dabbs	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
these	O
fish	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
likely	O
to	O
have	O
something	O
else	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
George	B-pers
Alehouse	I-pers
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
rustical	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
my	O
staff	O
to	O
shew	O
my	O
authority	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
third	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
near	O
his	O
feet	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
I	O
held	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
silk	O
one	O
,	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
Edmund	B-pers
Dadge	I-pers
:	O
the	O
second	O
I	O
held	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
linen	O
one	O
,	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
observ	O
'd	O
his	O
hand	O
under	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
third	O
lying	O
under	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
own	O
'd	O
by	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stacy	I-pers
.	O
Then	O
they	O
brought	O
in	O
Kingston	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
standing	O
together	O
,	O
Kingston	O
stood	O
before	O
Leeman	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Leeman	O
's	O
hand	O
under	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
something	O
;	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
swore	O
,	O
and	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
our	O
eyes	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
we	O
wanted	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
constable	O
hold	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Leeman	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Kingston	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Dage	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
Wiseham	O
depos	O
'd	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Dage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
morning	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
held	O
up	O
I	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
Leeman	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Kingston	O
Acquit	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
value	O
4	O
d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stacey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
that	O
same	O
morning	O
at	O
the	O
market	O
about	O
6	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
shads	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
dividing	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoner	O
's	O
standing	O
together	O
;	O
going	O
by	O
Kingston	O
he	O
directly	O
turn	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
him	O
pick	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
or	O
not	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
past	O
him	O
and	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
fishmonger	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
has	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
has	O
taken	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
that	O
other	O
man	O
.	O
We	O
secured	O
them	O
as	O
beforemention	O
'd	O
.	O
Leeman	O
Acq	O
.	O
Kingston	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribon	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Mellow	I-pers
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
++	O
.	O
Acquit	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
72	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
dye-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Nov.	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Beckenfield	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
,	I-pers
Ben	I-pers
the	I-pers
Coal-heaver	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Henry	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
hat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Dickenson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Maiden-lane	O
,	O
Wood-street	O
;	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
coming	O
from	O
St.	O
Martins	O
le	O
Grand	O
coffee	O
house	O
to	O
Gutter-lane	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
dead	O
wall	O
near	B-place
Goldsmith	I-place
's	I-place
hall	I-place
,	O
three	O
fellows	O
met	O
me	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
collar	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
me	O
,	O
pin	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
moon-light	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
very	O
plain	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
hit	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
blows	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
stood	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
my	O
arms	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
watch	O
and	O
thieves	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hold	O
my	O
tongue	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
kept	O
calling	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
which	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
down	O
an	O
alley	O
into	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
streight	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
within	O
50	O
or	O
60	O
yards	O
of	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
running	O
full	O
speed	O
when	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
mentions	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
made	O
no	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
430	O
,	O
517	O
,	O
535	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
14.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Crutchley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
81	O
guineas	O
,	O
4	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
number	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
.	I-pers
Tofts	I-pers
Esq	O
.	O
Nov.	O
19	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
serge	O
Jackets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
three	O
cloth-Jackets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
periwig	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
;	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hugoe	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
29	O
*	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ratcliff	B-place
Highway	I-place
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hugoe	I-pers
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
wig	O
again	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
jacket	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
part	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
were	O
lost	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Nov.	O
he	O
confest	O
taking	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Spring	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
confirm	O
'd	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
.	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
wig	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
were	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16	O
,	O
17	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Amy	B-pers
Gloom	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
pockets	O
,	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
mettle	O
buttons	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
hood	O
,	O
one	O
velvet	O
hood	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
lawn	O
sleeves	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Young	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
Oct.	O
16	O
*	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Elder-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Leonard	I-place
Shore-ditch	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
Ann	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
;	O
the	O
cap	O
she	O
has	O
now	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
she	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
;	O
the	O
shoes	O
and	O
stockings	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
mine	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
officer	O
for	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
Norton	O
Fallgate	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
Ann	B-pers
Hilliard	I-pers
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watchouse	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
examining	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
confest	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
encourag	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
this	O
thing	O
by	O
Amy	B-pers
Gloom	I-pers
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
granted	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
an	O
old	O
cap	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
said	O
was	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Young	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Briggs	O
.	O
Gloom	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Hilliard	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Gloom	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18	O
,	O
19	O
,	O
20	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Mcgennes	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Tobin	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
56	O
glass	O
bottles	O
,	O
54	O
drinking	O
glasses	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Roger	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
+	O
.	O
21	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Udall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
about	O
3	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Urwin	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
seven	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
35	O
s.	O
four	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
three	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
lac	O
'd	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
plain	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
russles	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
+	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Urwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	B-place
of	I-place
Bartletsquare	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
grocer	O
's	O
and	O
confectioner	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
can	O
better	O
prove	O
the	O
property	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Urwin	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
lost	O
seven	O
shirts	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
six	O
caps	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
lac	O
'd	O
,	O
four	O
plain	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
lac	O
'd	O
russles	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
plain	O
,	O
one	O
lac	O
'd	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
plain	O
ones	O
,	O
six	O
pillowbears	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
curtain	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
one	O
pewter	O
spoon	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
two	O
china	O
basons	O
,	O
two	O
towels	O
,	O
one	O
stays	O
cover	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
buroe	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
parlour	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pretty	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Vere-street	O
,	O
Clare-market	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
four	O
shirts	O
,	O
a	O
lace	O
cap	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
russles	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
some	O
gentlewoman	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
bring	O
things	O
for	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
31	O
s.	O
on	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
about	O
35	O
,	O
or	O
36	O
s.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Urwin	O
.	O
Are	O
these	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Urwin	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
buroe	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Raven	O
Inn	O
in	O
Bear-street	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
lives	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
where	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
ladies	O
of	O
pleasure	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anthony	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fillpot	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
50	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
+	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fillpot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Clare-court	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Clare-market	I-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
of	O
hats	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
was	O
12	O
months	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
facing	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
pins	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
window	O
were	O
fast	O
,	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
house	O
joins	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
all	O
fast	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
two	O
watchmen	O
awak	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
giving	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
my	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
shutter	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
press	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
keep	O
my	O
hats	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
upwards	O
of	O
five	O
dozen	O
of	O
hats	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
about	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
about	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
old	O
hats	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
Anthony	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
new	O
goal	O
Surry	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ecklin	O
the	O
evidence	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
he	O
believed	O
about	O
6	O
dozen	O
of	O
hats	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Codosa	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
transported	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
511	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Codosa	O
about	O
6	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ecklin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
Anth	O
.	O
Whittle	O
;	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
570	O
,	O
as	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
justly	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Nov.	O
was	O
12	O
months	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
directions	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bar	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
shutter	O
without	O
;	O
we	O
wrench	O
'd	O
the	O
staple	O
back	O
with	O
an	O
iron	O
crow	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
first	O
shutter	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
Anthony	O
Whittle	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
held	O
a	O
bag	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
11	O
old	O
hats	O
;	O
then	O
Edward	O
Thorp	O
lighted	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
took	O
the	O
crow	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
place	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
some	O
new	O
hats	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
handed	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
dozen	O
and	O
eleven	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
conveniently	O
carry	O
more	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
prevented	O
us	O
coming	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Ecklin	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
yards	O
off	O
,	O
looking	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
watchman	O
did	O
not	O
surprize	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
began	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
ended	O
about	O
three	O
;	O
Whittle	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
Codosa	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
then	O
in	O
Bell-Alley	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
share	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Anthony	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
the	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Thorp	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
home	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
then	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Ecklin	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
any	O
after	O
we	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
together	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
hats	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Fillpot	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
five	O
dozen	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
them	O
from	O
?	O
Fillpot	O
.	O
From	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
press	O
coming	O
in	O
as	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
your	O
window	O
fastened	O
?	O
Fillpot	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
wooden	O
bar	O
goes	O
a-cross	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
.	O
Eckling	O
.	O
Thorp	O
was	O
cast	O
for	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
now	O
transported	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
570	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mayoralty	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blachford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
23	O
,	O
24	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
one	O
wooden	O
drawer	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
four	O
silver	O
pocket	O
pieces	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
East	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
October	O
there	O
came	O
five	O
boys	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
just	O
before	O
12	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
very	O
civilly	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
brandy	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
how	O
I	O
must	O
divide	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
how	O
.	O
Hatton	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
his	O
evidence	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
liquor	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
sludge	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
change	O
for	O
sixpence	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
drawer	O
out	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
drawer	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
Harrington	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
all	O
I	O
was	O
worth	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
children	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
coming	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
behind	O
a	O
Vessel	O
and	O
screamed	O
out	O
,	O
thieves	O
and	O
murder	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
drawer	O
away	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
four	O
silver	O
pocket	O
pieces	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
groat	O
;	O
these	O
were	O
pieces	O
that	O
were	O
pledg	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
about	O
16	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Richard	B-pers
Pett	I-pers
,	O
Randolph	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
met	O
together	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
Thomas	O
Bunn	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
attempt	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
let	O
us	O
four	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
how	O
many	O
outs	O
she	O
should	O
make	O
;	O
Harrington	O
said	O
,	O
make	O
four	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
halfpennyworth	O
of	O
anniseed	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
dram	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
woman	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
deliver	O
all	O
you	O
are	O
worth	O
;	O
Randolph	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
went	O
round	O
the	O
computer	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
four	O
outlandish	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
groat	O
;	O
she	O
woman	O
screamed	O
out	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
near	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Wilsher	O
lane	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
emptied	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
sixpence	O
,	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
single	O
farthings	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Pett	I-pers
sold	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
pieces	O
for	O
eightpence	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
Inn	O
,	O
we	O
threw	O
the	O
three	O
others	O
into	O
the	O
Tower	O
ditch	O
;	O
my	O
share	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
came	O
to	O
ninepence	O
,	O
and	O
Harrington	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
Bunn	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dyer	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Dyer	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
Harrington	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Bunn	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Tidd	I-pers
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Randolph	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pett	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ormand	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
eight	O
pewter	O
dishes	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
13	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
two	O
pewter	O
water	O
plates	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
cover	O
,	O
four	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
pottage	O
pot	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
pottage	O
pot	O
,	O
two	O
saucepans	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
stew	O
pan	O
,	O
a	O
box	O
iron	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
heater	O
,	O
a	O
stand	O
for	O
a	O
box	O
iron	O
,	O
two	O
looking	O
glasses	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
two	O
diaper	O
napkins	O
,	O
one	O
dussel	O
cloak	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
six	O
linen	O
towels	O
,	O
three	O
cotton	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Ormand	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Ailoff	I-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
opposite	I-place
the	I-place
new	I-place
meeting	I-place
house	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
find	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
things	O
lost	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
and	O
27th	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
then	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
robbed	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
taken	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
thieves	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
you	O
'll	O
hear	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
goods	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
M.	O
Ormand	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
eight	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
mentioning	O
each	O
thing	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
bid	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
Forrester	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Hatton	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
evidence	O
,	O
who	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
.	O
(	O
the	O
evidence	O
in	O
the	O
farmer	O
trial	O
.	O
)	O
Anthony	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tidd	I-pers
,	O
Randolph	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
Dick	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
Ailoff	O
street	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
betwixt	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
linen	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
window	O
;	O
we	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
by	O
shoving	O
the	O
sash	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
concluded	O
to	O
go	O
again	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
Anthony	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
wrenched	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
tinder	O
box	O
and	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
Tidd	O
went	O
in	O
also	O
;	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
us	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
Bourne	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
below	O
in	O
the	O
kitchin	O
,	O
pewter	O
,	O
brass	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
they	O
put	O
them	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
Dick	B-pers
Pett	I-pers
and	O
Randolph	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
received	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
them	O
and	O
one	O
apron	O
in	O
our	O
parcel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
our	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tidd	I-pers
,	O
Randolph	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
,	O
Pett	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
;	O
Anthony	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Webster	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
all	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
after	O
we	O
were	O
gone	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
goods	O
were	O
they	O
you	O
had	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
copper	O
pot	O
,	O
two	O
saucepans	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
pot	O
,	O
some	O
dishes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
cover	O
to	O
cover	O
meat	O
with	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
bag	O
full	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
linen	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
looking	O
glass	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
our	O
's	O
to	O
one	O
Campey	O
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
for	O
12	O
shillings	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
Place	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Tidd	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Hatton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
;	O
Tidd	O
had	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
I.	O
Henry	O
Peal	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Tidd	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
12	O
shillings	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hind	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
when	O
Tidd	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
Hatton	O
was	O
telling	O
the	O
justice	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
;	O
Tidd	O
told	O
the	O
boy	O
he	O
lyed	O
in	O
saying	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
fast	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
Minous	O
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
for	O
12	O
shillings	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
big	O
a	O
thief	O
as	O
himself	O
.	O
Woodward	O
Harlow	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Tidd	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
Hind	O
.	O
Isabella	O
Collier	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
fast	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
up	O
at	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
?	O
M.	O
Ormand	O
.	O
We	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
the	O
pewter	O
rattling	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
dog	O
barked	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
shutter	O
was	O
ripp	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
hinges	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sash	O
shoved	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
hear	O
the	O
Jew	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
New	O
Goal	O
,	O
Surry	O
.	O
Tidd	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Bourne	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
boy	O
(	O
meaning	O
Hatton	O
)	O
from	O
Adam	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
16	O
,	O
in	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pennant	I-pers
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Curtise	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
worsted	O
for	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Row	B-pers
Rotheram	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
Row	O
Rotheram	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
frame	O
work	O
knitter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Cary	O
street	O
,	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
parish	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
November	O
13	O
a	O
neighbour	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
shop	O
in	O
Lincoln	B-place
's	I-place
Inn	I-place
was	O
on	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
what	O
haste	O
I	O
could	O
thither	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
smother	O
but	O
no	O
flame	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
stockings	O
about	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
holes	O
empty	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
a	O
shop	O
next	O
door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
mine	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
shut	O
up	O
some	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
open	O
and	O
a	O
pannel	O
broke	O
from	O
his	O
shop	O
into	O
a	O
pamphlet	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
that	O
into	O
mine	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
immediately	O
suspect	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
married	O
my	O
daughter	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
dead	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hosier	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
near	O
Hide	O
Park	O
corner	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Faulcon	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
selling	O
stockings	O
this	O
13th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
cheap	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Rotheram	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
came	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
stockings	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
defence	O
to	O
make	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Euphan	B-pers
Callwell	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
two	O
callicoe	O
shirts	O
,	O
17	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
six	O
India	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
eight	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
eight	O
callicoe	O
caps	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
stockings	O
,	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
gloves	O
,	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
October	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
,	O
without	O
his	O
knowledge	O
,	O
pawned	O
the	O
goods	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
with	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Newcomb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
James	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
.	O
October	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
through	O
Featherstone	B-place
Buildings	I-place
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
;	O
three	O
persons	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
jostled	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
watch	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
received	O
several	O
blows	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
continued	O
calling	O
out	O
till	O
they	O
fired	O
a	O
pistol	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
cut	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
the	O
ball	O
grazed	O
and	O
wounded	O
me	O
near	O
my	O
left	O
temple	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
scar	O
appeared	O
,	O
and	O
much	O
powder	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
that	O
will	O
remain	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
perceived	O
two	O
balls	O
had	O
gone	O
through	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
immediately	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Featherstone	O
Buildings	O
,	O
Holborn	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
watch-house	O
box	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
person	O
say	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
?	O
another	O
voice	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
water	O
;	O
in	O
an	O
instant	O
of	O
time	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
call	O
,	O
watch	O
,	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
25	O
yards	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
pistol	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
flash	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Clayton	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
leaning	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
ran	O
down	O
Chancery	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
lost	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
the	O
pistol	O
going	O
off	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
still	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
watch	O
,	O
thieves	O
,	O
murder	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
ran	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
near	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
Door	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
fell	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
my	O
stand	O
is	O
at	O
Great	O
Turnstile	O
,	O
Holborn	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
he	O
turned	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
Chancery	O
lane	O
.	O
Randolph	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
Holborn	O
feeding	O
a	O
coachman	O
's	O
horses	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
him	O
cry	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
pistol	O
and	O
hanger	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
hanger	O
lying	O
very	O
near	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
secured	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Red	O
Lion	O
street	O
with	O
a	O
shipmate	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
any	O
farther	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
can	O
find	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
leave	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
coming	O
by	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
called	O
Featherstone	O
Buildings	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
musket	O
or	O
a	O
pistol	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
coming	O
down	O
Holborn	O
,	O
I	O
presently	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
my	O
best	O
endeavour	O
to	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
these	O
fellows	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
a	O
pretty	O
way	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
made	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
missed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
almost	O
to	O
Chancery	O
lane	O
end	O
;	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
hanger	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
missed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
stoop	O
to	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
men	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Byall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
boys	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Farley	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
24	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
++	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
30	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
calves	O
skins	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Crosse	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
his	O
warehouse	O
for	O
his	O
skins	O
is	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
,	O
next	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
Win	O
Markham	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
heard	O
the	O
warehouse	O
door	O
unlock	O
and	O
somebody	O
go	O
in	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
locked	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
had	O
her	O
room	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
calves	O
skins	O
there	O
under	O
her	O
bed	O
among	O
some	O
foul	O
linen	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
key	O
to	O
that	O
warehouse	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
with	O
many	O
others	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
keys	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
was	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
being	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Adreanous	B-pers
Vander	I-pers
Bomonere	I-pers
,	O
October	O
31	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Bishopsgate	B-place
October	O
31	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
St.	O
Helen	O
's	O
gateway	O
.	O
Benjamin	O
Polock	O
saw	O
it	O
done	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
was	O
sweeping	O
the	O
church	O
door	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gone	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Polock	O
bid	O
him	O
to	O
abide	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
met	O
him	O
walking	O
towards	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
after	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
hat	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
sir	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
forgive	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
(	O
confessing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
)	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
thrown	O
over	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Lodge	O
's	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
Acq	O
.	O
33	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pound	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Dains	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
dead	O
goose	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Joffs	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
ripping	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
;	O
one	O
sash	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Maybrick	I-pers
,	O
December	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutors	O
were	O
journeymen	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
building	O
some	O
stables	O
,	O
from	O
Little	B-place
Moorfields	I-place
to	I-place
Moor	I-place
lane	I-place
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
December	O
3	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
of	O
going	O
in	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
their	O
master	O
's	O
apprentice	O
,	O
detected	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
saws	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
going	O
off	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36	O
,	O
37	O
,	O
38	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Procter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Derby	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
six	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
locket	O
,	O
one	O
chrystal	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
necklace	O
,	O
eight	O
gold	O
beads	O
,	O
five	O
pennyweight	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
four	O
broken	O
gold	O
ear	O
bobs	O
,	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
toothpick	O
case	O
,	O
one	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
scales	O
,	O
32	O
ounces	O
of	O
brass	O
weights	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roker	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
Lydia	B-pers
Roker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
opposite	B-place
the	I-place
London	I-place
Workhouse	I-place
in	I-place
Bishopsgate	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
supper	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
on	O
the	O
chain	O
;	O
I	O
shut	O
too	O
the	O
door	O
betwixt	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
and	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
supposed	O
indeed	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
chain	O
falling	O
off	O
the	O
hook	O
;	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
mentioned	O
them	O
all	O
over	O
)	O
the	O
brass	O
weights	O
were	O
to	O
weigh	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
three	O
drawers	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
all	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
shut	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
upon	O
the	O
compter	O
and	O
missed	O
this	O
box	O
immediately	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
till	O
until	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Leblon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
lodged	O
all	O
four	O
at	O
one	O
house	O
in	O
Kingsland	O
Road	O
at	O
one	O
Thomas	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
down	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
on	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
said	O
I	O
might	O
make	O
myself	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
his	O
mother	O
used	O
to	O
chare	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Roker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
how	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
all	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
shoved	O
his	O
back	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
came	O
open	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
chain	O
off	O
the	O
hook	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
three	O
little	O
drawers	O
with	O
weights	O
and	O
scales	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
bits	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
buttons	O
,	O
and	O
trifling	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Derby	O
Long	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Procter	I-pers
;	O
then	O
Long	O
and	O
Procter	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
still	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
brought	O
out	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
seal	O
,	O
several	O
gold	O
beads	O
,	O
several	O
old	O
farthings	O
,	O
and	O
halfpence	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
the	O
till	O
down	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
John	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
a	O
glass	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
some	O
children	O
's	O
toys	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
tin	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
flung	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
keannel	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Minous	O
in	O
Duke's-place	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
silver	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
say	O
what	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
gold	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
got	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
all	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
one	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
what	O
he	O
pleas	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
where	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
shillings	O
was	O
the	O
most	O
I	O
had	O
for	O
my	O
share	O
:	O
Procter	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
.	O
Ross	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
Brown	B-pers
Bear	I-pers
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
things	O
for	O
40	O
s.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Kingsland-road	O
,	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
quarrel	O
between	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
Long	O
,	O
Ross	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
about	O
some	O
gold	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
charging	O
each	O
other	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
from	O
one	O
another	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
hid	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gold	O
seal	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
locket	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
odd	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
business	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
I	O
attend	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
light	O
people	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
is	O
this	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
lodging	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
beds	O
are	O
there	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
about	O
43	O
beds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
is	O
this	O
house	O
in	O
Kingsland	O
Road	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Spread	O
Eagle	O
.	O
-	O
Rogers	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
fastening	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
houses	O
where	O
I	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
till	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
set	O
behind	O
a	O
gate	O
in	O
Dunning	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
till	O
next	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
owner	O
for	O
the	O
till	O
and	O
things	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
a	O
paper	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
Ross	O
's	O
Defence	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Procter	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
Leblon	O
.	O
)	O
Long	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
39	O
,	O
40	O
,	O
41	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Andrew	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pails	O
,	O
a	O
washing	O
tub	O
,	O
a	O
musket	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lockia	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
7	O
++	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
garret	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
there	O
also	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
42	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
sparib	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
peck	O
of	O
apples	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
20	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
keeps	O
the	O
Uxbridge	O
Waggon	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
accountable	O
for	O
all	O
goods	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
waggon	O
was	O
overturn	O
'd	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Lane	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
Chandos	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
Inn	O
,	O
at	O
Holborn-bridge	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
pretensions	O
of	O
assisting	O
in	O
loading	O
and	O
unloading	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
money	O
for	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
staid	O
longer	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
this	O
basket	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
intelligence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
New-street	O
,	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
basket	O
cut	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
43	O
,	O
44	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
spades	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
3	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
++	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
45	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wattag	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
worsted	O
damask	O
banjan	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
velvet	O
cap	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Emmit	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
Acquit	O
.	O
46	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
41	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jefferson	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
47	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hugh	B-pers
Colligan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
coffoy	O
seat	O
of	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
calimancoe	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Oct	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
48	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Watlin	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
John	I-pers
Peters	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Peters	I-pers
Jack	I-pers
,	O
late	B-place
of	I-place
Horsey	I-place
in	I-place
Norfolk	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
in	O
landing	O
and	O
running	O
goods	O
,	O
liable	O
to	O
pay	O
duty	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
March	O
11	O
,	O
1746	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Lacket	I-pers
.	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Horsey	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1746	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Peters	B-pers
Jack	I-pers
;	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
frequent	O
Mrs.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
there	O
call	O
riders	O
,	O
or	O
smugglers	O
;	O
they	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
ten	O
,	O
twelve	O
,	O
or	O
fourteen	O
in	O
company	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
1746	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
brass	O
piece	O
,	O
either	O
a	O
carbine	O
or	O
a	O
blunderbuss	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
.	O
On	O
that	O
day	O
the	O
cutter	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
all	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
there	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Lacket	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
go	O
away	O
?	O
Lacket	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
all	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
some	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
had	O
not	O
arms	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
that	O
brass	O
gun	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
return	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1746	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Horsey	O
to	O
see	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
one	O
Cosines	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
sled	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Bailey	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
?	O
adding	O
,	O
the	O
town	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
smugglers	O
,	O
and	O
perhaps	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
safe	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
once	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
the	O
customs	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
parted	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Manning	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
several	O
people	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Peirce	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
for	O
answer	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
no	O
body	O
here	O
but	O
Dick	B-pers
Cosines	I-pers
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
wants	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
tiff	O
of	O
punch	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Manning	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
such	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
smugglers	O
they	O
will	O
do	O
you	O
a	O
mischief	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
a	O
message	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eleven	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
arm	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
sled	O
to	O
the	O
barn	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
my	O
self	O
down	O
in	O
some	O
barley	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
hollow	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
gentlemen	O
do	O
when	O
they	O
catch	O
a	O
fox	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Chapman	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
executed	O
:	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
beat	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
they	O
oblig	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Peirce	O
's	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
Cockeye	O
great	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
rub	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
and	O
black	O
'd	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
they	O
put	O
a	O
gun	O
betwixt	O
my	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
me	O
round	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
their	O
member	O
of	O
parliament	O
;	O
then	O
Cock-eye	O
beat	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
leather	O
thong	O
;	O
afterwards	O
they	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
farmer	O
's	O
house	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Manning	O
's	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
without	O
giving	O
me	O
time	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
cloaths	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
a	O
line	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
and	O
whipp	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
their	O
whips	O
till	O
the	O
skin	O
was	O
all	O
off	O
my	O
fingers	O
;	O
I	O
begged	O
and	O
prayed	O
for	O
mercy	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
churchyard	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
long	O
knife	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
obliged	O
me	O
to	O
answer	O
such	O
questions	O
as	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
concerning	O
the	O
reasons	O
of	O
my	O
coming	O
down	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cord	O
and	O
tied	O
my	O
arms	O
round	O
me	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
cord	O
about	O
my	O
neck	O
and	O
held	O
me	O
up	O
upon	O
a	O
tree	O
;	O
they	O
held	O
me	O
up	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
let	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
me	O
to	O
unbutton	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
swear	O
damnation	O
to	O
my	O
soul	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
revealed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
very	O
immodest	O
questions	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Manning	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
Chapman	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
used	O
ill	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
got	O
to	O
them	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
used	O
so	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Peirce	O
's	O
house	O
again	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
spying	O
glass	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
your	O
cutter	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
swore	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
lay	O
concealed	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
34	O
or	O
35	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
cutter	O
unloaded	O
,	O
the	O
tea	O
was	O
in	O
oilskin	O
bags	O
that	O
held	O
about	O
27	O
pounds	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
casks	O
called	O
half	O
anchors	O
of	O
brandy	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
45	O
horses	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
load	O
and	O
go	O
off	O
from	O
sea	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rode	O
by	O
me	O
returning	O
from	O
the	O
Beach	O
,	O
they	O
rode	O
two	O
and	O
two	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Summerton	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
assist	O
in	O
loading	O
the	O
horses	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Yes	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
boat	O
came	O
on	O
shore	O
from	O
the	O
cutter	O
five	O
times	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross-examination	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
kept	O
a	O
coffee	O
house	O
at	O
Yarmouth	O
in	O
Norfolk	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
10	O
miles	O
from	O
Horsey	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
day	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
knows	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
10th	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Smith	O
,	O
only	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
Smith	O
was	O
armed	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
No	O
.	O
631	O
in	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pennant	I-pers
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
did	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
armed	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Beach	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rial	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farmer	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
at	O
Horsey	O
,	O
either	O
March	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
,	O
1746	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
any	O
arms	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
another	O
party	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Lucy	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
7	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
of	O
Budsdale	O
in	O
Suffolk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Watling	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
him	O
called	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
name	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
sir	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
hear	O
he	O
was	O
deemed	O
a	O
smuggler	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
husbandry	O
work	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Trapp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
town	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
does	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
go	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
name	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Watling	I-pers
;	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
smuggler	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
him	O
called	O
Peters	B-pers
Jack	I-pers
?	O
or	O
John	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
?	O
Trapp	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Yelverton	O
in	O
Norfolk	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fustin	I-pers
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
heard	O
him	O
called	O
Peters	B-pers
Jack	I-pers
and	O
Jack	B-pers
Peters	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
's	O
right	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Doe	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
executed	O
at	O
Tyburn	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
49	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Carbold	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Cockeye	I-pers
,	O
late	B-place
of	I-place
Horsey	I-place
in	I-place
Norfolk	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
,	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
in	O
landing	O
and	O
running	O
goods	O
liable	O
to	O
pay	O
duty	O
,	O
March	O
11	O
,	O
1746	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Lindow	I-pers
:	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Rowlsby	O
in	O
Norfolk	O
,	O
near	O
Horsey	B-place
;	O
I	O
remember	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rial	I-pers
at	O
Horsey	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
farmer	O
there	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
riders	O
used	O
to	O
frequent	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1746	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
smugglers	O
horses	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
came	O
there	O
on	O
horseback	O
March	O
10	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
smallish	O
pistols	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fired	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
off	O
against	O
the	O
barn	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
load	O
it	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Lindow	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
it	O
by	O
being	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
was	O
whipped	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
a	O
cutter	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Beach	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
Horsey	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
got	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
coming	O
by	O
spying	O
glasses	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
went	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
four	O
horses	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
30	O
or	O
40	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
loaded	O
his	O
horses	O
with	O
casks	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
brandy	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
loaded	O
their	O
horses	O
,	O
some	O
had	O
oil	O
skin	O
bags	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
tea	O
brought	O
in	O
such	O
bags	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
on	O
purpose	O
for	O
smuggling	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stick	O
his	O
pistols	O
in	O
his	O
girdle	O
:	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
people	O
were	O
armed	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
the	O
Beach	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Carbold	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
only	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Cockeye	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
arms	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
and	O
had	O
shot	O
that	O
one	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
them	O
by	O
his	O
side	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Beach	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
black	O
'd	O
his	O
face	O
and	O
whipp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Beach	O
armed	O
with	O
a	O
brass	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
armed	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
busy	O
on	O
the	O
Beach	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Kinning	O
,	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
customs	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
gang	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
too	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Landal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
these	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
farmer	O
and	O
lived	O
at	O
Shatsal	O
;	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Mortimore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
he	O
ever	O
followed	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
farming	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
served	O
overseer	O
of	O
the	O
poor	O
in	O
his	O
parish	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
esteemed	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
honesty	O
and	O
probity	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
keep	O
horses	O
upon	O
his	O
farm	O
?	O
Mortimore	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
sometimes	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
four	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
cut	O
tail	O
,	O
or	O
long	O
tail	O
horses	O
?	O
Mortimore	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
short	O
tail	O
horses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
smugglers	O
horses	O
long	O
or	O
short	O
tails	O
?	O
Mortimore	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
smugglers	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Booty	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
esteemed	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
country	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
reputation	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
smuggler	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Boyley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Shatsal	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
him	O
last	O
Michaelmas	O
was	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
esteemed	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
deemed	O
a	O
smuggler	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
family	O
there	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
cross	O
examination	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
home	O
brandy	O
or	O
tea	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
three	O
cart	O
horses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
50	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Oadwey	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Valentine	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pewter	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
twopence	O
,	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
dimity	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
stocks	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
51	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Knibb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Chalkley	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
an	O
infant	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
+	O
Martha	B-pers
Chalkley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
taking	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
forswear	O
myself	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
to	O
hell	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
us	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
put	O
apprentice	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
justly	O
tell	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
making	O
candles	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
to	O
stay	O
till	O
the	O
officer	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
upon	O
the	O
cellar	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
feel	O
up	O
my	O
petticoats	O
;	O
I	O
prayed	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
coming	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
last	O
haymaking	O
time	O
)	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
my	O
mistress	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
that	O
time	O
)	O
my	O
bed	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchin	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mistress	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
bed	O
cloaths	O
off	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
my	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
your	O
body	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
his	O
nastiness	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
word	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
I	O
mean	O
his	O
y	O
-	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
I	O
prayed	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
then	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
something	O
wet	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
willing	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
so	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
any	O
force	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
shoulders	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
continue	O
in	O
that	O
posture	O
.	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
to	O
any	O
person	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
was	O
asham	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
running	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
walk	O
as	O
I	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
you	O
observ	O
'd	O
,	O
after	O
you	O
awoke	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
was	O
then	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
bed-clothes	O
were	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
awake	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
did	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
He	O
wak	O
'd	O
me	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
y	O
-	O
d	O
into	O
my	O
body	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
awak	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
bid	O
me	O
hold	O
my	O
tongue	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
mistress	O
hear	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
cried	O
out	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
master	O
undrest	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
his	O
cloaths	O
were	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
ask	O
you	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
do	O
so	O
again	O
?	O
M.	O
Chalkley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
midwife	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
mother	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
betwixt	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
her	O
child	O
had	O
receiv	O
'd	O
some	O
great	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
examine	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
much	O
hurt	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
any	O
man	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
master	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
running	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
offering	O
some	O
violence	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
enter	O
'd	O
her	O
body	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
open	O
,	O
as	O
people	O
are	O
after	O
such	O
-	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
laceration	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
pressing	O
on	O
her	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
?	O
Bennet	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
midwife	O
.	O
[	O
She	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
midwife	O
,	O
who	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
likewise	O
.	O
]	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
52	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Brandel	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Alexander	B-pers
Brandel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
Change	B-place
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
mist	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
there	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
again	O
from	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Butcher	O
,	O
who	O
can	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
observ	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Swithins	O
Alley	O
,	O
attempting	O
to	O
pick	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
watch	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
went	O
through	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
followed	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
several	O
attempts	O
to	O
pick	O
several	O
pockets	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
north	O
gate	O
of	O
the	O
Exchange	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
he	O
was	O
ever	O
guilty	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
about	O
a	O
little	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
through	O
the	O
Change	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
53	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
2	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
of	O
thence	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
five	O
printed	O
pictures	O
in	O
frames	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
needle-work	O
sampler	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
frame	O
and	O
glass	O
,	O
one	O
velvet	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Red-Lyon	B-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
Watling-street	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
ground	O
floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
there	O
last	O
?	O
Woodward	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
there	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
who	O
bought	O
the	O
kettle	O
and	O
cap	O
,	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
can	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
selling	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
joiner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
journeyman	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Groves	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
not	O
intending	O
to	O
surprize	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
left	O
word	O
where	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
prints	O
were	O
not	O
demolish	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
them	O
I	O
found	O
with	O
the	O
sampler	O
at	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
written	O
account	O
;	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	O
:	O
my	O
shop	O
joyns	O
to	O
my	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
between	O
them	O
is	O
not	O
always	O
lock	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
work	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
:	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
committed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
'd	O
he	O
'd	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
honour	O
among	O
thieves	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
'd	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
what	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
understood	O
he	O
meant	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
safe	O
at	O
his	O
stand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
made	O
him	O
any	O
promises	O
?	O
Woodward	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
or	O
threats	O
either	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
swimming	O
bout	O
,	O
so	O
voluntarily	O
told	O
the	O
whole	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
about	O
2	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
'd	O
the	O
pin	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
down	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
only	O
a	O
single	O
lock	O
,	O
and	O
bolted	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
put	O
the	O
shutter	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
grabled	O
about	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
