TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
24th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Francis	B-pers
Cokayne	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1751	O
,	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
COKAYNE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
Sir	O
MARTIN	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GUNDRY	O
||	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
SMYTHE	I-pers
+	O
,	O
RICHARD	O
ADAMS	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
:	O
and	O
Justice	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
||	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Jarman	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Welden	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mynde	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Malivero	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Grisson	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Springe	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Usher	I-pers
,	O
Timothy	B-pers
Pierson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oswin	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spicer	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parton	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Jos	B-pers
Rooke	I-pers
,	O
Collin	B-pers
Donaldson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trislove	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Etherington	I-pers
.	O
187	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ridgeway	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
188	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Buck	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
189	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Grover	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	O
Groves	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Belsise	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Hampstead	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Jan.	O
my	O
stable	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
after	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
black	O
gelding	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Describe	O
this	O
gelding	O
.	O
Groves	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
three	O
white	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blaze	O
in	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
wall	O
eyes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Groves	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
loitering	O
about	O
us	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
last	O
hay-time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
little	O
things	O
before	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
horse	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
.	O
I	O
inquired	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
St.	O
Alban	O
's	O
(	O
knowing	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
near	O
Luton	O
,	O
in	O
Bedfordshire	O
)	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
horse	O
cry	O
'd	O
at	O
Watford	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
again	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Chapel	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Enfield	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
horse	O
worth	O
?	O
Groves	O
,	O
He	O
is	O
worth	O
11	O
or	O
12	O
l.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Chapel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Jan.	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
white	O
feet	O
,	O
a	O
blaze	O
down	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
wall	O
eyes	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Clayton	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
our	O
bailey	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
expected	O
him	O
every	O
hour	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
my	O
mistress	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
horses	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
uneasy	O
;	O
often	O
looking	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
though	O
he	O
suspected	O
every	O
body	O
he	O
saw	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
inquire	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
for	O
our	O
bailey	O
;	O
who	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
and	O
proffer	O
'd	O
the	O
horse	O
for	O
nine	O
guineas	O
;	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
was	O
true	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
afford	O
to	O
give	O
much	O
;	O
but	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
I	O
should	O
give	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
adding	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
whispering	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
ten	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
him	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
earnest	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
fetch	O
a	O
voucher	O
to	O
tell	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
otherwise	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
Bushey	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
common	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
by	O
,	O
proffer	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
himself	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
9	O
d.	O
towards	O
that	O
charge	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
send	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
answered	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
held	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
struggled	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
tore	O
his	O
cloaths	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
we	O
,	O
with	O
much	O
difficulty	O
,	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
such	O
man	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
calling	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
breakfast	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
there	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
such	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
subscribing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Thus	O
having	O
obtain	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
subscrib	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
curtisey	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
horse	O
advertised	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
a	O
man	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
at	O
Enfield	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
this	O
horse	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Jan.	O
(	O
describing	O
him	O
as	O
Abraham	B-pers
Chapel	I-pers
had	O
done	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
Bushey	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
John	O
Short	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
seven	O
men	O
could	O
do	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
hand-cuffs	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
chain	O
'd	O
him	O
too	O
,	O
yet	O
he	O
releas	O
'd	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
afterwards	O
he	O
tore	O
his	O
hand-cuffs	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
teeth	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kendal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Abraham	B-pers
Chapel	I-pers
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Jan.	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Chapel	O
buy	O
the	O
horse	O
for	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
(	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
horse	O
as	O
the	O
others	O
did	O
)	O
When	O
Ab	O
.	O
Chapel	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
voucher	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
his	O
father	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
any	O
body	O
should	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Chapel	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
one	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chair	O
where	O
he	O
sat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
himself	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
afterwards	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
All	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
could	O
say	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
mistaken	O
in	O
their	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
witness	O
being	O
all	O
ask	O
'd	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
answered	O
in	O
the	O
affirmative	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
190	O
,	O
191	O
,	O
192	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Huney	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wadsworth	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
17	O
pair	O
of	O
worstead	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
pair	O
of	O
yarn	O
,	O
ditto	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
worstead	O
cap	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Eliz	O
.	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
could	O
only	O
depose	O
to	O
finding	O
her	O
shop	O
window	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
the	O
above	O
goods	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
mentioned	O
;	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burn	I-pers
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
proved	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
the	O
three	O
persons	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
evidence	O
to	O
corroborate	O
his	O
testimony	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
acquitted	O
.	O
193	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
china	O
quart	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
9	O
.	O
||	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
at	O
Brumley	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
mug	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
another	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
link	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
going	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
benefit	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
walking	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
behind	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
china	O
mug	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
privately	O
looking	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
's	O
mug	O
,	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
I	O
had	O
stop	O
'd	O
a	O
thief	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
stood	O
close	O
by	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
assisted	O
me	O
or	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
of	O
a	O
china	O
mug	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
over	O
a	O
wall	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Widow	O
Withers	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
lanthorn	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
behind	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
mug	O
broke	O
in	O
pieces	O
.	O
The	O
pieces	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
compared	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
's	O
house	O
this	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
pots	O
of	O
slip	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
reckoning	O
was	O
paid	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ambler	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
this	O
mug	O
near	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gates	O
where	O
lay	O
some	O
dung	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
white	O
mug	O
or	O
a	O
china	O
mug	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
walking	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
,	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Scot	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
shov	O
'd	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
194	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Chassey	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
there	O
one	O
stock	O
bed	O
,	O
one	O
stock	O
bolster	O
,	O
one	O
feather	O
pillow	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
quilt	O
,	O
one	O
woollen	O
rug	O
,	O
two	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
one	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
peruke	O
.	O
||	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
,	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
Burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
195	O
.	O
196	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Horsey	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Colley	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Farmer	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
cambrick	O
hood	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Flocton	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
197	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Newgate-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
arm	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
down	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
secured	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
My	O
relation	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
More	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
touched	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
crowd	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
by	O
mistake	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
198	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Bisben	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
pound	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dalley	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Dalley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cheesemonger's-shop	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	B-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
behind	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gammon	O
of	O
bacon	O
hung	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
out	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hands	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
in	O
running	O
about	O
150	O
yards	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
his	O
heels	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
He	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
cry	O
'd	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
heavy	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
desiring	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
his	O
evidence	O
last	O
sessions	O
against	O
two	O
of	O
his	O
accomplices	O
,	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
154	O
,	O
155	O
,	O
115	O
.	O
116	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
released	O
out	O
of	O
confinement	O
but	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
he	O
committed	O
this	O
fact	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
199	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
pewter	O
dishes	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
scarlet	O
cloak	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
one	O
linen	O
hood	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Broadhurst	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
Feb.	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
200	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
+	O
Acq	O
.	O
201	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worstead	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
(	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
another	O
person	O
unknown	O
)	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hummerton	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
202	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hacker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assaulting	O
and	O
robbing	O
Ann	B-pers
Harrwood	I-pers
on	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
February	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
Acq	O
.	O
203	O
,	O
204	O
John	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
chimney-sweepers	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
steal	O
ing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prisoners	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
let	O
in	O
to	O
sweep	O
the	O
chimnies	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
secured	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
1.	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
205	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
bags	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
two	O
portugal	O
pieces	O
,	O
one	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
13	O
36	O
pieces	O
,	O
5	O
moidores	O
,	O
2	O
half-moidores	O
,	O
68	O
guineas	O
,	O
3	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Bill	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
||	O
Charles	B-pers
Bill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
chambers	O
in	O
Lions-Inn	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
inst	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
considerable	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
drawer	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
writing-desk	O
;	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
up	O
my	O
account	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
115	O
l.	O
part	O
in	O
Portugal	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
guineas	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
bags	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
yellow	O
canvas	O
,	O
mark	O
'd	O
R	O
H	O
,	O
1746	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
dirty	O
,	O
linen	O
bag	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
yellow	O
bag	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
betwixt	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
accidentally	O
left	O
my	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
lock	O
where	O
this	O
money	O
was	O
,	O
there	O
it	O
remained	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
betwixt	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
desk	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
saw	O
was	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
drew	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
two	O
bags	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
chamber	O
?	O
Bill	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
too	O
small	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Barber	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
,	O
therefore	O
we	O
lie	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
lodge	O
there	O
?	O
Bill	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
upon	O
missing	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Bill	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Curtice	I-pers
,	O
the	O
landress	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
at	O
once	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
her	O
servant	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
girl	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
lighted	O
a	O
fire	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
gentlemen	O
.	O
Looking	O
upon	O
.	O
my	O
desk	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
chamber	O
door	O
lying	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
:	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
was	O
,	O
about	O
what	O
time	O
she	O
took	O
this	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
lighted	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
in	O
an	O
unlucky	O
hour	O
;	O
seeing	O
the	O
key	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
tempted	O
,	O
seeing	O
a	O
yellow	O
bag	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
large	O
parcel	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
this	O
confession	O
in	O
presence	O
of	O
several	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
yellow	O
bag	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
letters	O
R.	B-pers
H	I-pers
.	I-pers
&	O
c.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
is	O
this	O
money	O
?	O
Bill	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Butterey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shacksby	O
's	O
Walk	O
,	O
Shadwell	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
11	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
knew	O
my	O
daughter	O
.	O
She	O
staid	O
till	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
shew	O
'd	O
this	O
money	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
money	O
about	O
you	O
,	O
tell	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
prevent	O
any	O
mistake	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
She	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
drop	O
'd	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
there	O
were	O
68	O
guineas	O
,	O
besides	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
Portugal	O
money	O
.	O
(	O
There	O
is	O
now	O
a	O
memorandum	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
that	O
was	O
made	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
told	O
over	O
upon	O
his	O
worship	O
's	O
table	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
think	O
in	O
all	O
there	O
is	O
110	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
linen	O
bag	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
yellow	O
bag	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
receiv	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
prize-money	O
belonging	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
her	O
husband	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
:	O
nor	O
could	O
she	O
tell	O
whether	O
she	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
a	O
banker	O
's	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
her	O
conosity	O
for	O
500	O
l.	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
talk	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
Bury	O
.	O
The	O
bag	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
memorandum	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
sealed	O
with	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
seal	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Curtice	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
chamber	O
door	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
light	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
unfortunately	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
too	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
carried	O
the	O
money	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
had	O
she	O
not	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
behind	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
locked	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
This	O
evidence	O
went	O
with	O
Butterey	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
of	O
peace	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Her	O
confession	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
signed	O
by	O
her	O
own	O
hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ambler	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
finding	O
the	O
yellow	O
bag	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
bosom	O
of	O
her	O
stays	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
receipt	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
206	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Dunslow	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
1	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
set	O
with	O
a	O
diamond	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
5	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
kid	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
5	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
Dresden	O
ruffles	O
,	O
4	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Padington	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
months	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
safe	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
My	O
kitchen	O
is	O
under	O
ground	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
servant	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
my	O
shutter	O
to	O
the	O
kitchen	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bolt	O
lay	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
windows	O
behind	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
tried	O
at	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
too	O
secure	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
undress	O
myself	O
:	O
my	O
drawers	O
were	O
all	O
standing	O
open	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
pincushion	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pin	O
,	O
fastened	O
a	O
diamond	O
ring	O
,	O
which	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
dressing	O
table	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
mourning	O
ring	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
diamond	O
and	O
lock	O
of	O
hair	O
under	O
it	O
;	O
five	O
shifts	O
,	O
five	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
fine	O
pair	O
of	O
Dresden	O
ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
two	O
strip	O
'd	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dresden	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
things	O
there	O
myself	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	B-pers
The	I-pers
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
her	O
things	O
where	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
a	O
shift	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Bond-street	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Matthews	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
night	O
before	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Hampshire	O
hog	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
near	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Botty	O
Jenkins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Cavenhau	I-pers
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
on	O
nights	O
;	O
or	O
whether	O
I	O
lay	O
over	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
lie	O
over	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
lay	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
out	O
as	O
the	O
dogs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
that	O
kitchen	O
window	O
was	O
made	O
fast	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
?	O
Prosser	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
maid	O
servant	O
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
say	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
fastened	O
it	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
about	O
the	O
shift	O
and	O
apron	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
woman	O
that	O
went	O
about	O
the	O
street	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Congreve	I-pers
.	O
After	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Cavenhau	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
Carnaby-market	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
said	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
things	O
that	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
shirts	O
belonging	O
to	O
Cavenhau	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
this	O
shift	O
and	O
apron	O
,	O
which	O
Mrs.	O
Matthews	O
said	O
belong	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
woman	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Caffery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
old	O
Bond-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
favour	O
to	O
ask	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
she	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
one	O
Laying	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
ring	O
.	O
which	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
by	O
my	O
drawer	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
two	O
guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Tompson	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
ring	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Cassery	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
diamond	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
motto	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
hoop	O
was	O
scollop	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
she	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
J.	O
Cassery	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
sent	O
could	O
neither	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
after	O
that	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
herself	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
O'Brian	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Caffery	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
ring	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Letitia	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
salt	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
Tottle	O
fields	O
bridewell	O
.	O
On	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
made	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
girl	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
not	O
returning	O
,	O
I	O
supposed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
look	O
'd	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
tongs	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Folks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
15	O
s.	O
upon	O
the	O
salt	O
,	O
Feb.	O
8.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Barty	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gold-smith	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
tea-tongs	O
broke	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
,	O
a	O
bookseller	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
myself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
208	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Biggerton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hand	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
tenant	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pettit	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
Acq	O
.	O
209	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parrey	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
keeps	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Stanhope-street	B-place
,	I-place
Clare-market	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
a	O
turn	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
observing	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
necessary-house	O
,	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
good	O
design	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
plates	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
210	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Talmage	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lynch	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
||	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
211	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
serge	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
tin	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Nutter	I-pers
,	O
February	O
15	O
.	O
||	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nutter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
hung	O
the	O
coat	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
pockets	O
up	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
went	O
accidentally	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stand	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
betwixt	O
six	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
once	O
met	O
her	O
by	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
my	O
fortune	O
told	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
woman	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
who	O
desired	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
this	O
old	O
coat	O
of	O
her	O
son	O
's	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
very	O
innocently	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
this	O
good	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
hers	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
yours	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
or	O
child	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
212	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
36	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
nine	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
three	O
pan	O
of	O
worsted	O
gloves	O
,	O
one	O
cotton	O
shut	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
slop-shop	O
at	O
Limehouse	B-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
by	O
whom	O
The	O
principal	O
evidence	O
was	O
one	O
Henry	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
,	O
who	O
could	O
convince	O
the	O
jury	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
burglary	O
and	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
his	O
evidence	O
not	O
being	O
confirmed	O
by	O
any	O
evidence	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Joshua	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
one	O
wicker	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
six	O
pewter	O
dishes	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
14	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
four	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
pottage-pot	O
and	O
cover	O
,	O
two	O
copper	O
saucepans	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
diaper	O
tablecloth	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
.	O
+	O
Henry	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
was	O
the	O
principal	O
evidence	O
in	O
this	O
also	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
testimony	O
remaining	O
unconfirmed	O
by	O
any	O
evidence	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
213	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sunderland	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sunderland	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Leicester-fields	B-place
,	O
the	O
prince	O
's	O
birthday	O
being	O
kept	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
in	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
middle-siz	O
'd	O
one	O
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
,	O
maker	O
,	O
no	O
number	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
a	O
key	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Slatre	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Sunderland	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Pray	O
let	O
the	O
advertisement	O
be	O
read	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
Whereas	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
mourning	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
's	O
gate	O
,	O
Leicester-fields	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
ribbon	O
but	O
no	O
seal	O
,	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
forgot	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
being	O
known	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
does	O
not	O
return	O
it	O
with	O
honour	O
,	O
or	O
send	O
it	O
to	O
S.	O
S.	O
at	O
the	O
plough	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
to-morrow	O
noon	O
,	O
she	O
shall	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
as	O
the	O
law	O
directs	O
;	O
if	O
pawn	O
'd	O
or	O
sold	O
,	O
please	O
to	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
above-mention	O
'd	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
your	O
money	O
again	O
with	O
thanks	O
.	O
If	O
returned	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
there	O
shall	O
be	O
no	O
questions	O
ask	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
particular	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Sunderland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
woman	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
standing	O
next	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
crowd	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
's	O
gate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
talk	O
with	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
?	O
Sunderland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
?	O
Sunderland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
advertised	O
in	O
this	O
method	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
the	O
best	O
method	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
watch	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
neither	O
read	O
nor	O
write	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brunner	I-pers
wrote	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Slatre	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bibby	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
in	O
Stanhope-street	O
.	O
This	O
watch	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
man	O
,	O
wanted	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
lend	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
take	O
2	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
paper	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
he	O
'd	O
mark	O
me	O
and	O
abused	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
the	O
other	O
came	O
first	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
whispering	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
suspicion	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
people	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
beat	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
bludgeon	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
inform	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
word	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
spite	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
now	O
gives	O
this	O
evidence	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
former	O
quarrel	O
?	O
Slatre	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
customer	O
of	O
ours	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
once	O
had	O
words	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
declare	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
malice	O
against	O
him	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
against	O
any	O
one	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Slatre	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
no	O
business	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Cammel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
ugly	O
fellows	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
stop	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
gone	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
they	O
sent	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
bludgeons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
a	O
proper	O
time	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
libel	O
was	O
burnt	O
at	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
person	O
with	O
him	O
was	O
named	O
Preston	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Preston	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
near	O
Covent-garden	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
midshipman	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
master	O
at	O
arms	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
ship	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
West-Indies	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
his	O
discredit	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
black	O
lion	O
to	O
drink	O
some	O
punch	O
:	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
apology	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bebby	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
as	O
much	O
upon	O
it	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
He	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
'd	O
show	O
him	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
get	O
so	O
much	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
then	O
you	O
'll	O
only	O
have	O
the	O
less	O
to	O
pay	O
when	O
you	O
fetch	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
lad	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
vouch	O
for	O
his	O
honesty	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
my	O
going	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
it	O
is	O
evident	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
got	O
dishonestly	O
,	O
recommend	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
pawned	O
my	O
cloaths	O
and	O
things	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
known	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
black	O
eye	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
by	O
some	O
girl	O
he	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
christian	O
name	O
.	O
He	O
quarrel	O
'd	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Harvey	O
about	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Preston	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harvey	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
character	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
watch	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
B.	O
Newman	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Harvey	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
two	O
Brewers	O
in	O
Maynard	O
street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
church	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
?	O
B.	O
Newman	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harvey	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
B.	O
Newman	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
prince	O
's	O
birth	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
a	O
scrape	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
'd	O
beat	O
him	O
for	O
bringing	O
him	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Preston	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
fought	O
with	O
their	O
fists	O
as	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
their	O
faces	O
broken	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Preston	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
purl	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
that	O
dispute	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
together	O
since	O
?	O
B.	O
Newman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Sunderland	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
watch	O
in	O
Leicester	O
fields	O
?	O
Sunderland	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
their	O
faces	O
broken	O
,	O
either	O
the	O
day	O
or	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
Prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
's	O
birth-day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
M.	O
Farrel	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Maynard	O
street	O
at	O
the	O
two	O
brewers	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Harvey	O
tell	O
him	O
about	O
his	O
bringing	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
scrape	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Preston	O
now	O
?	O
M.	O
Farrel	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
for	O
good	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
general	O
character	O
.	O
M.	O
Farrel	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
about	O
nine	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
farthest	O
by	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
commonly	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brittain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
twenty	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
school	O
at	O
the	O
college	O
at	O
Dublin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
general	O
Legonier	O
's	O
horse	O
with	O
a	O
fair	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
fact	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Brittain	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hair	O
merchant	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hatton-garden	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
house-keeper	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Slater	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
possible	O
for	O
the	O
person	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
your	O
shop	O
to	O
Maynard	O
street	O
and	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
first	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Slater	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
impossible	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
near	O
a	O
mile	O
distant	O
from	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
only	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
directly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
of	O
privately	O
stealing	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
214	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
1.	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Sir	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	I-pers
Knt	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	I-pers
company	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
and	O
company	O
,	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chapel	I-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
[	O
He	O
produces	O
the	O
draught	O
.	O
]	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
draught	O
drawn	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Revil	I-pers
for	O
1.	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
settle	O
accounts	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Revil	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
examined	O
it	O
more	O
particularly	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
extremely	O
well	O
forged	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
unwilling	O
to	O
have	O
sworn	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Revil	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Revil	O
write	O
?	O
Hankey	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
an	O
attempt	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
kind	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
forged	O
this	O
very	O
note	O
for	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
also	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
at	O
Guild-hall	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
also	O
forged	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
draughts	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
accomplice	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
himself	O
alone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
any	O
hopes	O
of	O
mercy	O
to	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
Hankey	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
reasonable	O
expectation	O
of	O
mercy	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Hankey	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
but	O
sensible	O
enough	O
.	O
The	O
note	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
29	O
Jan.	O
1750	O
.	O
Sir	O
Joseph	O
and	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
Pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Richard	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
,	O
or	O
bearer	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
upon	O
account	O
of	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Revil	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
this	O
shop	O
of	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
and	O
Company	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
took	O
this	O
draught	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
observed	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
draught	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Revil	O
to	O
draw	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
likely	O
the	O
balance	O
of	O
some	O
account	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
suppose	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forg	O
'd	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
up	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Revil	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
as	O
not	O
allow	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
forgery	O
to	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
before	O
Mr.	O
alderman	O
Whitaker	O
,	O
before	O
whom	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
produced	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
voluntary	O
confession	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
before	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
a	O
question	O
was	O
asked	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
saw	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
they	O
came	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
name	O
Thomas	B-pers
Revil	I-pers
like	O
his	O
handwriting	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
writing	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
return	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
these	O
persons	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
which	O
he	O
saw	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
Christopher	O
Green	O
,	O
at	O
whose	O
house	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
Christopher	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
crown	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
he	O
agreed	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
room	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
two	O
children	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
7	O
days	O
;	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
about	O
17	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Revil	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
away	O
without	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
this	O
note	O
for	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
desired	O
I	O
'd	O
step	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
get	O
ready	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
so	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
's	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
more	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
back	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
quarrel	O
with	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
15	O
or	O
16	O
l.	O
pound	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
took	O
20	O
l.	O
of	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
arrested	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
charges	O
came	O
to	O
7	O
l.	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
then	O
had	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
call	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
step	O
up	O
with	O
that	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
ask	O
me	O
some	O
questions	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
them	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
20	O
l.	O
note	O
,	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Hankey	O
came	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
forgery	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
gave	O
him	O
directions	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
keep	O
me	O
in	O
custody	O
till	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chapel	I-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
spoke	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
hoped	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
farther	O
trouble	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
making	O
the	O
money	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
draughts	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
confederates	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
it	O
also	O
at	O
Guild-hall	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
.	O
Who	O
are	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
's	O
partners	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chapel	I-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
partnership	O
before	O
the	O
date	O
upon	O
the	O
draught	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
since	O
the	O
year	O
47	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
as	O
second	O
clerk	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
I	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Revil	O
as	O
a	O
person	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
charge	O
,	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
his	O
discredit	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Revil	O
's	O
in	O
April	O
,	O
1748	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
till	O
Midsummer	O
last	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
his	O
fellow	O
clerk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
dishonesty	O
by	O
him	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
20	O
l.	O
each	O
,	O
drawn	O
upon	O
Sir	O
Joseph	O
and	O
Company	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
tried	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
215	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
,	O
Jan.	O
7	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mevin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
my	O
stand	O
is	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
,	O
facing	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Panyer-alley	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
Queen's-head-alley	O
into	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
one	O
turn	O
'd	O
towards	O
Newgate	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
towards	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Le	O
grand	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
here	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
some	O
old	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
golden	O
hall	O
in	O
aldersgate	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
six	O
pence	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
it	O
is	O
lead	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
collar	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
struggled	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
:	O
then	O
another	O
watchman	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
going	O
through	O
Newgate-market	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
these	O
shoemakers	O
pinchers	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
Panyer-alley	O
for	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
lead	O
;	O
we	O
weigh	O
'd	O
them	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
score	O
and	O
six	O
pounds	O
weight	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Lysles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
this	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
lead	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
five	O
score	O
and	O
six	O
pounds	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dubican	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
father	O
Mr.	O
Lancelot	O
Dubican	O
,	O
deposed	O
they	O
compared	O
the	O
lead	O
to	O
where	O
was	O
some	O
lately	O
missing	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
two	O
houses	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
citizens	O
of	O
London	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
fitted	O
exactly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
nearest	O
computation	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
them	O
houses	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
forty	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Ann	O
Wall	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
conversant	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
secret	O
places	O
under	O
boards	O
and	O
other	O
places	O
they	O
found	O
more	O
lead	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
these	O
houses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
;	O
the	O
latter	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
pickled	O
walnuts	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
50	O
pickle	O
cucumbers	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
twelve	O
ounces	O
of	O
anchovies	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Tringham	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Tringham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	B-place
old	I-place
change	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
gally	O
pot	O
of	O
anchovies	O
,	O
a	O
jar	O
of	O
pickle	O
walnuts	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
jar	O
with	O
some	O
cucumbers	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
Jan.	O
Mrs.	O
Tringham	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
seven	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
one	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
new	O
years	O
day	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
and	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
old	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
seeing	O
this	O
shop	O
,	O
Oakley	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
fine	O
mark	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
over	O
the	O
hatch	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
over	O
a	O
jar	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
other	O
jar	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
gally	O
pots	O
,	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Godard	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Oakley	O
took	O
one	O
jar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
jar	O
and	O
gally	O
pot	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
opened	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
one	O
was	O
cucumbers	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
walnuts	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
anchovies	O
;	O
Godard	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
but	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ask	O
you	O
where	O
you	O
got	O
them	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
knew	O
how	O
we	O
got	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
we	O
did	O
ourselves	O
.	O
He	O
knew	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
that	O
our	O
prey	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
could	O
lay	O
hold	O
on	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
these	O
goods	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
Between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
backwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
Godard	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
open	O
them	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
open	O
'd	O
them	O
ourselves	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
dealt	O
with	O
us	O
before	O
for	O
things	O
we	O
had	O
stolen	O
.	O
Godard	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
bought	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
but	O
old	O
iron	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Saxton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Thompson	O
and	O
Oakley	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
Godard	O
had	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
in	O
Thompson	O
and	O
Oakley	O
on	O
new	O
year	O
's	O
day	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
under	O
their	O
arms	O
two	O
jars	O
and	O
a	O
gally	O
pot	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
kitchen	O
directly	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Godard	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
Godard	O
do	O
for	O
a	O
living	O
?	O
M.	O
Saxton	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Oakley	O
,	O
and	O
Thompson	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
come	O
pretty	O
often	O
there	O
.	O
Godard	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
woman	O
's	O
face	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
216	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Judith	B-pers
Goatley	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
sack	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
cap	O
laced	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Debree	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
217	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
James	I-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
22	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
218	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Maclean	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
22	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
219	O
,	O
220	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wolf	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eighteen	O
damask	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
two	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
holland	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
holland	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Daniel	O
,	O
Feb.	O
9	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Daniel	O
Wright	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
live	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
Gore	I-place
.	O
I	O
intrusted	O
John	B-pers
Moulding	I-pers
,	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
upon	O
duty	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
London	O
;	O
February	O
the	O
eighth	O
and	O
ninth	O
he	O
brought	O
pewter	O
and	O
brass	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
brought	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
below	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
.	O
My	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
come	O
from	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Nov.	O
My	O
drawers	O
in	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
two	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
twelve	O
of	O
the	O
napkins	O
,	O
and	O
holland	O
sheets	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Moulding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
Joseph	O
Wolf	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
at	O
Downs	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
red	O
Lion	O
in	O
Gardiner-lane	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
shirt	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
coming	O
into	O
trouble	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
soldiers	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
having	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
rob	O
it	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
Wolf	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
chamber	O
door	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
hammer	O
and	O
chissel	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
three	O
drawers	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
tools	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Daniel	O
Wright	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sawyer	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
a	O
holland	O
shift	O
,	O
six	O
damask	O
napkins	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
damask	O
table-cloth	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
outside	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
Gyles	O
's	O
.	O
Wolf	O
gave	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
stays	O
to	O
pawn	O
or	O
sell	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
with	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
man	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
his	O
trouble	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
shop	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
holland	O
shift	O
there	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
woman	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
Wolf	O
gave	O
the	O
six	O
napkins	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
this	O
woman	O
?	O
Moulding	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
her	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
Brewer	O
's	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
the	O
table	O
cloth	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
brown	O
bear	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
full	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
whole	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
you	O
should	O
let	O
such	O
a	O
fool	O
as	O
Wolf	O
into	O
such	O
an	O
affair	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
lock	O
and	O
made	O
things	O
secure	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
should	O
never	O
have	O
been	O
found	O
out	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
concluded	O
to	O
go	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
without	O
Wolf	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
upon	O
duty	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
guard	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
hire	O
our	O
duty	O
of	O
the	O
corporal	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
leave	O
,	O
and	O
deserted	O
our	O
guard	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
at	O
Kensington	O
Gore	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
holland	O
sheets	O
,	O
twelve	O
damask	O
napkins	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
damask	O
table	O
cloth	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Denmark-street	O
;	O
Martin	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
stop	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
bring	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
vouch	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
upon	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Jenny	O
Monroe	O
,	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
They	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
she	O
said	O
;	O
but	O
Martin	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
crown	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
damask	O
table-cloth	O
and	O
12	O
napkins	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
share	O
of	O
what	O
Wolf	O
sold	O
?	O
Moulding	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stays	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
holland	O
shift	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
six	O
napkins	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
damask	O
table	O
cloth	O
we	O
sold	O
at	O
the	O
brown	O
bear	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
surrender	O
yourself	O
voluntarily	O
?	O
Moulding	O
.	O
I	O
discovered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
serjeant	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
and	O
voluntarily	O
delivered	O
myself	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wolf	I-pers
had	O
been	O
bragging	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
times	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
Joseph	O
Wolf	O
is	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
,	O
a	O
greater	O
rogue	O
than	O
I.	O
Eleanor	O
Gibs	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
brown	O
bear	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Moulding	O
and	O
another	O
soldier	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
for	O
8	O
and	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
of	O
gin	O
hot	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
catch	O
'd	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
all	O
her	O
houshold	O
goods	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
table	O
cloth	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Denmark-street	O
,	O
Martin	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
mother	O
had	O
sent	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
gave	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
one	O
Jenny	B-pers
Monroe	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
:	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
damask	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
damask	O
napkins	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
complained	O
his	O
wife	O
lay	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
then	O
all	O
alone	O
.	O
Wolf	O
Acq	O
.	O
Martin	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
221	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
falsely	O
causing	O
and	O
procuring	O
,	O
and	O
willingly	O
assisting	O
in	O
making	O
and	O
counterfeiting	O
a	O
seaman	O
's	O
will	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
navy-office	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
the	O
Namure	O
's	O
book	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
the	O
men	O
are	O
paid	O
their	O
wages	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
bring	O
that	O
book	O
from	O
?	O
Redman	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Navy-office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
find	O
one	O
Thomas	O
Williamson	O
's	O
name	O
in	O
that	O
book	O
?	O
Redman	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
able	O
seaman	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Namur	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
wages	O
were	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Redman	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
38	O
l.	O
he	O
entered	O
July	O
1	O
,	O
1746	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1749	O
,	O
the	O
ship	O
was	O
cast	O
away	O
in	O
Port	O
St.	O
David	O
's	O
road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
ran	O
from	O
the	O
ship	O
before	O
?	O
Redman	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
no	O
mark	O
put	O
down	O
for	O
run	O
:	O
it	O
appears	O
by	O
this	O
book	O
he	O
was	O
able	O
seaman	O
on	O
board	O
this	O
ship	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
died	O
before	O
,	O
or	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
expressed	O
in	O
this	O
book	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pinsent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
a	O
proctor	O
in	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Commons	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
our	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
'd	O
search	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
's	O
will	O
was	O
proved	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
administration	O
passed	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Namur	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
just	O
then	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
then	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
wait	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
search	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
administration	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
will	O
brought	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Gannon	I-pers
was	O
then	O
waiting	O
at	O
the	O
Paul	O
's	O
head	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
the	O
widow	O
of	O
Williamson	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
will	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'd	O
get	O
her	O
sworn	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
will	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
have	O
it	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
)	O
he	O
before	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Mary	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
probate	O
of	O
this	O
will	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
married	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
fleet	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
certificate	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
Dr.	O
Paul	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
sworn	O
;	O
he	O
administered	O
the	O
oath	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
Butler	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
probate	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
jurate	O
is	O
wrote	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
Dr.	O
Paul	O
signed	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
probate	O
was	O
fill	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
told	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
caveats	O
enter	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
caveats	O
enter	O
'd	O
.	O
They	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
enter	O
'd	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bishop	O
of	O
London	O
's	O
office	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
caveat	O
enter	O
'd	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hughs	O
,	O
a	O
proctor	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Chafilen	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
by	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
warn	O
'd	O
the	O
caveats	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
I	O
would	O
know	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Hughs	O
had	O
got	O
another	O
will	O
,	O
bearing	O
date	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
Herne	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
another	O
will	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
ready	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
accordingly	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Fleece	O
alehouse	O
;	O
I	O
tax	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
its	O
being	O
a	O
forgery	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
must	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
:	O
they	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Butler	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
confess	O
'd	O
Butler	O
and	O
Herne	O
brought	O
the	O
will	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
pounds	O
for	O
coming	O
to	O
swear	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
swore	O
,	O
that	O
Butler	O
and	O
Herne	O
brought	O
the	O
will	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
swear	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
executrix	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
his	O
Lordship	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
tavern	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
something	O
more	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Dog	O
tavern	O
;	O
there	O
Herne	O
and	O
Butler	O
both	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
whole	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
forgery	O
;	O
that	O
Herne	O
wrote	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
Butler	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Butler	O
wrote	O
the	O
name	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
subscribing	O
witnesses	O
to	O
the	O
will	O
:	O
this	O
confession	O
was	O
made	O
before	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hughs	O
,	O
the	O
proctor	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
sign	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Herne	O
bid	O
me	O
make	O
a	O
,	O
i	O
and	O
an	O
o	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
letter	O
for	O
letter	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
hurt	O
in	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
will	O
was	O
read	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
God	O
,	O
amen	O
.	O
I	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
mariner	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Namure	O
,	O
being	O
of	O
sound	O
and	O
disposing	O
mind	O
and	O
memory	O
,	O
do	O
hereby	O
make	O
this	O
my	O
last	O
will	O
and	O
testament	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
making	O
my	O
beloved	O
wife	O
Mary	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
of	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
,	O
sole	O
executrix	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Dated	O
Oct.	O
29	O
,	O
1747.	O
Tho	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
his	O
mark	O
[	O
x	O
]	O
.	O
Witnesses	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Herne	I-pers
.	O
[	O
The	O
will	O
is	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
will	O
last	O
?	O
Herne	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Commons	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
the	O
blank	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
fill	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
obtain	O
his	O
wages	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
probate	O
out	O
of	O
Doctor	O
's	O
Commons	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
me	O
another	O
will	O
to	O
fill	O
it	O
up	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
it	O
by	O
his	O
directions	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
wages	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
full	O
share	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
pounds	O
for	O
her	O
part	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
full	O
share	O
after	O
the	O
expences	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
were	O
deducted	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
wrote	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
his	O
mark	O
?	O
Herne	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
wrote	O
the	O
name	O
John	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
?	O
Herne	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
wrote	O
the	O
name	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
?	O
Herne	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
wrote	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Herne	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positively	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
done	O
?	O
Herne	O
.	O
At	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Short	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Bull-head	O
;	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
Catherine	O
Gannon	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Commons	O
to	O
obtain	O
a	O
probate	O
of	O
the	O
will	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
her	O
house	O
?	O
Herne	O
.	O
She	O
lives	O
in	O
Higin-Lane	O
;	O
she	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
there	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
widow	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
I	O
directed	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
two	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Commons	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Paul's-Head	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
sworn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
done	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
all	O
stop	O
'd	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
January	O
or	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
exact	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
together	O
after	O
we	O
made	O
the	O
will	O
almost	O
every	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
she	O
knew	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
people	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Paul's-Head	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
purl	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
name	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
will	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
at	O
the	O
Dog-Tavern	O
before	O
all	O
then	O
present	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
February	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
he	O
wrote	O
the	O
name	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
on	O
the	O
will	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
remember	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Compter	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Gannon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
do	O
this	O
as	O
another	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Commons	O
,	O
to	O
swear	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
pounds	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Herne	O
,	O
Herne	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
will	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
Butler	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
will	O
before	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
Commons	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smart	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
proctor	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
that	O
will	O
as	O
the	O
widow	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
,	O
Butler	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
shilling	O
paid	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
again	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
probare	O
was	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
sister	O
to	O
the	O
Mr.	O
Hughs	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
right	O
will	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
?	O
C.	O
Gannon	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Butler	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
ever	O
put	O
me	O
upon	O
this	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
except	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
women	O
to	O
swear	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
222	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Councel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chamberline	I-pers
.	O
Dec.	O
15	O
.	O
||	O
Acq	O
223	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
and	O
publishing	O
a	O
false	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
for	O
publishing	O
it	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
.	O
Nov	O
22	O
+	O
.	O
Hodgson	O
Bailes	O
.	O
I	O
formerly	O
kept	O
the	O
Three-Tun	O
Tavern	O
,	O
Crutched-Fryers	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
betwixt	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
fill	O
up	O
this	O
blank	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
writing	O
is	O
all	O
my	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
witnesses	O
names	O
and	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Hardey	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
by	O
when	O
you	O
did	O
it	O
?	O
Bailes	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
alone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
done	O
?	O
Bailes	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Three-Tun	O
Tavern	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
they	O
call	O
the	O
Bacchus	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
keeps	O
the	O
Three-Tun	O
Tavern	O
now	O
?	O
Bailes	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Floyd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
woman	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
called	O
herself	O
Harris	O
?	O
Bailes	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Carr	O
had	O
another	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
was	O
filled	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
blunderingly	O
fill	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
sometimes	O
employed	O
in	O
transacting	O
business	O
this	O
way	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
in	O
filling	O
up	O
powers	O
of	O
attorney	O
?	O
Bailes	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
often	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
fill	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
to	O
frequent	O
this	O
house	O
?	O
Bailes	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
not	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
agent	O
for	O
such	O
persons	O
that	O
wanted	O
such	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
?	O
Bailes	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
an	O
office	O
of	O
intelligence	O
?	O
Bailes	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
they	O
keep	O
a	O
prize-book	O
to	O
give	O
strangers	O
the	O
best	O
intelligence	O
they	O
can	O
of	O
prizes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
?	O
Bailes	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
remarkable	O
word	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Fivety	O
,	O
wrote	O
at	O
length	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
duly	O
executed	O
before	O
a	O
proper	O
magistrate	O
?	O
Bailes	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
resort	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
how	O
did	O
he	O
behave	O
?	O
Bailes	O
.	O
Very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
?	O
Bailes	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
fair	O
character	O
?	O
Bailes	O
.	O
Some	O
people	O
give	O
him	O
but	O
an	O
indifferent	O
one	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Bowles	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
John	B-pers
Hardey	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
midshipman	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Monmouth	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
third	O
lieutenant	O
on	O
board	O
that	O
ship	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Bowles	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
lost	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
board	O
a	O
French	O
privateer	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1747-8	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
command	O
of	O
capt	O
.	O
Harrison	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
fleet	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
alone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
other	O
John	B-pers
Hardey	I-pers
besides	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Monmouth	O
?	O
Bowles	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
a	O
midshipman	O
's	O
pay	O
and	O
a	O
foremast	O
man	O
's	O
pay	O
differently	O
rated	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
?	O
Bowles	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
.	O
Hen	O
.	O
Curle	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brett	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
that	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
prosecution	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
are	O
the	O
others	O
?	O
Curle	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Philip	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Hay	I-pers
;	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
agents	O
to	O
the	O
captors	O
for	O
the	O
prizes	O
taken	O
by	O
admiral	O
Hawke	O
,	O
in	O
October	O
,	O
1747	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
were	O
they	O
appointed	O
?	O
Curle	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
clerk	O
to	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
January	O
was	O
twelvemonth	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
office	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
the	O
21	O
of	O
Nov.	O
being	O
the	O
third	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
a	O
day	O
appointed	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
demanded	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
papers	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
concerning	O
the	O
Oct.	O
fleet	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
before	O
3	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
paid	O
,	O
the	O
agents	O
having	O
given	O
us	O
orders	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
the	O
bankers	O
hand	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
Tiscoe	O
,	O
Willis	O
and	O
Read	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
office	O
kept	O
?	O
Curle	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
Talbot-Court	O
.	O
Gracechurch-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
near	O
Lincoln's-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
understood	O
the	O
papers	O
were	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
in	O
your	O
book	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Hardey	I-pers
?	O
Curle	O
.	O
Yes	O
sir	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
May	O
prizes	O
;	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
year	O
he	O
there	O
was	O
rated	O
only	O
common	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
there	O
was	O
intitled	O
to	O
12	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
was	O
paid	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Monmouth	O
,	O
Dec.	O
2	O
,	O
1747	O
,	O
7	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
49	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
his	O
Executrix	O
,	O
received	O
3	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
May	O
fleet	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
paid	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
June	O
30	O
,	O
49	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
for	O
the	O
October	O
fleet	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
made	O
midshipman	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
47	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
due	O
upon	O
account	O
19	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
paid	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
office	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Curle	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
betwixt	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
o'clock	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
two	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
executed	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
made	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Hardey	I-pers
,	O
he	O
produced	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sedding	O
and	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
legal	O
and	O
good	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
being	O
executed	O
according	O
to	O
act	O
of	O
Parliament	O
;	O
we	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
past	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
Agents	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
paid	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
admit	O
him	O
to	O
sign	O
the	O
book	O
that	O
afternoon	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
came	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
Mr.	O
Sedding	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
agents	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
against	O
his	O
being	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
would	O
leave	O
a	O
draught	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Sedding	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
dispute	O
his	O
word	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
money	O
of	O
us	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
;	O
we	O
let	O
him	O
sign	O
the	O
books	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
book	O
produced	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
signing	O
for	O
both	O
the	O
payments	O
,	O
both	O
making	O
up	O
19	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Sedding	O
the	O
2d	O
day	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sedding	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
whenever	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
met	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
it	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
day	O
fix	O
'd	O
for	O
their	O
meeting	O
.	O
Tuesday	O
Jan.	O
15	O
.	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
and	O
Mr	O
Mason	O
were	O
the	O
only	O
persons	O
attending	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carr	O
came	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
receiving	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
forged	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Carr	O
produced	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
was	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
open	O
office	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
good	O
credit	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Southwark	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
a	O
certificate	O
for	O
her	O
sobriety	O
and	O
honesty	O
from	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
heads	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
from	O
his	O
manner	O
of	O
speaking	O
take	O
this	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
to	O
be	O
a	O
woman	O
he	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
?	O
Curle	O
.	O
Yes	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
dispatched	O
to	O
the	O
navy	O
office	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
whether	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
dead	O
or	O
alive	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
fleet	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
47	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
drowned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
John	B-pers
Hardey	I-pers
besides	O
one	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Monmouth	O
.	O
Curle	O
.	O
No	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
