TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
25th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winterbottom	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
,	O
1751	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WINTERBOTTOM	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DENNISON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BIRCH	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
++	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Hutchins	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ogilvie	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chappell	I-pers
,	O
Josiah	B-pers
Sheppard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
Eustace	B-pers
Kentish	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Moreden	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mount	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Grange	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Crosswell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marchant	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Linnall	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Murton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stamper	I-pers
.	O
1	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty-fourth	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a-stop	O
occasioned	O
by	O
a	O
coach	O
at	O
the	O
end	B-place
of	I-place
Birchin-lane	I-place
,	I-place
Lombard-street	I-place
;	O
standing	O
there	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
seeing	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
him	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
last	O
before	O
that	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
another	O
boy	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
near	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
mob	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
people	O
besides	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Bickerton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eighteen	O
yards	O
of	O
hair	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kanell	I-pers
widow	O
,	O
November	O
9	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kanell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
turner	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Theobald's-Row	B-place
,	O
I	O
lost	O
eighteen	O
yards	O
of	O
hair	O
cloth	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
either	O
the	O
8th	O
or	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wetherstone	O
,	O
in	O
Portugal-street	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
maker	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
maker	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
cloth	O
he	O
sold	O
me	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Bilham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
maker	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wetherstone	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
measured	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
hair	O
cloth	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
her	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Wetherstone	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
again	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
cloth	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Kanell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Wetherstone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
turner	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
cloth	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
November	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
any	O
hair	O
cloth	O
,	O
saying	O
there	O
was	O
18	O
or	O
19	O
yards	O
three	O
quarters	O
wide	O
,	O
he	O
measured	O
it	O
for	O
19	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
se'nnight	O
at	O
another	O
shop	O
offering	O
some	O
stolen	O
matting	O
.	O
Mark	O
Hall	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
matting	O
;	O
I	O
having	O
heard	O
of	O
this	O
cloth	O
being	O
stolen	O
,	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Two	O
men	O
brought	O
the	O
cloth	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
my	O
business	O
being	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
theirs	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
by	O
it	O
:	O
If	O
they	O
had	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
many	O
more	O
things	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
turning	O
way	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
failed	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
their	O
names	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Macknamar	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Israel	B-pers
Buckee	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
two	O
silver	O
watches	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
five	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
shillings	O
,	O
seven	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
shillings	O
,	O
five	O
silver	O
thimbles	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
stock-buckles	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve-buttons	O
with	O
stones	O
,	O
two	O
stay-buckles	O
with	O
Bristol	O
stones	O
;	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeves	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stock-ings	O
,	O
three	O
woollen	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
white	O
apron	O
,	O
eight	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
,	O
a	O
wooden	O
drawer	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Israel	O
Buckee	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Holywell-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
November	O
betwixt	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
five	O
my	O
wash-house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
burst	O
open	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
which	O
is	O
over	O
it	O
:	O
my	O
drawers	O
and	O
show-glass	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
shewed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tongs	O
much	O
bent	O
.	O
]	O
These	O
tongs	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
after	O
making	O
all	O
fast	O
,	O
were	O
standing	O
in	O
my	O
chimney	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
this	O
condition	O
,	O
laying	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
evidence	O
absconded	O
,	O
they	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
well	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
drawer	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
behind	O
Holywell-Mount	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
old	O
cloaths	O
laying	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
apprehended	O
might	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
Guest	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Withers	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
brother	O
Joseph	O
,	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
some	O
at	O
Salisbury	O
,	O
some	O
at	O
Newbery	O
,	O
some	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
at	O
Reading	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
cap	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
then	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Buckee	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
awaked	O
at	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
sleep	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
no	O
noise	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Holywell-lane	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Old	O
George-street	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
try	O
on	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
on	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
15	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Dog	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
his	O
brother	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
bring	O
a	O
Chissel	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
all	O
three	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
wash-house	O
through	O
some	O
boards	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
stayed	O
without	O
,	O
we	O
was	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
out	O
two	O
silver	O
watches	O
,	O
five	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
five	O
silver	O
thimbles	O
,	O
some	O
quantity	O
of	O
buttons	O
,	O
eight	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bristol	O
,	O
his	O
brother	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
we	O
sold	O
going	O
,	O
some	O
there	O
,	O
some	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
towns	O
names	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
seven	O
silver	O
spoons	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
flung	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
mark	O
'd	O
fearing	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
catched	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throwed	O
the	O
drawer	O
over	O
into	O
a	O
field	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
Holywell-Mount	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
old	O
rag	O
of	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
throwed	O
them	O
away	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
field	O
where	O
he	O
throwed	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
you	O
absent	O
?	O
Guest	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
were	O
the	O
old	O
cloaths	O
from	O
the	O
drawer	O
?	O
Buckee	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
lying	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
there	O
that	O
first	O
found	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
P.	I-pers
I	I-pers
was	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
a	O
greater	O
discovery	O
than	O
Guest	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
more	O
goods	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
than	O
Guest	O
could	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Remington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
in	O
Featherstone-street	O
.	O
He	O
begged	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
about	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
if	O
possible	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
brother	O
was	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
begged	O
of	O
'Squire	O
Withers	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
admitted	O
before	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Walden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
before	O
'Squire	O
Withers	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
robbed	O
Mr.	O
Buckee	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
saying	O
James	B-pers
Guest	I-pers
had	O
not	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
robbery	O
but	O
that	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
this	O
long	O
Charles	O
,	O
who	O
makes	O
it	O
his	O
bread	O
to	O
swear	O
people	O
's	O
lives	O
away	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
pull	O
off	O
my	O
shirt	O
and	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Buckee	O
's	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
get	O
clear	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
an	O
Indiaman	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
river	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Russel	B-pers
Parnell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
putting	O
Joseph	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Lyre	I-pers
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
a	O
Pinchbeck	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
pocket	O
piece	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
Oct.	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Lyre	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Lamport-street	B-place
,	I-place
Goodmans-fields	I-place
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
the	O
evidence	O
drinking	O
there	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
one	O
Roberson	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
having	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
cap	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Hall	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
pocket-piece	O
and	O
believe	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Going	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
George	O
Hall	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
eyes	O
and	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
resisted	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
some	O
half	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
pocket	O
piece	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Hall	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
by	O
a	O
lamp	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
George	O
Hall	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Back-lane	O
,	O
Cable-street	O
in	O
one	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
perswaded	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
we	O
John	O
Roberson	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
sitting	O
there	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
He	O
pull	O
'd	O
his	O
watch	O
out	O
to	O
wind	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
In	O
pulling	O
out	O
his	O
money	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
this	O
pocket-piece	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
'd	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
gentleman	O
will	O
do	O
for	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
with	O
his	O
cap	O
on	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
another	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
parted	O
with	O
Roberson	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
ran	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hands	O
round	O
his	O
neck	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
stirred	O
we	O
would	O
blow	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
right	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
pocket-piece	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
went	O
round	O
Stepney-fields	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
there	O
we	O
heard	O
people	O
were	O
after	O
us	O
.	O
Knowing	O
him	O
we	O
were	O
willing	O
to	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Stratford	O
.	O
There	O
we	O
heard	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
after	O
us	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
one	O
Dick	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
to	O
buy	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
single	O
case	O
,	O
we	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Minions	O
a	O
Jew	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
We	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
bed	O
together	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
his	O
company-keeper	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
discovery	O
of	O
all	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
information	O
full	O
against	O
him	O
and	O
other	O
persons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Roberson	I-pers
.	O
Some	O
time	O
about	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
this	O
Hall	O
,	O
were	O
together	O
with	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
three	O
full	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
this	O
alehouse	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
pocket-piece	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gough	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
industrious	O
,	O
and	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
-	O
Stevenson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
in	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pettey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
year	O
old	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
374	O
in	O
F.	O
Cokayne	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bulger	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
cap	O
:	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Highton	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Highton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
sixteenth	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
through	O
some	O
all	O
near	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
into	O
a	O
man	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
She	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
'd	O
let	O
her	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Street	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
running	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
he	O
but	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
followed	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
within	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
her	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Gyles	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
brought	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
chair-woman	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
half-pennyworth	O
of	O
small	O
beer	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
backward	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
me	O
several	O
bitches	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
had	O
me	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
headborough	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
6	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Bready	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hat-maker	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
called	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
with	O
some	O
hats	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
these	O
three	O
hats	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
with	O
these	O
hats	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
shuffle	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
and	O
I	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
hats	O
up	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Steven	B-pers
Pile	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
out	O
thence	O
thirty-four	O
calves	O
skins	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
two	O
linen	O
checque	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Steven	B-pers
Pile	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holbourn	B-place
,	O
am	O
a	O
currier	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
.	O
The	O
skins	O
were	O
hanging	O
in	O
my	O
shed	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
like	O
a	O
brewer	O
's	O
shed	O
,	O
the	O
pumps	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
work-shop	O
underneath	O
the	O
shed	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
checque	O
aprons	O
were	O
hanging	O
upon	O
a	O
line	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
The	O
boards	O
of	O
the	O
shed	O
were	O
broken	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
this	O
shed	O
belong	O
to	O
your	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
Pile	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
joins	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
without	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
?	O
Pile	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
opens	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
in	O
Cross-lane	O
joining	O
to	O
Holbourn	O
in	O
Star-court	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
such	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
money	O
of	O
them	O
presently	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
removed	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
goods	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
with	O
us	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
thoroughfare	O
that	O
goes	O
from	O
Holbourn	O
into	O
a	O
back-street	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
place	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
drying	O
room	O
by	O
breaking	O
a	O
board	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
by	O
breaking	O
the	O
lock	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
leather	O
,	O
36	O
skins	O
,	O
3	O
linen	O
aprons	O
that	O
hung	O
on	O
a	O
line	O
betwixt	O
two	O
houses	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
workshop	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
back	O
place	O
,	O
we	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
fearing	O
he	O
should	O
knock	O
against	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
by	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
my	O
apartment	O
;	O
we	O
sold	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
skins	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
taken	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
buys	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
stolen	O
goods	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
tenth	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
value	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
quarrelled	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
the	O
affair	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
heard	O
us	O
quarrel	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
.	O
So	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
divulged	O
the	O
whole	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
us	O
both	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
wet	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
sold	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Pros	O
.	O
What	O
goods	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
again	O
?	O
Pros	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
2	O
dozen	O
and	O
eight	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
this	O
evidence	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
a	O
Neighbour	O
was	O
not	O
robbed	O
of	O
some	O
leather	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
at	O
either	O
Davis	O
's	O
,	O
or	O
Wilks	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
reward	O
if	O
the	O
person	O
was	O
cast	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
dozen	O
and	O
eight	O
calf	O
skins	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
coloured	O
apron	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
quarrel	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
all	O
false	O
they	O
have	O
sworn	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
8	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
M'Clean	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
one	O
brass	O
copper	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
small	O
night-gowns	O
,	O
one	O
swanskin	O
blanket	O
,	O
one	O
skirt	O
of	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
one	O
wooden	O
tub	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wapping	B-place
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
between	O
the	O
11th	O
and	O
12th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
My	O
washhouse	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
dwellinghouse	O
;	O
I	O
fastened	O
the	O
shutter	O
of	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
cord	O
,	O
the	O
cord	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
washhouse	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
betwixt	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
night	O
gowns	O
of	O
my	O
child	O
's	O
,	O
three	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
and	O
table-cloth	O
in	O
a	O
tub	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
;	O
the	O
copper	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
brickwork	O
and	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
aprons	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
knowed	O
it	O
directly	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
check	O
shirt	O
of	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
channel	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
two	O
other	O
places	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Gore	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
which	O
way	O
she	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Sinclare	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
received	O
the	O
things	O
over	O
the	O
pales	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
asked	O
where	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
Constable	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
would	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
dried	O
the	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
We	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
except	O
this	O
apron	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pendery	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	O
Nelson	O
,	O
who	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
breaking	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Matzruk	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Brown	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
her	O
apron	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
throw	O
'd	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
cursed	O
apron	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Sinclare	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
sell	O
the	O
brass	O
copper	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
we	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
three-pence	O
and	O
this	O
old	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
with	O
any	O
person	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
Sinclare	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9	O
,	O
10	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Deverix	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
,	O
called	O
soosea	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Caleb	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Halfmoon	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Newgate-street	I-place
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
linendraper	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
the	O
22	O
of	O
Nov.	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
an	O
ell	O
of	O
cloth	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
trouble	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
cut	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
more	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
shift	O
.	O
Master	O
came	O
forward	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
orders	O
to	O
watch	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
thought	O
Deverix	O
had	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
cloak	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
coloured	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
that	O
hung	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
check	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
went	O
out	O
without	O
buying	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
master	O
they	O
had	O
something	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
Deverix	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Salutation	O
and	O
Cat	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
street	O
.	O
She	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
Indeed	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
immediately	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
Brown	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
a	O
person	O
about	O
the	O
Hospital-gate	O
,	O
that	O
swore	O
at	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
about	O
their	O
business	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
Brown	O
took	O
the	O
Handkerchiefs	O
out	O
of	O
More	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
]	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
soosea	O
for	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
shewed	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
twelve	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
the	O
piece	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
My	O
master	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
Evidence	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Chinia	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
they	O
were	O
seald	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
ever	O
since	O
,	O
in	O
searching	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
2	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
More	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
not	O
made	O
up	O
.	O
Deverix	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
More	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
together	O
at	O
Pencelling	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
cloath	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
peice	O
we	O
came	O
directly	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
'd	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
being	O
taken	O
.	O
More	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Deverix	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
into	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
little	O
doulass	O
to	O
make	O
my	O
child	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
cheapen	O
'd	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
Irish	O
to	O
make	O
sleves	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
bad	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
that	O
yard	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
there	O
are	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
More	O
about	O
14	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Deverix	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lanham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
More	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
other	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
but	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Becket	O
Mitchel	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
More	O
10	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
3	O
Cups	O
Inn	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
Husband	O
both	O
liv	O
'd	O
once	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Cow-Cross	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
pencilling	O
for	O
a	O
callico-printer	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Deverix	O
7	O
months	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
Penciller	O
,	O
she	O
served	O
me	O
faithfully	O
and	O
honestly	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
have	O
carried	O
away	O
pieces	O
of	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
pounds	O
value	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
service	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
being	O
taken	O
ill.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gurney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
workt	O
years	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
where	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
pencilled	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
More	O
by	O
seeing	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
come	O
and	O
go	O
with	O
others	O
to	O
and	O
from	O
work	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
speak	O
well	O
or	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
2	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
in	O
trouble	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Deverix	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
her	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
inoffensive	O
body	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
us	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
so	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
conduct	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
More	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Deverix	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
11	O
silk	O
Handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dobey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
Nov.	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Dobey	I-pers
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Haberdasher	O
of	O
Small-wares	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Holborn-Bridge	B-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
and	O
just	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
Shop	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
about	O
dusk	O
,	O
Nov.	O
29	O
.	O
My	O
boy	O
serv	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
missed	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
with	O
11	O
handkerchiefs	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Bethel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Holborn-bridge	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
masters	O
shop	O
last	O
Friday	O
night	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
India	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
none	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
London	O
made	O
;	O
I	O
show	O
'd	O
her	O
some	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
counter	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
she	O
must	O
give	O
for	O
the	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
for	O
one	O
singly	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
great	O
haste	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
suspicion	O
.	O
I	O
mist	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
other	O
counter	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
both	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
search	O
'd	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
piece	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Dobey	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
found	O
she	O
must	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
true	O
what	O
they	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gillham	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
yards	O
and	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
mix	O
'd	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Oct.	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
Hannah	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
quilter	O
at	O
times	O
near	O
4	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
without	O
a	O
servant	O
maid	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
11	O
o'clock	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
stay	O
and	O
cook	O
dinner	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
busy	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
shop	O
and	O
take	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
Indian	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
piece	O
?	O
H.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
shop	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
close	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
up	O
her	O
petticoat	O
and	O
on	O
her	O
right	O
side	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
her	O
petticoat	O
was	O
lose	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
her	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
drop	O
from	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
her	O
petticoat	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Theed	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
buying	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Camblet	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
and	O
hold	O
it	O
close	O
to	O
her	O
side	O
and	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
hat	O
and	O
cloak	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wilson	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
had	O
dispatched	O
her	O
customers	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
lump	O
near	O
her	O
knee	O
about	O
the	O
bigness	O
of	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
roll	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
search	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
piece	O
fell	O
from	O
her	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
right	O
hand	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
master	O
was	O
absent	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
Mistress	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
tax	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
was	O
for	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
backwards	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
dropt	O
it	O
down	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
petticoates	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
betwixt	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
,	O
for	O
business	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Wilson	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
and	O
dress	O
dinner	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
fish	O
,	O
and	O
dressed	O
it	O
:	O
and	O
did	O
other	O
necessaries	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
washed	O
my	O
hands	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
that	O
piece	O
up	O
,	O
thinking	O
to	O
agree	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
child	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
four	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
China	I-pers
.	O
She	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
last	O
March	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
and	O
exceeding	O
good	O
character	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
she	O
live	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
China	I-pers
.	O
She	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
five	O
weeks	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
upwards	O
of	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
thing	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
twice	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Srotetman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
heard	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
surprized	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
near	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
pains-taking	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
dishonest	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Piper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
shillings	O
,	O
7	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
November	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
.	O
These	O
two	O
parcels	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
]	O
are	O
two	O
gowns	O
taken	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
dyed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
neighbouring	O
pawnbroker	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
asked	O
his	O
servant	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
goods	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Piper	I-pers
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Slayter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
two	O
gowns	O
taken	O
to	O
pieces	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
one	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recolect	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
parcels	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
watered	O
since	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
parcels	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Slayter	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
rough	O
when	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
been	O
watered	O
since	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Gladen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Beard	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
key	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
produce	O
these	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
more	O
which	O
he	O
pawned	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
:	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Forsey	I-pers
,	O
November	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Brooks	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
yard	O
joining	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
up	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
back	O
stair	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
the	O
stair	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
for	O
some	O
linen	O
to	O
wash	O
:	O
I	O
drew	O
her	O
apron	O
aside	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
Robert	B-pers
Forsey	I-pers
's	O
shirts	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
market	O
woman	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
shirts	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
15	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Cousson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
one	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
bag	O
,	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Oct.	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Busby	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
Servant	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Cherry-tree	B-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
she	O
was	O
making	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
cloth	O
for	O
dinner	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
made	O
through	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
,	O
we	O
missed	O
her	O
in	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
drawers	O
and	O
trunk	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
and	O
money	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
horse	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
beyondEpping	O
where	O
her	O
friends	O
lived	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
believed	O
my	O
maid	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
,	O
the	O
cap	O
,	O
hat	O
,	O
sleeves	O
,	O
ruffles	O
and	O
apron	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
were	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
produced	O
the	O
bag	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
16	O
shilling	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
bag	O
,	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
Mr.	O
Conyers	O
,	O
she	O
then	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
it	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Oct.	O
1751.	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
when	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
with	O
stones	O
,	O
two	O
plain	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
holland	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buttons	O
,	O
two	O
dollars	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Isabella	O
,	O
Oct.	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Isabella	O
Bowman	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
by	B-place
the	I-place
Hermitage	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
night	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
she	O
broke	O
open	O
my	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
at	O
5	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
things	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
she	O
not	O
returning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
chest	O
locked	O
?	O
I	O
.	O
Bowman	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
a	O
bed	O
on	O
Sunday	O
pretending	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
the	O
chest	O
and	O
trunk	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
these	O
things	O
last	O
?	O
I	O
.	O
Bowman	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
taken	O
a	O
peticoat	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
rings	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
The	O
stone	O
ring	O
was	O
pin	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
robings	O
of	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
near	O
her	O
breast	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
Constable	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Tombe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Hadinote	I-pers
a	O
serjeant	O
of	O
the	O
guards	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
King-street	O
Westminster	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
bed	O
in	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
plain	O
ring	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
Lediard	O
where	O
we	O
searched	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
stone	O
ring	O
in	O
her	O
gown	O
lining	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
peticoate	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
swore	O
to	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hadinote	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Tilt-yard	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
she	O
had	O
four	O
rings	O
on	O
her	O
fingers	O
the	O
corporals	O
went	O
and	O
show	O
'd	O
her	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
aroom	O
in	O
Westminister	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Advertisement	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Lediard	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
advice	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
plain	O
rings	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
throw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
I	O
also	O
saw	O
the	O
stone	O
ring	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
owned	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
peticoat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
daughter	O
for	O
a	O
clean	O
petticoat	O
and	O
apron	O
to	O
put	O
on	O
,	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Duncomb	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
design	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
rings	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
kept	O
them	O
on	O
my	O
fingers	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
36	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Sharrard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Panel	O
Saw	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Abby	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
a	O
journeyman	O
Carpenter	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
corner	B-place
of	I-place
Plow-court	I-place
,	I-place
White-chapel	I-place
;	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
coat	O
Nov.	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
workshop	O
,	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
;	O
so	O
set	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
to	O
watch	O
while	O
they	O
dined	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
the	O
boy	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
saw	O
and	O
button	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18	O
,	O
19	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Roach	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Perdue	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
21	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
Cheese	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Blandford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
keeps	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
each	O
a	O
cheese	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
informed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
about	O
40	O
yards	O
from	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
cheeses	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
French	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pullen	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
Oct.	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pullen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
York-minister	B-place
at	I-place
Hyde-park	I-place
corner	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
from	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
July	O
to	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Oct.	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
by	O
his	O
desire	O
set	O
up	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
just	O
after	O
us	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
what	O
he	O
never	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
cupboard	O
below	O
;	O
about	O
six	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
money	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
six	O
pence	O
to	O
spend	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Horseshoe	O
and	O
Magpye	O
at	O
the	O
New-Bridge	O
Foot	O
,	O
the	O
justice	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
,	O
(	O
after	O
I	O
said	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
somebody	O
)	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
wrap	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
cloth	O
.	O
The	O
ring	O
had	O
M	O
B	O
B.	O
dated	O
1728	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
guineas	O
was	O
a	O
pale	O
one	O
with	O
a	O
crack	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
lock	O
with	O
a	O
case	O
knife	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pullen	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
that	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
clean	O
napkin	O
which	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
near	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
print	O
of	O
a	O
foot	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
inward	O
door	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
locked	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
yard	O
was	O
wall	O
'd	O
round	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
room	O
to	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
and	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Maclean	I-pers
the	O
officer	O
confirm	O
'd	O
that	O
of	O
his	O
confession	O
at	O
the	O
Horseshoe	O
and	O
Magpye	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
putting	O
John	B-pers
Ansell	I-pers
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
6	O
s	O
.	O
Nov.	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Ansell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
betwixt	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
betwixt	O
Ealing	B-place
and	O
Acton	B-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
him	O
sitting	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
button	O
'd	O
at	O
bottom	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
sir	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
surprize	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
in	O
so	O
publick	O
a	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
offer	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
confounded	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pause	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Come	O
sir	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
dally	O
.	O
I	O
still	O
made	O
no	O
offer	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
thinking	O
to	O
myself	O
whether	O
I	O
should	O
or	O
should	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
thing	O
you	O
can	O
spare	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
glove	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
a	O
thought	O
to	O
count	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
chain	O
hung	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
thank	O
ye	O
sir	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
much	O
good	O
may	O
do	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
thoughts	O
of	O
going	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
recollected	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
some	O
people	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
rode	O
back	O
,	O
knowing	O
if	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
alarm	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
towards	O
Uxbridge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
was	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
Ansell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
rode	O
and	O
alarmed	O
the	O
people	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Hat	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
galloped	O
away	O
without	O
knowing	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
riding	O
a	O
brown	O
or	O
bay	O
horse	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Hanwell-Heath	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
turn	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
towards	O
Brentford	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
short	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
nearer	O
way	O
.	O
And	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
3	O
or	O
400	O
yards	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
an	O
elbow	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Knevett	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
also	O
surrounded	O
by	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
horsemen	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
George	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Knevett	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
6	O
s.	O
3	O
d	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
arms	O
?	O
Ansell	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
presented	O
none	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
under	O
any	O
surprize	O
or	O
apprehension	O
of	O
danger	O
when	O
you	O
gave	O
him	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Ansell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
him	O
any	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
charity	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
Ansell	O
.	O
He	O
seemed	O
very	O
penitent	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
first	O
offence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Ansell	O
.	O
Nothing	O
but	O
the	O
bridle	O
and	O
a	O
whip	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Knevitt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Hat	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
alarmed	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
confirmed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Deschamps	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sober	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
fifteen	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
speak	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
at	O
liberty	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
untold	O
gold	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
Years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Mount-street	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
my	O
neighbour	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
twice	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
seen	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
esteemed	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
intimate	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Capt	O
:	O
Dunckley	O
in	O
Mount-street	O
;	O
he	O
bore	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
and	O
since	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
thing	O
he	O
ever	O
did	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bostock	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
birth	O
to	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
to	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Fitzer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
in	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
'd	O
him	O
at	O
Captain	B-pers
Dunckley	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
;	O
one	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Maskall	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	O
Morris	O
son	O
to	O
John	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
in	O
Newtoner's-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
Maskall	O
has	O
lodged	O
there	O
several	O
years	O
;	O
that	O
these	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
were	O
missing	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Nov.	O
John	B-pers
Maskall	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
burying	O
his	O
wife	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Nov.	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
asking	O
him	O
his	O
business	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
struck	O
him	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
missing	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
one	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Donnovan	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Exchange	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
Evidence	O
to	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
except	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Rachel	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Beacham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
Henrietta	B-pers
Dawes	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Oct.	O
25	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	O
Hyde	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Tittymouse-alley	B-place
.	O
I	O
am	O
mother	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
Betwixt	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Pollard	O
's	O
for	O
a	O
peck	O
of	O
coals	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
below	O
,	O
rubbing	O
her	O
hands	O
all	O
over	O
bloody	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
?	O
she	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Pollard	O
followed	O
me	O
directly	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
?	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
kill	O
'd	O
Henney	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
babe	O
lying	O
all	O
in	O
its	O
gore	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
what	O
account	O
did	O
Mrs.	O
Pollard	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Hyde	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
person	O
say	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
Henney	O
's	O
mother	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
So	O
Mrs.	O
Pollard	O
hearing	O
it	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
M.	O
Hyde	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
power	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Pollard	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
round	O
its	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
stab	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
its	O
breast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
was	O
she	O
?	O
M.	O
Hyde	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
six	O
years	O
old	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
next	O
January	O
.	O
Isabella	O
Pollard	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
her	O
mother	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
peck	O
of	O
coals	O
;	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
mother	O
?	O
it	O
is	O
murdered	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
mother	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rubbing	O
her	O
hands	O
all	O
over	O
blood	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
kil	O
l	O
'd	O
Henney	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
babe	O
lying	O
dead	O
all	O
in	O
its	O
gore	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
from	O
ear	O
to	O
ear	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
M.	O
Hyde	O
.	O
How	O
had	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
behave	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
before	O
this	O
?	O
M.	O
Hyde	O
.	O
She	O
behaved	O
in	O
my	O
sight	O
very	O
well	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
behave	O
amiss	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
sight	O
?	O
M.	O
Hyde	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
asked	O
the	O
child	O
any	O
questions	O
about	O
her	O
behaviour	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wickham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
above	O
her	O
wrist	O
all	O
bloody	O
;	O
somebody	O
said	O
they	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
murder	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Pollard	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
mother	O
as	O
beforementioned	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
in	O
our	O
back	O
wash-house	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
and	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
back	O
gate	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
almost	O
to	O
the	O
elbows	O
in	O
blood	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
M.	O
Hyde	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
senses	O
at	O
times	O
?	O
M.	O
Hyde	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knowed	O
her	O
any	O
otherwise	O
than	O
in	O
her	O
senses	O
,	O
I	O
wind	O
silk	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
clear	O
'd	O
my	O
bobbin	O
for	O
me	O
that	O
very	O
morning	O
my	O
child	O
was	O
murdered	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
imagine	O
could	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
M.	O
Hyde	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
imagine	O
what	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
any	O
one	O
here	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Featherly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
and	O
told	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
head	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
people	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
all	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
was	O
:	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
ni	O
black	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
case	O
knife	O
.	O
This	O
knife	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
all	O
over	O
blood	O
,	O
blade	O
and	O
handle	O
both	O
,	O
the	O
forepart	O
of	O
her	O
gown	O
was	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
dipped	O
in	O
a	O
tub	O
of	O
blood	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
knife	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
yard	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
many	O
people	O
saw	O
it	O
lie	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
Who	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
kill	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
she	O
upon	O
any	O
account	O
bore	O
any	O
grudge	O
or	O
ill-will	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
answered	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
against	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
asked	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
?	O
she	O
answered	O
she	O
was	O
tempted	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
tempted	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Pollard	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
senses	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Pollard	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
or	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
any	O
other	O
than	O
in	O
her	O
senses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
given	O
to	O
drink	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Pollard	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
liquor	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
24	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Peart	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
shoebuckles	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
knee-buckle	O
,	O
one	O
metal	O
medal	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Trimmer	I-pers
,	O
November	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Trimmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Haggerstone	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
>	O
throwed	O
my	O
goods	O
all	O
out	O
at	O
my	O
window	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
carried	O
safe	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
drawers	O
in	O
a	O
bureau	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
some	O
plate	O
,	O
they	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
after	O
I	O
staid	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lower	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
clear	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
of	O
my	O
effects	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
help	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
help	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
best	O
part	O
out	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
shoes	O
and	O
stockings	O
burnt	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
several	O
things	O
and	O
had	O
intelligence	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
room	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
's	O
warrant	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
daughter	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
her	O
father	O
had	O
not	O
given	O
her	O
some	O
plate	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hat-buckle	O
and	O
a	O
medal	O
;	O
she	O
show	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
medal	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
mixt	O
mettle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
hat	O
buckle	O
is	O
at	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
's	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Cross	O
in	O
Red-cross-street	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Fuller	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
remembered	O
something	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
held	O
the	O
candle	O
down	O
under	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
on	O
the	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
[	O
the	O
three	O
buckles	O
and	O
medal	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
lost	O
several	O
poundsin	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
fix	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
those	O
things	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
fire	O
?	O
Trimmer	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
exceeding	O
busy	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
self	O
,	O
being	O
almost	O
spent	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
cutting	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
danger	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
do	O
n't	O
go	O
to	O
do	O
me	O
more	O
damage	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
it	O
all	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brian	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
desist	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
hatchet	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
fire	O
at	O
Hagerstone	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Rule	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
his	O
daughter	O
a	O
knee	O
buckle	O
to	O
wear	O
in	O
her	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
she	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
girl	O
had	O
showed	O
her	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
and	O
a	O
medal	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
stones	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
his	O
daughter	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
his	O
daughter	O
if	O
she	O
wanted	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
yes	O
?	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
gold	O
or	O
silver	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
half-pence	O
would	O
do	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
linen	O
bag	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
reading	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
it	O
chink	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
left	O
still	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
both	O
carpenters	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
together	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rule	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
the	O
gentleman	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
assisting	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
his	O
daughter	O
show	O
'd	O
my	O
wife	O
several	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
all	O
of	O
a	O
tremble	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
the	O
gentleman	O
is	O
not	O
robb	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
himself	O
a	O
new	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
that	O
day	O
at	O
night	O
with	O
one	O
on	O
,	O
we	O
not	O
having	O
opportunity	O
to	O
talk	O
then	O
,	O
agreed	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
Green-Dragon	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
to	O
talk	O
more	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
Mr.	O
Rule	O
there	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
to	O
acquaint	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
mens	O
faces	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
them	O
several	O
years	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
an	O
odd	O
knee	O
buckle	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Anchor	O
in	O
Coleman-street	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
girl	O
.	O
Rule	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
sent	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
girl	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Beach-lane	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
cross	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
him	O
from	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
that	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
found	O
some	O
things	O
already	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
ordered	O
the	O
candle	O
to	O
be	O
held	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
silver	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
buckles	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
the	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
bag	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
rat	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
2	O
d	O
farthing	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
in	O
it	O
but	O
gum	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
his	O
acquaintance	O
came	O
to	O
hear	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
get	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Rule	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
fellow	O
workman	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Beach-lane	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
Fuller	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Henry	O
Fuller	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
room	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
his	O
daughter	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Rule	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
happen	O
'd	O
just	O
by	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
help	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
his	O
daughter	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
father	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
buckle	O
for	O
her	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
silver	O
buckles	O
in	O
the	O
prisoners	O
shoes	O
.	O
That	O
night	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
cost	O
22	O
s	O
and	O
6	O
d	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
candle	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
his	O
daughter	O
if	O
she	O
wanted	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
out	O
a	O
linen	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
gold	O
yet	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
the	O
fire	O
increased	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
bureau	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
when	O
I	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
by	O
them	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
these	O
shoe-buckles	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
them	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
snowglass	O
a	O
hundred	O
times	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Nov	O
Mr	O
.	O
Trimmer	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
serve	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
daughter	O
.	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
effects	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
warrant	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
medal	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
father	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
knee	O
buckles	O
;	O
we	O
kept	O
her	O
in	O
custody	O
till	O
we	O
found	O
her	O
Father	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Cross	O
in	O
Red-Cross-Street	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
feet	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
buckles	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
Mr	O
.	O
Trimmer	O
demanded	O
the	O
ax	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Newgate	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
2d	O
farthing	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
buckles	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
foot	O
from	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
joining	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
garden	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
link	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
swear	O
once	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
let	O
it	O
burn	O
and	O
welcome	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
still	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
stir	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Blackden	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Coleman-Street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
7	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
no	O
doubt	O
about	O
his	O
honesty	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
all	O
my	O
servants	O
,	O
I	O
believ	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
honest	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Maddock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
10	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
20	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
many	O
times	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
opportunities	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
me	O
injuries	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
room	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
2	O
years	O
and	O
have	O
done	O
business	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
where	O
has	O
been	O
hundreds	O
of	O
pounds	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
wrong	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
30	O
years	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
fellow	O
prentices	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
working	O
honest-man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cliff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
so	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
7	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
deemed	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Silcocks	O
Crosier	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Maddock	O
came	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
pounds	O
would	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Maddock	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
sad	O
thing	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
pounds	O
to	O
moderate	O
the	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
my	O
own	O
accord	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
sent	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
Lilley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Woldridge	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
3d	O
+	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Woldridge	I-pers
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	B-place
vessel	I-place
,	I-place
called	I-place
the	I-place
Sarah	I-place
and	I-place
Elizabeth	I-place
,	I-place
lying	I-place
at	I-place
Wapping-Stairs	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
that	O
were	O
gone	O
together	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
night	O
Nov.	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
house	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
Guinea	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
his	O
directions	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
Nov.	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
his	O
captain	O
for	O
some	O
wages	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
get	O
none	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
pawn	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
redeem	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
any	O
money	O
;	O
so	O
at	O
his	O
desire	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
more	O
;	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
with	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
chest	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass	O
mortar	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
Pestle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
copper	O
coffee	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
one	O
linen	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
.	O
Nov.	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
except	O
the	O
sheet	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
promising	O
her	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
iron	O
Racks	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
leaden	O
cistern	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
14	O
iron	O
bars	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Becker	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
28	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sophia	B-pers
Hockster	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
5	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
strainer	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
three	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
Nov.	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
South	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
by	I-place
Grosvenor-square	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
got	O
miserable	O
poor	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
Nov.	O
12.	O
and	O
desired	O
some	O
victuals	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
her	O
some	O
victuals	O
.	O
These	O
silver	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
loose	O
in	O
a	O
beaufet	O
.	O
The	O
parlour	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
kitchen	O
below	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cripps	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
Hammond	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
he	O
committed	O
her	O
for	O
further	O
examination	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
to	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
upon	O
her	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
confessed	O
stealing	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
places	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
of	O
the	O
tea	O
spoons	O
at	O
one	O
Griggs	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
every	O
thing	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
no	O
promises	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
make	O
friends	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
Ireland	O
,	O
and	O
cloath	O
me	O
from	O
head	O
to	O
foot	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
beg	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
transportation	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
transported	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
old	O
cloaths	O
,	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
away	O
in	O
a	O
handsome	O
manner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cripps	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
three	O
tea	O
spoons	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
in	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
hands	O
,	O
whom	O
she	O
called	O
Cousin	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
any	O
way	O
related	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
in	O
her	O
Grave	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
of	O
her	O
goods	O
in	O
your	O
hands	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
had	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29	O
,	O
30	O
,	O
31	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
120	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cunnick	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Cunnick	I-pers
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Abchurch-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
plumber	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
mettle	O
to	O
melt	O
that	O
was	O
very	O
offensive	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
my	O
man	O
to	O
come	O
betimes	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
he	O
came	O
just	O
after	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
let	O
in	O
about	O
four	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
alarmed	O
with	O
constables	O
and	O
watchmen	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
parcel	O
of	O
lead	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
brought	O
Foste	O
r	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
arms	O
bound	O
.	O
Hope	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
fire	O
melting	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Foster	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
bring	O
messages	O
to	O
Hope	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
lead	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
feet	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
ago	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
lead	O
to	O
Hope	O
's	O
lodging	O
at	O
Islington	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
Hope	O
,	O
he	O
beg	O
'd	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
hear	O
what	O
Foster	O
said	O
?	O
Cunnick	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
le-Grand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Howard	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
Foster	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
their	O
master	O
Hope	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
and	O
Foster	O
,	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
where	O
Hope	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
Hope	O
had	O
asked	O
them	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
betimes	O
and	O
call	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
jobb	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
pay	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
all	O
three	O
together	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
got	O
near	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
planted	O
them	O
against	O
the	O
church	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
this	O
signal	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
Foster	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
Howard	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
Hope	O
carried	O
his	O
parcel	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
,	O
deep	O
sea	O
lead	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
fifteen	O
ingots	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
all	O
cast	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
moulds	O
.	O
Howard	O
is	O
a	O
countryman	O
,	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
intraped	O
into	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clackliore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
my	O
stand	O
is	O
just	O
going	O
into	O
Newgate-street	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Foster	O
and	O
Howard	O
coming	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Le	O
Grand	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
lead	O
.	O
That	O
they	O
were	O
carrying	O
it	O
to	O
Islington	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
call	O
'd	O
Prison	O
Bars	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
another	O
watchman	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
examined	O
them	O
separately	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
said	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
has	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Foster	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
us	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Howard	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
place	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
Foster	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor's-house	O
.	O
We	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
Hope	O
opened	O
it	O
.	O
Foster	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
he	O
that	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
Hope	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
authority	O
to	O
give	O
such	O
persons	O
lead	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
said	O
we	O
must	O
speak	O
with	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
watchman	O
in	O
that	O
ward	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
Hope	O
John	B-pers
Whitaker	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
another	O
watchman	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
.	O
Hope	O
's	O
Defence	O
I	O
cast	O
all	O
the	O
lead	O
myself	O
that	O
very	O
morning	O
;	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
monday	O
morning	O
to	O
buy	O
all	O
the	O
lead	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
we	O
being	O
to	O
cast	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
some	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
awaked	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
melted	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
over	O
night	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
do	O
a	O
jobb	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
cast	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
church	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
about	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
them	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
my	O
own	O
lead	O
.	O
Foster	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
this	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
night	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
'd	O
satisfy	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
church	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
us	O
stop	O
till	O
he	O
called	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
called	O
us	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
lead	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
Howard	O
's	O
Defence	O
Hope	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
.	O
For	O
Hope	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
.	O
Hope	O
lives	O
in	O
Goswell	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
betwixt	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
light	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
I	O
sawa	O
matted	O
basket	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
candle	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
seemed	O
troublesome	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
know	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Newark	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seventeen	O
or	O
eighteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
And	O
now	O
I	O
do	O
