TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
24th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Francis	B-pers
Cokayne	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1751	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
COKAYNE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	O
Burnet	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Baron	O
Clive	O
+	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Prichard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Leech	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
~	O
Henry	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
~Henry	O
Newton	O
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
Christopher	O
Wilson	O
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
his	O
stead	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lem	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Labey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Deal	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Bagaley	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Leightonhouse	I-pers
,	O
||	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
,	O
Duncan	B-pers
Cambell	I-pers
,	O
||	O
Edward	B-pers
Bonham	I-pers
,	O
||	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Hedges	I-pers
and	O
||	O
Edward	B-pers
Bonham	I-pers
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
were	O
sworn	O
in	O
their	O
stead	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bosworth	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Mey	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bough	I-pers
.	O
256	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elisha	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Pease	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
eight-pence	O
halfpeny	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Peak	I-pers
,	O
March	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
partner	O
,	O
keeps	O
a	O
grocer	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Nicholas-lane	B-place
;	O
having	O
missed	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
mark	O
'd	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
sixty	O
half-pence	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Axford	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
scratch	O
a-cross	O
the	O
nose	O
of	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Axford	I-pers
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
there	O
was	O
missing	O
twenty	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Axford	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
and	O
joyn	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
Axford	O
chang	O
'd	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
his	O
penny	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Axford	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
change	O
,	O
one	O
halfpenny	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
mark	O
'd	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Prosser	O
to	O
put	O
out	O
all	O
the	O
halfpence	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
there	O
were	O
found	O
seventeen	O
mark	O
'd	O
ones	O
,	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
257	O
.	O
258	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pyner	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Suffolk	I-pers
and	I-pers
Barkshire	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
one	O
,	O
spring	O
table-clock	O
and	O
case	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
one	O
trunk	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
Earl	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
*	O
Ann	O
Stodard	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Suffolk	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
alone	O
,	O
in	O
Duke-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
two	O
boxes	O
;	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
two	O
boxes	O
directed	O
for	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
shilling	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
arguing	O
with	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
lose	O
his	O
morning	O
's	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
the	O
clock	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
help	O
me	O
look	O
about	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
two	O
boxes	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
porter	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
knew	O
the	O
people	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
clock	O
and	O
boxes	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
by	O
her	O
as	O
her	O
Lord	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
them	O
over-night	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
windows	O
all	O
fast	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
A.	O
Stodard	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
fast	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
afterwords	O
,	O
the	O
outward	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
had	O
a	O
hole	O
on	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
hand	O
and	O
push	O
back	O
the	O
iron	O
bolt	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
inward	O
door	O
also	O
was	O
cut	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bolt	O
push	O
'd	O
back	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Pyner	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
his	O
confession	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Mary	O
Bowen	O
,	O
did	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
in	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Suffolk	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
That	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
area	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
a	O
pannel	O
of	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
unbolted	O
the	O
sash	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
one	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
trunk	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Pyner	O
sign	O
this	O
confession	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
it	O
voluntarily	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
broke	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
clock	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
three	O
pound	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Bridges-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
clock	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
When	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
Pyner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
clock	O
too	O
well	O
to	O
his	O
sorrow	O
.	O
The	O
pawn-broker	O
's	O
man	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
prisoners	O
both	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
The	O
porter	O
told	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Pyner	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
:	O
That	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Hewet's-court	O
,	O
were	O
the	O
prisoners	O
both	O
lodged	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
these	O
goods	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
trunk	O
were	O
pack	O
'd	O
up	O
some	O
writings	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
delivered	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
trunk	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
to	O
morrow	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Duke's-court	O
by	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Meuse	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
written	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
To	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Barkshire	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
park	O
.	O
Pyner	O
gave	O
me	O
three-pence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
shilling	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
Ann	B-pers
Stodard	I-pers
had	O
depos	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
,	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Russel-court	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
these	O
two	O
prisoners	O
brought	O
this	O
clock	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
three	O
pounds	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
also	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
gentleman	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
March	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
Hampshire	O
Hog	O
in	O
Charles-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
remained	O
till	O
about	O
eleven	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Charles-street	O
:	O
About	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Thistle	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
out	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
;	O
about	O
twelve	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
walk	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
for	O
?	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
for	O
a	O
midwife	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
,	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
259	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
two	O
shifts	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
March	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
upon	O
charity	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
in	O
Feb.	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
14	O
days	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
at	O
Woolwich	O
,	O
amongst	O
some	O
sailors	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
stays	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
four	O
caps	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shifts	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
260	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
damask	O
shoes	O
,	O
one	O
china	O
dish	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
261	O
,	O
262	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jer	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Dort	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
pieces	O
of	O
wood	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Steadman	I-pers
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
263	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Brightman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
April	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
Arthur	O
Watts	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-cross	B-place
near	I-place
Charing-cross	I-place
,	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
;	O
I	O
lay	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
I	O
hung	O
my	O
watch	O
upon	O
a	O
nail	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
that	O
was	O
quarter	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
;	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
one	O
Walbank	O
,	O
in	O
Angel-court	O
Westminster	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Walbank	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
watch	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
Good-Friday	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Colman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
pawn-broker	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
mentioned	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
number	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
No	O
571	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
something	O
under	O
my	O
feet	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Walbank	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
264	O
,	O
265	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Nesbit	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Parnell	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
*	O
Edward	O
Buckland	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
missed	O
pots	O
often	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Nesbit	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
9	O
th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
selling	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
Parnell	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
went	O
backwards	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
lead	O
old	O
and	O
new	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
pint	O
and	O
quart	O
pots	O
,	O
squeez	O
'd	O
together	O
and	O
the	O
names	O
ras	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
amongst	O
them	O
the	O
two	O
pots	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
by	O
both	O
Buckland	O
and	O
Hodges	O
,	O
their	O
names	O
upon	O
each	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
there	O
Nesbit	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
sold	O
any	O
but	O
what	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
Parnell	O
.	O
Parnell	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
bought	O
any	O
but	O
what	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
Nesbit	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Nesbit	O
confess	O
stealing	O
your	O
pint	O
pot	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
?	O
Buckland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
:	O
This	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
or	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
About	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
May	O
9	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
ale-house	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
at	O
a	O
glass-house	O
;	O
I	O
empty	O
'd	O
the	O
pot	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
Nesbit	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
glasshouse	O
just	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
evidence	O
in	O
searching	O
Parnell	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Nesbit	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
sold	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
and	O
mine	O
together	O
to	O
Parnell	O
for	O
ten-pence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Parnell	O
lives	O
but	O
about	O
400	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Nesbit	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
which	O
being	O
petty	O
larceny	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
there	O
can	O
be	O
no	O
accessary	O
,	O
Parnell	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
266	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Judith	B-pers
Cevit	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
lac	O
'd	O
cap	O
,	O
one	O
napkin	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
now	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Dad	I-pers
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
a	O
servant	O
about	O
fourteen	O
days	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
account	O
was	O
about	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
It	O
came	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
own	O
'd	O
was	O
made	O
upon	O
her	O
threatening	O
her	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
267	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
gun	O
locks	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
++	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
268	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wicker	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
four	O
dozen	O
pounds	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
269	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
for	O
hoop-petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
sauce-pan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Stain	I-pers
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
270	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
measure	O
for	O
coles	O
,	O
bound	O
with	O
iron	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
half	O
bushel	O
measure	O
,	O
one	O
peck	O
measure	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
peck	O
measure	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
from	O
home	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
say	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
cellar	O
with	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
coal	O
measures	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
alley	O
towards	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
three	O
measures	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
and	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
measures	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
with	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
post	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Bear-alley	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
wanted	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
three-halfpence	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Seacoal-lane	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
271	O
,	O
272	O
,	O
273	O
,	O
274	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Commins	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Dudsdon	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
with	O
six	O
lancets	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
November	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Dudsdon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apothecary	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
returning	O
home	O
from	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Catharine	B-place
,	I-place
or	I-place
Bridges-street	I-place
,	I-place
I	I-place
know	I-place
not	I-place
which	I-place
,	I-place
not	I-place
knowing	I-place
where	I-place
they	I-place
end	I-place
;	I-place
opposite	I-place
York-street	I-place
end	I-place
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
seven	O
people	O
armed	O
with	O
pistols	O
and	O
cutlasses	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pistols	O
pointed	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
resistance	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
surrounded	O
me	O
and	O
rifled	O
my	O
pockets	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
with	O
six	O
lancets	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
whether	O
my	O
hat	O
fell	O
off	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
put	O
another	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
cut	O
me	O
through	O
that	O
and	O
my	O
wig	O
,	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
with	O
a	O
cut	O
in	O
each	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
of	O
whom	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
assistance	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
seized	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
thieves	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
rescued	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
seized	O
?	O
Dudsdon	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Morris	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
saw	O
Morris	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
surrounded	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
thought	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
who	O
gave	O
you	O
that	O
blow	O
on	O
your	O
arm	O
?	O
Dudsdon	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
that	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
chas	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
altho	O
'	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
chairmen	O
,	O
standing	O
at	O
Drury-lane	O
play-house	O
passage	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
watchmen	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
Prisoners	O
?	O
Dudsdon	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
case	O
and	O
instruments	O
again	O
?	O
Dudsdon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Freestone	I-pers
.	O
About	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
or	O
25th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Urwin	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
executed	O
,	O
(	O
see	O
No	O
100	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
)	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
,	O
met	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
together	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
we	O
met	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
thought	O
worth	O
robbing	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
nine	O
,	O
having	O
not	O
met	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
three	O
full	O
pots	O
standing	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
we	O
walk	O
'd	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
walk	O
'd	O
round	O
Bloomsbury-square	O
,	O
Grosvenor-square	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Strand	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
Bridges-street	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Morris	O
swore	O
an	O
oath	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
without	O
a	O
supper	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Vinegar-yard	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Field	I-pers
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
and	O
squeez	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
stand	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
resistance	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
Morris	O
went	O
to	O
rifling	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
too	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
present	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
hangers	O
were	O
drawn	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
most	O
or	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
hangers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
other	O
pistol	O
presented	O
besides	O
that	O
of	O
Field	O
's	O
?	O
Freestone	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Morris	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
case	O
of	O
lancets	O
,	O
the	O
case	O
was	O
shagreen	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
edge	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dudsdon	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
three	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
not	O
rob	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
Hayes	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
strike	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
;	O
Hayes	O
before	O
,	O
as	O
Morris	O
was	O
rifling	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
own	O
on	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rumble	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Dudsdon	O
had	O
got	O
Bryan	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Field	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
company	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
laid	O
a	O
stick	O
over	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
Bryan	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
home	O
to	O
Pendegrast	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
backside	O
the	O
Fox	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
(	O
See	O
No	O
254	O
in	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pennant	I-pers
's	O
mayoralty	O
)	O
Morris	O
there	O
produced	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
saw	O
it	O
advertised	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
Freestone	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
prisoners	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
did	O
Pendegrast	O
,	O
and	O
Field	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Woolse	I-pers
,	O
son	O
to	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Morris	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
.	O
Commins	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sick	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Bryan	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
in	O
this	O
country	O
.	O
Hayes	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
speak	O
.	O
For	O
Morris	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Morris	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Warner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
in	O
Whitechappel-court	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
arrested	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
,	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
on	O
Saltpeter-bank	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Morris	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Alexander	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
was	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
plaintif	O
,	O
Nov.	O
24	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
ten	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
roast	O
beef	O
hot	O
for	O
supper	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
to	O
the	O
tune	O
of	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
shillings	O
amongst	O
us	O
,	O
Morris	O
keeps	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
;	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
Saltpeter-bank	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
staid	O
till	O
one	O
;	O
Saltpeter-bank	O
is	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
stone	O
's	O
cast	O
from	O
Morris	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Scott	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
three	O
full	O
pots	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
re-take	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
had	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
after	O
two	O
o'clock	O
before	O
we	O
got	O
back	O
to	O
Morris	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
separated	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
agreed	O
to	O
meet	O
again	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
this	O
man	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Warner	O
had	O
an	O
action	O
of	O
mine	O
against	O
one	O
Sadler	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
at	O
Morris	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
there	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
supper	O
of	O
beef	O
and	O
pudding	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
to	O
supper	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
Warner	O
has	O
lost	O
my	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
no	O
care	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
sent	O
for	O
Warner	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
customer	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
eight	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
supper	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
serve	O
Mr.	O
Warner	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
person	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dispute	O
about	O
taking	O
him	O
without	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
Saltpeter-bank	O
and	O
watch	O
'd	O
for	O
this	O
Sadler	O
,	O
his	O
time	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
works	O
at	O
the	O
glass-house	O
,	O
so	O
do	O
I	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
black	O
Lion	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
quantity	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
together	O
till	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Shewler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Freestone	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Clarkenwel	O
bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
in	O
this	O
condition	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
could	O
sleep	O
in	O
his	O
bed	O
thinking	O
about	O
Morris	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
thief-takers	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
hang	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Shewler	O
.	O
I	O
drive	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
drank	O
many	O
gallons	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
Freestone	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Morris	O
as	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
respect	O
them	O
both	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
good	O
friendship	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Morris	O
fourteen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
for	O
whatever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sampson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
sixteen	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
ill	O
character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Morris	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
doors	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
handsom	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
body	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Farrel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
Commins	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lang	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
John	B-pers
Commins	I-pers
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
attended	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
nurse	O
which	O
I	O
recommended	O
to	O
attend	O
him	O
also	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Connoley	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
or	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
Christmas	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
turn	O
himself	O
in	O
his	O
bed	O
without	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
the	O
nurse	O
;	O
I	O
attended	O
him	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
sometimes	O
twice	O
a	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
under	O
my	O
hands	O
by	O
the	O
recommendation	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
cured	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Pratt	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Exeter-change-court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
Running-horse	O
:	O
I	O
laid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
salivation	O
;	O
he	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
agreement	O
,	O
paid	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
at	O
first	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
well	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Connoley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
nurse-keeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Commins	O
,	O
5	O
weeks	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
at	O
Exeter-change	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
I	O
attended	O
him	O
five	O
weeks	O
and	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
went	O
abroad	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
kept	O
his	O
bed	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lang	O
paid	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
a	O
week	O
for	O
my	O
board	O
wages	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Lang	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lang	O
.	O
She	O
confirm	O
'd	O
his	O
testimony	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
and	O
staymaker	O
:	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
one	O
shop	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
;	O
we	O
work	O
'd	O
together	O
for	O
one	O
William	O
Newton	O
,	O
in	O
Crown	O
court	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Lenard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Commins	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
better	O
,	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
is	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
honest	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
for	O
his	O
life	O
last	O
assizes	O
at	O
Kingston	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
so	O
:	O
But	O
he	O
was	O
honourably	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
an	O
evidence	O
for	O
him	O
there	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
All	O
acquitted	O
.	O
For	O
Commins	O
see	O
No	O
641	O
in	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
's	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
No	O
13	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Kingston	O
paper	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Commins	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Jack	O
the	O
Taylor	O
,	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Dec.	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Silver-street	B-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury-market	I-place
,	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
in	O
that	O
street	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
five	O
men	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
farther	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
turn	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
clap	O
'd	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
if	O
you	O
resist	O
or	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
repeating	O
it	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
affrignted	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
spirits	O
soon	O
arose	O
;	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
rifle	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
tumbled	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
little	O
fellow	O
very	O
busy	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
thieves	O
and	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
I	O
fell	O
the	O
gentleman	O
threw	O
open	O
his	O
parlour	O
window	O
,	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
alarmed	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
ran	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
is	O
James	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
else	O
,	O
he	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
jobb	O
'd	O
the	O
muzzle	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
narrowly	O
missed	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
soon	O
made	O
off	O
after	O
the	O
others	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
any	O
person	O
but	O
Hayes	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
amongst	O
other	O
people	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
thought	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Freestone	I-pers
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
deposed	O
that	O
himself	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Commins	I-pers
,	O
young	O
George	B-pers
Hussey	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
executed	O
last	O
Assizes	O
at	O
Reading	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Bryne	I-pers
and	O
Hays	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
did	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
testimony	O
not	O
being	O
strengthned	O
by	O
other	O
evidence	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
3	O
acquitted	O
.	O
275	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Snalock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stone	O
buttons	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rice	B-pers
Evers	I-pers
.	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Rice	O
Evers	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
and	O
broker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buttons	O
for	O
his	O
sleeves	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
three	O
pair	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
toss	O
them	O
from	O
hand	O
to	O
hand	O
very	O
artfully	O
:	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
one	O
link	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
afterward	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
must	O
give	O
you	O
your	O
price	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
handled	O
them	O
again	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
tell	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
likes	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
price	O
I	O
'll	O
come	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
other	O
link	O
:	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
this	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
buttons	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
the	O
justice	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
to	O
have	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
buttons	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
a	O
gaming	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
had	O
only	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
dropped	O
the	O
buttons	O
in	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
coal	O
box	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
behind	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Tomb	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
same	O
:	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
276	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
April	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hatton-garden	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
and	O
was	O
quarter	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
last	O
Monday	O
sen'night	O
my	O
wife	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
candle	O
at	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
doors	O
open	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
trunk	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
,	O
Wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bivon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
watchman	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
cellar	O
with	O
this	O
petticoat	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
us	O
different	O
stories	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
and	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Graunt	I-pers
,	O
another	O
watchman	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
Bivon	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
produced	O
the	O
petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
deposed	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
petticoat	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
277	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Parset	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
278	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Pritchard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grimstead	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
March	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grimstead	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
washerwoman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Red	B-place
Lion	I-place
Street	I-place
I	O
felt	O
something	O
behind	O
me	O
move	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
walked	O
by	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
then	O
Edmund	O
Sleath	O
followed	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
flung	O
the	O
hat	O
down	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
speak	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
strike	O
you	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
your	O
hat	O
?	O
Grimstead	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sleath	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
pursuing	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
yards	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
279	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
Charles	O
Peirce	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
this	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
pockets	O
,	O
were	O
hanging	O
upon	O
the	O
banisters	O
or	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
that	O
lives	O
a-cross	O
the	O
street	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
go	O
out	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
at	O
a	O
pawn	O
broker	O
's	O
offering	O
to	O
pawn	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
handker	O
chiefs	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
with	O
the	O
letter	O
P.	O
upon	O
it	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
round	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
my	O
keys	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
sold	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
Jobb	O
Holt	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
gin	O
shop	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rutherford	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
280	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
canvas	O
trousers	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
mentioned	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
detected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Leaden-hall	O
street	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
with	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
waistcoats	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
and	O
the	O
trousers	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
one	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
waistcoats	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hitchman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
a	O
blew	O
and	O
white	O
waistcoat	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
5	O
shillings	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hermitage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
black	O
horse	O
in	O
Well	O
Street	O
facing	O
Well	O
close	O
Square	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pickle	O
herring	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
hours	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
neither	O
shoe	O
nor	O
stocking	O
on	O
then	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
4	O
waistcoats	O
on	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
waistcoat	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
then	O
shoes	O
and	O
stockings	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
at	O
the	O
hog	O
and	O
armour	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Leaden-hall	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
accidentally	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
those	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
281	O
,	O
282	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Arthur	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Innes	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
stock	O
beds	O
,	O
one	O
feather	O
bolster	O
,	O
two	O
feather	O
pillows	O
,	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
one	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
three	O
iron	O
grates	O
,	O
all	O
valued	O
at	O
22	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shadwell	B-place
parish	I-place
,	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
warehouse	O
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
padlock	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
door	O
besides	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Bury	O
's	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
neighbour	O
and	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Murphy	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
bedding	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
lying	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
2	O
pillows	O
,	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
Murphy	O
told	O
me	O
Walter	O
Innes	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
'd	O
take	O
him	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
his	O
directions	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
selling	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Norman-court	O
,	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
grates	O
to	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Donnovan	I-pers
.	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Donnovan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
grates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
dogs	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Innes	I-pers
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
old	O
beds	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
old	O
grates	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Otway	I-pers
's	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
not	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
bedding	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
grates	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
six	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
grates	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
grates	O
,	O
they	O
weigh	O
110	O
pounds	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
penny	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Innes	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
sell	O
such	O
things	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
this	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
broke	O
up	O
house	O
keeping	O
had	O
such	O
goods	O
to	O
dispose	O
on	O
.	O
Murphy	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
and	O
asleep	O
when	O
Innes	O
brought	O
in	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
Murphy	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Innes	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
283	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
60	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ambrose	B-pers
and	I-pers
John	I-pers
Crawley	I-pers
,	O
Esqrs	O
.	O
April	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Makenzey	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Ambrose	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
are	O
partners	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
foreman	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
set	O
by	O
3	O
square	O
bars	O
of	O
iron	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
to	O
make	O
some	O
gudgens	O
on	O
for	O
the	O
West-Indies	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
under	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Lime	O
house	O
causeway	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
with	O
these	O
3	O
pieces	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Collingburg	I-pers
and	O
Richard	O
Sire	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
him	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
ba	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Makenzey	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Moffrs	O
,	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Company	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
284	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Rachel	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
and	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Wyer	I-pers
,	O
April	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
Anthony	O
Wyer	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Montague-street	B-place
,	I-place
Spittlefields	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
eleventh	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
young	O
child	O
below	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
daddy	O
,	O
daddy	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
has	O
stole	O
my	O
mammy	O
's	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
run	O
down	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
detected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Bell-lane	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
;	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
too	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Burdect	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
Wyer	O
run	O
,	O
I	O
run	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
woman	O
almost	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
the	O
gown	O
loose	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
not	O
bundled	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
she	O
said	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
ever	O
stole	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
White-chappel	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
you	O
look	O
a	O
little	O
concern	O
'd	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
uneasy	O
in	O
my	O
mind	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
half	O
a	O
day	O
's	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
hold	O
those	O
things	O
while	O
she	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
285	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Dunslow	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
with	O
one	O
ruby	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
diamonds	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
a	O
mother	O
of	O
pearl	O
patch	O
box	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	O
Marshal	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
business	O
at	O
Westminster	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
home	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
haste	O
home	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
burst	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
small	O
diamond	O
ring	O
with	O
the	O
rim	O
gold	O
,	O
a	O
mother	O
of	O
pearl	O
patch	O
box	O
rim	O
'd	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
the	O
chases	O
were	O
iron	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
twelve	O
that	O
night	O
:	O
my	O
servant	O
and	O
son	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
the	O
maid	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
the	O
kitchen	O
is	O
backwards	O
where	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Colgrave	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
watchmen	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
tell	O
the	O
prisoner	O
we	O
wanted	O
some	O
plates	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
we	O
burst	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
bed	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
girl	O
some	O
questions	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
place	O
backwards	O
in	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
discharge	O
the	O
man	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
she	O
had	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
up	O
in	O
rags	O
,	O
and	O
tuck	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
hole	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
which	O
go	O
up	O
over	O
the	O
necessary	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
||	O
||	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
206	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Sessions	O
paper	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
286	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
dwelling	O
house	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Frederick	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
one	O
rugg	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
one	O
rugg	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
knife	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
against	O
the	O
will	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Frederick	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
Frederick	O
Benson	O
was	O
a	O
Hamburger	O
and	O
understood	O
English	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
talked	O
it	O
not	O
very	O
intelligible	O
,	O
so	O
Christopher	O
Gates	O
a	O
Hanoverian	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
interpret	O
sentence	O
by	O
sentence	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
as	O
follows	O
,	O
Frederick	O
Benson	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
morning	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
three	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
attacked	O
me	O
in	B-place
the	I-place
street	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
Tower	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
attacked	O
you	O
?	O
Benson	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
fire	O
and	O
a	O
good	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
thus	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
near	O
there	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
must	O
I	O
have	O
money	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
you	O
thief	O
I	O
lent	O
you	O
ten	O
shillings	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
searched	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
snuff	O
box	O
and	O
knife	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
thief	O
pull	O
off	O
your	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
frighten	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
pull	O
off	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
on	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
buckles	O
from	O
my	O
shoe	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
stick	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
thief	O
come	O
no	O
more	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
so	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
till	O
five	O
o'clock	O
to	O
watch	O
his	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Luke	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
story	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
an	O
order	O
from	O
a	O
justice	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
justice	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
knows	O
his	O
name	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
to	O
me	O
last	O
night	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
pay	O
him	O
10	O
s.	O
I	O
said	O
for	O
what	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
dram	O
to	O
drink	O
together	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ordered	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
above	O
five	O
minutes	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
beer	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
women	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
the	O
voice	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
talking	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
proposed	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
there	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
meet	O
a	O
watchman	O
before	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
Luke	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
him	O
understand	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Mary	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
called	O
the	O
Bremen-arms	O
by	O
the	O
Tower-ditch	O
side	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
near	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
I	O
used	O
ill	O
here	O
last	O
night	O
?	O
the	O
maid	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
said	O
you	O
used	O
a	O
man	O
ill	O
,	O
you	O
clapp	O
'd	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
'd	O
shoot	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
you	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
M.	O
Hall	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
heard	O
it	O
talked	O
of	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Bremen-arms	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
another	O
alehouse	O
hard	O
by	O
the	O
black	O
boy	O
and	O
trumpet	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
our	O
pots	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
answer	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
make	O
?	O
M.	O
Hall	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
authority	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
do	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
said	O
at	O
whose	O
house	O
he	O
did	O
this	O
thing	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
St.	O
Catharine's-court	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
with	O
neither	O
coat	O
nor	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bremen-arms	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
money	O
over-night	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
three	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
five-pence	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
received	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
there	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
you	O
owe	O
me	O
ten	O
shillings	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
Then	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
go	O
fetch	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
cloaths	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
Then	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
must	O
not	O
I	O
have	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
said	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
owe	O
you	O
nothing	O
;	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
very	O
easy	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
brandy	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
drank	O
none	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
kept	O
it	O
all	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
no	O
change	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
him	O
then	O
of	O
having	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
met	O
you	O
without	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
ten	O
shillings	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
understand	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
some	O
words	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
all	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
This	O
foreigner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
past	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
smoaking	O
a	O
pipe	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
a	O
pot	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
then	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
have	O
drank	O
them	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
light	O
enough	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
We	O
sat	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
India	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Wapping	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
trifle	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
redeem	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
laying	O
the	O
case	O
so	O
plausible	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
could	O
I	O
sit	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
is	O
sitting	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
my	O
rest	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
down	O
and	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
before	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
just	O
at	O
hand	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
pay	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
a	O
dram	O
together	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Smith	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
talk	O
of	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
such	O
talk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
talk	O
of	O
three	O
half	O
crowns	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
nor	O
of	O
his	O
coming	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Windmill	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
near	O
Tower-hill	O
:	O
On	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
day	O
kept	O
as	O
a	O
patron	O
to	O
our	O
country	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
dish	O
of	O
fish	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
child	O
that	O
was	O
ill	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
up	O
too	O
;	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
a	O
man	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
thinking	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
a	O
blanket	O
in	O
my	O
lap	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
shipmate	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Friend	O
,	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Bunn	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
sell	O
beer	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
a	O
pot	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
for	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
bring	O
two	O
pots	O
,	O
so	O
Mr.	O
Bunn	O
brought	O
two	O
pots	O
in	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
about	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
from	O
India	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
customers	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
you	O
a	O
present	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bunn	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
nothing	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
Said	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
lend	O
me	O
six	O
shillings	O
I	O
'll	O
leave	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
tied	O
his	O
coat	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
off	O
and	O
flung	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
as	O
it	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
piddle	O
with	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
design	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
shut	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
that	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
bundle	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
the	O
knife	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bunn	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
freely	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
half	O
gallon	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
may	O
call	O
and	O
pay	O
me	O
when	O
you	O
will	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
for	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bunn	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
go	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
woman	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
days	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gilsoyn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
shapes	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Gilsoyn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
any	O
man	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Gilsoyn	O
.	O
There	O
may	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
spoken	O
,	O
but	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
abou	O
t	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lovet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
:	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
deals	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
has	O
always	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
?	O
M.	O
Lovet	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cromartie	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
civil	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
twelve-month	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
always	O
paid	O
me	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
instead	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
served	O
his	O
king	O
and	O
country	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
helping	O
to	O
take	O
thieves	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
287	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Henry	I-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Linch	I-pers
,	O
March	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
lives	O
on	O
Garlick-hill	B-place
:	O
When	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
:	O
A	O
little	O
child	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
telling	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
with	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
pursued	O
by	O
Edward	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
288	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Crips	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
brass	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
,	O
March	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Giles	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brass-founder	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
finish	O
'd	O
and	O
unfinish	O
'd	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Manwarring	I-pers
brought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
brass	O
,	O
some	O
old	O
some	O
new	O
cast	O
,	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
new	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Manwarring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
old	O
brass	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
fourscore	O
pound	O
weight	O
within	O
these	O
five	O
months	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
amongst	O
this	O
parcel	O
seeing	O
some	O
new	O
cast	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
watched	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
came	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
acquainted	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
289	O
,	O
290	O
,	O
291	O
,	O
292	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Placket	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stanninot	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
*	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
pounds	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Walsingham	B-pers
Beezley	I-pers
,	O
March	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
*	O
See	O
No	O
569	O
in	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
's	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
and	O
No	O
304	O
in	O
Sir	O
Samuel	O
Pennant	O
's	O
.	O
Walsingham	O
Beezley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brewer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
my	O
servant	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Hockley	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Hole	I-place
,	O
which	O
I	O
rent	O
,	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
copper	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
the	O
bricklayer	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
my	O
copper	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cave	O
's	O
a	O
copper-smith	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
set	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
copper	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
new	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
easy	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
made	O
in	O
a	O
singular	O
form	O
,	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
washing	O
tub	O
than	O
a	O
copper	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
copper-smith	O
's	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
now	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not-how	O
it	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
New-market	O
,	O
coming	O
home	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
man	O
cry	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-pers
,	I-pers
D	I-pers
-	O
n	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
you	O
break	O
my	O
neck	O
:	O
There	O
I	O
saw	O
four	O
men	O
with	O
this	O
copper	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
George-Wright	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
Luke	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
Freeman	O
and	O
Stanninot	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Country-Jack	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
Stanninot	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
knew	O
before	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
heavy	O
bargain	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
this	O
from	O
Moorfields	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
they	O
are	O
about	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
them	O
till	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
copper	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
They	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thieves	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
copper	O
was	O
secured	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cave	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
advertised	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
do	O
here	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
uncommon	O
copper	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
spout	O
almost	O
as	O
thick	O
as	O
my	O
leg	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
All	O
four	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
293	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
12	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
294	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Tindey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
three-halfpence	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Matthew	I-pers
,	O
April	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Matthew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
basket	O
in	O
Thames-street	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
Bridge	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
pitched	O
my	O
basket	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
loaves	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
touch	O
'd	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
turning	O
towards	O
the	O
old	O
Swan	O
;	O
some	O
body	O
had	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
twelve	O
inches	O
from	O
his	O
feet	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
pitch	O
'd	O
my	O
basket	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Binks	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
baker	O
with	O
his	O
basket	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
baker	O
's	O
pocket	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
at	O
first	O
imagin	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
baker	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
went	O
another	O
way	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
baker	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
295	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Paul	B-pers
Scantling	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
stealing	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
stuff	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
everlasting	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Collings	I-pers
,	O
March	O
22	O
++	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
evidence	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
his	O
appearance	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
times	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
mind	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
when	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
296	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Grigg	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
wall	O
and	O
breaking	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Jenning	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
April	O
4.	O
one	O
Gramwell	O
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
heard	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
went	O
down	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
before	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
297	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Duncombe	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
March	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Duncombe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
sign	B-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Cider	I-place
Hogshead	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Hidepark-corner	I-place
:	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
awaked	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
it	O
was	O
time	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
directly	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
you	O
be	O
uneasy	O
,	O
leave	O
somewhat	O
that	O
is	O
good	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
if	O
she	O
goes	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
She	O
staid	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
wife	O
crying	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
accusing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
.	O
Gibbs	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
everlastingly	O
burn	O
in	O
hell	O
flames	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
his	O
eyes	O
might	O
fall	O
into	O
it	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
knew	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
more	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
lying	O
asleep	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
all	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
pull	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
trod	O
on	O
my	O
toes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
never	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
something	O
to	O
my	O
profit	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
money	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
never	O
hurt	O
you	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
watch	O
'd	O
when	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
green-stall	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
an	O
upper	O
shelf	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
accordingly	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
the	O
Stall	O
from	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Duncombe	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
or	O
hardly	O
so	O
much	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Duncombe	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
my	O
husband	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
before	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
another	O
room	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
passion	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
turn	O
the	O
people	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
I	O
hurried	O
him	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
be	O
angry	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
do	O
better	O
with	O
the	O
company	O
than	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
four	O
minutes	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
stairs	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
my	O
husband	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
angry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
house	O
if	O
my	O
husband	O
would	O
trust	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
must	O
run	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
directly	O
;	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
served	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
Corbet	O
,	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
Altham	O
Corbet	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
White-bear	O
in	O
Pickadilly	O
to	O
supper	O
:	O
I	O
attend	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
hospital	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Hydepark	O
corner	O
:	O
Coming	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Duncombe	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
shut	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
stay	O
there	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
remember	O
Mrs.	O
Duncombe	O
's	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
late	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
reason	O
you	O
had	O
for	O
staying	O
?	O
Corbet	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
playing	O
at	O
cards	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
winning	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
going	O
backwards	O
?	O
Corbet	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
while	O
Mrs.	O
Duncombe	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Corbet	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
Mrs.	O
Duncombe	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
him	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
let	O
any	O
body	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
then	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
wish	O
'd	O
as	O
before	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
continued	O
in	O
this	O
story	O
of	O
denying	O
it	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Duncombe	O
came	O
down	O
without	O
his	O
stockings	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
like	O
a	O
mad-man	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Duncombe	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
home	O
for	O
you	O
are	O
very	O
safe	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Gibbs	O
has	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Gibbs	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
your	O
prosecuting	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Duncombe	O
;	O
then	O
Gibbs	O
fell	O
down	O
upon	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hang	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
witnesses	O
;	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Duncombe	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
purse	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
gold	O
or	O
silver	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
Duncombe	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
free	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
would	O
tell-where	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Corbet	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
drank	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
share	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
friends	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
prosecuted	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
afterwards	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
purse	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
light	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
another	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
better	O
than	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
Gibbs	O
went	O
backward	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Duncombe	O
heard	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
stay	O
out	O
for	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
just	O
got	O
in	O
again	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
She	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
he	O
had	O
let	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
knowledge	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
let	O
some	O
body	O
in	O
,	O
or	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
twenty-three	O
guineas	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
double	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
shall	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
clear	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
wish	O
'd	O
terrible	O
wishes	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
her	O
crying	O
her	O
husband	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
stamp	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
ruin	O
'd	O
to	O
all	O
intents	O
and	O
purposes	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Duncombe	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
Gibbs	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
Gibb	O
's	O
hearing	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Duncombe	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
purse	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
silver	O
and	O
gold	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
forgiveness	O
of	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
evidence	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
sit	O
on	O
his	O
seat	O
.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Corbet	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
,	O
Jackson	O
,	O
staid	O
to	O
light	O
me	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
,	O
he	O
drank	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
account	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
lamp-lighter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
play	O
at	O
cards	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Corbet	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Duncombe	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Sir	O
Walter	B-pers
Blacket	I-pers
's	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cooper	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
hard	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
used	O
the	O
house	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
ask	O
these	O
evidences	O
one	O
question	O
,	O
i.e	O
.	O
Whether	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
know	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
I	O
did	O
in	O
a	O
joak	O
.	O
Corbet	O
to	O
the	O
Q.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
hearsay	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
the	O
guinea	O
you	O
changed	O
there	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
at	O
Christmas	O
time	O
given	O
me	O
for	O
box	O
money	O
.	O
Duncombe	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
kept	O
the	O
house	O
these	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
only	O
by	O
rubbing	O
out	O
his	O
reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
swearing	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
so	O
much	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
general	O
bad	O
character	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
can	O
have	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
had	O
known	O
him	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Dorset	I-pers
about	O
eleven	O
;	O
Ann	B-pers
Dorset	I-pers
three	O
;	O
Martha	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
298	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Gaywood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
buckskins	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
and	I-pers
John	I-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
the	O
aforesaid	O
,	O
February	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Stanwell	B-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
leather	O
dresser	O
under	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
brother	O
who	O
are	O
partners	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
February	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
our	O
maid	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
our	O
warehouse	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
miss	O
any	O
skins	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
hat	O
which	O
we	O
thought	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
us	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
before	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
it	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
double-locked	O
the	O
warehouse	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
searched	O
about	O
and	O
missed	O
ten	O
buckskins	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
put	O
there	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
about	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
imagined	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
about	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
sent	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
we	O
taxed	O
him	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
threatned	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
also	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
easy	O
with	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
taken	O
the	O
ten	O
skins	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
5	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Wantage	O
in	O
Berkshire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
5	O
he	O
sold	O
at	O
Wheatly	O
in	O
Oxfordshire	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
named	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Radford	O
's	O
,	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
cut	O
into	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
whole	O
skin	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
the	O
workmens	O
private	O
marks	O
upon	O
all	O
the	O
skins	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
chuse	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
skin	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
299	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Judeth	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
14	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
300	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Solomon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
April	O
10	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
going	O
through	O
Red-lion-street	B-place
,	I-place
Goodman's-fields	I-place
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
snatched	O
my	O
hat-off	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
strike	O
you	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Strickland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
into	O
Quiet-row	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
it	O
being	O
no	O
thorough-fare	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hat	O
found	O
lying	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
his	O
feet	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
mud	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
301	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
bed	O
tick	O
,	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
three	O
stuff	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
one	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Clifford	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
March	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
302	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
not	O
surrendering	O
himself	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
order	O
in	O
council	O
,	O
August	O
7	O
,	O
1747.	O
as	O
information	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
being	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
with	O
others	O
in	O
landing	O
and	O
running	O
goods	O
,	O
liable	O
to	O
pay	O
duty	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Chatwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
sollicitor	O
of	O
the	O
customs	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
this	O
information	O
,	O
July	O
13	O
,	O
1747	O
.	O
against	O
divers	O
smugglers	O
for	O
riding	O
with	O
fire	O
arms	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
A	O
paper	O
is	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
sees	O
in	O
it	O
John	O
Baker	O
of	O
Hadley	B-place
;	O
this	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Burdus	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
upon	O
oath	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
justice	O
sign	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
oath	O
administred	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ramsdon	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
's	O
office	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Celley	I-pers
.	O
M.	O
Sharp	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
council	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
information	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
before	O
the	O
king	O
in	O
council	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
principal	O
secretaries	O
of	O
state	O
,	O
held	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
August	O
7	O
,	O
1747.	O
where	O
I	O
attended	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
directions	O
to	O
issue	O
an	O
order	O
from	O
his	O
majesty	O
and	O
privy-council	O
,	O
to	O
require	O
all	O
the	O
persons	O
to	O
surrender	O
in	O
forty	O
days	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
act	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
printer	O
of	O
the	O
London	O
