TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
24th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Francis	B-pers
Cokayne	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1751	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	B-pers
COKAYNE	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
,	O
Baron	O
Legge	O
+	O
,	O
Richard	O
Adams	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Seth	B-pers
Avis	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Brecknock	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Neave	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
,	O
Wiltshire	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Holloway	B-pers
Brecknock	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewington	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hawker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Filewood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Melvil	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
M'Gowan	I-pers
.	O
351	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
May	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gang's-man	O
,	O
at	O
Ralph	B-place
's	I-place
key	I-place
:	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
hogshead	O
of	O
sugar	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
seven	O
separate	O
times	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
ware-house	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
156	O
.	O
We	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
Robert	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
to	O
watch	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
which	O
we	O
suspected	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
buildings	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
tying	O
up	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
sugar	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Barbados	O
sugar	O
,	O
above	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
he	O
to	O
that	O
hogshead	O
you	O
say	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Shaw	O
.	O
He	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
hogshead	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
expose	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
hogshead	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
ware-house	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
it	O
belongs	O
to	O
:	O
I	O
weigh	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
had	O
lost	O
one	O
hundred	O
,	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
and	O
odd	O
pounds	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
ware-house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
with	O
the	O
sugar	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
352	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
two	O
women	O
's	O
caps	O
,	O
a	O
water	O
pail	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
,	O
April	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hitchcock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
perriwig-maker	O
,	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
business	O
one	O
day	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
without	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
work-house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
with	O
more	O
,	O
lie	O
folded	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
tray	O
with	O
a	O
cloth	O
over	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
work-house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
workhouse	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
Ragfair	O
,	O
one	O
for	O
fourpence	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
sixpence	O
;	O
also	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
cap	O
and	O
pail	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
whom	O
,	O
or	O
for	O
what	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
one	O
cap	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
I	O
can	O
sware	O
to	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
mistress	O
of	O
the	O
workhouse	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Hitchcock	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
help	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
be	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
I	O
recommended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
staid	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
,	O
but	O
lay	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
nights	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
from	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
Mrs.	O
Hitchcock	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
and	O
lighted	O
a	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
things	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
knowing	O
she	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
master	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
glass-house	O
at	O
Ragfair	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
salmon	O
.	O
This	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
were	O
on	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
forgiveness	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
353	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
frocks	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
four	O
towels	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
duffel	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	O
Cotes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Limehouse	B-place
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
master	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
.	O
Between	O
the	O
20th	O
and	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
there	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
advertised	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Caple-street	O
,	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
them	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
his	O
mess-mate	O
to	O
whom	O
they	O
belonged	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Cotes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
another	O
man	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
,	O
and	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
354	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
36	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6	O
*	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Luke	I-place
's	I-place
parish	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
:	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
the	O
lead	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Justice	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Rivers	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
cloth-worker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
trade	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
business	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
missed	O
some	O
lead	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
watched	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
this	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
on	O
Saturday	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
to	O
a	O
plumber	O
opposite	O
the	O
Crown	O
alehouse	O
at	O
little	O
Moregate	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
unmelted	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
lead	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
he	O
took	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
weighing	O
six	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner-take	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
Jones	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
business	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
great	O
necessity	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
want	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
355	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
to	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
holland	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
December	O
the	O
1st	O
*	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Priggs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
daughter	O
to	O
Isaiah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Spittlefields	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
as	O
a	O
chair-woman	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
many	O
things	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
turn	O
'd	O
away	O
a	O
maid	O
on	O
that	O
occasion	O
:	O
After	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
still	O
lost	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
mis	O
'd	O
this	O
shirt	O
in	O
the	O
washing	O
,	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
much	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
much	O
pains	O
to	O
perswade	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lost	O
things	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
another	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
and	O
enquir	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
this	O
shirt	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
shirt	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
or	O
my	O
wife	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
name	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
she	O
used	O
frequently	O
to	O
bring	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
shirt	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
356	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Judith	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Farril	I-pers
,	O
May	O
15	O
*	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brewer	O
's	O
servant	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
drinking	O
there	O
till	O
night	O
,	O
being	O
upon	O
my	O
own	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
by	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
home	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
liquor	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
my	O
bed	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
we	O
sat	O
sometime	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
after	O
that	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
more	O
liquor	O
below	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
pull	O
'd	O
your	O
cloaths	O
off	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
my	O
cloaths	O
on	O
again	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
sixpence	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
breeches	O
quite	O
under	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
awaked	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
breeches	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
them	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
door	O
stood	O
a-jarr	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
table	O
stood	O
before	O
it	O
which	O
was	O
shov	O
'd	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
this	O
door	O
open	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
way	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
girls	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
girl	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
these	O
two	O
were	O
left	O
behind	O
.	O
The	O
six	O
girls	O
were	O
all	O
search	O
'd	O
but	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
denied	O
knowing	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
or	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
wrote	O
a	O
mittimus	O
to	O
send	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
knew	O
were	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
tell	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
release	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
there	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
feather	O
bed	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
whether	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
come	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
without	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
laid	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
another	O
girl	O
that	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
hid	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
search	O
that	O
place	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
bolster	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Justice	O
sent	O
another	O
person	O
to	O
bid	O
the	O
constable	O
search	O
the	O
bolster	O
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
order	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
bolster	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
shake	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
described	O
it	O
,	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
bed	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Justice	O
put	O
the	O
confession	O
in	O
writing	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Justice	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
writing	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
write	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'night	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
my	O
gown	O
about	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
penny	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
inn	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
some	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
bed	O
for	O
us	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
I	O
lodged	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
drank	O
some	O
rum	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
paid	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
bed	O
but	O
left	O
him	O
directly	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
sixpence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
green	O
string	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
topknot	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bolster	O
of	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
Justice	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
357	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
jacket	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
canvass	O
trowsers	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
canvass	O
bag	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
;	O
five	O
shirts	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
one	O
wig	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
pillowbears	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Farley	I-pers
,	O
April	O
28	O
++	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
and	O
David	B-pers
Farley	I-pers
were	O
two	O
sailors	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
ship	B-place
call	I-place
'd	I-place
the	I-place
Friends	I-place
Glory	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
New-Castle	I-place
collier	I-place
,	I-place
lying	I-place
near	I-place
Execution-dock	I-place
;	O
they	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
chests	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
board	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
formerly	O
sailed	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
same	O
ship	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
them	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
where	O
they	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
358	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass	O
pail	O
with	O
a	O
copper	O
bail	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Swish	I-pers
;	O
one	O
copper	O
sauce-pan	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
,	O
May	O
18	O
++	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Swish	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Palentine	B-place
houses	I-place
in	I-place
Newington	I-place
road	I-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
pail	O
last	O
Saturday	O
night	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
reading	O
the	O
papers	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
advertised	O
,	O
stop	O
'd	O
,	O
supposing	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
other	O
evidence	O
lodges	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
copper	O
sauce-pan	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
again	O
yesterday	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-mayor	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoemaker	O
row	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
goods	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sale	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
call	O
'd	O
Broad-court	O
in	O
our	O
parish	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
with	O
the	O
pail	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
some	O
dock	O
leaves	O
,	O
his	O
sister	O
had	O
two	O
sauce-pans	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
several	O
stories	O
about	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
,	O
he	O
order	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
advertise	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
pail	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sauce-pans	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
is	O
foreman	O
to	O
a	O
nightman	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
together	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
;	O
a	O
soldier	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
a	O
jobb	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
cockey	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
glad	O
of	O
a	O
jobb	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
carry	O
this	O
bundle	O
(	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Hounsditch	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
talk	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
turning	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
turn	O
up	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Shoemaker-row	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
set	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
stall	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
a	O
pretty	O
while	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
cockey	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
hinder	O
me	O
in	O
another	O
jobb	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
spend	O
the	O
whole	O
day	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
as	O
near	O
together	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
your	O
worship	O
.	O
The	O
mob	O
gather	O
'd	O
round	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
went	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
359	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
cotten	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Torrent	I-pers
,	O
April	O
9	O
++	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Torrent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
time	O
only	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	B-place
in	I-place
Gravel-lane	I-place
Hounsditch	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
home	O
from	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
recomended	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
lodge	O
;	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
my	O
servant	O
that	O
draws	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
business	O
turning	O
a	O
throwster	O
's	O
mill	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
left	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
plate	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
searched	O
my	O
drawers	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
eating	O
his	O
supper	O
,	O
I	O
accused	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
with	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
fact	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
merciful	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
proper	O
officer	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
buttons	O
,	O
and	O
bowl	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
a	O
gold-smith	O
in	O
George-yard	O
,	O
Bishop	O
's	O
gate-street	O
,	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
day	O
following	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
and	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
in	O
officer	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
who	O
deliver	O
'd	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
buckles	O
,	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
and	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Although	O
he	O
had	O
bad	O
them	O
so	O
long	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
advertise	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
at	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
's	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
direction	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
l.	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wardley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
throw	O
myself	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
great	O
God	O
of	O
Heaven	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
360	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Colston	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
and	O
crape	O
hat-band	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
May	O
1	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Colston	I-pers
.	O
The	O
night	O
before	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Fleet-market	B-place
going	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
alone	O
,	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
behind	O
and	O
my	O
heels	O
were	O
trip	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
fall	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
before	O
past	O
by	O
me	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
struck	O
with	O
?	O
Colston	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
:	O
As	O
the	O
person	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
teach	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
and	O
enquired	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
apprehensive	O
of	O
these	O
people	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
watchmen	O
were	O
out	O
calling	O
the	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
some	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
none	O
forcibly	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
hat	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
night-house	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
persons	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Colslon	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
discern	O
him	O
?	O
Colslon	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
light	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
lamps	O
afforded	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
enough	O
to	O
discern	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
face	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
hat	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
redeemed	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Field	O
lane	O
at	O
a	O
brokers	O
.	O
The	O
hat	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
sad	O
piece	O
of	O
work	O
about	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
other	O
people	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
immediately	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
came	O
and	O
send	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
does	O
this	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
graturity	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
glad	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
sixpence	O
or	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
since	O
been	O
retaken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Colston	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
Epsora	O
races	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ind	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
4th	O
or	O
5th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
other	O
person	O
did	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
hat-band	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
others	O
slung	O
him	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
Fleet-market	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
gentleman	O
down	O
,	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
said	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
361	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Stretton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smallwood	I-pers
,	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smallwood	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
coming	O
through	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
challeng	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
him	O
sumbling	O
behind	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
surtout	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
a	O
belt	O
to	O
it	O
that	O
button	O
'd	O
before	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Whitechapel	O
to	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Gate	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
a	O
fellow	O
gave	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
me	O
passing	O
through	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
362	O
.	O
363	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
fir	O
rafters	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Constable	I-pers
,	O
April	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
364	O
,	O
365	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
David	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
sconce	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
one	O
chimney	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
May	I-pers
,	O
March	O
1	O
,	O
1750	O
.	O
+	O
See	O
No	O
666	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
in	O
John	O
Blachford	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
Feb.	O
was	O
twelvemonth	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
weeks	O
;	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
diamond	O
ring	O
,	O
sheets	O
,	O
glasses	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
glasses	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
S.	O
May	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Lebeck	O
's	O
head	O
in	O
Catharine's-street	O
,	O
going	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
deposited	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
lumber	O
room	O
in	O
Denmark	B-place
court	I-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
three	O
rooms	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Love	O
's	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
in	O
Catharine-street	O
again	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
these	O
glasses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Love	O
's	O
?	O
S.	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Kelso	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
day	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
her	O
character	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
the	O
glasses	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
them	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
glasses	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
?	O
S.	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
?	O
S.	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
one	O
time	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
trial	O
against	O
Kelso	O
for	O
these	O
very	O
glasses	O
?	O
S.	O
May	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
here	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
S.	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
my	O
oath	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
If	O
Mr.	O
May	O
had	O
been	O
here	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
you	O
took	O
your	O
oath	O
?	O
S.	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
frequently	O
with	O
this	O
woman	O
after	O
you	O
miss	O
'd	O
these	O
glasses	O
?	O
S.	O
May	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
keep	O
your	O
goods	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Love	O
's	O
?	O
S.	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
there	O
seven	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
lock	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
you	O
kept	O
them	O
?	O
S.	O
May	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
tell	O
us	O
the	O
reason	O
you	O
left	O
that	O
house	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
Lebeck	O
's	O
head	O
?	O
S.	O
May	O
.	O
Because	O
we	O
had	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
live	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
business	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Come	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
your	O
safety	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
bawdy	O
houses	O
were	O
attempted	O
to	O
be	O
pull	O
'd	O
down	O
?	O
S.	O
May	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
again	O
since	O
?	O
S.	O
May	O
.	O
Because	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
our	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
sell	O
any	O
thing	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
there	O
an	O
action	O
brought	O
against	O
Kelso	O
at	O
the	O
court	O
of	O
Common	O
pleas	O
by	O
your	O
husband	O
for	O
these	O
very	O
glasses	O
?	O
S.	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Kelso	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Prince's-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
April	O
was	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
two	O
glasses	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
suffer	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
valued	O
by	O
a	O
proper	O
person	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
those	O
sort	O
of	O
goods	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
glasses	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
custody	O
now	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
fixed	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
lodging	O
room	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Great	O
Pultney	O
street	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
she	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
kept	O
the	O
Lebeck	O
's	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
Mr.	O
Ellis	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
blanket	O
warehouse	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
value	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
wearer	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
worth	O
5	O
l.	O
I	O
gave	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
4	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
she	O
had	O
another	O
husband	O
living	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
so	O
now	O
Evans	O
and	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
together	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
seven	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
denied	O
it	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
glasses	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
?	O
Kelso	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Evans	O
present	O
when	O
you	O
bought	O
them	O
?	O
Kelso	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
appraised	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
for	O
stealing	O
ing	O
these	O
glasses	O
(	O
in	O
this	O
court	O
)	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
my	O
indictment	O
granted	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
my	O
prosecutors	O
:	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
receipt	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
glasses	O
;	O
they	O
made	O
my	O
man	O
a	O
prisoner	O
to	O
destroy	O
his	O
evidence	O
that	O
wrote	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
going	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Kelso	O
,	O
and	O
valuing	O
the	O
glasses	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Kenister	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
there	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
last	O
January	O
was	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
those	O
glasses	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
clean	O
'd	O
them	O
every	O
week	O
,	O
sometimes	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
Heywood	O
's	O
bagnio	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Ann	O
Jones	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
time	O
the	O
bawdy-houses	O
were	O
pulled	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
Mr.	O
May	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Love	O
's	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
5.	O
in	O
Denmark-court	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Love	O
was	O
so	O
careful	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
trusted	O
nobody	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
May	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
1749	O
,	O
and	O
January	O
the	O
30th	O
following	O
I	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
'	O
She	O
hired	O
Ann	B-pers
Sinclair	I-pers
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
an	O
inventory	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
missed	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
five	O
shillings	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
prosecuted	O
Mr.	O
Kelso	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
May	O
was	O
asked	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
how	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
since	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
suspected	O
me	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Sinclair	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
hired	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
May	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
eleven	O
weeks	O
and	O
some	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Ann	O
Jones	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
May	O
wanted	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
as	O
her	O
cook	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
bar	O
maid	O
.	O
Her	O
husband	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
bawdy	O
house	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
you	O
must	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
never	O
kept	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
'll	O
excuse	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
choose	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
;	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
going	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
discharge	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
an	O
extreme	O
good	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
recommend	O
her	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
May	O
's	O
company	O
early	O
and	O
late	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
sometimes	O
been	O
brought	O
home	O
by	O
the	O
porter	O
so	O
drunk	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
stand	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
nurse	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
John	O
Park	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
buying	O
some	O
pictures	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dunning	O
,	O
a	O
broker	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
upon	O
two	O
glasses	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
they	O
had	O
gilt	O
frames	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
for	O
a	O
chimney	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
looked	O
upon	O
them	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
or	O
like	O
them	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
March	O
was	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Dunning	O
?	O
Park	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Park	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
broker	O
this	O
28	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
remember	O
March	O
more	O
than	O
any	O
other	O
month	O
?	O
Park	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
profits	O
and	O
loss	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
past	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
applied	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
to	O
recollect	O
this	O
affair	O
?	O
Park	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
no	O
farther	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
the	O
subpoena	O
to	O
attend	O
?	O
Park	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
can	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
first	O
applied	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
recollect	O
yourself	O
.	O
Park	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
P.	O
S.	O
Mrs.	O
May	O
did	O
appear	O
in	O
court	O
after	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Kelso	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
would	O
swear	O
that	O
the	O
glasses	O
were	O
their	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
sworn	O
.	O
366	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
May	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
White-lion	B-place
,	I-place
Brookstreet	I-place
,	I-place
Grosvenor-square	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
copper	O
tea	O
kettle	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
enquire	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
[	O
Produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
fact	O
when	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
]	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Paradice	O
Row	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
kettle	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
this	O
kettle	O
for	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
pledged	O
it	O
for	O
four	O
shillings	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
wife	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
friend	O
's	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
that	O
woman	O
lives	O
now	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford-market	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
367	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ralph	B-pers
Suthernwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
putting	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
robbing	O
Paul	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
Gandon	I-pers
,	I-pers
of	I-pers
a	I-pers
hat	I-pers
,	I-pers
value	I-pers
4	I-pers
s.	I-pers
and	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
of	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
Paul	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
Gandon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	O
Earl	O
Street	O
,	O
seven	O
Dials	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Old	O
Bethlam	O
to	O
sup	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
coming	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
young	O
child	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
.	O
My	O
two	O
apprentices	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
Paul	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
youngest	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
flambeaux	O
lighting	O
us	O
,	O
going	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
after	O
10	O
o'clock	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
bellows	O
maker	O
,	O
within	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
doors	O
of	O
Broad	B-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
stopped	O
my	O
apprentice	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
flambeaux	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
wife	O
the	O
child	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
shook	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
swore	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
knock	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
my	O
wife	O
go	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
gone	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
yards	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
distiller	O
's	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
might	O
leave	O
my	O
wig	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
dirty	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
was	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
murder	O
!	O
thieves	O
!	O
the	O
rogue	O
in	O
a	O
white	O
coat	O
has	O
knocked	O
my	O
husband	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
down	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
met	O
and	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
assist	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Monmouth-street	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gandon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
going	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
youngest	O
apprentice	O
was	O
lighting	O
us	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
brandy	O
shop	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
strike	O
the	O
blow	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
down	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
snatched	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
my	O
child	O
's	O
neck	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
bulk	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
my	O
eyes	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
wrap	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
down	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
near	O
a	O
window	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
a	O
watchman	O
up	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
hard	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
assist	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
husband	O
away	O
fearing	O
mischief	O
.	O
Ogle	O
.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
apprentice	O
was	O
before	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
flambeaux	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
near	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Drury	O
lane	O
in	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
blew	O
the	O
light	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
's	O
hand	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
mater	O
took	O
the	O
flambeaux	O
and	O
shook	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
that	O
for	O
?	O
then	O
my	O
master	O
went	O
on	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
his	O
eyes	O
and	O
limbs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
on	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
hat	O
that	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
head	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
shoved	O
her	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
bulk	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
white	O
coat	O
has	O
rob	O
'd	O
my	O
husband	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
when	O
he	O
blow	O
'd	O
the	O
light	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
distiller	O
's	O
shop	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
plainly	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
ever	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
this	O
night	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
they	O
answer	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
negative	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
fourteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
lighting	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
something	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
what	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
run	O
the	O
flambeaux	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
as	O
I	O
hold	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
underhanded	O
with	O
the	O
light	O
downwards	O
;	O
he	O
immediately	O
blew	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
shook	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
about	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
struck	O
my	O
master	O
over	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
hat	O
fell	O
from	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
white	O
coat	O
has	O
knock	O
'd	O
my	O
husband	O
down	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
my	O
mistress	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
coming	O
along	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
their	O
heels	O
slip	O
'd	O
and	O
they	O
broke	O
two	O
panes	O
of	O
glass	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
James	O
M'Pearson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
smith	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
cry	O
of	O
murder	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
hearing	O
the	O
words	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
a	O
shop	O
where	O
they	O
sell	O
old	O
glass	O
bottles	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
white	O
one	O
,	O
his	O
foot	O
slip	O
'd	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
villain	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
M'Pearson	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
going	O
past	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
M'Pearson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
They	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
my	O
wife	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
coming	O
home	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
mob	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
fighting	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
bottle	O
shop	O
a	O
man	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
shoved	O
me	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
two	O
panes	O
of	O
glass	O
;	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
watch	O
,	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
has	O
the	O
man	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
honest	O
man	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
business	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
wrong	O
'd	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
hat	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
at	O
the	O
Plough	O
in	O
Thomas	O
street	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
distiller	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
a	O
wig	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
friend	O
take	O
your	O
wig	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
suffer	O
no	O
disturbance	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
return	O
and	O
give	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
satisfaction	O
you	O
can	O
desire	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
prodigious	O
noise	O
abroad	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
They	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
I	O
'd	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
child	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
would	O
be	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
laid	O
her	O
child	O
down	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
return	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
husband	O
and	O
apprentices	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
people	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
nothing	O
but	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
dirty	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
were	O
enquir	O
'd	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
then	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
his	O
wife	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
fright	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
bundle	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
She	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
was	O
wrap	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cloak	O
round	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
's	O
neck	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
it	O
appear	O
by	O
the	O
bundle	O
as	O
though	O
it	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
'd	O
take	O
notice	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
nothing	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Gandon	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
so	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Gandon	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
neck	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Short	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
chair-man	O
,	O
and	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Carral	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
Mrs.	O
Crow	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
:	O
when	O
all	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
cap	O
and	O
feather	O
at	O
our	O
door	O
,	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
She	O
first	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
bundle	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Crow	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
safe	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
368	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sophia	B-pers
Swarts	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
April	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Bullock	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
swear	O
the	O
spoon	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bullock	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
plate	O
under	O
my	O
care	O
:	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
spoon	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
came	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
spoon	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
cook	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
spoon	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Clark	O
.	O
She	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Swarts	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Feathers	O
in	O
Charles-court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
one	O
night	O
's	O
lodging	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
odd	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
her	O
lodging	O
where	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
before	O
.	O
Then	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
letters	O
there	O
were	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
J.	O
I	O
.	O
B.	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
father	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
name	O
Isabella	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
it	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
satisfy	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
informed	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
signifies	O
nothing	O
to	O
enquire	O
here	O
for	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
is	O
mad	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
maid	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
enquiry	O
she	O
should	O
lose	O
her	O
place	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
but	O
found	O
none	O
.	O
Upon	O
enquiry	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
Esquire	O
Bullock	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
upon	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
wrong	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
wanted	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
able	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
its	O
place	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hartley	O
's	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hartley	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Woolpack	O
and	O
naked	O
Boy	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
she	O
ever	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Ellice	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
bears	O
an	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lawson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
better	O
than	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Goodman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
at	O
Stony	O
Stratford	O
where	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Eliard	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
near	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
alway	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Frances	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Luke	B-pers
Chenner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
369	O
,	O
370	O
,	O
371	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Quinn	I-pers
,	O
||	O
Jos	B-pers
Dowdell	I-pers
,	O
||	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Crawford	I-pers
,	O
*	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
George	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
May	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
||	O
See	O
No	O
236	O
,	O
237	O
,	O
in	O
Sir	O
Samuel	O
Pennant	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
No	O
22	O
,	O
and	O
586	O
,	O
in	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
sen'night	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
James's-street	B-place
to	O
Covent-garden	O
from	O
Long-acre	O
in	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
some	O
persons	O
,	O
they	O
swore	O
they	O
'd	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
how	O
many	O
there	O
were	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
imagined	O
my	O
money	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
four	O
pounds	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
delivered	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
who	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
rummage	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
too	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
delivered	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
coach	O
hire	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
did	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
now	O
you	O
may	O
drive	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cullin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
May	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Bridges-street	O
to	O
the	O
French-horn	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
robbing	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
first	O
up	O
to	O
Long-acre	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
a	O
coach	O
turning	O
down	O
to	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
going	O
to	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
we	O
ran	O
up	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
Dowdell	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
Quinn	O
and	O
Talbot	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Dowdell	O
demand	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
blow	O
their	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
:	O
he	O
within	O
delivered	O
his	O
money	O
and	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
Dowdell	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Dowdell	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ordered	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
drive	O
on	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
turned	O
back	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Long-acre	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
Dowdell	O
,	O
the	O
chain	O
belonging	O
to	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
metal	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
that	O
to	O
Talbot	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Talbot	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
till	O
Thursday	O
night	O
was	O
fortnight	O
,	O
then	O
Quinn	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
French-horn	O
together	O
,	O
Dowdell	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
once	O
shipmates	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
sen'night	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Dowdell	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
shewed	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
a	O
silver	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
friends	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutors	O
watch	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
Dowdell	O
where	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Quinn	O
,	O
Cullin	O
and	O
Talbot	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
directions	O
were	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
Cullin	O
at	O
the	O
French-horn	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
took	O
Quinn	O
at	O
a	O
lodging	O
house	O
in	O
Newtoner's-lane	O
;	O
upon	O
our	O
shewing	O
him	O
the	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
justice	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
fact	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
he	O
committed	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
Talbot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
one	O
Field	O
.	O
When	O
Talbot	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
after	O
Cullin	O
had	O
related	O
that	O
account	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
Cullin	O
had	O
said	O
enough	O
for	O
himself	O
and	O
him	O
too	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
Talbot	O
,	O
besides	O
returning	O
from	O
transportation	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
Panton-street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
looking	O
into	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
use	O
him	O
ill	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
in	O
Tothill-fields	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Cullin	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
Mr.	O
Talbot	O
?	O
Talbot	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
street	O
robberies	O
.	O
372	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Alexander	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
nineteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Catherine	O
,	O
May	O
8	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wilson	O
lives	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
Covent-garden	I-place
,	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
hosier	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
her	O
shopman	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
tea	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
called	O
out	O
Mr.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
told	O
me	O
we	O
were	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
ran	O
down	O
towards	O
Covent	O
garden	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
we	O
lost	O
ten	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
round	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
by	O
giving	O
us	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
stockings	O
rather	O
then	O
be	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Balendine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
facing	O
the	O
hosier	O
's	O
shop	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
over	O
the	O
grate	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
stockings	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Balendine	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
o'clock	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
over	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
who	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Balendine	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
coat	O
he	O
has	O
now	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
stockings	O
?	O
Balendine	O
.	O
The	O
street	O
is	O
not	O
very	O
broad	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
always	O
stockings	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
for	O
show	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
different	O
colours	O
,	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
dark	O
greys	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
captain	O
Collet	O
's	O
facing	O
this	O
hosier	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
at	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
shop	O
door	O
which	O
joins	O
the	O
hosier	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
wondered	O
what	O
made	O
him	O
stand	O
there	O
so	O
long	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
business	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
looked	O
every	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
full	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
my	O
old	O
lady	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
shall	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
stared	O
his	O
eyes	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
hosier	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
look	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
set	O
his	O
foot	O
upon	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
scraper	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
over	O
the	O
grating	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
stockings	O
of	O
light	O
greys	O
and	O
other	O
colours	O
,	O
a	O
pretty	O
big	O
bundle	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
tied	O
round	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
man	O
has	O
robbed	O
the	O
stocking	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Apothecary	O
's	O
door	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
in	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
betwixt	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
about	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
King-street	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
General	O
Ligonier	B-pers
on	O
horseback	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
fifteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
my	O
aunt	O
's	O
shop	O
that	O
day	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
leering	O
about	O
there	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Heath	O
called	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
stockings	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Bridges-street	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
till	O
after	O
7	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
evidences	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
is	O
at	O
Kingston	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
373	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Hizard	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Oliver	B-pers
Husters	I-pers
,	O
May	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Vice	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
tell	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
the	O
pawnbroker	O
if	O
such	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
stop	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
after	O
this	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
shift	O
and	O
bed	O
gown	O
and	O
one	O
apron	O
,	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
My	O
neighbour	O
sent	O
his	O
servant	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
goods	O
,	O
begging	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
them	O
if	O
brought	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
2	O
hours	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
apron	O
,	O
bed	O
gown	O
and	O
shift	O
;	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
prove	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
or	O
two	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
dram	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
remember	O
whether	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
374	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Hatton	I-pers
,	I-pers
||	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Forrister	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
sixty	O
china	O
cups	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
four	O
china	O
saucers	O
,	O
one	O
bow	O
china	O
tea	O
pot	O
,	O
one	O
earthen	O
tea	O
pot	O
,	O
two	O
pickle	O
dishes	O
earthen	O
ware	O
,	O
five	O
fish	O
plates	O
earthen	O
ware	O
,	O
one	O
earthen	O
fish	O
strainer	O
,	O
one	O
show	O
glass	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
+	O
||	O
See	O
No	O
25.	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
keeps	O
an	O
earthen	O
ware	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
lay	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
the	O
windows	O
and	O
doors	O
were	O
all	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bolts	O
and	O
keys	O
were	O
so	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
A	O
shutter	O
was	O
broke	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
broke	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
about	O
two	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
missing	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
many	O
glasses	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brebrook	I-pers
.	O
George	O
Hall	O
the	O
evidence	O
sent	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
desiring	O
I	O
'd	O
take	O
up	O
this	O
Forrister	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
Hall	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
by	O
Hall	O
's	O
direction	O
to	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
George	O
Hall	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
house	O
breaking	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
this	O
china	O
shop	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
things	O
on	O
purpose	O
for	O
such	O
work	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
betwixt	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
first	O
try	O
'd	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
in	O
halves	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
watchmen	O
were	O
going	O
about	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
at	O
past	O
one	O
o'clock	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
kennel	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
broke	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
he	O
first	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
tea	O
pots	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bag	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
five	O
fish	O
strainers	O
,	O
six	O
tumblers	O
made	O
of	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
china	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
much	O
,	O
because	O
we	O
broke	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
china	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
two	O
little	O
china	O
plates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
square	O
plate	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
path	O
when	O
the	O
watchman	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
bag	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
me	O
so	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
our	O
lodgings	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
two	O
women	O
sixpence	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
in	O
Duke's-place	O
where	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
our	O
things	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
Minous	O
,	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
grumbled	O
at	O
the	O
price	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
we	O
were	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
leave	O
this	O
sort	O
of	O
life	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
hang	O
me	O
I	O
then	O
thought	O
to	O
hang	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
voluntarily	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
discovery	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
the	O
Jew	O
have	O
the	O
things	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
in	O
Ragfair	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
people	O
directly	O
;	O
this	O
prisoner	O
has	O
hang	O
'd	O
two	O
men	O
here	O
before	O
.	O
Brebrook	O
carried	O
us	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
said	O
nothing	O
about	O
Jones	O
,	O
was	O
he	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
this	O
robbery	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
say	O
nothing	O
against	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Brebrook	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Lecock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
,	O
some	O
are	O
here	O
now	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
are	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Brebrook	O
.	O
Are	O
these	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
you	O
found	O
in	O
Ragfair	O
?	O
Brebrook	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
more	O
now	O
at	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Are	O
these	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
covers	O
which	O
I	O
brought	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
teapots	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
they	O
sitted	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
pots	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
china	O
one	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Hall	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
we	O
meet	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Ragfair	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
bargain	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
David	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
he	O
had	O
`	O
been	O
out	O
a	O
picking	O
pockets	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
got	O
any	O
body	O
here	O
that	O
have	O
seen	O
us	O
together	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
we	O
were	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
gallery	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
together	O
in	O
this	O
way	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
burglary	O
.	O
375	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Judith	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
nine	O
diamond	O
stones	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Lemas	I-pers
.	O
+	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Lemas	I-pers
is	O
a	O
Venetian	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
English	O
,	O
so	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
A	O
seafearing	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
a	O
ring	O
from	O
off	O
my	O
finger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
done	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
At	O
her	O
aunt	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Duke	O
's	O
place	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Judith	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
was	O
her	O
aunt	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
she	O
speak	O
the	O
Italian	O
language	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
I	O
understand	O
a	O
little	O
English	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
her	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
become	O
acquainted	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
In	O
an	O
alehouse	O
drinking	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
from	O
a	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
ring	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
days	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
by	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
Her	O
aunt	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
did	O
she	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
ring	O
upon	O
your	O
finger	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
my	O
finger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
room	O
was	O
you	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
Above	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
bed-chamber	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
near	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
near	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
ring	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
rose	O
diamond	O
ring	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
eight	O
little	O
diamonds	O
and	O
one	O
large	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
it	O
now	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
taken	O
against	O
your	O
will	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
taken	O
by	O
force	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
hinder	O
her	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
She	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
own	O
finger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
there	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
Above	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
another	O
way	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
live	O
there	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
Three	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
ring	O
from	O
his	O
finger	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Had	O
there	O
not	O
been	O
familiarities	O
pass	O
'd	O
between	O
us	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
that	O
?	O
Lemas	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
paid	O
her	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
376	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
May	O
17	O
.	O
+	O
Matthew	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
friday	O
night	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
after	O
a	O
civil	O
manner	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
send	O
out	O
for	O
liquor	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
ten	O
minutes	O
she	O
laid	O
her	O
hand	O
about	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
a	O
kissing	O
me	O
;	O
her	O
other	O
hand	O
was	O
working	O
about	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
beer	O
,	O
but	O
sober	O
enough	O
when	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
directly	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
clap	O
'd	O
my	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
that	O
sat	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
.	O
The	O
people	O
without	O
were	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
come	O
here	O
to	O
breed	O
a	O
riot	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
glass	O
bottle	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
cut	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
wounded	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
other	O
people	O
put	O
up	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
stones	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
that	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
now	O
who	O
abused	O
me	O
.	O
One	O
person	O
brought	O
an	O
iron	O
poker	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
knives	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
perceive	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
Going	O
my	O
round	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
ten	O
this	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
abus	O
'd	O
and	O
robb	O
'd	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
place	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
blood	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
person	O
in	O
it	O
but	O
the	O
fellow	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
now	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
to	O
secure	O
any	O
body	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
up	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
wife	O
next	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
assistance	O
and	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
and	O
she	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
also	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
called	O
a	O
bawdy-house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
very	O
bad	O
proceedings	O
there	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
turn-key	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry-Compter	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
had	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
lodge	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
secured	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
pledg	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Holloway-lane	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
33	O
s.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
7	O
d.	O
for	O
interest	O
.	O
Produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Gravellane	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
chimney	O
corner	O
among	O
the	O
coals	O
.	O
I	O
pledg	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
is	O
returned	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Keys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
see	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
/	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
dispatched	O
the	O
room	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
both	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
persons	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
many	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
your	O
watch	O
was	O
lost	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
some	O
radishes	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
followed	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
or	O
touched	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
him	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
labouring-man	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
some	O
radishes	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
struggling	O
with	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
the	O
women	O
were	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
took	O
his	O
watch	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
knew	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
so	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
again	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
continues	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
kill	O
all	O
the	O
women	O
there	O
till	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
right	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
court	O
to	O
that	O
where	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
hubbub	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
women	O
who	O
stood	O
by	O
say	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
usual	O
in	O
that	O
court	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
it	O
look	O
'd	O
like	O
a	O
rocker	O
of	O
a	O
cradle	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
wav	O
'd	O
it	O
about	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
in	O
a	O
vulgar	O
manner	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
every	O
woman	O
he	O
met	O
till	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
His	O
head	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
then	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
A	O
neighbour	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
if	O
he	O
met	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
bloody	O
?	O
Watchman	O
.	O
What	O
this	O
woman	O
speaks	O
of	O
was	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
outrageous	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
gore	O
blood	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
377	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cluneys	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
snuffbox	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Jethroe	B-pers
Weacher	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jethroe	O
,	O
Feb.	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
Jethroe	O
Weacher	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
arms	O
in	O
King's-street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
In	O
February	O
last	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
Fox	B-place
ale-house	I-place
in	I-place
York-buildings	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
Christmas	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
billeted	O
upon	O
you	O
?	O
Weacher	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
:	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
quarters	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
Parade	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
ninepence	O
per	O
week	O
for	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
till	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
threepence	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
let	O
this	O
house	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
Thursday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
back	O
by	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lie	O
to	O
my	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
:	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
opportunities	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
upon	O
duty	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Gate	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
seeking	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
his	O
father	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
27	O
l.	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
it	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
the	O
Saturday	O
after	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
:	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
,	O
so	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
landlady	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
great	O
sufferer	O
by	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
deserted	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
as	O
a	O
deserter	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Savoy	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Blue-anchor	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
William	B-pers
Liberton	I-pers
;	O
accordingly	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
direction	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
10	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
8	O
l.	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Savoy	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gate-house	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
your	O
wife	O
or	O
you	O
?	O
Weacher	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
wife	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
you	O
then	O
?	O
Weacher	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
room	O
for	O
her	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
watch	O
last	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
it	O
?	O
Weacher	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
the	O
after	O
noon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
fact	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Gate	O
?	O
Weacher	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
fear	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
off	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
did	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Weacher	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
power	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
lodgings	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
your	O
wife	O
absent	O
herself	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Weacher	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
with	O
my	O
consent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
she	O
live	O
with	O
?	O
Weacher	O
.	O
She	O
lodged	O
with	O
a	O
widow	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
does	O
so	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
suspect	O
her	O
going	O
away	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
