TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
25th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Eighth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Francis	B-pers
Cokayne	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1751	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
FRANCIS	O
COKAYNE	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
LEE	O
*	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BURNET	I-pers
+	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
CLIVE	O
||	O
,	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rampshire	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Burnell	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Lynch	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Nemes	I-pers
,	O
Wilkinson	B-pers
Brathwait	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Prew	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Astie	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Punt	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jaumard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Speers	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Deschampus	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gerret	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sarsfield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lowry	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Sheldon	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Neile	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Laundale	I-pers
.	O
544	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Pallont	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Filiwisky	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Frederick	B-pers
Filiwisky	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
under	O
Ludgate	B-place
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deseaves	O
being	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
gentleman	O
ran	O
and	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Axe	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Deseaves	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
under	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
crowd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rushed	O
by	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
like	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
down	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Coming	O
through	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
,	O
clapped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
replied	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
yours	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
welcome	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
545	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheller	I-pers
.	O
++	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wheller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
,	O
at	O
the	B-place
Mitre	I-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
apprentice	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
cook	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
2	O
d.	O
18	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
fastened	O
down	O
in	O
another	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
where	O
I	O
lie	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
does	O
not	O
lie	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
all	O
but	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
about	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
often	O
found	O
the	O
lock	O
hampered	O
,	O
but	O
always	O
found	O
it	O
locked	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
marked	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
left	O
with	O
two	O
crosses	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
fastened	O
the	O
box	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
master	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
left	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Maidenhead	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
his	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
shew	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
servant	O
maid	O
there	O
having	O
changed	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shillings	O
I	O
had	O
marked	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
let	O
my	O
master	O
know	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
two	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
Tom	B-pers
Wheller	I-pers
's	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
money	O
out	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
us	O
the	O
fork	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
unlock	O
and	O
lock	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
Maidenhead	O
,	O
and	O
changed	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
identity	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martindale	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
latterly	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
trick	O
of	O
idling	O
his	O
time	O
away	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
546	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bacon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
John	B-pers
Bretley	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
Oct.	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bretley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
on	O
Muswell-hill	B-place
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Masterman	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
brown	O
mare	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
dark	O
muzzle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
slippers	O
,	O
under	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
wooden	O
clogs	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
road	O
to	O
Highgate	O
;	O
I	O
replied	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
turning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
miss	O
his	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
towards	O
High-gate	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
within	O
about	O
forty	O
or	O
fifty	O
yards	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Masterman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
back	O
and	O
saw	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
mask	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
yards	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
mistrusting	O
his	O
errand	O
,	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
under	O
my	O
coat	O
to	O
push	O
in	O
my	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
large	O
seals	O
,	O
hung	O
visibly	O
to	O
be	O
seen	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
shoot	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
or	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
or	O
such	O
like	O
words	O
.	O
He	O
replied	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
your	O
watch	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
you	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
unhappy	O
man	O
,	O
drove	O
to	O
it	O
by	O
necessity	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
honour	O
,	O
and	O
drove	O
to	O
the	O
utmost	O
distress	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
use	O
you	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
;	O
-	O
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
shoot	O
you	O
through	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
pistol	O
within	O
my	O
reach	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hat	O
towards	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
you	O
much	O
service	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
conceal	O
any	O
;	O
I	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
me	O
,	O
search	O
me	O
;	O
which	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
designed	O
to	O
have	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
shillings	O
into	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
his	O
horse	O
about	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
yards	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
shall	O
have	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
advertise	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
rode	O
very	O
fast	O
off	O
towards	O
Highgate	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
seeing	O
Mr.	O
Masterman	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
servant	O
,	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ride	O
by	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
he	O
turned	O
towards	O
Pinchley-common	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
mounted	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
took	O
a	O
handle	O
of	O
a	O
rake	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Masterman	O
's	O
servant	O
mounted	O
another	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
overtook	O
me	O
at	O
Highgate	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
inquired	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
directed	O
wrong	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
our	O
mistake	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
Spaniard	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
described	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
turning	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
's	O
corner	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
cut	O
cross	O
through	O
the	O
gravel	O
pits	O
,	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
North-end	O
.	O
We	O
also	O
called	O
out	O
as	O
we	O
rode	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
North-end	O
we	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
.	O
By	O
this	O
time	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
a	O
little	O
alarmed	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
miles	O
beyond	O
there	O
he	O
quitted	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
to	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
My	O
horse	O
was	O
almost	O
knocked	O
up	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
jumped	O
upon	O
the	O
horse	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
quitted	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
a	O
hedge	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
some	O
persons	O
dragged	O
out	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Hammond	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
wizard	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
quitted	O
his	O
horse	O
.	O
]	O
On	O
his	O
cross-examination	O
beyond	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
Highgate	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
pretty	O
hard	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
fight	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
about	O
two	O
miles	O
riding	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
watch	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
hole	O
as	O
he	O
rode	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
his	O
mittimus	O
was	O
made	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
another	O
room	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
there	O
begged	O
his	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
That	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
North-end	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
riding	O
extreme	O
hard	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
quit	O
his	O
mare	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
certain	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
was	O
upon	O
that	O
mare	O
which	O
he	O
himself	O
afterwards	O
mounted	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
then	O
seemed	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
rode	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
spurred	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Griffice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Masterman	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bretley	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
my	O
master	O
had	O
any	O
horses	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
pointed	O
out	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
there	O
goes	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saddled	O
two	O
horses	O
,	O
he	O
mounted	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
High-gate	O
,	O
where	O
a	O
man	O
informed	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
turned	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
rode	O
round	O
the	O
two	O
roads	O
that	O
go	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
several	O
persons	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
man	O
gone	O
that	O
way	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
turnpike	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
through	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
turned	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Spaniards	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
gone	O
by	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
riding	O
full	O
speed	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bretley	O
,	O
I	O
informed	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
believed	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
description	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
describe	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
robbed	O
him	O
?	O
Griffice	O
.	O
He	O
described	O
him	O
as	O
having	O
a	O
thin	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
riding	O
a	O
dark	O
bay	O
mare	O
with	O
a	O
brown	O
muzzle	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
turn	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
down	O
the	O
great	O
road	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
view	O
of	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
riding	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
being	O
rather	O
better	O
mounted	O
than	O
Mr.	O
Bretley	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
informing	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
highwayman	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
to	O
a	O
hedge	O
,	O
quitted	O
his	O
mare	O
,	O
and	O
jumped	O
over	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
crowd	O
of	O
people	O
got	O
about	O
his	O
mate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Bretley	O
get	O
on	O
the	O
mare	O
;	O
for	O
my	O
horse	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
the	O
hedge	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
field	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
or	O
two	O
had	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Bretley	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
tied	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
thumbs	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
watch	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
mounted	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
dismount	O
my	O
mare	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
she	O
throw	O
me	O
?	O
Griffice	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
on	O
full	O
speed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
case	O
no	O
man	O
can	O
give	O
evidence	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
According	O
to	O
the	O
description	O
Mr.	O
Bretley	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Grubb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bretley	O
's	O
house	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
forty	O
yards	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Bretley	O
's	O
gate	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
brown	O
mare	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Bretley	O
rode	O
afterwards	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
whipping	O
and	O
spurring	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
expected	O
she	O
would	O
throw	O
him	O
every	O
minute	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
just	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
Highgate	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
mask	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
his	O
clothes	O
and	O
his	O
mare	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
mind	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
Mr.	O
Bretley	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
after	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
mare	O
,	O
and	O
can	O
swear	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
mare	O
I	O
saw	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
clothes	O
.	O
The	O
mare	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
bay	O
with	O
a	O
brown	O
muzzle	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
one	O
Eldridge	O
upon	O
the	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
a	O
highway-man	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
horseback	O
turn	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
,	O
who	O
rode	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
rate	O
.	O
We	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
about	O
fifty	O
pole	O
from	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
crept	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
covered	O
pretty	O
much	O
with	O
bushes	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
quitted	O
the	O
mare	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
saw	O
riding	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mare	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
mind	O
her	O
.	O
Eldridge	O
confirmed	O
what	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
field	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Harison	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Ditton	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
riding	O
down	O
the	O
hill	O
very	O
fast	O
,	O
whipping	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
rode	O
up	O
the	O
hill	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
highwayman	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
turn	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
mounted	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
rode	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
ground	O
of	O
him	O
every	O
minute	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
people	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
them	O
a	O
highwayman	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
upon	O
Golder	O
's	O
Green	O
,	O
jumped	O
off	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
through	O
a	O
hedge	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
over	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
The	O
hedge	O
was	O
difficult	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
jump	O
my	O
horse	O
over	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
a	O
little	O
lower	O
,	O
got	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
stile	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
second	O
field	O
;	O
I	O
likewise	O
jumped	O
my	O
horse	O
over	O
the	O
stile	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
force	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
.	O
Presently	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
man	O
say	O
there	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hedge	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
I	O
saw	O
whipping	O
and	O
riding	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Sidney	I-pers
,	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
was	O
apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
served	O
upwards	O
of	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
character	O
;	O
who	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
cross-examination	O
,	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
once	O
made	O
an	O
elopement	O
from	O
his	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
times	O
would	O
stay	O
out	O
till	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Evan	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hager	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Linley	I-pers
,	O
Harwood	O
Lassiter	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Going	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Newhouse	I-pers
,	O
had	O
all	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
547	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Ramsey	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Tompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Daniel	B-pers
Widenham	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
,	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
September	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Widenham	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
play-house	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
play	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
Coming	O
away	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
playhouse	O
door	O
in	O
Bridges	O
Street	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
pot	O
and	O
a	O
dram	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
reply	O
,	O
but	O
walked	O
on	O
.	O
She	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
accosted	O
me	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
gone	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
persisted	O
in	O
following	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mary	O
,	O
will	O
not	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
your	O
company	O
?	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
ticked	O
up	O
this	O
gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
shall	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
welcome	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
detain	O
the	O
company	O
you	O
have	O
left	O
behind	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
into	O
White-Horse-Yard	B-place
,	O
they	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
caught	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
my	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
forced	O
them	O
to	O
lose	O
their	O
hold	O
.	O
Then	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
fellows	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
struck	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
stunned	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
against	O
the	O
rails	O
.	O
They	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
men	O
held	O
me	O
while	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
a	O
green	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
shilling	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
so	O
remarkable	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
night	O
?	O
Widenham	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
lamp	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
knocked	O
against	O
the	O
rails	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
observed	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
548	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Chipingdale	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
549	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Walthew	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
26	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
12	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
12	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
three	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hancock	I-pers
,	O
October	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
again	O
at	O
divers	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Hills	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Twentyman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
all	O
deposed	O
they	O
took	O
them	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Many	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
550	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Alice	B-pers
Nixon	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Drinkwater	I-pers
and	O
Anne	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
one	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
along	O
the	O
fields	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Old-street	O
church	O
,	O
I	O
struck	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Red	O
Lion-street	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
fellows	O
that	O
had	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
ship	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
parted	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
arm	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
treat	O
me	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
Blackmary	B-place
's	I-place
hole	I-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
stairs	O
we	O
had	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
and	O
water	O
mixed	O
together	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
18	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
by	O
themselves	O
in	O
my	O
sob	O
;	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
soon	O
squandered	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
head	O
giddy	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
granted	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
in	O
my	O
shoes	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Drinkwater	I-pers
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
that	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
known	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
heard	O
his	O
wife	O
say	O
,	O
Drinkwater	O
,	O
get	O
up	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
called	O
him	O
James	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
'd	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
to	O
sleep	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
to	O
preserve	O
my	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
then	O
felt	O
there	O
by	O
putting	O
my	O
thumb	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
awaked	O
when	O
the	O
clock	O
strack	O
three	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
,	O
Drinkwater	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
cold	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
trod	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
straps	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
,	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
Drinkwater	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
were	O
my	O
buckles	O
;	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
damning	O
her	O
blood	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
sell	O
them	O
because	O
you	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
calling	O
me	O
impudent	O
son	O
of	O
a	O
bitch	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
money	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
feel	O
for	O
the	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
also	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
play	O
any	O
tricks	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
sign	O
this	O
paper	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
paper	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
already	O
wrote	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
signed	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
through	O
fear	O
;	O
Drinkwater	O
's	O
wife	O
had	O
the	O
buckles	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
agreeable	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
stay	O
till	O
quite	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
I	O
could	O
lose	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
staid	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
sleep	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
why	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
breakfast	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
all	O
a	O
dram	O
a-piece	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
at	O
breakfast	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
justice	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
551	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Edward	I-pers
Aires	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
M'Grant	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
&	O
c.	O
+	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
552	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Pope	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	O
Lincoln	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Lincoln	I-pers
.	O
My	O
mother	O
lives	O
in	O
Tower-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
servant	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
and	O
pawning	O
them	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Longate	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
produced	O
two	O
shirts	O
pawned	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lawn	O
apron	O
.	O
The	O
gown	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
pawned	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
evidence	O
;	O
it	O
appeared	O
the	O
two	O
shirts	O
were	O
callico	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
gown	O
the	O
evidence	O
deposed	O
to	O
as	O
her	O
sister	O
Juliana	O
's	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
553	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Pryer	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
blue	O
cloth	O
coat	O
with	O
a	O
scarlet	O
lining	O
,	O
one	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	O
Harrison	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Granvil	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
one	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
14	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
stuff	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Goss-square	B-place
,	I-place
Fleet	I-place
street	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Richardson	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Grantham	O
in	O
Lincolnshire	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
Monday	O
to	O
Sunday	O
following	O
;	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
above	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
left	O
below	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
hired	O
herself	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Newgate-market	O
who	O
recommended	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
how	O
she	O
had	O
served	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawers	O
below	O
stairs	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
drawer	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
purse	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
from	O
another	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
;	O
I	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
guinea	O
,	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
pieces	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
crime	O
she	O
ever	O
committed	O
;	O
I	O
forgave	O
her	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
;	O
upon	O
farther	O
searching	O
my	O
drawers	O
I	O
found	O
several	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
particularly	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
stuff	O
.	O
14	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
petticoat	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Granvil	O
's	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
dyed	O
and	O
not	O
made	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Irish	O
stuff	O
made	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Granvil	O
's	O
petticoat	O
made	O
into	O
a	O
petticoat	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
(	O
Both	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
also	O
found	O
a	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
marked	O
D	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
to	O
wash	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
she	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
suit	O
of	O
clothes	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Henry	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
then	O
;	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
trunk	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
lace	O
off	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
burnt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Hemmings-row	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
to-morrow	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
these	O
things	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
till	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
this	O
yellow	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pew	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Day	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Day	O
owned	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
muslin	O
apron	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Pow	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Day	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to-morrow	O
will	O
be	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
gold	O
off	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
;	O
also	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
Irish	O
stuff	O
,	O
the	O
yellow	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
linen	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
apron	O
was	O
not	O
mentioned	O
then	O
)	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Westwood	O
's	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Westwood	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
More	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
554	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Whittum	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Newbolt	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
Jane	O
Newbolt	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
sheep	O
's	O
heart	O
to	O
broil	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
mug	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
from	O
betwixt	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
to	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
drank	O
his	O
pint	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
penny-worth	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
silver	O
pint	O
pot	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
he	O
and	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
musing	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
my	O
maid	O
being	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
gone	O
with	O
the	O
silver	O
mug	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
enquired	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
she	O
brought	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
mug	O
squeezed	O
and	O
bent	O
together	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
J.	O
Newbolt	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
there	O
been	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
J.	O
Newbolt	O
.	O
There	O
had	O
been	O
several	O
companies	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
when	O
the	O
last	O
penny-worth	O
was	O
drawn	O
,	O
then	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
but	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
J.	O
Newbolt	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
box	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
pint	O
mug	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
?	O
J.	O
Newbolt	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
particular	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
drew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
this	O
mug	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
waited	O
for	O
somebody	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
at	O
that	O
table	O
but	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
some	O
pots	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
mug	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Column-street	O
,	O
I	O
cried	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
stole	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
silver	O
mug	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
was	O
no	O
thorough	O
fare	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
throng	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
mug	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
somebody	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
stood	O
near	O
to	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
mug	O
in	O
their	O
hand	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
mug	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
E.	O
Brown	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
other	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
E.	O
Brown	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
but	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
mug	O
last	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
maid	O
deliver	O
the	O
mug	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
speaks	O
on	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
maid	O
went	O
out	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
him	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
betwixt	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
maid	O
delivered	O
the	O
last	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
maid	O
said	O
the	O
mug	O
was	O
missing	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
15	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
hostler	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
I	O
believe	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Prew	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
jewry	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
hostler	O
with	O
me	O
six	O
months	O
and	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
servant	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
this	O
ago	O
?	O
Prew	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
almost	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
found	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
sworn	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
where	O
he	O
lives	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
555	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	O
Rogers	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publickhouse	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Bedlam	I-place
.	O
The	O
silver	O
spoon	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
use	O
,	O
I	O
wiped	O
it	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
leaving	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
spoon	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
parish	O
officer	O
,	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
the	O
workhouse	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
the	O
affair	O
,	O
and	O
desiring	O
,	O
if	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
should	O
be	O
heard	O
of	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
Smock-alley	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Eakins	O
's	O
;	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
carried	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
for	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eakins	I-pers
.	O
This	O
spoon	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
one	O
Cooper	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
first	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
then	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
she	O
replied	O
here	O
,	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
where	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
advertised	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
This	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
spoon	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
friend	O
's	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Eakins	O
's	O
house	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
spoon	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
three	O
witnesses	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
If	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
receivers	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
thieves	O
.	O
She	O
received	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
an	O
officer	O
indeed	O
!	O
The	O
officers	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bishopsgate	O
will	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
relief	O
,	O
which	O
makes	O
me	O
lie	O
about	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
a	O
whoring	O
or	O
thieving	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
how	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
bread	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
556	O
,	O
557	O
,	O
558	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Alexander	B-pers
Byrne	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mallone	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Terence	B-pers
M'Cane	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
mettle	O
tobacco-box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
nine	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
thirtieth	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
to	O
Catherine-wheel	O
Alley	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
Whitechapel-bars	B-place
I	O
was	O
followed	O
by	O
four	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
alley	O
.	O
I	O
pushed	O
on	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
within	O
a	O
stone	O
's	O
throw	O
of	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
overtook	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
Mallone	O
and	O
M'Cane	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
as	O
fine	O
a	O
moon	O
light	O
night	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
all	O
four	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
door	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
Byrne	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
Wayland	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
they	O
bid	O
m	O
e	O
hold	O
my	O
tongue	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
.	O
Mallone	O
and	O
the	O
Evidence	O
led	O
me	O
beyond	O
the	O
passage	O
behind	O
the	O
pump	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
deliver	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
watch	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
money	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
Evidence	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
nine	O
shillings	O
and	O
three	O
pence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
shilling	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
left	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
M'Cane	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
stood	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
Byrne	O
stood	O
facing	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
with	O
cutlasses	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
M'Cane	O
had	O
no	O
weapon	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
Byrne	O
and	O
M'Cane	O
were	O
both	O
stooping	O
when	O
my	O
shoe-buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
which	O
took	O
them	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
concealed	O
any	O
thing	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brain	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
my	O
watch	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
saved	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
described	O
them	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
several	O
neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
armed	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
eight	O
minutes	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
understand	O
,	O
within	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
about	O
seven	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Wayland	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
together	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
money	O
by	O
robbing	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
all	O
four	O
attacked	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
Catherine-wheel	O
Alley	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
turned	O
him	O
up	O
under	O
a	O
gateway	O
.	O
Byrne	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
Mallone	O
and	O
I	O
each	O
a	O
sword	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
nine	O
shillings	O
and	O
three	O
pence	O
,	O
his	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
tobacco-box	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Byrne	O
and	O
I	O
first	O
attacked	O
him	O
;	O
Byrne	O
ran	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
his	O
chin	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
passed	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
saw	O
we	O
had	O
attacked	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
turned	O
back	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
your	O
weapons	O
naked	O
?	O
Wayland	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
M'Cane	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
Mallone	O
took	O
the	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
were	O
the	O
four	O
men	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
spent	O
a	O
shilling	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
Winifred-street	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
ground	O
room	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
there	O
Byrne	O
and	O
Mallone	O
fought	O
about	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
afterwards	O
,	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
took	O
us	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
us	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
two	O
swords	O
and	O
pistol	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
by	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
instruments	O
they	O
had	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
from	O
Byrne	O
.	O
Ask	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
what	O
the	O
Evidence	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
Smart	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
continue	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
promised	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Evidence	O
turned	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
cutlass	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
turn	O
Evidence	O
tomorrow	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
company	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
By	O
the	O
great	O
God	O
you	O
shall	O
hear	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
great	O
God	O
and	O
sweet	O
Jesus	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Indeed	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
You	O
shall	O
hear	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
stand	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Bosworth	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
and	O
Mark	B-pers
Chailes	I-pers
were	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
swords	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
half	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
me	O
till	O
they	O
saw	O
Stanley	O
,	O
then	O
Mallone	O
whipped	O
up	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
hangers	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
cut	O
,	O
saying	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
grab	O
;	O
Byrne	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
shot	O
Mark	B-pers
Chailes	I-pers
in	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
cut	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
stood	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
arguing	O
and	O
fighting	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
buckles	O
from	O
Byrne	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
hat	O
also	O
produced	O
,	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
by	O
Stanley	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
entry	O
,	O
betwixt	O
Winifred-street	O
and	O
Catherine-wheel	O
Alley	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
some	O
hangers	O
lying	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoners	O
seemed	O
in	O
a	O
dispute	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
Robinson	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
him	O
;	O
Mallone	O
whipped	O
a	O
hanger	O
up	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
eyes	O
,	O
if	O
here	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
grab	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
candle	O
was	O
struck	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
Chailes	O
to	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
off	O
went	O
a	O
pistol	O
close	O
by	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
Chailes	O
called	O
out	O
he	O
was	O
shot	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
never	O
mind	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
Byrne	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
cuts	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
submit	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
If	O
you	O
are	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
go	O
for	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
brought	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
witness	O
took	O
the	O
silver	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
Byrne	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
hat	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Wayland	O
first	O
submitted	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
blamed	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
Evidence	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stanley	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
my	O
life	O
can	O
be	O
saved	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
discovery	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
replied	O
,	O
Then	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
is	O
to	O
tell	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
shewed	O
us	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
as	O
likewise	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Evidence	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
,	O
he	O
likewise	O
knew	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidences	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Clark	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
Byrne	O
for	O
robberies	O
committed	O
in	O
George	O
's	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
Robinson	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
saw	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
.	O
M'Cane	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
taken	O
in	O
Robinson	O
's	O
own	O
house	O
.	O
For	O
Mallone	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goods	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
printer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Chiswel-street	O
near	O
Morefields	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
Mallone	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
Easter	O
Tuesday	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
no	O
man	O
could	O
behave	O
better	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
eight	O
or	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
per	O
week	O
for	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
three	O
weeks	O
upon	O
liking	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
remarkably	O
sober	O
,	O
all	O
my	O
men	O
in	O
their	O
several	O
classes	O
agreed	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
not	O
desirous	O
of	O
liquor	O
,	O
nor	O
given	O
to	O
cursing	O
and	O
swearing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Perrin	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
Gyles	O
Nottingham	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Yandal	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
fellow-servants	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
the	O
apprentice	O
,	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hemmings	I-pers
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
word	O
from	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
a	O
careful	O
saving	O
fellow	O
,	O
he	O
generally	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lay	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
but	O
that	O
unhappy	O
night	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lagoe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
years	O
in	O
Ireland	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
sober	O
lad	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
For	O
M.	O
Cane	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Duplex	I-pers
.	O
M.	O
Cane	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
so	O
am	O
I	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
trial	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
others	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
employed	O
him	O
till	O
Christmas	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
recommended	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Duplex	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
diligent	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
in	O
a	O
remarkable	O
good	O
manner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
persons	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
suspected	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
an	O
offence	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
,	O
I	O
worked	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
extremely	O
well	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
559	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Parent	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
eight	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Stamma	I-pers
,	O
October	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
560	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Bridget	B-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Magarth	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Acq	O
.	O
561	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Deborah	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
d.	O
one	O
yard	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
four	O
diaper	O
clouts	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
562	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Kendrick	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
22	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
printing	O
letters	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
,	O
October	O
11	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
563	O
,	O
564	O
,	O
565	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bunks	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Mandeville	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
&	O
c.	O
one	O
linen	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
silver	O
stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
metal	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Sept	O
,	O
29	O
.	O
||	O
Joseph	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Plastow	O
in	O
Essex	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
from	O
Rag-Fair	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Dragon	O
in	O
Church-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
where	O
my	O
horse	O
was	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
spoke	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
and	O
pin	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
evidence	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
I	O
thought	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
;	O
they	O
searched	O
my	O
side	O
pockets	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
shoe	O
and	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
my	O
watch	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
4	O
s	O
,	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
stock	O
and	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Chandler	O
.	O
Mandeville	O
's	O
hand	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
handy	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
?	O
Chandler	O
.	O
Not	O
very	O
light	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
but	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
know	O
them	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
took	O
my	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
out	O
;	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
silver	O
;	O
them	O
two	O
I	O
know	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
Holmes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
stock	O
off	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
snatched	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
;	O
Symonds	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
have	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
no	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
strip	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dispute	O
betwixt	O
them	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
accordingly	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
towards	O
Whitechapel	O
church	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
my	O
way	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
.	O
Presently	O
I	O
perceived	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
coming	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
came	O
any	O
further	O
they	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
Red	O
Lion-street	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
my	O
inn	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
hostler	O
and	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
)	O
by	O
whose	O
direction	O
they	O
found	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
Justice	O
Richards	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
knew	O
Newton	O
and	O
Mandeville	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
before	O
my	O
face	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
view	O
of	O
Newton	O
,	O
he	O
standing	O
by	O
my	O
side	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
A	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
he	O
deposed	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
knees	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
breeches	O
knees	O
of	O
Holmes	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
were	O
shown	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
put	O
in	O
fear	O
?	O
Chandler	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
clear	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
about	O
seven	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
fact	O
;	O
we	O
met	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Queen's-head	O
,	O
an	O
alehouse	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
lane	O
;	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
set	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Sept.	O
29	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
consented	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
we	O
met	O
that	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
with	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
apprehended	O
yet	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Stepney-fields	O
;	O
about	O
nine	O
we	O
stopped	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Church-lane	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
give	O
me	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
about	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
little	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
resistance	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
shov	O
'd	O
him	O
against	O
a	O
wall	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
four	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
whilst	O
they	O
took	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
stock	O
buckle	O
;	O
Holmes	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
us	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Mandeville	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
;	O
we	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
our	O
way	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
Blue	O
Anchor	O
in	O
the	O
Back	O
lane	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
slip	O
and	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
every	O
man	O
a	O
share	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
taken	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
there	O
;	O
Holmes	O
had	O
the	O
knee	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
breeches	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
charged	O
Mandeville	O
,	O
Newton	O
.	O
and	O
me	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
Holmes	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
stock	O
and	O
stock	O
buckle	O
;	O
the	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
our	O
rendezvous	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
only	O
metal	O
we	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
on	O
a	O
shelf	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
shewn	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
deposed	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
&	O
c.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
you	O
armed	O
?	O
Symonds	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
only	O
one	O
large	O
knife	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
We	O
had	O
intelligence	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
where	O
these	O
prisoners	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
so	O
one	O
Valentine	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Millings	I-pers
,	O
Collet	O
Stanley	O
,	O
Harris	O
,	O
Macdaniel	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
made	O
a	O
very	O
stout	O
resistance	O
.	O
but	O
we	O
over-powered	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
Bunks	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
grab	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
be	O
hanged	O
at	O
first	O
as	O
at	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
knee	O
buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
after	O
his	O
mittimus	O
was	O
made	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
game	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
saying	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
what	O
signifies	O
it	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
your	O
friends	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
send	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
save	O
you	O
from	O
the	O
surgeons	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bartington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
evidence	O
Symonds	O
,	O
together	O
often	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Mandeville	O
produced	O
his	O
discharge	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
to	O
prove	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Symonds	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
dated	O
September	O
20	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
566	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Mutter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
Sept.	O
1	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Black	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
an	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Round	O
Court	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
10	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
wagered	O
of	O
3d	O
.	O
about	O
their	O
height	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lost	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
pay	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
he	O
should	O
pay	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
all	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
jarring	O
words	O
betwixt	O
them	O
two	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
the	O
deceased	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
abused	O
that	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
man	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
replied	O
,	O
that	O
now	O
was	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
turned	O
from	O
near	O
the	O
shops	O
towards	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
flying	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
passed	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
May	O
's	O
buildings	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
them	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
strike	O
at	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
his	O
kinsman	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
said	O
Mutter	O
had	O
cut	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
home	O
leaning	O
on	O
his	O
kinsman	O
's	O
shoulders	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
all	O
lodged	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wadle	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
.	O
A	O
surgeon	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
through	O
his	O
scull	O
,	O
which	O
bled	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
also	O
a	O
wound	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
thumb	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
weapon	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
when	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
deceased	O
?	O
Tompson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
nineteenth	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
keep	O
his	O
bed	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
second	O
days	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
on	O
his	O
legs	O
when	O
he	O
received	O
these	O
blows	O
?	O
Tompson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
down	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
strike	O
the	O
deceased	O
above	O
once	O
?	O
Tompson	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
levelled	O
at	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
deceased	O
strike	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Tompson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
light	O
night	O
?	O
Tompson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
lamp	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
deceased	O
called	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
wounds	O
were	O
there	O
?	O
Tompson	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
cuts	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross-examination	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
seemed	O
always	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
friendly	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
but	O
the	O
deceased	O
might	O
have	O
struck	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
he	O
turned	O
back	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
he	O
did	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
first	O
cousins	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Tompson	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Black	O
's	O
in	O
Round-Court	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Bonner	O
,	O
a	O
painter	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Tompson	O
to	O
deliver	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
finding	O
him	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
meeting	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
just	O
without	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
steaks	O
together	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
the	O
deceased	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
company	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
then	O
drinking	O
the	O
third	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
wager	O
laid	O
about	O
the	O
height	O
of	O
twelve	O
new	O
halfpence	O
,	O
when	O
laid	O
one	O
upon	O
another	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
Tompson	O
lost	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wagered	O
about	O
their	O
heights	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
laid	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
not	O
an	O
inch	O
taller	O
than	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
measured	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
taller	O
by	O
an	O
inch	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lost	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
six	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
threepences	O
lost	O
;	O
Tompson	O
paid	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
refused	O
to	O
pay	O
his	O
threepence	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
deceased	O
paid	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
words	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
down	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
the	O
wager	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
spend	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
with	O
any	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
any	O
of	O
us	O
to	O
cover	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
spend	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
four	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
It	O
struck	O
twelve	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Chandos-street	O
,	O
there	O
they	O
had	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
called	O
the	O
prisoner	O
scoundrel	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
a	O
scoundrel	O
than	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
man	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
replied	O
,	O
Nothing	O
like	O
the	O
time	O
present	O
.	O
I	O
smiled	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
quarrel	O
about	O
so	O
small	O
a	O
matter	O
as	O
threepence	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
pretty	O
hard	O
on	O
towards	O
May	O
's	O
Buildings	O
;	O
being	O
about	O
seven	O
yards	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
the	O
deceased	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
blows	O
towards	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
weapon	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
hold	O
up	O
his	O
hands	O
to	O
guard	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
no	O
resistance	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
a	O
step	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
,	O
James	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
Mutter	O
has	O
cut	O
me	O
with	O
something	O
or	O
other	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
blood	O
run	O
much	O
.	O
We	O
walked	O
pretty	O
hard	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
a	O
light	O
was	O
brought	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
left	O
temple	O
,	O
which	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
.	O
A	O
surgeon	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
farther	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
left	O
arm	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
cut	O
about	O
an	O
inch	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
long	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
cut	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
thumb	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
wound	O
below	O
his	O
eye	O
:	O
they	O
all	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
a	O
sharp	O
pointed	O
instrument	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
ordered	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross-examination	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
lived	O
together	O
in	O
a	O
friendly	O
manner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
no	O
malice	O
betwixt	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
on	O
his	O
own	O
account	O
,	O
not	O
upon	O
the	O
calling	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
possible	O
there	O
might	O
have	O
been	O
blows	O
before	O
he	O
turned	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
,	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
poor	O
Mutter	O
;	O
that	O
as	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
(	O
there	O
was	O
Mutter	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
bed	O
)	O
he	O
shewed	O
him	O
his	O
blood	O
on	O
his	O
sleeve	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Mutter	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
see	O
your	O
own	O
handy	O
works	O
?	O
Mutter	O
answered	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
all	O
your	O
own	O
fault	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
aggressor	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
deceased	O
ordered	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
the	O
word	O
scoundrel	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
blows	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
natured	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
likewise	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
facing	O
each	O
other	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
blows	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
the	O
wounds	O
were	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wadle	I-pers
.	O
They	O
all	O
four	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
bleeding	O
at	O
the	O
left	O
temple	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
held	O
her	O
apron	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blood	O
ran	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Take	O
care	O
of	O
Mutter	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
cut	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
die	O
;	O
so	O
his	O
kinsman	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
cut	O
with	O
?	O
Wadle	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
surgeon	O
said	O
,	O
Perhaps	O
the	O
wound	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
dangerous	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
not	O
take	O
Mutter	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
yet	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
deceased	O
replied	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
hurt	O
poor	O
Mutter	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
ailed	O
him	O
to	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
mischief	O
with	O
the	O
knife	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
man	O
a	O
small	O
sword	O
to	O
threaten	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
fearing	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
mad	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
cut	O
Anderson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
his	O
own	O
fault	O
,	O
replied	O
he	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
temples	O
first	O
;	O
then	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
place	O
on	O
his	O
forehead	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
ought	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
knife	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
knife	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
one	O
Steward	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
Get	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mutter	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
the	O
knife	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Throw	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
he	O
threw	O
up	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
making	O
a	O
faint	O
motion	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
thrown	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
cutting	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
or	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
knife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
place	O
was	O
that	O
on	O
his	O
forehead	O
?	O
Wadle	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
red	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
rising	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
very	O
little	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
insisted	O
upon	O
our	O
taking	O
care	O
of	O
Mutter	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
again	O
.	O
On	O
his	O
cross-examination	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
They	O
two	O
lived	O
in	O
great	O
friendship	O
together	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
judged	O
the	O
small	O
place	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
was	O
not	O
done	O
with	O
a	O
hand	O
,	O
except	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
one	O
nuckle	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
small	O
,	O
if	O
given	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
a	O
lad	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
in	O
any	O
body	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
all	O
lived	O
together	O
in	O
friendship	O
like	O
brethren	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Steward	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bedfellow	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
asleep	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
they	O
awaked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
that	O
noise	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
and	O
Anderson	O
had	O
quarrelled	O
about	O
a	O
wager	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
refused	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
Coming	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
called	O
him	O
scoundrel	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
more	O
a	O
scoundrel	O
than	O
you	O
are	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
quarrel	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
cut	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
the	O
landlord	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
taxed	O
him	O
with	O
cutting	O
the	O
deceased	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
;	O
then	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
desire	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
seint	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
surgeon	O
had	O
dressed	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
use	O
me	O
so	O
?	O
the	O
prisoner	O
replied	O
,	O
You	O
struck	O
me	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
denied	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
struck	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchmen	O
were	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kelley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
bleeding	O
from	O
three	O
several	O
wounds	O
;	O
I	O
dressed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
attended	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
my	O
treating	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
wounds	O
in	O
any	O
danger	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
on	O
his	O
temple	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
instrument	O
,	O
which	O
must	O
be	O
sharp	O
pointed	O
,	O
had	O
penetrated	O
the	O
scull	O
,	O
and	O
wounded	O
the	O
brain	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
deceased	O
sensible	O
?	O
Kelley	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
delirious	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
afterwards	O
at	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
die	O
?	O
Kelley	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
nineteenth	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
His	O
other	O
wounds	O
were	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
thumb	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
scratch	O
under	O
his	O
eye	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
with	O
a	O
sharp	O
pointed	O
instrument	O
;	O
the	O
flesh	O
was	O
raised	O
on	O
his	O
thumb	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
cut	O
intirely	O
off	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
only	O
divided	O
from	O
the	O
part	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
temperal	O
bone	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
ten	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
insensible	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
about	O
two	O
the	O
morning	O
following	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
this	O
quarrel	O
?	O
Kelley	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
he	O
would	O
exclaim	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
bad	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
what	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
?	O
Kelley	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
his	O
fist	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
blood	O
running	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
struck	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Kelley	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
particulars	O
of	O
what	O
passed	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
remember	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Kelley	O
.	O
He	O
seemed	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
master	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
house	O
in	O
Round-Court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
about	O
a	O
wager	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Chandos	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
scoundrel	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
kick	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
my	O
saying	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
allow	O
it	O
,	O
his	O
cousin	O
came	O
and	O
prevented	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
fight	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
then	O
for	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
forehead	O
,	O
which	O
caused	O
a	O
bump	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
school	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
of	O
a	O
peaceable	O
disposition	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
peaceable	O
,	O
sober	O
,	O
and	O
discreet	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
quarrel	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Comming	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
called	O
a	O
quarrelsome	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
quietly	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Reney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
peaceable	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
a	O
rankorous	O
disposition	O
on	O
any	O
consideration	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cleland	O
.	O
He	O
once	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behaved	O
quietly	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
about	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
appeared	O
always	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sober	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
addicted	O
to	O
any	O
passion	O
whatsoever	O
.	O
Margaret	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Cleland	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
a	O
quarrelsome	O
disposition	O
,	O
but	O
of	O
a	O
mild	O
good	O
natured	O
temper	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
disguised	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
quarrelsome	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
567	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newcomb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
vessel	O
,	O
weighing	O
nineteen	O
pounds	O
,	O
value	O
19	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Medcalf	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
568	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Blee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
October	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
.	O
This	O
day	O
sevennight	O
,	O
passing	O
along	O
Ludgate-hill	B-place
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Bartlift	I-pers
called	O
out	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
cast	O
my	O
eye	O
into	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
drew	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
kennel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
Peter	B-pers
Bartlift	I-pers
.	O
This	O
day	O
sevennight	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Wills	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
men	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
occasion	O
to	O
blow	O
my	O
nose	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
along	O
side	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
two	O
companions	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
catched	O
at	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
breast	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
eye	O
upon	O
these	O
chaps	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
close	O
behind	O
Mr.	O
Wills	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Will	O
's	O
Pocket	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
You	O
rascal	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wills	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
picked	O
your	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
handed	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
companions	O
,	O
who	O
dropped	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
seeing	O
it	O
lie	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
held	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
sight	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
lad	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
bread	O
.	O
Terence	B-pers
Dear	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
an	O
object	O
of	O
charity	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Maynard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
569	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pound	O
and	O
six	O
ounces	O
of	O
brass	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Gyles	I-pers
,	O
October	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
570	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Eliot	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
leaden	O
pipe	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rapley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
571	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Francis	I-pers
Medows	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Wills	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
yards	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
26	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Eyres	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Edward	O
,	O
September	O
21	O
.	O
||	O
Edward	B-pers
Eyres	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
York-street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
;	O
upon	O
my	O
return	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
looking	O
at	O
some	O
lawn	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
passed	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
tell	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
surprized	O
she	O
should	O
offer	O
him	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
apprehended	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
appearance	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
occasion	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
offering	O
so	O
low	O
a	O
price	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
steal	O
.	O
This	O
made	O
me	O
determine	O
to	O
watch	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
shop	O
for	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
fitting	O
,	O
something	O
that	O
seemed	O
considerable	O
bulky	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
putting	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
drawing	O
nearer	O
,	O
she	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
gown	O
next	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
covered	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
my	O
passing	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
printed	O
cotton	O
;	O
about	O
eight	O
inches	O
of	O
the	O
selvidge	O
lay	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
uncovered	O
at	O
her	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
;	O
the	O
piece	O
was	O
folded	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
behind	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
her	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
book	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
pen	O
made	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
writing	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
observed	O
she	O
kept	O
drawing	O
it	O
up	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
sensible	O
she	O
had	O
drawn	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
forwards	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
people	O
of	O
mine	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
to	O
prevent	O
what	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
going	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
away	O
they	O
should	O
follow	O
her	O
and	O
bring	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
cotton	O
hang	O
down	O
below	O
her	O
coats	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
yards	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
people	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Maycomb	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Boston	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
They	O
carried	O
her	O
backwards	O
;	O
a	O
mob	O
gathered	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
as	O
she	O
stood	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
searched	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
lawn	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
;	O
both	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Eyres	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
used	O
our	O
shop	O
for	O
six	O
months	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
lawns	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
;	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
6	O
s.	O
per	O
yard	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
lawn	O
or	O
printed	O
cotton	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
on	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
and	O
lawn	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
Mr.	O
Eyres	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
cotton	O
is	O
worth	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
lawn	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
printer	O
's	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Boston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Eyres	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
remember	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Saturday	O
September	O
21	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Eyres	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
cotton	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
forward	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
hang	O
down	O
,	O
it	O
dragged	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Eyres	O
had	O
described	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Maycomb	O
to	O
follow	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
far	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
placed	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Maycomb	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
he	O
stooped	O
down	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
which	O
she	O
let	O
fall	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
fall	O
?	O
Boston	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
we	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
the	O
initial	O
letter	O
of	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
initial	O
and	O
final	O
letters	O
of	O
my	O
surname	O
upon	O
the	O
cotton	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
she	O
complained	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
a	O
stool	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
wrote	O
my	O
name	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
pencil	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
hardly	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
now	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Newcomb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Eyres	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
times	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
hang	O
down	O
below	O
her	O
clothes	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
buying	O
the	O
lawn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
then	O
?	O
Maycomb	O
.	O
We	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
lawn	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
above	O
20	O
yards	O
before	O
we	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
placed	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
let	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
cotton	O
fall	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
petticoat	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
wrote	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Eyres	O
's	O
cotton	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
that	O
forenoon	O
from	O
the	O
printer	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
do	O
so	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
much	O
affrighted	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
searched	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
the	O
lawn	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
gown	O
or	O
petticoat	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
lawn	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Eyres	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
upon	O
a	O
stool	O
,	O
complaining	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
mind	O
to	O
get	O
from	O
the	O
stool	O
;	O
I	O
lifted	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
something	O
soft	O
tucked	O
under	O
her	O
stays	O
behind	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
up	O
under	O
a	O
petticoat	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
;	O
I	O
wrote	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
cotton	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
Number	O
125	O
.	O
572	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Lawrence	B-pers
M	I-pers
Duff	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
bearing	O
date	O
July	O
24	O
,	O
1750	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
34	O
l.	O
by	O
which	O
note	O
the	O
said	O
Lawrence	O
did	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
Effee	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
now	O
Effee	B-pers
Jefferies	I-pers
,	O
upon	O
demand	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
then	O
unsatisfied	O
,	O
for	O
Feb.	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
573	O
,	O
574	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
Weston	B-pers
Rakes	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
of	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
penknife	O
,	O
value	O
a	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
September	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Hatton	B-place
Garden	I-place
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
September	O
15	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
quarter	O
of	O
Hatton	O
Garden	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
I	O
was	O
collared	O
by	O
two	O
persons	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
expression	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
deliver	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
Weston	B-pers
Rakes	I-pers
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
first	O
;	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
pockets	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
and	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
from	O
another	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
lancets	O
and	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
request	O
,	O
Rakes	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
lancets	O
and	O
keys	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
must	O
change	O
hats	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
Rakes	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
penknife	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
lost	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
was	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
lamp	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
me	O
;	O
Rakes	O
faced	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
pointed	O
at	O
Rakes	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
both	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
confession	O
put	O
in	O
writing	O
?	O
