TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
26th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
CRISP	O
GASCOYNE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
,	O
1752	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
CRISP	O
GASCOYNE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
*	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
CLIVE	I-pers
+	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
LEGGE	O
||	O
,	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
++	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Hopley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Malcot	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Piggot	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Summerset	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burkett	I-pers
,	O
Jos	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Healey	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Blundall	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bagnall	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Greening	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jumard	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Speers	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cubbidge	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Dudley	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Wyatt	I-pers
.	O
1	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Edward	I-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
and	O
woollen	O
curtains	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
sender	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
stew-pan	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
Edward	O
and	O
Sarah	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Nov.	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
husband	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
find	O
him	O
:	O
They	O
were	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
from	O
April	O
till	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
one-pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
2	O
s.	O
per	O
week	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
furnish	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
went	O
to	O
gather	O
elder	O
berries	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
'd	O
pay	O
me	O
on	O
their	O
return	O
;	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
left	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
room-door	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
Every	O
thing	O
was	O
gone	O
except	O
the	O
chairs	O
,	O
table	O
and	O
bedstead	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
brass	O
sender	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
stew-pan	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
bolster	O
,	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
curtains	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Pearcy	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
stew	O
pan	O
and	O
brass	O
sender	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
curtains	O
,	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
one	O
quilt	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
.	O
These	O
goods	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
Question	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
had	O
my	O
key	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
?	O
M.	O
Howard	O
.	O
None	O
but	O
her	O
own	O
daughter	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
upon	O
my	O
giving	O
you	O
10	O
s	O
?	O
M	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
indeed	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pearcy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
was	O
in	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
in	O
September	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Pearcy	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
as	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
goods	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
produc	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutrix	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
upon	O
my	O
promising	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
10	O
s.	O
but	O
having	O
a	O
from	O
a	O
tree	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
the	O
berries	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
places	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
harnesses	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Long-Acre	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
Coachmaker	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
chariot	O
harnesses	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
having	O
seen	O
them	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
a	O
horse	O
in	O
a	O
hackney-coach	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Flin	I-pers
,	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Flin	I-pers
came	O
and	O
said	O
before	O
justice	O
Cox	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
The	O
justice	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
return	O
the	O
harnesses	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
the	O
best	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
man	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
.	O
One	O
harness	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
had	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Flin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
hackney-coach	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
harness	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dickerson	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dickerson	O
valued	O
it	O
at	O
15	O
s.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
a	O
coachman	O
.	O
William	O
Dickerson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Coachmaker	O
,	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
harness	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
;	O
I	O
hung	O
it	O
up	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
valued	O
it	O
at	O
three	O
crowns	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Cross-Keys	O
in	O
Gracechurch	O
Street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
another	O
man	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
16	O
s.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
business	O
near	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
Gate	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
harness	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
inquir	O
'd	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
then	O
in	O
Bloomsbury-Square	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
William	B-pers
Flin	I-pers
wanted	O
such	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dickerson	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
that	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Johnson	O
stay	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Lane-End	O
the	O
while	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
14	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
16	O
s.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
once	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
but	O
once	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
not	O
surrendering	O
himself	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Order	O
in	O
council	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
produced	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
issues	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
4	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dust	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lockhart	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
October	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Lockhart	O
Gordon	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
or	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Bedford-Head	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
and	O
walking	O
under	O
the	O
piazzas	O
by	O
myself	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
pull	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
immediately	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
pocket	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
breast	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
turned	O
his	O
body	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
seeing	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
fall	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
He	O
pointed	O
at	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
him	O
that	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
flung	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
ugly	O
fellows	O
about	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
drew	O
my	O
sword	O
,	O
saying	O
I	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
match	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Bedford	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
playhouse	O
guards	O
who	O
were	O
not	O
then	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
this	O
from	O
the	O
Bedford	O
coffee-house	O
?	O
Gordon	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
discern	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
person	O
?	O
Gordon	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
(	O
the	O
lamps	O
being	O
lighted	O
)	O
very	O
light	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
and	O
refused	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
;	O
this	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fresh	O
courage	O
,	O
who	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
abusively	O
saying	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
words	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purport	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
I	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
Gordon	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
touch	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
stand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Gordon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
thro	O
'	O
Covent-Garden	O
piazzas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
ran	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
a	O
great	O
crowd	O
about	O
the	O
gentleman	O
when	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parnel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
blacksmith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
Soho	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
sucked	O
at	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
breast	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
know	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Parnel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
18	O
or	O
19	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
,	O
Hanover-Square	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
15	O
or	O
16	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
Faulcon	O
at	O
Hide-Park-Corner	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
wrong	O
'd	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Millers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
jobbs	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
labourer	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Millers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Penelope	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
George	I-pers
Lister	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
House	I-pers
;	O
one	O
linnen	O
shift	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
one	O
linnen	O
shift	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
two	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
October	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Esther	B-pers
Charlton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ilive	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Nov.	O
24	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
court	O
called	O
Dudley	O
Court	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
purse	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
October	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Lock-and-Key	O
in	O
Hog-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Dudley-Court	B-place
,	O
and	O
had	O
three	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
(	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
in	O
number	O
)	O
.	O
Being	O
lame	O
on	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
undo	O
my	O
purse	O
with	O
my	O
teeth	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
out	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
jumped	O
upon	O
me	O
and	O
clasped	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
neck	O
,	O
da	O
-	O
ng	O
my	O
eyes	O
and	O
limbs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
immediately	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
forcibly	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
no	O
body	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
was	O
near	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
paid	O
your	O
reckoning	O
?	O
Mears	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
immediately	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
constable	O
searched	O
her	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
employment	O
?	O
Mears	O
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
stable	O
near	O
Denmark-Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
your	O
lameness	O
?	O
Mears	O
.	O
It	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
cut	O
on	O
my	O
nuckle	O
,	O
which	O
has	O
been	O
opened	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
times	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harrop	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
High-Street	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
heard	O
t	O
he	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
thief	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
church	O
I	O
made	O
water	O
in	O
the	O
Church-yard	O
against	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
.	O
There	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
purse	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
lost	O
with	O
his	O
money	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
Roundhouse	O
window	O
faces	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
lay	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
his	O
wife	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
loose	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mears	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
or	O
two	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
alley	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
knowing	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
and	O
family	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
shilling	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
cried	O
out	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
revenged	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Milbourne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchmaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Mears	O
before	O
,	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
buying	O
and	O
selling	O
horses	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
yesterday	O
at	O
Hicks's-Hall	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
his	O
business	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
to	O
tuck	O
a	O
bitch	O
up	O
that	O
pox	O
'd	O
me	O
seven	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
declare	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
that	O
man	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
8.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
warrant	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Lascells	O
and	O
Maxwell	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
Pray	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
bearer	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
287	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
place	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
Lascells	O
and	O
Maxwell	O
)	O
and	O
publishing	O
it	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
,	O
Sept.	O
23	O
.	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
9	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Stocker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
15	O
.	O
||	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
depos	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
Richard	B-pers
Airs	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dailey	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
18	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Dailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Eagle-Street	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
the	O
brass	O
pot	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
my	O
next-door	O
neighbour	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
pot	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
just	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
Guilty	O
1	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
See	O
her	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
508.	O
in	O
last	O
paper	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
20	O
.	O
||	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
appeared	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
also	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
swearing	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Isaac	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Arthur	B-pers
Swaine	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
January	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
Arthur	B-pers
Swaine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
of	O
me	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
week	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
last	O
Christmas	O
at	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
there	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
leaving	O
the	O
door	O
locked	O
;	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
clean	O
sheets	O
laid	O
on	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
to	O
take	O
lodgings	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
pretending	O
that	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
before	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
enquired	O
into	O
and	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
knowing	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
detained	O
him	O
on	O
this	O
theft	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
your	O
sheets	O
again	O
?	O
Swaine	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Kent	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
speaks	O
of	O
his	O
sheets	O
being	O
lost	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
crime	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Gloucestershire	O
cheeses	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Curtise	I-pers
,	O
November	O
22	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Curtise	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
view	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
take	O
up	O
two	O
Gloucestershire	O
cheeses	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
cheeses	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Holborn	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
cheeses	O
lying	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
kennel	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Horseman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
rug	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
iron	O
pot	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
November	O
11	O
.	O
||	O
Edward	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Salt	B-place
Peter	I-place
Bank	I-place
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
taking	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
a	O
strange	O
woman	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
pawned	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
in	O
White	O
Lion-Street	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
there	O
by	O
one	O
Susanna	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
in	O
her	O
own	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
?	O
Barret	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
constable	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
goods	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Pratt	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Susanna	O
Whitehead	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buttons	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
October	O
11	O
.	O
||	O
Patrick	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
by	O
eleven	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
neither	O
the	O
prisoner	O
nor	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
poker	O
and	O
a	O
hammer	O
lying	O
by	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
my	O
effects	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buttons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
hands	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
buttons	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
spent	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
buttons	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
ring	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buttons	O
pledged	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Fox	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
so	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
Devil	O
possessed	O
her	O
:	O
My	O
servant	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
Constable	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
owned	O
taking	O
the	O
gold	O
ring	O
and	O
buttons	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
mention	O
the	O
sum	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
A	O
handkerchief	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
rings	O
,	O
buttons	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
were	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
and	O
Wife	O
's	O
initial	O
letters	O
of	O
their	O
names	O
in	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
buttons	O
,	O
S	O
Q	O
P.	O
I	O
fetched	O
Harrison	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
buttons	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
locked	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
buttons	O
.	O
(	O
She	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
buttons	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
my	O
child	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
returned	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
blinded	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
none	O
might	O
see	O
what	O
had	O
been	O
done	O
within	O
:	O
The	O
money	O
and	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
you	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chest	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
all	O
there	O
were	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Newtoner's-Lane	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
there	O
:	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
rent	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
buttons	O
:	O
At	O
first	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
taking	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
d	O
-	O
d.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
;	O
the	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
about	O
her	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
offering	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
hired	O
servant	O
to	O
them	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
demand	O
my	O
wages	O
when	O
my	O
time	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hold	O
my	O
tongue	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
lay	O
me	O
fast	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milkwoman	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
served	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
since	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hodges	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
bread	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
her	O
own	O
father	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
behalf	O
in	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
character	O
stained	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Sarah	I-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
her	O
late	O
husband	O
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
She	O
likewise	O
stood	O
charg	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Urswell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
being	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Oats	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
they	O
lived	O
in	O
King's-Head-Yard	B-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
last	O
lord-mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
drinking	O
in	O
our	O
apartments	O
above	O
both	O
together	O
:	O
She	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
he	O
followed	O
her	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
into	O
their	O
apartment	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
fighting	O
in	O
their	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
part	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
standing	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
pull	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
squatted	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
hearth	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pull	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
sit	O
upon	O
the	O
cold	O
hearth	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
stand	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
brick	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
clapp	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
forehead	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
now	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
frightened	O
;	O
he	O
tied	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
right	O
sober	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
keep	O
it	O
tied	O
up	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
not	O
get	O
cold	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
then	O
into	O
my	O
apartment	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
there	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
very	O
agreeable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
mentioned	O
about	O
the	O
blow	O
above	O
stairs	O
?	O
M.	O
Oats	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
and	O
knew	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
continue	O
at	O
that	O
apartment	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
M.	O
Oats	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
there	O
but	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Infirmary	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Between	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
and	O
Monday	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
M.	O
Oats	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
a	O
day	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
blow	O
struck	O
?	O
M.	O
Oats	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ferrey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
and	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
both	O
in	O
one	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Infirmary	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
flung	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
brick	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
more	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Boare	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
ward	O
to	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
us	O
'd	O
frequently	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
our	O
nurse	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
say	O
his	O
wife	O
did	O
it	O
by	O
slinging	O
a	O
brick	O
.	O
After	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
'd	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
how	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
lord-mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
drinking	O
together	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
grew	O
drowsy	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
her	O
head	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
her	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
she	O
kick	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
private	O
parts	O
,	O
and	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
resented	O
,	O
and	O
words	O
arose	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
godmother	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
part	O
,	O
whereupon	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
brick	O
,	O
flung	O
it	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
struck	O
her	O
?	O
Boare	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
seem	O
friendly	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
?	O
Boare	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
often	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
on	O
Sunday	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Agate	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
lord-mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
fighting	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
man	O
say	O
,	O
Sally	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
peace	O
,	O
be	O
quiet	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
never	O
strike	O
you	O
more	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
dog	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
cut	O
you	O
down	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Kentish	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
London	O
Hospital	O
when	O
the	O
deceas	O
'd	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
wound	O
on	O
his	O
forehead	O
;	O
the	O
bone	O
was	O
bare	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
fractured	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
he	O
became	O
exceeding	O
ill	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
,	O
mi	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
trapann	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
accordingly	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
deceas	O
'd	O
complain	O
'd	O
also	O
of	O
a	O
violent	O
pain	O
in	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
blooded	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
methods	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
to	O
relieve	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
all	O
ineffectual	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
appear	O
'd	O
on	O
your	O
trapanning	O
him	O
?	O
Kentish	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
matter	O
appear	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
opening	O
his	O
head	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
lodg	O
'd	O
under	O
the	O
dura	O
mater	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
matter	O
upon	O
the	O
brain	O
under	O
the	O
forehead	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
brain	O
was	O
mortified	O
:	O
We	O
opened	O
his	O
body	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
inflamation	O
on	O
his	O
stomach	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
liver	O
which	O
lies	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
symptoms	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
appearances	O
of	O
the	O
bod	O
y	O
after	O
dislocation	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
?	O
Kentish	O
.	O
The	O
violent	O
blow	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
the	O
appearance	O
you	O
saw	O
on	O
his	O
stomach	O
might	O
have	O
occasioned	O
his	O
death	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
had	O
that	O
wound	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
?	O
Kentish	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
his	O
death	O
was	O
owing	O
to	O
that	O
blow	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
forehead	O
?	O
Kentish	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
appearances	O
of	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
from	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
meant	O
to	O
do	O
him	O
any	O
ill	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
him	O
any	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Absolam	B-pers
Stennet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
and	O
Berston	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Esqr	O
s.	O
Nov.	O
10	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
laid	O
over	O
again	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
South	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Leonard	O
,	O
widow	O
,	O
upon	O
Richard	B-pers
Hule	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
Dec.	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Hule	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New	O
Cross-street	O
,	O
by	O
Leicester	O
fields	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
a	O
baker	O
:	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Drury-lane	B-place
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
baker	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
customer	O
's	O
maid	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
in	O
Duke	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
she	O
there	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
please	O
to	O
have	O
?	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Plough	O
,	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
you	O
will	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
Mistress	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
have	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
before	O
hand	O
:	O
She	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
knee	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buss	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
push	O
'd	O
her	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
behind	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
by	O
her	O
to	O
catch	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
push	O
'd	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
either	O
with	O
her	O
fast	O
or	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
I	O
want	O
?	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
quite	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
minutes	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
by	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
put	O
in	O
fear	O
?	O
Hule	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
see	O
some	O
men	O
below	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
knock	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
I	O
first	O
see	O
you	O
?	O
Hule	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
a	O
court	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
9	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
it	O
appear	O
I	O
was	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
all	O
that	O
blessed	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Lucy	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
me	O
ill	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
dragg	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Lucy	B-pers
Field	I-pers
The	O
Constable	O
and	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
about	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
several	O
other	O
persons	O
.	O
Acqu	O
.	O
19	O
,	O
20	O
,	O
21	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Redhate	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
loaves	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Goman	I-pers
,	O
November	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
22	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Thrift	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Thomas	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Baker	O
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Shoemaker-Row	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
journeyman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
.	O
Having	O
missed	O
money	O
at	O
times	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
the	O
shop	O
being	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
below	O
in	O
the	O
bakehouse	O
,	O
I	O
concealed	O
myself	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
shop	O
been	O
shut	O
up	O
?	O
M.	O
Jordan	O
.	O
Almost	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
cut	O
himself	O
some	O
victuals	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
hammer	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
raised	O
up	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
till	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
till	O
locked	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
M.	O
Jordan	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
never	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
but	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
out	O
some	O
half-pence	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
shuting	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
he	O
made	O
free	O
with	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
enough	O
;	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
my	O
Pardon	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
10	O
d.	O
all	O
in	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
ever	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jordan	O
:	O
Mistress	O
suspected	O
somebody	O
had	O
been	O
opening	O
her	O
till	O
;	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
concealed	O
ourselves	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bake-house	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
shop	O
)	O
and	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
himself	O
some	O
victuals	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
hammer	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
half-pence	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
Mistress	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
enough	O
;	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
pretty	O
fellow	O
for	O
robbing	O
me	O
?	O
He	O
begged	O
her	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
there	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
halfpence	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
twelve-pence	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
customer	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bake-house	O
door	O
for	O
2	O
quartern	O
loaves	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
half-pence	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
my	O
supper	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Birk	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
thread	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
Nov.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Birk	O
.	O
Last	O
Month	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
on	O
Snow-Hill	B-place
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
Day	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
by	O
the	O
lamps	O
and	O
lights	O
at	O
Windows	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
shoulder	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
countryman	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
my	O
Friends	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
we	O
'll	O
talk	O
the	O
times	O
over	O
when	O
we	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Birk	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
Saracen	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
gateway	I-place
:	O
with	O
great	O
persuasion	O
I	O
did	O
go	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
under	O
the	O
gate-way	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
private	O
part	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
talked	O
such	O
indecent	O
sodomitical	O
language	O
best	O
omitted	O
here	O
)	O
wanting	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
some	O
private	O
place	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
ashamed	O
to	O
offer	O
that	O
brutish	O
action	O
to	O
any	O
mankind	O
?	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
d	O
-	O
able	O
poor	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
surrender	O
that	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
from	O
ear	O
to	O
ear	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
instrument	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
he	O
jabb	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
it	O
struck	O
against	O
my	O
teeth	O
and	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
my	O
head	O
about	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
or	O
it	O
had	O
cut	O
my	O
mouth	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
to	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
got	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
up	O
with	O
some	O
weapon	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
temple	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
another	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
breast	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
that	O
brought	O
blood	O
from	O
me	O
many	O
days	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
his	O
hand	O
at	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
presently	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
pocket	O
half	O
inside	O
out	O
,	O
my	O
purse	O
and	O
7	O
shillings	O
in	O
it	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
also	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
power	O
to	O
get	O
far	O
,	O
but	O
fell	O
down	O
again	O
in	O
my	O
blood	O
:	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
people	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
blood	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
properly	O
,	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
could	O
speak	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Birk	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
some	O
that	O
are	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
charged	O
him	O
?	O
Birk	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
ran	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Birk	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
that	O
same	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
whither	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
done	O
me	O
the	O
mischief	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
also	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
by	O
lord	O
mayor	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
Little	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
person	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
murder	O
!	O
murder	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Fountain	O
tavern	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lay	O
betwixt	O
the	O
post	O
and	O
the	O
house	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
all	O
in	O
gore	O
blood	O
:	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
2	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
seveveral	O
people	O
passing	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
get	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
;	O
we	O
set	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
water	O
and	O
washed	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
he	O
bled	O
from	O
his	O
temple	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
fellow	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
run	O
down	O
Snow	O
hill	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
people	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
hill	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
people	O
bringing	O
him	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
murdered	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
?	O
We	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
countryman	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
knock	O
'd	O
you	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
green	O
apron	O
on	O
,	O
the	O
countryman	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
7	O
shillings	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
and	O
could	O
hardly	O
speak	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
so	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Griffiths	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
Ten	O
Bells	O
facing	O
the	O
Saracen's-Head	O
on	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
person	O
call	O
out	O
murder	O
!	O
murder	O
!	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
mob	O
about	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
that	O
was	O
hurt	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
Fountain	O
tavern	O
.	O
The	O
mob	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
on	O
Snow-Hill	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
Three	O
Bushes	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
both	O
robbed	O
and	O
murdered	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
no	O
matter	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
so	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
wounded	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
did	O
me	O
the	O
injury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
Exchange	O
home	O
down	O
Snow-Hill	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
leading	O
the	O
prisoner	O
along	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
robbed	O
and	O
murdered	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
man	O
were	O
rising	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
wounded	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
Fountain	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
who	O
did	O
him	O
the	O
injury	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
declared	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
in	O
Newgate-Street	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
wanted	O
to	O
rescue	O
him	O
,	O
others	O
declared	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
hold	O
him	O
without	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
asking	O
how	O
we	O
dare	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
more	O
friends	O
than	O
enemies	O
about	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
something	O
tucked	O
into	O
his	O
coat	O
that	O
stood	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
dropped	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
friends	O
I	O
believe	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
lost	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
almost	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Le	O
Grand	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
red	O
and	O
yellow	O
)	O
dropping	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bosom	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
dropped	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
may	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Then	O
some	O
people	O
drove	O
us	O
about	O
as	O
tho	O
'	O
they	O
intended	O
to	O
drive	O
us	O
down	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
about	O
Woodstreet	O
end	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
cry	O
China	O
oranges	O
or	O
lemons	O
,	O
silberts	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
goods	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
without	O
any	O
officer	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
one	O
came	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
I	O
directed	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
persons	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
person	O
there	O
knew	O
him	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wounded	O
man	O
singled	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
amongst	O
about	O
fourteen	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
did	O
him	O
the	O
injury	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
speak	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
24	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susanna	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
mahogany	O
tea	O
chest	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
five	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Musgrove	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Musgrove	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Frying	B-place
Pan	I-place
Alley	I-place
,	I-place
Spital-fields	I-place
,	O
and	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
kitchen	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
last	O
?	O
Musgrove	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
at	O
breakfast	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
word	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
were	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
received	O
intelligence	O
that	O
the	O
tea	O
chest	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
particular	O
account	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Musgrove	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
were	O
that	O
morning	O
safe	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
the	O
tea	O
chest	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
dresser	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
candlesticks	O
on	O
the	O
mantlepiece	O
,	O
the	O
bonnet	O
and	O
apron	O
being	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
twelve	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
tea	O
chest	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
A	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
justice	O
Gore	O
for	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Frances	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
such	O
a	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
chess	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
my	O
apron	O
on	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
tea	O
chest	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
some	O
time	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
October	O
,	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
destitute	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
tea	O
chest	O
to	O
pledge	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
to	O
bring	O
at	O
times	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
things	O
stolen	O
;	O
he	O
mentioned	O
the	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
such	O
one	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
chest	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
secured	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
those	O
things	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lives	O
in	O
Angel	O
Alley	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Farley	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
rug	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
September	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Martha	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
.	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
lodging	O
on	O
her	O
own	O
account	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
lodging	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
away	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
h	O
er	O
again	O
?	O
M.	O
Alexander	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
bed	O
in	O
Hog-Lane	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Herring	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
sheet	O
and	O
the	O
rug	O
.	O
Marphet	O
Allen	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
but	O
of	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Herring	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
one	O
sheet	O
and	O
the	O
rug	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
the	O
sheet	O
was	O
pledged	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rug	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
November	O
by	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Farley	I-pers
,	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
Herring	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
eighteen-pence	O
on	O
the	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
nine-pence	O
on	O
the	O
rug	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Herring	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
cohabited	O
with	O
that	O
man	O
(	O
name	O
William	B-pers
Farley	I-pers
)	O
he	O
beat	O
me	O
very	O
barborously	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
pawned	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
26	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Barbara	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Flinn	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Flinn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Norfolk-Street	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
once	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
behaved	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
sober	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
stole	O
a	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Flinn	O
.	O
She	O
being	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
times	O
with	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
robb	O
'd	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
and	O
there	O
freely	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
one	O
Bibby	O
's	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
who	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Vaughan	O
.	O
I	O
hired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
the	O
lord-mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
discharg	O
'd	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
doing	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
come	O
on	O
Thursday	O
at	O
noon	O
to	O
help	O
the	O
maid	O
dress	O
dinner	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
a	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
laced	O
cap	O
,	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
riding-hood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
shoes	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
cap	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
then	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
desire	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
shoes	O
,	O
petticoat	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rasbridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
pawn	O
'd	O
these	O
shoes	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Black	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
petticoat	O
in	O
pawn	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
there	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
1	O
or	O
4	O
s.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
lodging	O
that	O
sweeps	O
the	O
streets	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
direction	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
miss	O
Vaughan	O
almost	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
paid	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
;	O
and	O
wanting	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
buy	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
27	O
,	O
28	O
,	O
29	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Susanna	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
M'Alla	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Nov.	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
Alexander	O
M'Alla	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Mary	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Globe	O
,	O
between	O
Marygold-Court	O
and	O
Exeter-Change	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Globe	B-place
alehouse	I-place
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
then	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
ask	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
?	O
M'Alla	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mary	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
if	O
she	O
'd	O
drink	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
we	O
only	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
had	O
one	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
drank	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
straitway	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
M'Alla	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Forrister	I-pers
with	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
watch	O
when	O
at	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
directly	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Mary	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
and	O
Susannah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
coming	O
down	O
Marygold-Court	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
that	O
court	O
,	O
Forrister	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
and	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
before	O
justice	O
Lediard	O
.	O
Upon	O
their	O
examination	O
they	O
all	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
committed	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Tothilfields-Bridewell	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
your	O
watch	O
since	O
?	O
M'Alla	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
it	O
twice	O
;	O
nor	O
can	O
I	O
charge	O
it	O
upon	O
any	O
particular	O
person	O
.	O
Upon	O
their	O
second	O
examination	O
Mary	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
told	O
the	O
justice	O
she	O
saw	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
take	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
string	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
with	O
it	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
any	O
body	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
?	O
M'Alla	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Forrister	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
out	O
his	O
watch	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
horses	O
in	O
Marygold	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
M'Daniel	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Globe	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
round	O
him	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
two	O
minutes	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
about	O
four	O
minutes	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
secured	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
M'Daniel	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
their	O
second	O
examination	O
Mary	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
said	O
she	O
saw	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
take	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
string	O
and	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
as	O
to	O
herself	O
?	O
Forrister	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Dawson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
walking	O
towards	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
pretty	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
main	O
force	O
he	O
dragg	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
Girls	O
followed	O
us	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
;	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hannah	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
||	O
Hannah	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Brentford	B-place
;	O
on	O
May	O
the	O
3d	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
washing	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
night	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
fallen	O
up	O
my	O
windows	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
iron-pin	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
key	O
within-side	O
;	O
so	O
fastened	O
the	O
window	O
up	O
with	O
an	O
awl-tack	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
leather	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
door	O
and	O
one	O
window	O
;	O
my	O
journeyman	O
got	O
up	O
first	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
(	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
translator	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
translates	O
old	O
shoes	O
for	O
me	O
)	O
he	O
found	O
my	O
window-shutter	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
pumps	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
's	O
kitt	O
was	O
intirely	O
gone	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
second	O
hand	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
inquired	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
pumps	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
10	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
sold	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
17	O
d.	O
My	O
journeyman	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
work	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
translated	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquour	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
shoes	O
out	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
pin	O
to	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
iron	O
pin	O
,	O
or	O
much	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lives	O
;	O
with	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
another	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
of	O
mine	O
on	O
his	O
feet	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
journeyman	O
that	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
prosecutor	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
wanted	O
money	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
with	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
shoes	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
travels	O
about	O
and	O
is	O
since	O
gone	O
away	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
journeyman	O
brought	O
the	O
shoes	O
to	O
my	O
son	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
my	O
son	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
journeyman	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
away	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
he	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
at	O
night	O
?	O
M.	O
More	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
seeking	O
after	O
work	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sister	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
betwixt	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
servant	O
came	O
with	O
shoes	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
recollect	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
?	O
E.	O
More	O
.	O
Because	O
it	O
was	O
Brentford	O
fair	O
day	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
afterwards	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
31	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Slow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Nov	O
.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
then	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
purse	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
one	O
leather	O
pocket	O
,	O
two	O
two-guinea	O
pieces	O
,	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
one	O
moidore	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
pounds	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
++	O
Samuel	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
breeches-maker	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Long-lane	B-place
near	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
;	O
last	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
the	O
partition	O
that	O
comes	O
into	O
a	O
closet	O
,	O
which	O
closet	O
opens	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
through	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
house	O
joins	O
to	O
mine	O
,	O
the	O
hole	O
was	O
broke	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
pannel	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
two	O
boards	O
split	O
in	O
two	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
in	O
length	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lath	O
and	O
plaister	O
was	O
broke	O
through	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
might	O
with	O
case	O
get	O
through	O
:	O
all	O
was	O
safe	O
and	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
drawers	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
purses	O
and	O
pocket	O
and	O
money	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
20	O
l.	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
two-guinea	O
pieces	O
,	O
two	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
one	O
moidore	O
,	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
six	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
silver	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
leather	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
pocket	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
particular	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
gold	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
green	O
purse	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
gold	O
in	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
lay	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
middle	O
drawer	O
in	O
my	O
chamber	O
where	O
I	O
lie	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
:	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Slow	O
's	O
wife	O
was	O
knocking	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
almost	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
the	O
neighbour	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
him	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
believe	O
your	O
husband	O
is	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
perhaps	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
shew	O
;	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Slow	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
bye	O
and	O
bye	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
shut	O
my	O
windows	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
awake	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
?	O
Becket	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Becket	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
noise	O
above	O
stairs	O
?	O
Becket	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
apartment	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
pretending	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pannel	O
loose	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
fasten	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
My	O
closet	O
is	O
a	O
longish	O
dark	O
place	O
:	O
He	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
examined	O
it	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
the	O
pannel	O
fastens	O
on	O
his	O
side	O
and	O
not	O
on	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
last	O
?	O
Becket	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
through	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
broke	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
Becket	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
into	O
the	O
affair	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
lodged	O
in	O
his	O
garret	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
lodger	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
broke	O
their	O
house	O
into	O
mine	O
to-day	O
?	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
nobody	O
but	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
lodger	O
in	O
my	O
garret	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
afterwards	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
flush	O
of	O
money	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
fetched	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
searched	O
and	O
found	O
both	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
the	O
leather	O
pocket	O
which	O
had	O
my	O
silver	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
were	O
found	O
?	O
Becket	O
.	O
Silver	O
and	O
gold	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
the	O
house	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
where	O
you	O
found	O
that	O
pocket	O
?	O
Becket	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
made	O
doors	O
from	O
one	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
room	O
is	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
backside	O
your	O
closet	O
?	O
Becket	O
.	O
He	O
keeps	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
hands	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
description	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
of	O
this	O
pocket	O
to	O
persons	O
you	O
talked	O
with	O
?	O
Becket	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
coarse	O
in	O
the	O
grain	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
off	O
so	O
clean	O
as	O
sometimes	O
leather	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
side	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
speck	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
grain	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
pick	O
it	O
out	O
from	O
a	O
hundred	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
you	O
knew	O
it	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
stitched	O
with	O
yellow	O
silk	O
?	O
Becket	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
's	O
a	O
place	O
looks	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
stitched	O
with	O
yellow	O
silk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
any	O
body	O
it	O
was	O
stitched	O
with	O
yellow	O
silk	O
?	O
Becket	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Becket	O
missed	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
20	O
l.	O
he	O
lighted	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
my	O
money	O
is	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
house	O
is	O
broke	O
out	O
into	O
Slow	O
's	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
closet	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
hole	O
big	O
enough	O
for	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
in	O
the	O
pannel	O
out	O
of	O
Slow	O
's	O
passage	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
closet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
plaister	O
wall	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
plaister	O
wall	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
only	O
wainscot	O
or	O
boards	O
nailed	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Slow	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
found	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
he	O
came	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
notion	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
ready	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
was	O
secure	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
search-warrant	O
was	O
got	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
left	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
walked	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
passed	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
me	O
,	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
rattling	O
of	O
money	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
surprizing	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
robbed	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
came	O
the	O
officer	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Becket	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
below	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Greenwood	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
linnen	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Becket	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
or	O
less	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
that	O
leather	O
pocket	O
and	O
tossed	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Becket	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
pocket	O
in	O
which	O
my	O
silver	O
was	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-House	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
hearing	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
walked	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
you	O
better	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
running	O
a	O
great	O
hazard	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
make	O
Mr.	O
Becket	O
easy	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
doubtless	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
is	O
embezzled	O
away	O
,	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
remainder	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
suppose	O
I	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
the	O
remainder	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
my	O
character	O
is	O
blasted	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
he	O
hang	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
conversation	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Mansion-House	O
before	O
we	O
appeared	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
this	O
conversation	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
none	O
by	O
but	O
he	O
and	O
I.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wood-Street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
breeches-maker	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
pocket	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
he	O
call	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
?	O
Newton	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
desire	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
that	O
a	O
pocket	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
proof	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
pocket	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Becket	O
appeared	O
before	O
Sir	O
George	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
for	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
being	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
looked	O
among	O
some	O
rubbish	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
trunk	O
all	O
rags	O
and	O
very	O
ordinary	O
stuff	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
little	O
linnen	O
bag	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
knees	O
,	O
so	O
sent	O
it	O
out	O
by	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
looked	O
farther	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
leather	O
pocket	O
in	O
that	O
trunk	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Becket	O
directly	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
many	O
years	O
to	O
keep	O
his	O
money	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
silk	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
mention	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
silk	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
place	O
that	O
he	O
meant	O
was	O
a	O
stain	O
in	O
the	O
grain	O
of	O
the	O
leather	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Becket	O
's	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
black	O
breeches	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
fetched	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
pockets	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
Slow	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
quandary	O
.	O
Q.	O
Amongst	O
whose	O
things	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
pocket	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
Amongst	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Greenwood	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
pocket	O
has	O
got	O
yellow	O
stitches	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
stitch	O
'd	O
with	O
stuff	O
of	O
any	O
colour	O
?	O
At	O
last	O
Mr.	O
Nash	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
crease	O
;	O
then	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Becket	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
place	O
I	O
meant	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
a	O
flutter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
lengthened	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
consider	O
better	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
how	O
the	O
thing	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ripshaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
Taylor	O
:	O
I	O
remember	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
pocket	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
was	O
a	O
Twelvemonth	O
:	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
angry	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
two	O
pockets	O
would	O
be	O
sufficient	O
to	O
hold	O
his	O
money	O
and	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
pocket	O
again	O
?	O
Ripshaw	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
:	O
There	O
is	O
not	O
an	O
honester	O
man	O
in	O
London	O
than	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Seagood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
descriptions	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
for	O
knowing	O
the	O
pocket	O
,	O
was	O
by	O
yellow	O
stitches	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goodness	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Seagood	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
;	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Langford	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
many	O
sums	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Langford	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
ever	O
was	O
born	O
down	O
to	O
this	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
he	O
worked	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Langford	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jordan	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
last	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
Christendom	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
opportunities	O
to	O
defraud	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
apprentices	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
sometimes	O
a	O
corner	O
,	O
or	O
circle	O
too	O
many	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
your	O
boy	O
has	O
given	O
me	O
this	O
too	O
much	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
clock-engraver	O
.	O
Mandevile	O
Sinnersal	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
nor	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
32.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gall	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Gall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
back	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
laid	O
a	O
plate	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
dresser	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
Gower	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
taken	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
John	O
Bamfield	O
,	O
a	O
pewterer	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
:	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
33	O
,	O
34	O
,	O
35	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Aubery	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Maddor	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
three	O
loaves	O
of	O
bread	O
value	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
slice	O
of	O
gingerbread	O
value	O
one-penny	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Rebecca	O
did	O
steal	O
.	O
+	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Lowe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Chelsea	B-place
parish	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
Chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
shut	O
up	O
my	O
shop	O
as	O
usual	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
awak	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
noise	O
:	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
cat	O
making	O
a	O
rummaging	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
should	O
fly	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
again	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
window	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
loaf	O
of	O
bread	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
loaves	O
of	O
bread	O
and	O
some	O
ginger-bread	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
some	O
other	O
affair	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
notice	O
they	O
had	O
confessed	O
this	O
fact	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Tothilfields	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
Watson	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
Barker	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
confessed	O
this	O
fact	O
;	O
Barker	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
my	O
glass	O
window	O
with	O
his	O
elbow	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Midhurst	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Barker	O
and	O
Aubery	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
apprehended	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Watson	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
Burker	O
and	O
Aubery	O
had	O
first	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
but	O
through	O
mistake	O
broke	O
open	O
her	O
shop	O
.	O
They	O
confessed	O
they	O
twisted	O
the	O
pin	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
about	O
till	O
the	O
key	O
fell	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
broke	O
the	O
glass	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
loaves	O
and	O
one	O
slice	O
of	O
gingerbread	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
shop	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
?	O
Midhurst	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cloaths-shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
known	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
?	O
Midhurst	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
Barker	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
Midhurst	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
13	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
under-turnkey	O
to	O
Tothilfields	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
when	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
evidence	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
our	O
place	O
,	O
Aubery	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
their	O
breaking	O
this	O
shop	O
open	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
four	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
prisoners	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Pen	O
Burnet	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
intended	O
to	O
rob	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths-shop	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Jews-Row	O
,	O
by	O
Chelsea	O
college	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
happen	O
'd	O
on	O
this	O
chandler's-shop	O
;	O
Barker	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
pin	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
it	O
about	O
till	O
the	O
key	O
fell	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
glass	O
with	O
his	O
elbow	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
loaves	O
and	O
gingerbread	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
said	O
.	O
Maddox	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
now	O
;	O
Barker	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
by	O
many	O
people	O
his	O
age	O
,	O
they	O
wondering	O
that	O
so	O
little	O
a	O
lad	O
as	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
such	O
an	O
attempt	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
above	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
three	O
prisoners	O
,	O
Thomas	O
Pen	O
Burnet	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
in	O
the	O
Ambery	O
beyond	O
Tothilfields	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
till	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
resolution	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
we	O
met	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Willow-Walk	O
and	O
met	O
no	O
body	O
that	O
we	O
thought	O
would	O
be	O
for	O
our	O
advantage	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
where	O
this	O
woman	O
lives	O
,	O
but	O
our	O
intention	O
was	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Midhurst	O
,	O
because	O
Pen	O
Burnet	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
mistake	O
and	O
broke	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Lowe	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
the	O
pin	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
dropp	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
window-shutter	O
,	O
and	O
Barker	O
broke	O
the	O
window	O
with	O
his	O
elbow	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
twopenny	O
loaf	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
gingerbread	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
got	O
out	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
roll	O
'd	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Road	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
resolution	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
we	O
met	O
,	O
but	O
met	O
none	O
that	O
suited	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Pen	O
Burnet	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
Barker	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
joyner	O
,	O
Aubery	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
labouring-work	O
,	O
Madox	O
is	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
Barker	O
lives	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
come	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Barker	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
being	O
acquainted	O
with	O
some	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
ship	O
in	O
Broadway	O
.	O
Aubery	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Burker	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
evidence	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
gone	O
along	O
the	O
streets	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Maddox	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
brought	O
here	O
unawares	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
Barker	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
own	O
mother	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
13	O
years	O
old	O
next	O
June	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
these	O
lads	O
have	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
willing	O
to	O
save	O
any	O
body	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
will	O
be	O
13	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
next	O
June	O
;	O
my	O
mother	O
sending	O
him	O
out	O
for	O
sugar	O
and	O
butter	O
for	O
breakfast	O
.	O
with	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
he	O
unfortunately	O
met	O
with	O
these	O
boys	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Aubery	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
,	O
Barker	O
and	O
Madox	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
36	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Holland	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
;	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
November	O
21	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Red	B-place
Lion	I-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Theobald	I-place
's	I-place
Row	I-place
,	O
and	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
wash	O
'd	O
for	O
family	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
servant	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
how-do-you	O
do	O
,	O
yesterday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
,	O
which	O
day	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
shirt	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
James	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
.	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
body	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
