TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
26th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1752	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Robert	B-pers
Alsop	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1752	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
ROBERT	O
ALSOP	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
PARKER	O
*	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
FOSTER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BIRCH	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
||	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Squire	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Heavieside	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
Alexander	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wildman	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Anson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Case	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boulter	I-pers
,	O
Job	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Waker	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Deschamps	I-pers
,	O
*	O
John	O
Deschamps	O
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Moren	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
his	O
stead	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huddle	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boorsher	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Manvell	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Landwith	I-pers
.	O
321	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
160	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
val	O
12	O
s.	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
dwelling	O
house	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Earl	B-pers
of	I-pers
Thanet	I-pers
,	O
June	O
18	O
,	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shirman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
Earl	O
of	O
Thanet	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
the	O
middle	B-place
of	I-place
Cow-lane	I-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
Ralph	B-pers
Boz	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
about	O
3	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
last	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
unlocked	O
the	O
door	O
it	O
was	O
bolted	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
within	O
side	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
got	O
a	O
ladder	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
five	O
parcels	O
of	O
lead	O
rolled	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
162	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
Tools	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
lead	O
and	O
compared	O
,	O
which	O
fitted	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
fresh	O
cut	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Box	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Beadle	O
,	O
Jenkins	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
at	O
almost	O
3	O
o'clock	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
head	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
at	O
the	O
empty	O
house	O
before	O
mentioned	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
up	O
Mr.	O
Shirman	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
witness	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Cow-lane	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
beat	O
my	O
rounds	O
on	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
.	O
coming	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
stand	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
2	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
,	O
turning	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
court	O
,	O
there	O
stood	O
a	O
Man	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
a	O
cellar	O
window	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
come-up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
pushed	O
off	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
head	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
drawed	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
a	O
knock	O
at	O
you	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Man	O
that	O
ran	O
away	O
came	O
there	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
brewer	O
's	O
servant	O
found	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
compared	O
also	O
and	O
fitted	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
322	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Incledon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
chintz	O
curtains	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
one	O
quilt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Utteridge	I-pers
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Utteridge	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
four	O
nights	O
.	O
The	O
sixth	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
rope	O
was	O
found	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
room	O
windov	O
,	O
fastened	O
to	O
it	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
maid	O
lock	O
his	O
chamber	O
door	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
unlocked	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
met	O
with	O
your	O
goods	O
again	O
?	O
Utteridge	O
.	O
No	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Read	I-pers
.	O
I	O
unlocked	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
a	O
quarer	O
before	O
five	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cord	O
fastened	O
to	O
a	O
stape	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
like	O
a	O
ladder	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
missing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lain	O
at	O
that	O
inn	O
at	O
Hammersmith	B-place
where	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
lives	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
paid	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
This	O
time	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
323	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Alien	I-pers
burglariously	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
4	O
silver	O
watches	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
hilted	O
hanger	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
salt	O
,	O
2	O
silver	O
teaspoons	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Alien	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
shop	O
shut	O
up	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
about	O
four	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
shutter	O
had	O
a	O
hole	O
cut	O
in	O
it	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
a	O
hand	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
fastened	O
with	O
two	O
iron	O
pins	O
within	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
four	O
silver	O
watches	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
a	O
shagreen	O
outside	O
case	O
,	O
a	O
hanger	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
salt	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
last	O
?	O
Alien	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
over	O
night	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
they	O
hung	O
on	O
small	O
hooks	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
twice	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
some	O
body	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
going	O
to	O
shut	O
it	O
there	O
lay	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
dial	O
plates	O
to	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
watches	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
,	O
having	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Alien	O
.	O
One	O
Mr.	O
Philipson	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
some	O
other	O
account	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
before	O
Justice	O
Chamberlaine	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
these	O
plates	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
cut	O
the	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
salt	O
had	O
a	O
crest	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
reason	O
he	O
beat	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
silver	O
hilt	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Philipson	I-pers
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
New-prison	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
try	O
to	O
get	O
Justice	O
Chamberlaine	O
to	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
watches	O
in	O
Grubstreet	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
the	O
Justice	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
New-prison	O
and	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
watches	O
were	O
pawned	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
keeper	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Belomey	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
shagreen	O
watch	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
for	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
He	O
brought	O
the	O
watch	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
in	O
another	O
name	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
also	O
produced	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
told	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
open	O
a	O
shop	O
and	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
satisfied	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alien	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
his	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
goods	O
he	O
lost	O
could	O
he	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
2	O
:	O
watches	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Alien	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
once	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
hole	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
discover	O
it	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Belomey	I-pers
the	O
pawnbroker	O
confirmed	O
that	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
two	O
watches	O
in	O
pawn	O
at	O
two	O
different	O
times	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
delivering	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
persons	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
prison	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
such	O
things	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
either	O
hanged	O
or	O
transported	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
watches	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
by	O
the	O
advertisement	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
evidence	O
against	O
another	O
young	O
lad	O
:	O
I	O
cleared	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
two	O
watches	O
in	O
Spittlefield	O
's	O
market	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
Indictments	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
324	O
,	O
325	O
,	O
326	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Signal	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Catharine	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
George	B-pers
Derby	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
third	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
silver	O
buckles	O
and	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Derby	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Ratcliff	B-place
highway	I-place
on	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
June	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
three	O
men	O
attacked	O
me	O
,	O
swearing	O
,	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
what	O
arms	O
they	O
had	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
some	O
loose	O
silver	O
,	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
India	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
complained	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
it	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
ears	O
of	O
the	O
thief	O
catchers	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
nights	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
's	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Randolph	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Signal	O
said	O
Branch	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
by	O
two	O
corners	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
tore	O
it	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
buckles	O
were	O
pawned	O
near	O
the	O
May-pole	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
he	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
said	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
(	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
)	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
my	O
buckles	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
his	O
buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
such	O
words	O
spoke	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taking	O
them	O
?	O
Derby	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
.	O
Randolph	B-pers
Branch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
commit	O
street	O
robberies	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
this	O
gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Bridges	O
Square	O
,	O
Ratcliff	O
highway	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Derby	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Branch	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
no	O
arms	O
,	O
only	O
Signal	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
penknife	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
36	O
s.	O
piece	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
silver	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
gentleman	O
mentions	O
.	O
Signal	O
took	O
the	O
buckles	O
from	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
Ward	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
to	O
Signal	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
equally	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Signal	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
my	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
Catharine	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
Ward	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Branch	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
nothing	O
,	O
we	O
cheated	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
part	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
buckles	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
company	O
with	O
Signal	O
.	O
Signal	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
Branch	O
.	O
She	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
doesall	O
hours	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
what	O
we	O
went	O
about	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
we	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
heard	O
us	O
talk	O
how	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Signal	O
.	O
That	O
evidence	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
474	O
in	O
Blachford	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
25	O
in	O
Cokayne	O
's	O
mayoralties	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
the	O
buckles	O
my	O
self	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
is	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Branch	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
transport	O
her	O
and	O
hang	O
me	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Waringer	I-pers
,	O
clerk	O
to	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
confession	O
of	O
Signal	O
and	O
Ward	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Ward	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
but	O
one	O
robbery	O
besides	O
that	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
confirmed	O
that	O
of	O
their	O
confession	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	O
.	O
Neither	O
of	O
the	O
evidences	O
heard	O
any	O
confession	O
from	O
Catharine	O
Hart	O
.	O
Signal	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
only	O
my	O
wife	O
know	O
:	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Ward	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
and	O
light	O
of	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
his	O
fellow	O
prisoner	O
)	O
then	O
we	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
out	O
late	O
drinking	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
along	O
Ratcliff	O
highway	O
,	O
Branch	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
genteman	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
stoop	O
down	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
for	O
Christ	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
n't	O
take	O
his	O
buckles	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
Hart	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Signal	O
.	O
Hart	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Signal	O
and	O
Ward	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
327	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Hoult	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
persons	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
20	O
,	O
at	O
Horsey	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
county	I-place
of	I-place
Norfolk	I-place
,	O
being	O
armed	O
with	O
fire-arms	O
and	O
other	O
offensive	O
weapons	O
,	O
did	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
riotously	O
assemble	O
together	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
running	O
and	O
landing	O
uncustomed	O
goods	O
;	O
and	O
goods	O
liable	O
to	O
pay	O
duty	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
paid	O
or	O
secured	O
,	O
March	O
11	O
,	O
1646-7	O
+	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lindow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
at	O
Horsey	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Norfolk	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Royal	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1746	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
house	O
frequented	O
by	O
smugglers	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
that	O
year	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
20	O
or	O
upwards	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
chief	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
armed	O
;	O
they	O
staid	O
till	O
11	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
when	O
word	O
was	O
brought	O
that	O
the	O
cutter	O
was	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
among	O
them	O
?	O
Lindow	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
among	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
quartered	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Pearse	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
another	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
smugglers	O
resorted	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Lindow	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
sea	O
side	O
with	O
them	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
coming	O
cross	O
the	O
field	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Pearse	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
down	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
some	O
not	O
so	O
soon	O
.	O
They	O
laid	O
down	O
their	O
arms	O
on	O
the	O
beach	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
boat	O
brought	O
tubs	O
and	O
oilskin	O
bags	O
from	O
a	O
cutter	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
thrown	O
on	O
the	O
shore	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
men	O
loaded	O
their	O
horses	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
tubs	O
were	O
half	O
anchors	O
of	O
brandy	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
one	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
brandy	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
before	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
sea	O
side	O
?	O
Lindow	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
go	O
away	O
loaded	O
towards	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Winterton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
particular	O
circumstance	O
do	O
you	O
recollect	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Lindow	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
it	O
by	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
's	O
coming	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
king	O
's	O
officer	O
.	O
The	O
smugglers	O
flung	O
their	O
pieces	O
about	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
particular	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
whipped	O
him	O
and	O
used	O
him	O
cruelly	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
631	O
in	O
Calvert	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Locket	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Pearse	O
's	O
at	O
Horsey	O
twelve	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
several	O
times	O
among	O
the	O
smugglers	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
1746	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
armed	O
in	O
general	O
with	O
pieces	O
slung	O
across	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
flung	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
towards	O
the	O
sea	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
having	O
an	O
account	O
brought	O
that	O
the	O
cutter	O
was	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
others	O
at	O
Royal	O
's	O
house	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
Horsey	O
from	O
the	O
sea	O
side	O
?	O
Locket	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
distance	O
of	O
time	O
is	O
so	O
long	O
that	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
,	O
or	O
tell	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
499	O
in	O
Cokayne	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
328	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Arlington	I-pers
,	I-pers
commonly	I-pers
known	I-pers
by	I-pers
the	I-pers
name	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Young	I-pers
Papist	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
divers	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
20	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
at	O
Horsey	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
county	I-place
of	I-place
Norfolk	I-place
,	O
did	O
unlawfully	O
and	O
riotously	O
assemble	O
themselves	O
together	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
aiding	O
and	O
assisting	O
in	O
the	O
landing	O
and	O
running	O
uncustomed	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
liable	O
to	O
pay	O
duty	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
paid	O
or	O
secured	O
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
,	O
1746	O
7	O
*	O
The	O
evidences	O
were	O
John	B-pers
Locket	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Lindow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Riol	I-pers
.	O
The	O
latter	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
amongst	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
Lindow	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
no	O
arms	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Locket	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
flung	O
cross	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Pearse	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
sea	O
side	O
for	O
a	O
tub	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
329	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Pere	B-pers
de	I-pers
Bree	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Peter	I-pers
de	I-pers
Bree	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Pere	I-pers
de	I-pers
Bress	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Peter	I-pers
de	I-pers
Bress	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Pere	I-pers
de	I-pers
Permon	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Peter	I-pers
de	I-pers
Permon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
box	O
bound	O
with	O
iron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
70	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Howel	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
May	O
22	O
++	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
Frenchman	B-pers
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
speak	O
English	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
arrived	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
at	O
London	O
from	O
Paris	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Lewis	O
,	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
in	O
Jermyn-street	B-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
leave	O
to	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
that	O
my	O
servants	O
might	O
be	O
of	O
use	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
understanding	O
English	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
70	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
picture	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
trifles	O
in	O
a	O
strong	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
between	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
and	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
for	O
Dorsetshire	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
my	O
box	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
in	O
a	O
pond	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
letters	O
in	O
it	O
directed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
dress	O
a	O
dinner	O
on	O
the	O
prince	O
of	O
Wales	O
's	O
birth-day	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
returned	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
found	O
66	O
guineas	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
else	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
box	O
into	O
the	O
park	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
pond	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
this	O
without	O
your	O
making	O
use	O
of	O
promises	O
or	O
threats	O
?	O
Pitt	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
little	O
or	O
no	O
money	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Howel	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Pitt	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
searched	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
found	O
66	O
guineas	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pitt	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
returned	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
garret	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pitt	O
's	O
room	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
for	O
a	O
hammer	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
pool	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
confess	O
in	O
French	O
or	O
English	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
In	O
French	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
before	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
fob	O
66	O
guineas	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
searched	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
broke	O
the	O
lock	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
box	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
in	O
a	O
pond	O
called	O
the	O
Cow-Pond	O
in	O
the	O
Green-Park	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
an	O
inch	O
and	O
half	O
open	O
,	O
full	O
of	O
water	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
letters	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
and	O
advertised	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
330	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Daniels	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
vierges	O
made	O
of	O
steel	O
and	O
brass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
June	O
5	O
++	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
and	O
sell	O
all	O
manner	O
of	O
tools	O
and	O
materials	O
in	O
the	O
watch	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Newgate-street	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
several	O
times	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
missed	O
some	O
vierges	O
;	O
we	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
laid	O
a	O
trap	O
for	O
him	O
by	O
counting	O
what	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
counted	O
them	O
on	O
his	O
account	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
that	O
number	O
was	O
altered	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
vierges	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
bolted	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
has	O
got	O
some	O
of	O
your	O
vierges	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
chap	O
that	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
gross	O
in	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
denied	O
it	O
boldly	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
dropped	O
down	O
under	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
;	O
that	O
one	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
through	O
which	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
passed	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
which	O
there	O
were	O
15	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Gatford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
vierges	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
by	O
his	O
coming	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
my	O
master	O
vierges	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
them	O
out	O
as	O
usual	O
on	O
a	O
paper	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
chuse	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
height	O
he	O
wanted	O
.	O
Another	O
person	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
that	O
wanted	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
serve	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
paper	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
pour	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
box	O
which	O
he	O
then	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pour	O
some	O
aside	O
and	O
shut	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
bolted	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
called	O
my	O
master	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
counted	O
them	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
dozen	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
counted	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
dozen	O
and	O
eight	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
found	O
15	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
two	O
dropped	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
up	O
just	O
the	O
number	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Topham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
found	O
15	O
vierges	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
two	O
were	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
had	O
he	O
bought	O
&	O
c.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
make	O
vierges	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
once	O
made	O
three	O
dozen	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
having	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
bottom	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
about	O
two	O
dozen	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
over	O
for	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
are	O
them	O
.	O
Welch	O
.	O
Those	O
are	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
making	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
made	O
by	O
one	O
Ward	O
;	O
what	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
are	O
quite	O
of	O
a	O
different	O
sort	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
331	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Tobias	B-pers
Pilgrim	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Tobias	B-pers
Pilgrim	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
chamberlain	O
's	O
office	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
came	O
after	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
as	O
the	O
people	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
marked	O
T.	O
P.	O
James	O
Mills	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
chamberlain	O
's	O
office	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
coming	O
out	O
again	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Pilgrim	O
and	O
I	O
;	O
I	O
,	O
being	O
behind	O
,	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Pilgrim	O
's	O
pocket	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
detected	O
him	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
wanted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pilgrim	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
He	O
insisted	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
people	O
going	O
into	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
thinking	O
to	O
pass	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
there	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
making	O
free	O
several	O
young	O
men	O
.	O
The	O
office	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
cleared	O
;	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
going	O
down	O
stairs	O
there	O
lay	O
a	O
red	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
picked	O
somebody	O
's	O
pocket	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
because	O
a	O
gentleman	O
has	O
lost	O
several	O
bank	O
notes	O
in	O
a	O
pocket	O
book	O
.	O
Then	O
this	O
gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
so	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
before	O
alderman	O
Chitty	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
the	O
man	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Bear-and-Ragged-staff-yard	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
person	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
lived	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
charged	O
with	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
you	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
this	O
witness	O
's	O
character	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
no	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
inquire	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
Hannah	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
inquire	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
name	O
?	O
H.	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
inquire	O
for	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
cooper	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
332	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
cask	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
50	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
rappee	O
snuff	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Devall	I-pers
,	O
April	O
16	O
+	O
As	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
carman	O
,	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
his	O
cart	O
from	O
the	O
custom	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
snuff	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
he	O
rested	O
his	O
cart	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
parcel	O
to	O
another	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
returned	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
cask	O
of	O
snuff	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
who	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
were	O
detected	O
in	O
selling	O
it	O
in	O
Shoemaker	O
Row	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
cask	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
333	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Rock	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barrot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Finch	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
produces	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
paper	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
was	O
writing	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
writing	O
]	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
shewing	O
these	O
stockings	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Tutt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
for	O
some	O
children	O
's	O
apron	O
strings	O
.	O
She	O
bid	O
me	O
half	O
price	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Finch	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
mistrust	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
up	O
that	O
parcel	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
gentleman	O
's	O
shop	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
parcel	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
bundled	O
together	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
gentleman	O
owed	O
me	O
a	O
particular	O
spite	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
this	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
334	O
,	O
335	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Breech	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
from	O
thence	O
six	O
great	O
coats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Michael	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
servant	O
John	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
could	O
only	O
prove	O
the	O
doors	O
were	O
fast	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
missing	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
principal	O
evidence	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
be	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
committed	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
resting	O
singly	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
acquitted	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
336	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Meadows	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Pury	B-pers
Kester	I-pers
did	O
break	O
,	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
out	O
thence	O
four	O
China	O
bowls	O
,	O
one	O
pewter	O
dish	O
;	O
one	O
pewter	O
can	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Pury	O
.	O
++	O
This	O
also	O
resting	O
on	O
the	O
single	O
evidence	O
of	O
Haines	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
337	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Macquin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
,	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wint	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
watch	O
string	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
2	O
silver	O
seals	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wint	I-pers
.	O
As	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
our	O
lodging	O
at	O
Islington	B-place
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
May	O
6	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
attacked	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
sword	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
half	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
second	O
field	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Pullins	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
four	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
by	O
my	O
turning	O
up	O
my	O
coat	O
he	O
saw	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
demanded	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
unwilling	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
My	O
wife	O
pushed	O
forwards	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
thrust	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
his	O
sword	O
against	O
my	O
rib	O
,	O
and	O
fearing	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
went	O
through	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
with	O
both	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
argued	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
soft	O
manner	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
strove	O
to	O
break	O
his	O
sword	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
too	O
much	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
his	O
sword	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
tumbled	O
backwards	O
down	O
the	O
hill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
.	O
He	O
recovered	O
and	O
attacked	O
me	O
again	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
holding	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
his	O
sword	O
towards	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
the	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Walbank	O
.	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
the	O
very	O
day	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Wint	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Martha	B-pers
Wint	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
second	O
field	O
the	O
prisoner	O
passed	O
us	O
and	O
walked	O
briskly	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
afterwards	O
standing	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
rails	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
down	O
his	O
head	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
sword	O
by	O
degrees	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
speak	O
,	O
and	O
pointed	O
his	O
sword	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
breast	O
.	O
I	O
expected	O
nothing	O
but	O
murder	O
.	O
I	O
pushed	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
three	O
fields	O
before	O
I	O
found	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
robbery	O
committed	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
man	O
that	O
stopped	O
us	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Walbank	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
(	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
Saturday	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
watch	O
you	O
lost	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
desire	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Walbank	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Walbank	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
watch	O
that	O
Carrol	O
brought	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Walbank	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Carrol	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
carry	O
above	O
one	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Carrol	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
for	O
whom	O
I	O
work	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
pawned	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
shirts	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
ask	O
three	O
guineas	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
but	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
338	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
leaden	O
pipe	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
cock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jane	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
339	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Adkerson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
upon	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
for	O
slaying	O
Mary	B-pers
Adkerson	I-pers
his	O
wife	O
,	O
June	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
[	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
bed	O
of	O
a	O
fine	O
boy	O
,	O
now	O
living	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
lying-in	O
hospital	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
instant	O
.	O
She	O
complained	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
there	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
kicked	O
and	O
bruised	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
belly	O
and	O
stomach	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
.	O
From	O
these	O
words	O
a	O
suspicion	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
body	O
was	O
opened	O
and	O
inspected	O
by	O
two	O
physicians	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
external	O
or	O
internal	O
appearance	O
of	O
such	O
usage	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
evidences	O
examined	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
died	O
of	O
a	O
fever	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
]	O
340	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Rice	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
Blundel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Trumbel	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
did	O
steal	O
12	O
bushels	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
341	O
,	O
342.	O
Charles	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
human	O
hair	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isabella	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Archibald	B-pers
Glass	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
court	O
granted	O
them	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
their	O
indictment	O
.	O
343	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Bready	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
June	O
24	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
344	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
James	I-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
stuff	O
and	O
silk	O
petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
Dorothy	O
Philips	O
,	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Aug	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
near	O
the	O
Meuse	O
gate	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
pawned	O
the	O
petticoat	O
in	O
Masham	O
street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Horse	O
ferry	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
there	O
now	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
345	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Belcher	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
five	O
shillings	O
June	O
the	O
3d	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Norton	O
.	O
The	O
chaise	O
to	O
the	O
Devises	O
having	O
been	O
robbed	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
it	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
take	O
the	O
thief	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
post	O
chaise	O
,	O
the	O
post	O
boy	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
stopped	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
half	B-place
way	I-place
house	I-place
between	I-place
Knightsbridge	I-place
and	I-place
Kensington	I-place
As	O
we	O
came	O
near	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
driver	O
stop	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
tinderbox	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
directly	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
this	O
minute	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
the	O
tinderbox	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
do	O
n't	O
frighten	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
a	O
trifle	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
give	O
him	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
from	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
a	O
five	O
shilling	O
piece	O
and	O
a	O
dollar	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
the	O
pistol	O
concealed	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
money	O
pretty	O
hard	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
five	O
shilling	O
piece	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
:	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
I	O
snap	O
'd	O
my	O
pistol	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
staggered	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	B-pers
,	I-pers
O	I-pers
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
700	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
took	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
hit	O
him	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
neckcloth	O
off	O
and	O
tied	O
his	O
hands	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
errand	O
I	O
came	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
them	O
a	O
good	O
journey	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
?	O
Norton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
clear	O
morning	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
lives	O
?	O
Norton	O
to	O
the	O
Q.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Witch	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
I	O
take	O
a	O
thief	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Messinger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
post	O
chaise	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Norton	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
at	O
Hide	O
Park	O
Corner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
the	O
highwayman	O
between	O
Knightsbridge	O
and	O
Kensington	O
,	O
we	O
should	O
not	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
coming	O
,	O
get	O
the	O
pistol	O
ready	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
pistol	O
snap	O
.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
lord	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
Norton	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
lose	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
?	O
Messinger	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
pursuit	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cry	O
,	O
O	O
lord	O
,	O
the	O
moment	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
your	O
lordship	O
and	O
the	O
honourable	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
346	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Friendly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
June	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
this	O
horse	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
team	O
for	O
carrying	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
chaldron	O
of	O
coals	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
an	O
Act	O
of	O
parliament	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
produced	O
the	O
act	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
read	O
it	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
driver	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
347	O
,	O
348	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Burgen	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Jeffery	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
300	O
yards	O
of	O
ribband	O
,	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
knives	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
mettle	O
buckles	O
and	O
buttons	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Jeffery	O
.	O
*	O
Jeffery	O
Burton	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Barking	B-place
Dog	I-place
Walk	I-place
near	I-place
Windmill	I-place
Hill	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
locked	O
all	O
my	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
up	O
my	O
shutters	O
by	O
10	O
o'clock	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Burchingall	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
attempt	O
made	O
to	O
break	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
casement	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
was	O
from	O
the	O
roof	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
tiles	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hole	O
made	O
through	O
the	O
ceiling	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
had	O
nothing	O
more	O
to	O
do	O
than	O
open	O
my	O
back	O
door	O
that	O
was	O
bolted	O
with	O
three	O
bolts	O
within	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
300	O
yards	O
of	O
ribband	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
two	O
sheets	O
that	O
we	O
lay	O
in	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pretty	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
buttons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Burgen	I-pers
told	O
me	O
he	O
hid	O
several	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
hay	O
cock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
Lane	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
when	O
you	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Burton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
Between	O
12	O
and	O
one	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
7	O
night	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
Lane	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
pales	O
,	O
Burgen	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
next	O
.	O
Lane	O
took	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
panes	O
of	O
glass	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
got	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
roof	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
Lane	O
got	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
handed	O
the	O
tiles	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
Burgen	O
.	O
Burgen	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
stick	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
handed	O
up	O
to	O
Lane	O
,	O
who	O
punched	O
a	O
hole	O
through	O
the	O
ceiling	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
nothing	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
jump	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
after	O
pulling	O
off	O
my	O
clothes	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
unbolted	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
pales	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
stood	O
and	O
watched	O
,	O
fearing	O
any	O
body	O
should	O
come	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
rifled	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
ribbands	O
and	O
all	O
sorts	O
of	O
hardware	O
,	O
some	O
mettle	O
Buckles	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
knives	O
.	O
Burgen	O
hid	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
hay	O
cock	O
,	O
some	O
were	O
taken	O
upon	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
together	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
.	O
I	O
confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Burgen	O
confessed	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Pinches	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
about	O
6	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Merriot	I-pers
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
heard	O
that	O
a	O
shop	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
thieves	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Black-boy	O
alley	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
all	O
in	O
bed	O
together	O
.	O
We	O
turned	O
up	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
between	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
the	O
tick	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
ribbands	O
and	O
knives	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Are	O
these	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
writing	O
on	O
the	O
paper	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
knives	O
are	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
on	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
roll	O
of	O
ribbands	O
.	O
Pinches	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
evidence	O
to	O
New-prison	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
Burgen	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
wished	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
make	O
some	O
discovery	O
of	O
sheepstealing	O
,	O
besides	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
he	O
had	O
spoke	O
sooner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Merriot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Pinches	O
and	O
others	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Black-boy	O
alley	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
in	O
bed	O
together	O
,	O
we	O
turned	O
up	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
ribbands	O
upon	O
the	O
sacking	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burchingall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
14	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
alone	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Burton	O
's	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
shutters	O
and	O
windows	O
were	O
shut	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
after	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
door	O
opens	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
into	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
through	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
few	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
my	O
going	O
out	O
and	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
.	O
Richard	O
Lane	O
is	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
this	O
bundle	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
well	O
filled	O
with	O
hard-ware	O
)	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
on	O
business	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
inquire	O
for	O
a	O
parcel	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
and	O
white	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
said	O
were	O
ribbands	O
and	O
hardware	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
officer	O
gone	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
I	O
should	O
come	O
into	O
trouble	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
without	O
opening	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
lane	O
beyond	O
Islington	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
bank	O
side	O
among	O
some	O
nettles	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
bundle	O
by	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
that	O
bundle	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
walking	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
air	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
this	O
evidence	O
said	O
she	O
hid	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
hearing	O
a	O
shop	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
they	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Lane	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
I	O
left	O
at	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
.	O
Burgen	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
but	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
light	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Hughes	O
in	O
Golden	O
lane	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
pewter	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
;	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
get	O
over	O
the	O
pales	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
us	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
hosier	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
349	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Osbourne	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
April	O
29	O
.	O
||	O
Acq	O
.	O
350	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Bollard	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Pollard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
not	O
surrendering	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
order	O
in	O
council	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
produced	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
crown	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
the	O
issues	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
351	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Bollard	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Pollard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
not	O
surrendering	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
order	O
in	O
council	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
produced	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
the	O
issues	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
352	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
353	O
,	O
354	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Quinn	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rushbatch	I-pers
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
355	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Notre	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Crook	I-pers
,	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
356	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Calder	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
June	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Pary	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
forty	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
in	O
my	O
boat	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
eight	O
crown	O
parcels	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
in	O
London	O
for	O
Abraham	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
I	O
do	O
business	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
shore	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
halfpence	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
twenty	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
a	O
penny	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Airey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
near	O
Temple	O
bar	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
penny	O
in	O
halfpence	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
done	O
up	O
in	O
two	O
parcels	O
,	O
one	O
had	O
five	O
shillings	O
worth	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
in	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
boat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
357	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
a	O
rape	O
committed	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Catharine	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
,	O
an	O
infant	O
about	O
11	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Renton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
and	O
man-midwife	O
,	O
I	O
served	O
my	O
time	O
in	O
Edinburgh	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
justice	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
Catharine	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
outward	O
lips	O
of	O
her	O
womb	O
somewhat	O
swelled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
skin	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
torn	O
.	O
Upon	O
opening	O
the	O
inward	O
lips	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
inflamed	O
with	O
a	O
laceration	O
and	O
confusion	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
inward	O
lip	O
.	O
There	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
great	O
violence	O
used	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
swear	O
her	O
body	O
was	O
entered	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
venereal	O
disease	O
on	O
her	O
very	O
strong	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Renton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
from	O
a	O
strain	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
examine	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
could	O
not	O
determine	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
venereal	O
disease	O
,	O
though	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
spots	O
on	O
the	O
sore	O
slap	O
of	O
his	O
shirt	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
were	O
from	O
such	O
a	O
disease	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
him	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
certain	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
venereal	O
disease	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
examined	O
upon	O
oath	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
358	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilford	I-pers
,	I-pers
was	I-pers
indicted	I-pers
for	I-pers
the	I-pers
wilful	I-pers
murder	I-pers
of	I-pers
Sarah	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Sarah	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
May	O
25	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Undershill	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Dyer's-street	B-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
crazy	O
;	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Fleet-lane	O
.	O
They	O
left	O
a	O
box	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
soon	O
after	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
17	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
22	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
said	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
ten	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
awaked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
had	O
struck	O
a	O
light	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
bed	O
's	O
feet	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
talk	O
so	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
almost	O
cut	O
her	O
head	O
off	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
lighted	O
a	O
match	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
blood	O
run	O
off	O
his	O
arm	O
to	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
bloody	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
his	O
elbow	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
wife	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
while	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
returned	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
lay	O
his	O
wife	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
with	O
her	O
face	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
near	O
the	O
chimney	O
;	O
her	O
throat	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
her	O
head	O
almost	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bloody	O
knife	O
was	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
quite	O
dead	O
,	O
dressed	O
all	O
but	O
her	O
bodice	O
,	O
cap	O
and	O
apron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
?	O
Undershill	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
?	O
Undershill	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Woods	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
produces	O
a	O
clasp	O
knife	O
all	O
bloody	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
Undershill	O
's	O
door	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
women	O
crying	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
candle	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
Undershill	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
one	O
hand	O
upon	O
her	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
head	O
almost	O
cut	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
knife	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Cooling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
Undershill	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
murder	O
committed	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
his	O
right	O
arm	O
and	O
left	O
knee	O
were	O
both	O
covered	O
with	O
fresh	O
blood	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
killed	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
very	O
willingly	O
die	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
loved	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
knife	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
lying	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
among	O
blood	O
in	O
the	O
condition	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
received	O
sentence	O
immediately	O
to	O
be	O
executed	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
cast	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
)	O
and	O
his	O
body	O
to	O
be	O
dissected	O
and	O
anatomized	O
.	O
Note	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
case	O
after	O
the	O
new	O
act	O
of	O
parliament	O
.	O
359	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Russia	O
drab	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Manners	I-pers
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
360	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Frances	B-pers
Monday	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
place	O
to	O
the	O
jurors	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
June	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
John	O
Hall	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
se'nnight	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
staid	O
late	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
into	O
my	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Grey's-Inn-lane	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Westminster	O
to	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
passing	O
by	O
the	O
new	O
church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
this	O
woman	O
came	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
drink	O
some	O
Dorchester	O
ale	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
the	O
Black	O
Swan	O
between	O
the	O
new	O
church	O
and	O
Exeter	O
Change	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
but	O
one	O
glass	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
some	O
shrub	O
.	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bottle	O
to	O
take	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
three	O
shillings	O
for	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
pulling	O
out	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
another	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
next	B-place
door	I-place
to	I-place
the	I-place
red	I-place
house	I-place
in	I-place
Exeter	I-place
Court	I-place
.	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
four	O
shillings	O
.	O
She	O
seemed	O
to	O
speak	O
as	O
though	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
desire	O
it	O
I	O
only	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
for	O
the	O
conveniency	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
Presently	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
she	O
slapped	O
my	O
face	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
several	O
blows	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
senses	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
will	O
prevent	O
your	O
telling	O
tales	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
affected	O
a	O
hem	O
,	O
calling	O
Dick	O
.	O
She	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
I	O
'll	O
rip	O
your	O
guts	O
out	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
strong	O
as	O
she	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
murdered	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
comply	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
she	O
scrabbled	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
guinea	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
halfpence	O
again	O
for	O
a	O
breakfast	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
still	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
a	O
guinea	O
more	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
by	O
swearing	O
I	O
never	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
or	O
meddle	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
got	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
talked	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
no	O
constable	O
.	O
Then	O
came	O
a	O
beadle	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
offered	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
what	O
he	O
desired	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
'd	O
swear	O
a	O
robbery	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lives	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
voice	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
also	O
heard	O
a	O
man	O
say	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
halfpence	O
;	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
a	O
robbery	O
against	O
you	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
that	O
man	O
in	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
name	O
?	O
M.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
her	O
sirname	O
,	O
her	O
Christian	O
name	O
is	O
Jane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
keeps	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
M.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
lives	O
in	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairwoman	O
and	O
washerwoman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
M.	O
Smith	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
two	O
men	O
and	O
their	O
wives	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
have	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
it	O
is	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
361	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
23s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Court	I-pers
from	O
his	O
person	O
secretly	O
,	O
June	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
his	O
recognisance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
362	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Ballentine	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	O
McCuller	O
,	O
on	O
Mary	O
wife	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
and	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
did	O
ravish	O
and	O
carnally	O
know	O
,	O
May	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
her	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
from	O
near	O
a	O
watch-house	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
lodging-house	B-place
in	I-place
Well-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
two	O
beds	O
;	O
in	O
one	O
lay	O
two	O
women	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
flung	O
her	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
bed	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
resisted	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
all	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
tore	O
her	O
cloaths	O
,	O
kept	O
her	O
daughter	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
M'Culler	O
kept	O
her	O
from	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
call	O
in	O
any	O
assistance	O
for	O
her	O
mother	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
her	O
daughter	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
mother	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
of	O
being	O
only	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
covered	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
cloaths	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
contrivance	O
of	O
one	O
Westwood	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
extort	O
money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
called	O
Oliver	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
watchmen	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
with	O
her	O
which	O
he	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
daughter	O
lying	O
sleeping	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
with	O
their	O
gown	O
tails	O
over	O
their	O
heads	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
That	O
from	O
thence	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
M'Culler	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
and	O
her	O
daughter	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
all	O
four	O
left	O
the	O
watch-house	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
holding	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
exceeding	O
lovingly	O
together	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Patridge	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
in	O
another	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
pulled	O
off	O
her	O
cloaths	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
after	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
bed	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
words	O
in	O
anger	O
passed	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
soul	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
them	O
two	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
,	O
whom	O
her	O
mother	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
sit	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
363	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hammonds	I-pers
,	O
May	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
keeps	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Butcher	B-place
Row	I-place
,	I-place
Temple	I-place
Bar	I-place
;	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
pewter	O
plates	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
plates	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
367	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
79	O
yards	O
of	O
camblet	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
.	O
The	O
said	O
Hall	O
was	O
cast	O
last	O
sessions	O
for	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
reader	O
is	O
referred	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
304	O
in	O
that	O
paper	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
368	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
72	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
called	O
Long	O
Ell	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
by	O
James	O
Hall	O
,	O
convicted	O
for	O
it	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
May	O
14	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
reader	O
is	O
referred	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
304	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
369	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
Newark	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
having	O
married	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
22d	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
majesty	O
's	O
reign	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
for	O
marrying	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
wife	O
being	O
living	O
.	O
No	O
prosecutor	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
370	O
,	O
371	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ezekiel	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Keeling	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Slam	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
united	O
company	O
trading	O
to	O
the	O
East	O
Indies	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
over	O
again	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
over	O
again	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clothworker	O
and	O
set	O
cloth	O
for	O
the	O
East	O
India	O
company	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
my	O
journeymen	O
.	O
The	O
dyer	O
brought	O
the	O
cloth	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
set	O
and	O
dry	O
.	O
The	O
dyer	O
brought	O
in	O
9	O
half	O
pieces	O
of	O
popinger	O
green	O
,	O
about	O
21	O
or	O
22	O
yards	O
each	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
took	O
9	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
nine	O
head	O
ends	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
India	O
house	O
the	O
inspectors	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
popinger	O
green	O
sold	O
for	O
per	O
yard	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
about	O
three	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
others	O
trade	O
in	O
popinger	O
green	O
besides	O
the	O
India	O
company	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
The	O
Turkey	O
company	O
did	O
formerly	O
,	O
but	O
latterly	O
they	O
do	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
have	O
measured	O
pieces	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
found	O
them	O
short	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
evidence	O
Briggs	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
from	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
bred	O
a	O
clothworker	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
of	O
Wakefield	O
in	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
worked	O
at	O
my	O
business	O
in	O
London	O
before	O
last	O
November	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
employed	O
as	O
journeymen	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
some	O
half	O
pieces	O
about	O
six	O
quarters	O
wide	O
,	O
and	O
21	O
or	O
22	O
yards	O
long	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
measured	O
them	O
over	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
length	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
over	O
21	O
yards	O
they	O
tore	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
head	O
end	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
yard	O
taken	O
from	O
each	O
half	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
tore	O
it	O
off	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
Barnes	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
Keeling	O
was	O
assisting	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
thrown	O
together	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
Barnes	O
gave	O
me	O
three	O
yards	O
and	O
Keeling	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
three	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
thing	O
done	O
in	O
all	O
clothworkers	O
shops	O
throughout	O
London	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
their	O
aprons	O
were	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
off	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
were	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
they	O
then	O
being	O
wet	O
,	O
are	O
put	O
upon	O
the	O
tainters	O
,	O
and	O
stretched	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
length	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Must	O
not	O
this	O
stretching	O
be	O
detrimental	O
to	O
the	O
clothes	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
usual	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
,	O
where	O
you	O
have	O
worked	O
before	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
worked	O
in	O
London	O
above	O
six	O
weeks	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
like	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
your	O
three	O
yards	O
?	O
Briggs	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
mine	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
meeting	O
with	O
a	O
Yorkshire	O
man	O
,	O
one	O
Bothman	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
cloth	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
three	O
short	O
yards	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
a	O
fool	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
dye	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
Saxon	O
green	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
might	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
them	O
to	O
dye	O
,	O
which	O
cost	O
me	O
sixteen	O
pence	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
taylor	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
in	O
Shoemaker	O
Row	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
for	O
3	O
half	O
crowns	O
to	O
a	O
piece	O
broker	O
.	O
Barnes	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
knows	O
we	O
have	O
of	O
these	O
popinger	O
greens	O
which	O
come	O
in	O
that	O
are	O
not	O
thirty	O
nine	O
yards	O
long	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
cloths	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
half	O
cloths	O
must	O
run	O
in	O
proportion	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
impossible	O
to	O
pull	O
these	O
from	O
thirty	O
nine	O
to	O
forty	O
eight	O
if	O
we	O
pull	O
them	O
bit	O
by	O
bit	O
.	O
Keeling	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
ask	O
that	O
evidence	O
whether	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
cut	O
any	O
of	O
that	O
cloth	O
?	O
Briggs	O
to	O
the	O
Q	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
aiding	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
holding	O
the	O
cloth	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
wet	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Barnes	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
my	O
master	O
would	O
speak	O
what	O
he	O
knows	O
of	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
discovered	O
any	O
villainy	O
in	O
Barnes	O
,	O
except	O
this	O
.	O
He	O
knows	O
I	O
have	O
threatened	O
him	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
often	O
suspected	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Keeling	O
about	O
17	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Keeling	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
nine	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
For	O
Barnes	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Barnes	O
18	O
or	O
20	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
near	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Barnes	O
these	O
12	O
or	O
14	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
372	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
money	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
June	O
7	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Gravel	I-place
lane	I-place
June	O
7.	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
with	O
his	O
other	O
hand	O
and	O
clapped	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
five	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
unbuttoned	O
the	O
waistbane	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fob	O
pocket	O
a	O
crack	O
'd	O
farthing	O
and	O
a	O
cane	O
head	O
studed	O
with	O
silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Wiseman	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
moon	O
light	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
neither	O
light	O
nor	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Wiseman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
lamps	O
?	O
Wiseman	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
,	O
deliver	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
under	O
my	O
throat	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
deliver	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
deliver	O
your	O
hat	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
let	O
go	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
perhaps	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
felt	O
hat	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
let	O
the	O
poor	O
man	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
felt	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
blood	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Old	O
Gravel	O
lane	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
somebody	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
watchman	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
rob	O
and	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
and	O
inquired	O
for	O
the	O
headborough	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
Betwixt	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
worth	O
of	O
sallop	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
lane	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
by	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
forbear	O
looking	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
others	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
About	O
12	O
at	O
noon	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
by	O
me	O
again	O
in	O
Ratcliff	O
highway	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
could	O
not	O
forbear	O
looking	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
makes	O
that	O
man	O
look	O
at	O
you	O
so	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
reason	O
enough	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
collared	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
and	O
fetched	O
about	O
fourteen	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
rescued	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
before	O
justice	O
Bury	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Spring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Monday	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
at	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
telling	O
me	O
the	O
story	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
passed	O
as	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
makes	O
that	O
man	O
look	O
at	O
you	O
so	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
down	O
Gravel	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
looking	O
behind	O
them	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
;	O
we	O
overtook	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
some	O
broad	O
stones	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
round	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
last	O
night	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
last	O
night	O
.	O
We	O
pushed	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Black-boy	O
alehouse	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
above	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
a	O
score	O
of	O
Irishmen	O
arose	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
rescued	O
from	O
us	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
11	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
he	O
says	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
often	O
in	O
coalheaving	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
5	O
l.	O
in	O
copper	O
home	O
that	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Burford	O
Camphire	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
very	O
often	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
fellow	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
really	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
almost	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
morning	O
about	O
6	O
o'clock	O
I	O
saw	O
Wiseman	O
as	O
drunk	O
as	O
a	O
man	O
could	O
be	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
that	O
night	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
to	O
a	O
bawdy	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
whores	O
have	O
robbed	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
declared	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Murphy	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
lodged	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
15	O
months	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
before	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
my	O
door	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
eleven	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
key	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
my	O
child	O
being	O
ill	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
sleep	O
after	O
three	O
o'clock	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
maid	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Deyly	I-pers
,	O
the	O
servant	O
,	O
confirmed	O
her	O
testimony	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
awaked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
373	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Seagoe	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
pistol	O
loaded	O
with	O
gunpowder	O
and	O
leaden	O
slugs	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
on	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
Milbourne	I-pers
unlawfully	O
and	O
maliciously	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
felonious	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
May	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
Milbourne	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
over-right	B-place
Isleworth	I-place
church	I-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
driving	O
the	O
coach	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Drake	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
'd	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
thumb	O
with	O
my	O
whip	O
,	O
and	O
repeated	O
my	O
blow	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
his	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Immediately	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
unbuttoned	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
another	O
;	O
but	O
calling	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
demand	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Milbourne	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
fright	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
owned	O
his	O
intent	O
was	O
to	O
shoot	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
Milbourne	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
of	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
between	O
his	O
bidding	O
you	O
to	O
stop	O
and	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
struck	O
the	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Milbourne	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
minutes	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
rob	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
along	O
Sion-lane	O
with	O
some	O
chaises	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
rob	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
seeing	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
thinking	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
