TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
26th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1752	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Robert	B-pers
Alsop	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1752	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ALSOP	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
*	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BURNET	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
||	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
CLIVE	O
+	O
,	O
RICHARD	O
ADAMS	O
++	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
or	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
which	O
jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kirk	I-pers
,	O
Ralph	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Winning	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Marcoone	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hugget	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Woolridge	I-pers
,	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Vanlute	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Roby	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
500	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
d.	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
warehouse	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
merchants	B-pers
of	I-pers
Almaine	I-pers
,	O
commonly	O
called	O
Hants	O
Town	O
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Martin	B-pers
Elkin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
agent	O
to	O
the	O
merchants	O
of	O
Almaine	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
several	O
warehouses	O
at	O
the	O
Steel-yard	B-place
;	O
I	O
employed	O
John	B-pers
Stubley	I-pers
to	O
watch	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
some	O
lead	O
upon	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
lead	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
begged	O
I	O
'd	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
prosecute	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stubley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
watchman	O
at	O
the	O
Steel	O
Yard	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
a	O
ladder	O
that	O
the	O
bricklayers	O
had	O
been	O
using	O
,	O
which	O
stood	O
against	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
ladder	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
employed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Mails	O
,	O
the	O
bricklayer	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
under	O
your	O
arm	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Only	O
a	O
little	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
lead	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
31	O
inches	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
14	O
wide	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
evidence	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lead	O
had	O
been	O
newly	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
a	O
hip	O
;	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
measure	O
,	O
the	O
lead	O
fitted	O
the	O
place	O
exactly	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
been	O
nail	O
'd	O
on	O
with	O
nails	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
forced	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
501	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Susannah	B-pers
Higgs	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
velvet	O
cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
cap	O
laced	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
April	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
502	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
James	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
books	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Noble	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bookseller	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Court	I-place
.	O
He	O
produced	O
four	O
books	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
books	O
at	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Huson	O
,	O
in	O
Maiden	O
Lane	O
;	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
now	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
22	O
others	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bookseller	O
at	O
the	O
Cicero	O
's	O
Head	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
brought	O
these	O
books	O
to	O
me	O
Aug.	O
29	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
brought	O
some	O
others	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Noble	O
all	O
the	O
books	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Noble	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
books	O
which	O
I	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Huson	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Noble	O
's	O
books	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
knows	O
I	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
G	O
uilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
503	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Froude	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Davidson	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	O
Davidson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Alexander	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
in	O
Bell	B-place
Yard	I-place
,	I-place
King	I-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
9s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
going	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
,	O
miss	O
'd	O
3s	O
.	O
6d	O
.	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
before	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
for	O
breaking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
was	O
struggling	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
her	O
pocket	O
came	O
off	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
shook	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
My	O
landlady	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
my	O
landlady	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
she	O
accused	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
witness	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
this	O
money	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
half-penny	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
jump	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
murder	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wright	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
besides	O
the	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davidson	I-pers
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
504	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
Benj	O
.	O
Anderton	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
lost	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
till	O
in	O
my	O
kitchen	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
one	O
Franklin	O
,	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
confessed	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
periwig	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
till	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
twopence	O
farthing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
robb	O
'd	O
my	O
brother	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
till	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
company	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Parrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
baby	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
fact	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Munford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
honesty	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
often	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
after	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
505.	O
Jenkin	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
l.	O
5	O
s	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mould	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
27	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
506	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
44	O
s.	O
one	O
callico	O
petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s	O
,	O
one	O
Holland	O
shift	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
21	O
s.	O
two	O
Holland	O
mobs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Oct.	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Greyhound	B-place
inn	I-place
,	I-place
Drury	I-place
Lane	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
a	O
bed	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
by	O
inquiring	O
about	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
barber	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
shift	O
in	O
a	O
wash	O
tub	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
waiting	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
washed	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
taking	O
them	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
stays	O
for	O
13	O
s.	O
she	O
had	O
my	O
petticoat	O
on	O
.	O
That	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
lay	O
at	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
Inn	O
,	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
,	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
given	O
me	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lain	O
there	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
bawdy	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
507	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jolley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goad	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Sept.	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	O
Goad	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Grange	B-place
Inn	I-place
,	I-place
Carey	I-place
Street	I-place
;	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
six	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
into	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
us	O
as	O
an	O
object	O
of	O
charity	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
a	O
little	O
fault	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
man	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
no	O
money	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
a	O
chairman	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
guineas	O
in	O
the	O
sand	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
taking	O
both	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
halfpence	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
chairman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
neither	O
father	O
nor	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
not	O
quite	O
thirteen	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
508	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
2l	O
*	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
509	O
,	O
510	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Merrit	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Dallison	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
stuff	O
petticoats	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rickards	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Rickards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Three	B-place
Fox	I-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
Charterhouse	I-place
Lane	I-place
.	O
My	O
business	O
is	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
in	O
stables	O
.	O
The	O
lock	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
we	O
put	O
it	O
ajar	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
Aug.	O
22	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
awoke	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
standing	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
further	O
notice	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
sit	O
in	O
only	O
her	O
flats	O
for	O
two	O
days	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
this	O
a	O
barbarous	O
action	O
?	O
About	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Poll	O
Merrit	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Dallison	I-pers
.	O
Said	O
Merrit	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
Said	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
passed	O
on	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
Poll	O
Merrit	O
had	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
gown	O
on	O
New	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
touchstone	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
If	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
your	O
gown	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
on	O
Poll	O
Merrit	O
's	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
for	O
them	O
several	O
nights	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
now	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
come	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Ann	B-pers
Dallison	I-pers
sing	O
in	O
a	O
chamber	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
cleaning	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
stable	O
.	O
I	O
threw	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
wood	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
Who	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
I	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Poll	O
Merrit	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
?	O
She	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
.	O
Bid	O
her	O
look	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
come	O
up	O
and	O
give	O
you	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
her	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
stay	O
,	O
depend	O
upon	O
it	O
I	O
am	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
must	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
discontent	O
for	O
?	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
?	O
Poll	O
Merrit	O
had	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
gown	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
petticoats	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
shirt	O
made	O
into	O
an	O
apron	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
petticoat	O
on	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dallison	I-pers
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
stays	O
:	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
served	O
the	O
warrant	O
.	O
Poll	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
commit	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
Nan	B-pers
Dallison	I-pers
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
surprized	O
.	O
Nan	B-pers
Dallison	I-pers
ran	O
down	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Street	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
her	O
again	O
.	O
Going	O
up	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
Dallison	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
upon	O
the	O
ramble	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
watchman	O
talk	O
to	O
some	O
people	O
in	O
Long	O
Lane	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
from	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Merrit	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
cover	O
their	O
nakedness	O
before	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rickards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
just	O
married	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Rickards	I-pers
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
She	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Merrit	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
night	O
before	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Dallison	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
walking	O
down	O
Long	O
Lane	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Rickards	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
us	O
why	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
something	O
that	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
tight	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
that	O
I	O
now	O
live	O
with	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
drunken	O
creature	O
,	O
I	O
wan	O
t	O
to	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
Dallison	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
an	O
uncle	O
and	O
aunt	O
in	O
Long	O
Lane	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
old	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
Charterhouse	O
Lane	O
,	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Rickards	O
;	O
Ann	B-pers
Dallison	I-pers
asked	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dallison	I-pers
cleared	O
me	O
then	O
.	O
Dallison	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rickards	O
met	O
me	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
together	O
in	O
Long	O
Lane	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
made	O
me	O
go	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
married	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
often	O
attempted	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
would	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
condition	O
with	O
the	O
soul	O
disease	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
drunkenest	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
Poll	O
Merrit	O
or	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
and	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
happy	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
a	O
false	O
story	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
kissed	O
her	O
lips	O
,	O
or	O
touched	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
once	O
live	O
over	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
husband	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
admitted	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
made	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
.	O
Merrit	O
acquitted	O
,	O
Dallison	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
511	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susannah	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wicker	O
basket	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
24	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
eels	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
wooden	O
salmon	O
kit	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
penny	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Sep.	O
26	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
512	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Robert	I-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
one	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Merideth	I-pers
,	O
one	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bridge	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Sarah	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
is	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
behind	B-place
the	I-place
Rummer	I-place
tavern	I-place
Chancery-lane	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
were	O
lost	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
suspected	O
and	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
after	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
some	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
513	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
velvet	O
cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Oakman	I-pers
,	O
October	O
11	O
++	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
514	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
,	O
October	O
19	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sparks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Baptist	B-place
head	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Old	I-place
Bailey	I-place
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
spoon	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
or	O
Thursday	O
,	O
the	O
nineteenth	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
swear	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
sometimes	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
along	O
Threadneedle-street	O
,	O
this	O
day	O
seven-night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
dirty	O
condition	O
and	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
bosom	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
by	O
the	O
condition	O
she	O
appeared	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Frost	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
spoon	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
some	O
private	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
her	O
by	O
'Squire	O
Gore	O
's	O
gateway	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
up	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
gateway	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
position	O
that	O
I	O
concluded	O
the	O
spoon	O
was	O
no	O
more	O
in	O
her	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
where	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
concealed	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
wife	O
or	O
daughter	O
must	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
arms	O
and	O
shook	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
spoon	O
dropped	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
indecent	O
expression	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
spoon	O
dropped	O
from	O
her	O
?	O
Chapman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
condition	O
that	O
it	O
plainly	O
appeared	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
came	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
ask	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
coming	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Frost	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
spoon	O
that	O
is	O
produced	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
?	O
Chapman	O
.	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
Threadneedle-street	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Frost	O
.	O
Standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
last	O
Thursday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gardner	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
believed	O
a	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
by	O
that	O
had	O
stolen	O
a	O
spoon	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
suspect	O
that	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
proper	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Chapman	O
went	O
and	O
stoped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
deliver	O
up	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
or	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
into	O
'Squire	O
Gore	O
's	O
gateway	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
way	O
to	O
prevent	O
any	O
people	O
from	O
going	O
in	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
back-kitchin	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
vain	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
your	O
wife	O
,	O
maid	O
,	O
or	O
daughter	O
,	O
must	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
and	O
shook	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
spoon	O
dropped	O
from	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
indecent	O
condition	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
It	O
fell	O
just	O
between	O
her	O
legs	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newcome	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sparks	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
missed	O
the	O
spoon	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
seven-night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
there	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Newcome	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
there	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Newcome	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
there	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
spoon	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
brown	O
paper	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
read	O
the	O
mark	O
and	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
515	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
sattin	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
two	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
August	O
5	O
++	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Black	I-pers
.	O
My	O
lodging	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Elington	O
,	O
Middle-street	B-place
Cloth-fair	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
landlady	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
in	O
a	O
lodger	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
like	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
for	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
hear	O
nothing	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
bed	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
shirts	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
brought	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
then	O
unlocked	O
my	O
chest	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
my	O
night	O
cap	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
tied	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
Charles	B-pers
Malphus	I-pers
was	O
in	O
bed	O
with	O
the	O
new	O
lodger	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
seeing	O
but	O
little	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Malphus	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
cap	O
you	O
was	O
inquiring	O
after	O
last	O
night	O
in	O
our	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
stranger	O
lay	O
bald	O
headed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
a	O
messenger	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
chest	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
locked	O
it	O
after	O
you	O
put	O
your	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
robbery	O
and	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
intelligence	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
went	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Elington	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
lodging	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
Mr.	O
Black	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
When	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
shilling	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
so	O
quick	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
surprise	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sent	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
people	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
check	O
'd	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
bundle	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
then	O
?	O
A.	O
Elington	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
he	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
he	O
brought	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
roll	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
writer	O
to	O
a	O
lawyer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
return	O
?	O
A.	O
Elington	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
an	O
old	O
neckcloth	O
behind	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Black	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
a	O
check	O
'd	O
handkerchief	O
your	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
home	O
in	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Malphus	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lay	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Black	O
lock	O
his	O
chest	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Malphus	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
unlock	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
morning	O
down	O
to	O
Blackwall	O
,	O
having	O
heard	O
my	O
brother	O
was	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
Indies	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
five	O
days	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
and	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
spent	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
by	O
people	O
that	O
had	O
read	O
the	O
advertisement	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Coulson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Newstreet	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
years	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
he	O
wronged	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
pin	O
's	O
point	O
.	O
Eady	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
for	O
any	O
harm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
employment	O
?	O
E.	O
Price	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
.	O
He	O
goes	O
to	O
market	O
and	O
sells	O
greens	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
E.	O
Price	O
.	O
In	O
Shoe	O
lane	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Crofts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
business	O
?	O
J	O
Crofts	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
lighterman	O
.	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
understand	O
he	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
but	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoe	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
whose	O
house	O
?	O
S.	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
his	O
landlady	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
lad	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
does	O
he	O
follow	O
for	O
a	O
livelyhood	O
?	O
S.	O
Carter	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
fisherman	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
business	O
?	O
Harwood	O
.	O
I	O
understand	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
fisherman	O
.	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
sea	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
lately	O
?	O
Harwood	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
past	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
516	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Carrol	B-pers
Phenix	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hezekiah	B-pers
Senecal	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
22	O
++	O
Hezekiah	O
Senecal	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Ludgate	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
a	O
picture	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
stood	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
two	O
minutes	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
like	O
mine	O
hang	O
below	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
wiped	O
my	O
nose	O
but	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
rascal	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
indeed	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
shifted	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
one	O
side	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
post	O
where	O
a	O
man	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
held	O
out	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
see	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
?	O
Senecal	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
mob	O
gathered	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Duck	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
ducked	O
,	O
but	O
should	O
be	O
carried	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
an	O
oilman	O
on	O
Ludgate	O
Hill	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
.	O
You	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
;	O
a	O
good	O
piece	O
of	O
it	O
hung	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
blue	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
fellow	O
at	O
a	O
post	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
slipped	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
and	O
got	O
near	O
the	O
post	O
,	O
seeming	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
in	O
ended	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stood	O
there	O
:	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
William	O
I	O
obick	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
going	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
before	O
given	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
for	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
Coming	O
towards	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
picture	O
shop	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
.	O
A	O
thief	O
,	O
a	O
thief	O
!	O
He	O
has	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
shuffled	O
round	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
lugged	O
me	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
517	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bulwinkle	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Franks	I-pers
Oct.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Franks	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Sepulchre	I-place
's	I-place
parish	I-place
,	O
and	O
missed	O
two	O
shirts	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
the	O
fifteenth	O
of	O
October	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
518	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Simon	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
guinea	O
.	O
and	O
5	O
s	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
privately	O
and	O
secretly	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grear	I-pers
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Oct.	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	O
Grear	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Six	B-place
Bells	I-place
at	I-place
Kensington	I-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
nineteenth	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
He	O
complained	O
he	O
was	O
dry	O
and	O
cold	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
Another	O
soldier	O
came	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
them	O
a	O
quartern	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
bowl	O
of	O
punch	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Take	O
and	O
drink	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
paid	O
for	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
to	O
sleep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Grear	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
more	O
distracted	O
in	O
mind	O
than	O
drunk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
about	O
?	O
Grear	O
.	O
Because	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
awaked	O
by	O
something	O
busy	O
about	O
my	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
amaze	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
nobody	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pockets	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
gone	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newbolt	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
with	O
another	O
soldier	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
bag	O
that	O
he	O
carries	O
his	O
things	O
in	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
in	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
begged	O
that	O
I	O
'd	O
not	O
take	O
his	O
life	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
guinea	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
distributed	O
the	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
among	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
his	O
comrades	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
got	O
a	O
hundred	O
lashes	O
for	O
it	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
he	O
when	O
he	O
confessed	O
this	O
?	O
Grear	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Grear	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
four	O
doors	O
from	O
the	O
alehouse	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
?	O
Grear	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
over	O
or	O
under	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
first	O
of	O
all	O
?	O
Grear	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
alehouse	O
,	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
parade	O
at	O
Kensington	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
one	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
then	O
,	O
taking	O
but	O
one	O
draught	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Six	O
Bells	O
at	O
Kensington	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
soldiers	O
,	O
came	O
together	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
the	O
nineteenth	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
wanted	O
some	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
soldiers	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Dale	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
treated	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
himself	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
bowl	O
of	O
punch	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
made	O
that	O
long	O
before	O
in	O
came	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
made	O
him	O
and	O
me	O
drink	O
each	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
considering	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
,	O
seeming	O
very	O
much	O
vex	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
punch	O
to	O
Simon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
sat	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
after	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
whether	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
punch	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
other	O
people	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Simon	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
two	O
.	O
The	O
Newbury	O
coach	O
stopp	O
'd	O
at	O
three	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
in	O
came	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
company	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
last	O
night	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
at	O
the	O
centry	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
guard	O
,	O
and	O
secure	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
up	O
my	O
wife	O
rather	O
sooner	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newbolt	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
who	O
should	O
be	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
soldier	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
There	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
these	O
silver	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
cartouch	O
box	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
had	O
the	O
guinea	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
charge	O
,	O
he	O
himself	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confessing	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
buckles	O
too	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
merciful	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
guinea	O
produced	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Newbolt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
last	O
evidence	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dale	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
buckles	O
in	O
the	O
thing	O
that	O
he	O
carries	O
his	O
cartridges	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
round	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
guard	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
faces	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
soldiers	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
that	O
man	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dale	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
sorry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
merciful	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
guinea	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
thirteen	O
pence	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
soldiers	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
beer	O
,	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
sober	O
,	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Viner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
upwards	O
of	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
almost	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
going	O
on	O
with	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
,	O
sober	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
loves	O
to	O
work	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
bread	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Parkin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
behaved	O
like	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
His	O
wife	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
twice	O
or	O
thrice	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
and	O
sober	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
sometimes	O
getting	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sneath	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
groom	O
to	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Levelon	I-pers
Gower	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Crew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
have	O
tried	O
him	O
in	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
honest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
519.	O
Honor	B-pers
Furness	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Geary	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
chrystal	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Peter	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
city	O
to	O
my	O
home	O
in	O
King	O
Street	O
,	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
with	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
pass	O
'd	O
Temple	O
Bar	O
.	O
She	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
George	B-place
alehouse	I-place
,	I-place
between	I-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
and	I-place
Temple	I-place
Bar	I-place
,	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Black	I-pers
master	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
some	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
her	O
company	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
fob	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
before	O
she	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
but	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
noise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
room	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
by	O
ourselves	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
undressed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
quite	O
to	O
her	O
smock	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
,	O
Watchman	O
,	O
very	O
loud	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
slipped	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
very	O
pretty	O
fellow	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
me	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
it	O
to	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
Watch	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
open	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
cane	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Black	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
wicket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
not	O
paid	O
your	O
reckoning	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
pay	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
pushed	O
my	O
cane	O
through	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Black	O
sweeping	O
his	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sober	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
four	O
guineas	O
reward	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
at	O
five	O
guineas	O
.	O
Then	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
porter	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
He	O
produces	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Hammon	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
that	O
watch	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Are	O
not	O
you	O
father	O
to	O
this	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
that	O
I	O
carry	O
.	O
Holding	O
a	O
child	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
old	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
me	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
She	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Murphet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Bibby	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Stanhope	O
Street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
something	O
like	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Thomas	O
Bibby	O
,	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
advertised	O
then	O
?	O
Murphet	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
not	O
advertised	O
before	O
you	O
parted	O
with	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Murphet	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Murphet	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
six	O
guineas	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
worth	O
?	O
Murphet	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
worth	O
ten	O
pounds	O
?	O
Murphet	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
lend	O
your	O
money	O
upon	O
goods	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Murphet	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
lent	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
sold	O
,	O
or	O
parted	O
with	O
,	O
there	O
having	O
been	O
some	O
rumour	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
a	O
stolen	O
watch	O
?	O
Murphet	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
again	O
?	O
Murphet	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Murphet	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
once	O
before	O
brought	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
employment	O
?	O
Murphet	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
was	O
that	O
who	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Murphet	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
dealt	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
for	O
?	O
Murphet	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
for	O
small	O
things	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
my	O
sister-in-law	O
.	O
Her	O
name	O
is	O
Bibby	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
this	O
watch	O
at	O
our	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
advertised	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
watch	O
advertised	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
at	O
Paris	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
seal	O
to	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
made	O
at	O
Paris	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
fetch	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
you	O
read	O
the	O
advertisement	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
advertisement	O
lead	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
give	O
proper	O
descriptions	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
upon	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
hour	O
hand	O
not	O
being	O
described	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
advertisement	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
a	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
whom	O
she	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
think	O
she	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
paid	O
you	O
the	O
money	O
back	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
replaced	O
from	O
your	O
shop	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
another	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
any	O
way	O
fearful	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
would	O
lend	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
business	O
she	O
was	O
of	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
carry	O
the	O
other	O
watch	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
redeem	O
it	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
fetch	O
it	O
in	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Oakley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
a	O
factory	O
in	O
Ironmonger	O
Lane	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bibby	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
fourteenth	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
execution	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
small	O
debt	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
imagined	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
spite	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
neighbours	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
had	O
passed	O
his	O
word	O
for	O
her	O
safe	O
return	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
could	O
borrow	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
debt	O
was	O
six	O
guineas	O
.	O
She	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
much	O
distressed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
bound	O
to	O
pray	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
leave	O
this	O
gold	O
watch	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
money	O
himself	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
advance	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Bibby	O
in	O
company	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Oakley	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
this	O
watch	O
was	O
pawned	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
his	O
money	O
?	O
Oakley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
this	O
watch	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
pledged	O
as	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
six	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
deliver	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
?	O
Oakley	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
Bibby	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
that	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
landlord	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
saying	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
deliver	O
this	O
watch	O
back	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
Thursday	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
before	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
paper	O
with	O
the	O
advertisement	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
directed	O
by	O
some	O
people	O
to	O
Ironmonger	O
Lane	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
understood	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
case	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
best	O
way	O
will	O
be	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
up	O
quietly	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
employed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
again	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
she	O
replied	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
sudge	O
,	O
adding	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
fear	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
keep	O
it	O
till	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
security	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
same	O
watch	O
?	O
Oakley	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Upon	O
finding	O
she	O
was	O
apprehended	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
inquired	O
of	O
an	O
attorney	O
what	O
I	O
must	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
my	O
best	O
way	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hammond	O
,	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
attorney	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hammond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Angel	O
in	O
Ironmonger-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
,	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Oakley	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Oakley	O
said	O
,	O
Look	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
return	O
the	O
watch	O
upon	O
receiving	O
six	O
guineas	O
;	O
afterwards	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
produced	O
?	O
Hammond	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
the	O
hour	O
and	O
minute	O
hands	O
were	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
Paris	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
broke	O
my	O
leg	O
and	O
arm	O
by	O
a	O
fall	O
from	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
two	O
children	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
kind	O
,	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
call	O
at	O
my	O
lodgings	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
stir	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
sell	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
all	O
my	O
clothes	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
three	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
six	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
angry	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
three	O
guineas	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
child	O
's	O
father	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bibby	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Oakley	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lent	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
That	O
very	O
night	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
brought	O
me	O
from	O
my	O
lodgings	O
up	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
George	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
far	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Fountain	O
Tavern	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
top	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
replied	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
go	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
advantage	O
of	O
one	O
you	O
have	O
known	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
you	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
He	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
the	O
watchman	O
called	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
his	O
reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
shoved	O
him	O
and	O
I	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
till	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
In	O
our	O
unhappy	O
way	O
of	O
life	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
seldom	O
we	O
have	O
witnesses	O
by	O
when	O
we	O
take	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
any	O
place	O
,	O
or	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
520	O
,	O
521	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Trenter	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Dorothy	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Steel	I-pers
,	O
September	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Edward	O
guilty	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
522	O
,	O
523	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Richens	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Little	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Drury	B-pers
Otley	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
one	O
cambrick	O
apron	O
,	O
three	O
muslin	O
caps	O
,	O
two	O
cambrick	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Otley	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
one	O
laced	O
muslin	O
cap	O
,	O
two	O
plain	O
muslin	O
caps	O
,	O
one	O
Holland	O
shift	O
ruffled	O
,	O
one	O
large	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
other	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Lydia	B-pers
Otley	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
cambrick	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Otley	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
two	O
linnen	O
caps	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Osbourne	I-pers
;	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Drury	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Osbourne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Drury	O
Otley	O
.	O
Esq	O
;	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
september	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
ironing	O
in	O
the	O
laundry	O
over	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
adjoining	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
laundry	O
;	O
some	O
hanging	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
on	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
The	O
sashes	O
were	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
shutters	O
not	O
done	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
door	O
opens	O
into	O
a	O
passage	O
.	O
The	O
window	O
that	O
the	O
thief	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
servants	O
hall	O
,	O
then	O
through	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
through	O
the	O
scullery	O
;	O
then	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
through	O
the	O
passage	O
into	O
the	O
laundry	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
about	O
eight	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
,	O
then	O
Margaret	O
Wade	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
laundry	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Otley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
laundry	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
there	O
;	O
about	O
eight	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Starter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
'Squire	O
Otley	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
people	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
aprons	O
and	O
handkerchiefs	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
Hesson	O
cage	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
the	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
about	O
Little	O
's	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
on	O
:	O
Richens	O
had	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
her	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
stockings	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
red	O
cloak	O
in	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
also	O
a	O
shift	O
pawned	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
swore	O
before	O
Justice	O
Burkhead	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
from	O
Little	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
shoes	O
and	O
stockings	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
from	O
Richens	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Anne	B-pers
Osbourne	I-pers
,	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
mentioning	O
whose	O
property	O
.	O
&	O
c.	O
]	O
Susanna	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Otley	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
windows	O
and	O
doors	O
were	O
fastened	O
that	O
night	O
by	O
me	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
window	O
that	O
the	O
thieves	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
servants	O
hall	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
no	O
pane	O
was	O
then	O
broke	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pane	O
broke	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
?	O
S.	O
Harwood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
our	O
coachman	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Richens	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
girl	O
[	O
meaning	O
Little	O
]	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
that	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cap	O
.	O
Little	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
work	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
man	O
,	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
For	O
Richens	O
,	O
see	O
her	O
trial	O
,	O
Numb	O
.	O
119	O
,	O
in	O
Alderman	O
Winterbottom	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
524.	O
Edward	B-pers
Spelman	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
deed	O
,	O
purporting	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
article	O
of	O
agreement	O
made	O
in	O
January	O
1709	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
uttering	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
false	O
,	O
forged	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Hugh	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
of	O
37736	O
l.	O
6	O
s	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
maintain	O
the	O
charge	O
as	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
so	O
produced	O
no	O
evidence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
525	O
,	O
526	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Purcell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Patrick	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
that	O
Purcell	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Aimey	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
with	O
menaces	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
violent	O
manner	O
,	O
did	O
demand	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Aimey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Square	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Hays	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
Catherine	B-pers
Grinfield	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
servant	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
the	O
Temple	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
into	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Square	I-place
,	O
within	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
our	O
own	O
home	O
,	O
Gore	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
,	O
stop	O
directly	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
coachman	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
repeating	O
the	O
words	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
.	O
Then	O
Gore	O
came	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
put	O
a	O
pistol	O
towards	O
my	O
left	O
breast	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
,	O
deliver	O
all	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
this	O
instant	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
repeated	O
it	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
hast	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
Gore	O
?	O
Aimey	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
sure	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
were	O
poor	O
servants	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
,	O
drive	O
off	O
directly	O
.	O
The	O
coachman	O
drove	O
to	O
our	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
put	O
the	O
women	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Grinfield	I-pers
,	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
Gore	O
stopping	O
a	O
gentleman	O
on	O
foot	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
watch	O
!	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
The	O
gentleman	O
was	O
scuffling	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
captain	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
drawn	O
his	O
sword	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
other	O
with	O
Gore	O
?	O
Aimey	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
till	O
after	O
Gore	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Charlton-House	O
,	O
in	O
Pall-Mall	O
.	O
The	O
pistol	O
lay	O
just	O
by	O
his	O
side	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Although	O
we	O
called	O
watch	O
and	O
thieves	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
for	O
several	O
minutes	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
moon	O
light	O
night	O
.	O
Gore	O
had	O
been	O
pricked	O
in	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
bled	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
coachman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
driving	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
home	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
turn	O
into	O
the	O
Square	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
walking	O
together	O
.	O
Gore	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
within	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
blood	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
immediately	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
so	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
stopt	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
and	O
clapped	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
,	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
with	O
his	O
right	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
their	O
money	O
;	O
they	O
replied	O
they	O
were	O
but	O
poor	O
servants	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
nothing	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
demanded	O
it	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
made	O
the	O
same	O
reply	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
presented	O
his	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
off	O
,	O
off	O
,	O
off	O
(	O
for	O
so	O
he	O
expressed	O
himself	O
)	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
drove	O
directly	O
to	O
our	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
but	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
did	O
Hughs	O
come	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Conner	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
within	O
ten	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Conner	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
women	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Grinfield	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
gave	O
his	O
wife	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
the	O
footman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
stone	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
attacking	O
a	O
single	O
gentleman	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Square	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
saw	O
us	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
,	O
as	O
did	O
also	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
thinking	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
accomplices	O
.	O
I	O
flung	O
the	O
stone	O
at	O
Gore	O
,	O
but	O
missed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
down	O
Pall-Mall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
Hughs	O
ran	O
on	O
the	O
flag	O
stones	O
,	O
within	O
the	O
posts	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
Gore	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
150	O
yards	O
;	O
I	O
kicked	O
up	O
his	O
heels	O
in	O
Pall-Mall	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
force	O
of	O
his	O
fall	O
the	O
pistol	O
flew	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
upon	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
minutes	O
before	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
footman	O
came	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
one	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
led	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
when	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
reason	O
that	O
he	O
left	O
us	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
better	O
mark	O
coming	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
thought	O
to	O
attack	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Grinfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Gore	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
the	O
footboy	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
speak	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grinfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
husband	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
coach	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
coachman	O
and	O
footman	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
engaged	O
with	O
one	O
Captain	O
Browning	O
:	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
about	O
forty	O
yards	O
when	O
Gore	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pistol	O
lying	O
by	O
his	O
side	O
when	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
a	O
centinel	O
at	O
Charlton-House	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Hughs	O
run	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
Hughs	O
in	O
Pall-Mall	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
be	O
my	O
prisoner	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
's	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
instrument	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
.	O
Gore	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
with	O
some	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
through	O
Pall-Mall	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
people	O
cry	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
That	O
coachman	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
heaved	O
a	O
stone	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
aside	O
to	O
shun	O
the	O
stone	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
kicked	O
up	O
my	O
heels	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
stopt	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
These	O
witnesses	O
were	O
all	O
there	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Conner	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
there	O
on	O
such	O
an	O
account	O
?	O
Conner	O
.	O
Captain	O
Browning	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Gore	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
about	O
the	O
stature	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
footman	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purport	O
.	O
Gore	O
guilty	O
,	O
Hughs	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
527	O
,	O
528	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
.	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Patton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Oct.	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Patton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Hand	B-place
and	I-place
Racket	I-place
in	I-place
Hedge-Lane	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
parish	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
together	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
they	O
staid	O
there	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
tankard	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
They	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
mild	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
with	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
another	O
upon	O
the	O
shelf	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
my	O
boy	O
came	O
down	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
for	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
replied	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
drawing	O
this	O
tankard	O
for	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
Welch	O
sitting	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
will	O
come	O
presently	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
saw	O
Smith	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
tap-room	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Seeing	O
my	O
tankard	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
challenged	O
them	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Smith	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
kitchin	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
and	O
maid	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
about	O
the	O
bench	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
where	O
Smith	O
was	O
standing	O
,	O
but	O
under	O
the	O
bench	O
between	O
Welch	O
's	O
legs	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
tankard	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
is	O
called	O
French	O
plate	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
people	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Patton	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
one	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
.	O
The	O
base	O
metal	O
tankard	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Patton	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Smith	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
kitchin	O
with	O
his	O
face	O
towards	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
strange	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
kitchin	O
who	O
had	O
sent	O
me	O
down	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
gone	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
with	O
the	O
beer	O
.	O
In	O
searching	O
about	O
the	O
tap-room	O
this	O
base	O
metal	O
tankard	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
between	O
Welch	O
's	O
legs	O
under	O
the	O
bench	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
fed	O
a	O
little	O
dog	O
there	O
and	O
should	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fish	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
,	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
boy	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
mild	O
beer	O
,	O
then	O
Smith	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchin	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
staid	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
tankards	O
in	O
the	O
kitchin	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
hearing	O
the	O
bell	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Smith	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
boy	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
Smith	O
walked	O
past	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
tap-room	O
door	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
half	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
asking	O
my	O
leave	O
by	O
way	O
of	O
compliment	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
welcome	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
Fish	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
base	O
metal	O
one	O
found	O
under	O
Welch	O
's	O
legs	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
cross	O
legged	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
denied	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
theirs	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Smith	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
washing	O
the	O
dishes	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
Smith	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
kitchin	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
usual	O
for	O
strange	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
kitchin	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
boy	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
window	O
that	O
commands	O
the	O
kitchin	O
,	O
through	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
Smith	O
walking	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
towards	O
the	O
door	O
immediately	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Corral	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
October	O
2	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Corral	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Swan-alley	B-place
,	I-place
Coleman-street	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Coach	I-place
and	I-place
Horses	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
publick	I-place
house	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
twelfth	O
instant	O
Welch	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
drawn	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
Smith	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
Corral	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
another	O
silver	O
mug	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
Welch	O
was	O
seated	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
mug	O
brought	O
to	O
Smith	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
making	O
them	O
a	O
welch	O
rabbit	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
seated	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
close	O
together	O
as	O
two	O
men	O
could	O
be	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
table	O
about	O
two	O
feet	O
six	O
inches	O
long	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
settle	O
near	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
them	O
converse	O
together	O
?	O
Corrall	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
lean	O
their	O
heads	O
together	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
silver	O
mugs	O
standing	O
before	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
candle	O
was	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
table	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
mantlepiece	O
aloft	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
usual	O
place	O
.	O
Smith	O
's	O
pint	O
being	O
out	O
he	O
ordered	O
the	O
maid	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
fill	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
maid	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
she	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
drank	O
once	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
pint	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
very	O
much	O
she	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
They	O
staid	O
some	O
considerable	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
just	O
stepped	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
gone	O
a	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Welch	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
one	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
two	O
and	O
a	O
welch	O
rabbit	O
,	O
all	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
both	O
together	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
they	O
continue	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
after	O
you	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
?	O
Corral	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
The	O
pot	O
was	O
missed	O
before	O
the	O
mugs	O
were	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
moved	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
My	O
maid	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
,	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
which	O
Smith	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
French	O
plate	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
after	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Corrall	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Corrall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Hearing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
a	O
tankard	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
metal	O
mug	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
mugs	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
before	O
?	O
Corrall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
both	O
my	O
mugs	O
were	O
silver	O
that	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
soul	O
near	O
the	O
table	O
but	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
The	O
base	O
metal	O
one	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
that	O
which	O
Smith	O
was	O
drinking	O
out	O
of	O
;	O
having	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
that	O
make	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
two	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
directly	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
had	O
no	O
belly	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
litle	O
rim	O
round	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
goes	O
straight	O
up	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twelfth	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
a	O
trifle	O
of	O
time	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
again	O
about	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
then	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
pint	O
,	O
I	O
drew	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
times	O
the	O
same	O
mug	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
then	O
Smith	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
which	O
was	O
drawn	O
him	O
in	O
another	O
silver	O
mug	O
.	O
He	O
sat	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
table	O
with	O
Welch	O
on	O
a	O
settle	O
near	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Smith	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
welch	O
rabbit	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
two	O
mugs	O
you	O
set	O
before	O
them	O
silver	O
ones	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Stock	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
Smith	O
drank	O
his	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
bid	O
the	O
boy	O
fill	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Stock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
above	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
they	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Stock	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
near	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
continued	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Stock	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
facing	O
them	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
I	O
was	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
that	O
silver	O
mug	O
which	O
is	O
missing	O
last	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Stock	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
moment	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
for	O
a	O
mug	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
missed	O
it	O
directly	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
at	O
most	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
mug	O
of	O
that	O
shape	O
which	O
is	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
mug	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Stock	O
.	O
Because	O
the	O
boy	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
two	O
mugs	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
and	O
set	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
mug	O
was	O
missing	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Stock	O
.	O
The	O
mug	O
that	O
Smith	O
had	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
base	O
metal	O
one	O
put	O
in	O
its	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
boy	O
here	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Stock	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
,	O
being	O
wanted	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
mugs	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
and	O
wipe	O
out	O
the	O
score	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
had	O
paid	O
their	O
reckoning	O
,	O
in	O
both	O
their	O
hearing	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
set	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
base	O
metal	O
mug	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
mug	O
you	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Stock	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Stock	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
had	O
eat	O
the	O
welch	O
rabbit	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
news	O
paper	O
to	O
read	O
,	O
but	O
Welch	O
removed	O
the	O
candle	O
from	O
the	O
table	O
to	O
the	O
mantlepiece	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Column	I-pers
,	O
On	O
the	O
twelfth	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
attempt	O
to	O
swear	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
took	O
but	O
little	O
notice	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
candle	O
to	O
be	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
a	O
reading	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
master	O
had	O
bid	O
the	O
boy	O
clear	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
strange	O
silver	O
mug	O
is	O
this	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
out	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
possession	O
has	O
this	O
base	O
metal	O
mug	O
been	O
since	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Welch	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
and	O
had	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
that	O
stands	O
here	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
Smith	O
)	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
sit	O
down	O
facing	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Smith	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
absolutely	O
deny	O
that	O
of	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
where	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
it	O
manifest	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
all	O
the	O
afternoon	O
till	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
at	O
my	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
Smith	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
observe	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
cheek	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
perfectly	O
well	O
both	O
by	O
his	O
countenance	O
and	O
speech	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Stock	I-pers
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Stock	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
asked	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
to	O
pick	O
them	O
out	O
from	O
amongst	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
set	O
in	O
front	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
did	O
.	O
For	O
Welch	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fore-street	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Welch	O
these	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
journeyman	O
shoemaker	O
and	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
plate	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
Jeffery	O
Chandler	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
in	O
Fore-street	O
.	O
Welch	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
between	O
thirteen	O
and	O
fourteen	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Morris	B-pers
Power	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twenty	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
that	O
hurt	O
his	O
character	O
before	O
.	O
Miles	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hosier-lane	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
,	O
and	O
remember	O
his	O
coming	O
from	O
Ireland	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Wetherall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Welch	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
honest	O
and	O
just	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Redlion-street	O
,	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
For	O
Smith	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Plea	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Balsover-street	O
,	O
near	O
Oxford	O
road	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Plea	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
no	O
business	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Smith	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
lodge	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Plea	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
somewhere	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
the	O
twelfth	O
of	O
October	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
we	O
lived	O
there	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
accidentally	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
urgent	O
to	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
staid	O
till	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
drink	O
tea	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
full	O
half	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
you	O
must	O
allow	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
justice	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
clocks	O
vary	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
in	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
business	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Plea	O
.	O
I	O
