TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
25th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winterbottom	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1752	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
Where	O
may	O
be	O
had	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
,	O
The	O
Genuine	O
TRIALS	O
at	O
Large	O
before	O
the	O
High	O
Court	O
of	O
Admiralty	O
,	O
held	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
.	O
Published	O
by	O
the	O
Permission	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
Inspection	O
of	O
the	O
COURT	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WINTERBOTTOM	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
MARTIN	B-pers
WRIGHT	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GUNDRY	O
+	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
SMYTHE	I-pers
||	O
,	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
++	O
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.B	O
.	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Flight	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Leapidge	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Crosfield	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Weeble	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shuttleworth	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ranby	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Collin	B-pers
Dollinson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Vear	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wilde	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
,	O
Jacob	B-pers
Roundeau	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jullian	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
130	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Hudy	B-pers
Bang	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cadington	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
and	O
Co	O
.	O
Jan.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
131	O
,	O
132	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Branham	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Robert	B-pers
Bugg	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
penknife	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
7	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Dec.	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	O
Bugg	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
,	O
near	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
returned	O
back	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Hays	O
came	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
clapped	O
a	O
short	O
sword	O
,	O
or	O
hanger	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
belly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
'll	O
run	O
you	O
through	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
in	O
as	O
desperate	O
a	O
manner	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
express	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
repeated	O
the	O
words	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
;	O
Broughton	O
clapped	O
a	O
horse	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
muzzle	O
under	O
my	O
chin	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
or	O
stir	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
in	O
as	O
desperate	O
manner	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
Hays	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
shillings	O
,	O
a	O
penknife	O
,	O
some	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
little	O
using	O
things	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
examined	O
my	O
pocket	O
again	O
,	O
found	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
before	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
within	O
10	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
?	O
Bugg	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
light	O
directly	O
opposite	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
moonlight	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
lights	O
in	O
other	O
shops	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lamp	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
as	O
perfect	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
particularly	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
Broughton	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
look	O
after	O
us	O
,	O
turn	O
your	O
head	O
another	O
way	O
,	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
towards	O
Long-Acre	O
till	O
they	O
were	O
got	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
rods	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
shop	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
came	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
wished	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
sooner	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
related	O
the	O
particulars	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
dressed	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
size	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
blue-grey	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
tall	O
fellow	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
short	O
think	O
fellow	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
horseman	O
's	O
coat	O
and	O
boots	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
whip	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
thong	O
twisted	O
round	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
and	O
search	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
houses	O
here	O
abouts	O
of	O
ill	O
same	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
Newtoner's-Lane	O
,	O
by	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
standing	O
,	O
as	O
though	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
conversation	O
,	O
against	O
a	O
wall	O
;	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
passed	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
the	O
watchman	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
softly	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoners	O
went	O
into	O
Drury-lane	O
towards	O
the	O
Cole-yard	O
;	O
we	O
followed	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
thinking	O
they	O
might	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
upper-end	O
they	O
stopped	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
Cole-yard	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
lost	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
get	O
more	O
help	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
armed	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
watchman	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
a	O
house	O
or	O
two	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
had	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Scepter	O
alehouse	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
knew	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
people	O
;	O
the	O
landlord	O
said	O
,	O
after	O
we	O
described	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
drinking	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
told	O
to	O
their	O
names	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
loaded	O
a	O
pistol	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
that	O
you	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Bugg	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
appeared	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
cloaths	O
they	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
only	O
their	O
hats	O
and	O
wigs	O
were	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
arms	O
and	O
whip	O
were	O
dropped	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
there	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
searched	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
your	O
penknife	O
again	O
?	O
Bugg	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Broughton	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
know	O
my	O
face	O
by	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
any	O
particular	O
mark	O
?	O
Bugg	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mark	O
of	O
a	O
flambeaux	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
his	O
face	O
appeared	O
as	O
it	O
does	O
now	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Hayes	O
.	O
Were	O
we	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
of	O
shelter	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
public	O
street	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
passed	O
us	O
?	O
Bugg	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
public	O
street	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Maid	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
my	O
beat	O
is	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
calling	O
the	O
hour	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
by	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
men	O
could	O
he	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
them	O
and	O
their	O
dress	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
tall	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
thick	O
man	O
,	O
both	O
in	O
blue-grey	O
;	O
the	O
shortest	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
horseman	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
buckskin	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
boots	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
whip	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
fearful	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
them	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
armed	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
called	O
my	O
round	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
hat	O
(	O
he	O
having	O
none	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
)	O
to	O
disguise	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
in	O
Newtoner's-lane	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
stood	O
as	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
making	O
water	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
sleeve	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
they	O
answered	O
the	O
description	O
given	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boots	O
and	O
horsewhip	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
on	O
apace	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bugg	O
being	O
fat	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
walk	O
fast	O
enough	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
some	O
little	O
way	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
blew	O
out	O
my	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
slung	O
my	O
lanthorn	O
to	O
a	O
hook	O
at	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
watched	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
Cole	O
yard	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
Mr.	O
King	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
the	O
prisoners	O
the	O
men	O
you	O
saw	O
in	O
Newtoner's-Lane	O
?	O
Maid	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Ind	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Scepter	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
charged	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
King	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
stopped	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Those	O
are	O
the	O
very	O
men	O
we	O
saw	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
and	O
followed	O
afterwards	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
watchman	O
came	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
they	O
described	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
mentions	O
the	O
cloaths	O
as	O
the	O
others	O
had	O
done	O
)	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Hall	O
and	O
Brian	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Ind	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Bugg	O
described	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Ind	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
three	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
there	O
that	O
afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
soon	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Hays	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Broughton	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
also	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
hanger	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
said	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
took	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
by	O
whom	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ind	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Scepter	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bugg	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
evidences	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
that	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
once	O
fetched	O
Hays	O
from	O
Salisbury	O
goal	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
ironed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
come	O
and	O
pay	O
me	O
a	O
visit	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
'd	O
do	O
me	O
a	O
mischief	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
crown	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
Broughton	O
wanted	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
whip	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
pledge	O
;	O
then	O
Hays	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
not	O
borrow	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
get	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
James	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
audacious	O
lay	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
;	O
he	O
laugh	O
'd	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
described	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
they	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
being	O
dressed	O
as	O
they	O
described	O
;	O
I	O
loaded	O
my	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
stopped	O
just	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
hanger-belt	O
from	O
off	O
Broughton	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
had	O
a	O
scabbard	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Elias	B-pers
Linder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
mob	O
come	O
down	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
near	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
calling	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
Parker's-lane	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
Hays	O
was	O
running	O
down	O
Drury-lane	O
with	O
this	O
hanger	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
drawn	O
,	O
two	O
men	O
had	O
once	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
got	O
clear	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Bugg	O
's	O
door	O
he	O
fell	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
the	O
hanger	O
as	O
he	O
fell	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
penknife	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Bugg	O
say	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Connaway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Broughton	O
throw	O
the	O
pistol	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pistol	O
and	O
sword	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
pistol	O
loaded	O
?	O
Connaway	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
drew	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
lighting	O
a	O
lady	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
made	O
towards	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
cocked	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
horsewhip	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
running	O
:	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
flambeaux	O
over	O
the	O
face	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
having	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
answered	O
to	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Broughton	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
described	O
his	O
cloaths	O
as	O
the	O
others	O
had	O
done	O
before	O
.	O
)	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
pursued	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
commit	O
another	O
robbery	O
.	O
Broughton	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
,	O
from	O
six	O
o'clock	O
till	O
past	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
Eleanor	O
Hall	O
was	O
there	O
a	O
washing	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
(	O
But	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
appeared	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Hays	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
For	O
Hays	O
,	O
see	O
No	O
.	O
271	O
,	O
in	O
Cokayne	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
133	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Whitmore	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
forty	O
false	O
,	O
feigned	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
pieces	O
of	O
coin	O
of	O
this	O
kingdom	O
,	O
called	O
shillings	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
Matthias	O
Standfast	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
detect	O
some	O
coiners	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
Man	O
,	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
Red-lion	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
;	O
we	O
found	O
forty	O
counterfeit	O
shillings	O
in	O
a	O
cavity	O
under	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
also	O
some	O
implements	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
rents	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Standfast	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Mary	O
Hays	O
does	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Headborough	O
:	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trustram	I-pers
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
coiners	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Strinubold	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Constable	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
's	O
room	O
)	O
we	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
he	O
produced	O
,	O
plaster	O
of	O
Paris	O
,	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
a	O
file	O
,	O
a	O
bottle	O
with	O
some	O
quicksilver	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
forty	O
pieces	O
of	O
coin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
coin	O
is	O
made	O
of	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
made	O
of	O
pewter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
they	O
imitate	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
King	O
William	O
's	O
shillings	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trustram	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
Mary	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
does	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
seemingly	O
confus	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
bad	O
company	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
company	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
a	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
were	O
hid	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Standfast	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
behind	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
Hays	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
covered	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
cloths	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
signal	O
to	O
shew	O
us	O
that	O
the	O
money	O
lay	O
there	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Standfast	O
took	O
this	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
wrap	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
rag	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
like	O
shillings	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
pewter	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
The	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
last	O
summer	O
I	O
saw	O
Ann	B-pers
Whitmore	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
at	O
work	O
on	O
this	O
money	O
in	O
Hog	O
lane	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
Baker	O
see	O
Numb	O
.	O
601	O
,	O
in	O
Cokayne	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
)	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
at	O
whose	O
house	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
casting	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
mould	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
pewter	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
finished	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
twopenny	O
loaf	O
,	O
and	O
cheese	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
month	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
came	O
so	O
early	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
was	O
in	O
some	O
goal	O
,	O
either	O
New-Prison	O
or	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
again	O
,	O
there	O
sat	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
those	O
counterfeit	O
shillings	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
,	O
finishing	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
upon	O
my	O
word	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
begin	O
and	O
finish	O
these	O
sort	O
of	O
things	O
five	O
years	O
ago	O
:	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
put	O
some	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
again	O
with	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
more	O
:	O
I	O
pretended	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
shops	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
put	O
them	O
between	O
my	O
teeth	O
,	O
and	O
bit	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
,	O
pretending	O
that	O
people	O
had	O
tried	O
them	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
leave	O
her	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
she	O
saw	O
what	O
would	O
become	O
of	O
Baker	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
see	O
me	O
hang	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
meant	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
hold	O
her	O
head	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
tongue	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
her	O
neck	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
you	O
so	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
this	O
man	O
where	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
advis	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
she	O
then	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
Monday	O
to	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
By	O
all	O
relations	O
this	O
Mrs.	O
Baker	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
were	O
old	O
practitioners	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
as	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
plain	O
work	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
cripple	O
for	O
five	O
weeks	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
till	O
the	O
Constable	O
brought	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hole	O
.	O
M	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
About	O
eighteen	O
years	O
ago	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
cast	O
for	O
her	O
life	O
for	O
such	O
Practices	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
was	O
burnt	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
the	O
winter	O
before	O
that	O
;	O
her	O
sister	O
was	O
also	O
cast	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
transported	O
;	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
last	O
summer	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
for	O
changing	O
some	O
such	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
you	O
put	O
off	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
her	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
five	O
years	O
ago	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
three	O
years	O
running	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
benefit	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
so	O
doing	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
She	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
what	O
she	O
pleas	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
will	O
you	O
do	O
me	O
one	O
favour	O
?	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
nam	O
'd	O
Baker	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Strong	O
,	O
has	O
happen	O
'd	O
into	O
a	O
sad	O
scrape	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
got	O
into	O
either	O
Bridewell	O
or	O
New-Prison	O
;	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
there	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
walk	O
so	O
far	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
herself	O
,	O
but	O
wish	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
trusty	O
friend	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
to	O
trust	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
prison	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
walk	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
mind	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
she	O
perswaded	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
stay	O
all	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
night	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
two	O
six	O
pences	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
nobody	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
but	O
she	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
do	O
you	O
accuse	O
me	O
with	O
robbing	O
you	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
six	O
pence	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
ways	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
do	O
n't	O
make	O
words	O
about	O
it	O
you	O
must	O
breakfast	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
lock	O
'd	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
for	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
and	O
went	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
for	O
some	O
chips	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
fire	O
,	O
she	O
returned	O
without	O
any	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
these	O
men	O
rapp	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
we	O
are	O
come	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
some	O
melted	O
mettle	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
meant	O
,	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
what	O
is	O
this	O
about	O
mettle	O
?	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
men	O
search	O
'd	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
this	O
money	O
and	O
my	O
two	O
sixpences	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
dread	O
;	O
we	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
say	O
you	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
M	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
She	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
set	O
stamps	O
with	O
them	O
two	O
six-pences	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
leave	O
off	O
making	O
shillings	O
:	O
she	O
has	O
lived	O
first	O
with	O
one	O
man	O
,	O
then	O
another	O
,	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
Patrick	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
made	O
evidence	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
information	O
,	O
thinking	O
to	O
strengthen	O
his	O
evidence	O
more	O
against	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
599	O
,	O
in	O
Cokayne	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
know	O
me	O
put	O
some	O
off	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
put	O
all	O
off	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
off	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
instruments	O
did	O
I	O
use	O
in	O
making	O
this	O
money	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
She	O
made	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
wooden	O
instrument	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
made	O
by	O
a	O
Joyner	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
cut	O
a	O
spout	O
to	O
pour	O
the	O
mettle	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
maker	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
chocolate	O
in	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
put	O
any	O
off	O
for	O
me	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
body	O
but	O
my	O
self	O
that	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
shops	O
and	O
change	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
London	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
place	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
strange	O
she	O
ca	O
n't	O
find	O
some	O
person	O
that	O
has	O
seen	O
me	O
with	O
bad	O
money	O
or	O
putting	O
it	O
off	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
:	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
could	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
divers	O
places	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
tried	O
in	O
this	O
Court	O
yourself	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
fact	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
give	O
your	O
evidence	O
here	O
on	O
such	O
an	O
occasion	O
?	O
M	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
It	O
does	O
appear	O
by	O
searching	O
the	O
short-hand	O
minutes	O
of	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
E.	O
Baker	O
,	O
Hays	O
did	O
give	O
her	O
evidence	O
against	O
her	O
as	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
134	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Stephen	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
certain	O
order	O
for	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
To	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
,	O
Merchant	O
,	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Jamaica	O
.	O
SIR.	O
``	O
Please	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
bearer	O
Stephen	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
the	O
sum	O
``	O
of	O
ten	O
pounds	O
ten	O
shilling	O
being	O
wages	O
due	O
from	O
``	O
the	O
ship	O
Lovely	O
Ann	O
,	O
``	O
And	O
you	O
will	O
oblige	O
,	O
``	O
Your	O
humble	O
servant	O
,	O
``	O
Francis	B-pers
Taiton	I-pers
.	O
''	O
and	O
offering	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Francis	B-pers
Taiton	I-pers
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
Nov.	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Tevamlow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Ratcliff-Cross	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
Jamaica	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
ten	O
guineas	O
for	O
the	O
run	O
home	O
in	O
the	O
Lovely	O
Ann	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
a	O
lodging	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
accepted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
landlord	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
take	O
my	O
note	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
certain	O
Francis	B-pers
Taiton	I-pers
,	O
till	O
I	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
merchant	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
must	O
send	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
slip	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
another	O
shilling	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
friend	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
lodge	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
security	O
I	O
had	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
lent	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
note	O
:	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
another	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Both	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
cheat	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
wrote	O
both	O
the	O
notes	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
Captain	O
's	O
name	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
once	O
failed	O
with	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
notes	O
produced	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
read	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
135	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Bulline	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guns	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
two	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Prescilla	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
four	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
four	O
linnen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
one	O
cloath	O
coat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Grover	I-pers
,	O
December	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Grover	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
at	O
Stanmore	B-place
;	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
twenty-second	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
stable	O
and	O
bolted	O
the	O
door	O
within	O
side	O
;	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
but	O
they	O
that	O
knew	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
stables	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
opens	O
to	O
the	O
common	O
standing	O
wide	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
box-coat	O
gone	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
also	O
my	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
coat	O
,	O
shoes	O
,	O
boots	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
gun	O
,	O
which	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
my	O
bed-side	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
long	O
gun	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
binn	O
below	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
the	O
sheets	O
from	O
the	O
bed	O
till	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
my	O
mistress	O
with	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
searched	O
the	O
hay	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
and	O
advertised	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
guineas	O
reward	O
:	O
on	O
Thursday	O
or	O
Friday	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bourne	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
in	O
broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
afterwards	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
short	O
gun	O
carried	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baily	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
advertised	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Morton	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
had	O
word	O
sent	O
by	O
Colonel	O
Mountague	B-pers
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
Nottingham	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
my	O
boots	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
shirts	O
,	O
marked	O
H.	O
G.	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
other	O
gun	O
at	O
Northampton	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
directions	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
should	O
give	O
my	O
Mistress	O
all	O
this	O
trouble	O
(	O
He	O
once	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
guns	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Bourne	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Morton	O
confirmed	O
that	O
of	O
their	O
buying	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
and	O
the	O
gun	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
136	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Sandford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spur	O
,	O
valued	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Clowes	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
137	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Aaron	B-pers
Cohen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty-two	O
Leghorn	O
straw	O
hats	O
,	O
value	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mordecai	B-pers
Cohen	I-pers
,	O
February	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
138	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Roger	B-pers
Woldridge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Laboure	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Laboure	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
Cornhill	B-place
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
there	O
stood	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
took	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
there	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
shewed	O
four	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
he	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
last	O
?	O
Laboure	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
not	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
boy	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
and	O
welcome	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
90	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
139	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cavendish	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
sauce-pan	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Litton	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
140	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
thirteen	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Francis	O
,	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
going	O
home	O
through	O
Drury	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
h.	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
cross	O
the	O
kennel	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
with	O
what	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
apron	O
and	O
thirteen	O
pence	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
murder	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
second	O
blow	O
,	O
and	O
again	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
you	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
;	O
he	O
cut	O
my	O
eyebrow	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
bled	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
;	O
he	O
snatched	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
off	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
great	O
observation	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
cloaths	O
and	O
his	O
voice	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
goal	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
shewing	O
me	O
one	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
;	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
colour	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
cut	O
my	O
apron	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
afterwards	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
thought	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Harlequin	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Fox	O
and	O
spent	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
goal	O
two	O
months	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
E.	O
Manning	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
goal	O
till	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
another	O
robbery	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
some	O
leather	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
:	O
In	O
September	O
last	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
detained	O
as	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	O
Jones	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
prison	O
;	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
likew	O
ise	O
knew	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
robbed	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
to	O
go	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
taken	O
that	O
had	O
committed	O
many	O
robberies	O
in	O
and	O
near	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Dame	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
you	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
remember	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
you	O
robbed	O
me	O
in	O
Drury	O
lane	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
an	O
apron	O
and	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
thirteen-pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
cut	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
eye	O
,	O
and	O
pointed	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
eye	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
eye	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
shewed	O
a	O
scar	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
said	O
also	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Fox	O
and	O
Goose	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
her	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
others	O
concerned	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
and	O
constable	O
to	O
the	O
goal	O
.	O
She	O
confirmed	O
that	O
of	O
their	O
conversation	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
about	O
sixty	O
people	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
affair	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
with	O
one	O
Peter	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
,	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
arm	O
in	O
arm	O
;	O
she	O
missed	O
her	O
apron	O
in	O
the	O
Fox	O
and	O
Goose	O
in	O
the	O
Play-house	O
Passage	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
man	O
searched	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
act	O
a	O
part	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
receive	O
a	O
farthing	O
of	O
value	O
from	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
parish	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Church-lane	O
by	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
so	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Ask	O
that	O
witness	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Fox	O
and	O
Goose	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
Hurst	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Collings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
Monday	O
,	O
early	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
last	O
summer	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
was	O
robbed	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
nor	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
herself	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
greed	O
waistcoat	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
who	O
struck	O
her	O
and	O
knocked	O
her	O
down	O
:	O
then	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
a	O
man	O
far	O
less	O
than	O
he	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
apron	O
:	O
when	O
the	O
people	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
opened	O
her	O
mouth	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
herself	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
drunken	O
robbery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
7	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
141	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Powney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Downes	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
three	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
half-pint	O
mug	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
five	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
garters	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
linnen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
+	O
Mrs.	O
Downes	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
:	O
my	O
daughter	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
made	O
fast	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to-bed	O
:	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
she	O
awakened	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
heard	O
the	O
chain	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
move	O
:	O
we	O
both	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
till	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
noise	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
watchman	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
windows	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
fast	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
wide	O
open	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
till	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
maids	O
up	O
:	O
he	O
called	O
also	O
another	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
backdoor	O
was	O
also	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
no	O
mark	O
of	O
violence	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
thought	O
that	O
was	O
opened	O
after	O
the	O
person	O
was	O
in	O
:	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
lost	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
buroe	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
five	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
milk	O
pot	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
half	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
garters	O
with	O
silver	O
buckles	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
came	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
spoon	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
stopped	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Downes	O
's	O
cook	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
if	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
two-pair-of-stairs	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
by	O
getting	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
gutter	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
buroe	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
buried	O
all	O
the	O
plate	O
under	O
the	O
pavement	O
in	O
a	O
stable	O
where	O
he	O
works	O
in	O
Adam	O
's	O
muse	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
a	O
servant	O
there	O
,	O
one	O
Edward	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
;	O
he	O
brought	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
along	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
when	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
things	O
:	O
he	O
confessed	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
had	O
in	O
two	O
places	O
,	O
one	O
parcel	O
under	O
the	O
manger	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
parcel	O
in	O
another	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
under	O
ground	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
tablespoon	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
spoon	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Downes	O
's	O
servant	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Downes	O
's	O
house	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
till	O
my	O
husband	O
informed	O
me	O
afterwards	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
spoon	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
(	O
She	O
produced	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
others	O
by	O
its	O
being	O
wore	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
bowl	O
.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Downes	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
much	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
some	O
of	O
our	O
own	O
servants	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
somebody	O
who	O
was	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
spoon	O
,	O
telling	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
tall	O
man	O
,	O
named	O
Powney	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
spoon	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
deposed	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
signed	O
his	O
confession	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lees	I-pers
.	O
(	O
He	O
is	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
Confession	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
name	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
writing	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
sign	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wrote	O
mine	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
witness	O
,	O
before	O
Samuel	B-pers
Thrasher	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
without	O
any	O
threatening	O
or	O
promises	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Justice	O
also	O
sign	O
his	O
name	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
is	O
read	O
,	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
)	O
``	O
That	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
Marlow	O
's	O
stable	O
,	O
that	O
join	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Downes	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
there	O
lighted	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
open	O
a	O
buroe	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
opened	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
went	O
to	O
pawn	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
table	O
spoons	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
buried	O
the	O
plate	O
as	O
before	O
mentioned	O
.	O
''	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
142	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Jefferys	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
Charles	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ely	B-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
Holborn	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
about	O
break	O
of	O
day	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
,	O
named	O
James	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
hanging	O
up	O
to	O
dry	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
come	O
up	O
stairs	O
besides	O
the	O
alehouse	O
boy	O
;	O
Black	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
nobody	O
come	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
over	O
against	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
in	O
Turn-again	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
me	O
Mr.	O
Powell	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
once	O
lived	O
,	O
who	O
talked	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Griffith	O
's	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Lane	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
shirts	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
woman	O
ran	O
away	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
this	O
boy	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Horshoe	O
and	O
Magpye	O
at	O
Holborn	O
Bridge	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
recollected	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
going	O
up	O
Holborn	O
the	O
boy	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lodged	O
them	O
in	O
Fleet	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
now	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
there	O
to	O
demand	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
six	O
shirts	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Black	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
morning	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
sawaying	O
about	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
7	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
143	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burges	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Leeman	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Dec.	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Susannah	B-pers
Leeman	I-pers
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Rummer	B-place
Tavern	I-place
in	I-place
Chancery-Lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
many	O
plates	O
and	O
things	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
twelfth	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
lost	O
several	O
plates	O
and	O
dishes	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
scullery	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
stopped	O
some	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
Rummer	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
John	B-pers
Leeman	I-pers
's	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
come	O
through	O
my	O
house	O
several	O
times	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
several	O
of	O
my	O
plates	O
cut	O
in	O
four	O
pieces	O
,	O
(	O
each	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Smith	O
and	O
Broker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
plates	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
I	O
stopped	O
them	O
and	O
informed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
she	O
could	O
sell	O
some	O
pewter	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
small	O
trifle	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
144	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
vessel	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
butt	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hope	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
and	O
Co	O
.	O
Dec.	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
145	O
,	O
146.	O
John	B-pers
Shovel	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Westcote	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
February	O
17	O
.	O
||	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
147	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
not	O
taken	O
;	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
plank	O
of	O
mahogany	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tickle	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
and	O
Co	O
.	O
Jan	O
25	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
148	O
,	O
149	O
,	O
150.	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
where	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
did	O
utter	O
and	O
publish	O
as	O
true	O
a	O
certain	O
false	O
forged	O
promissary	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
25	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Agent	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
regiment	O
that	O
Captain	O
Andrew	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
was	O
pay-master	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
Captain	O
Andrew	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
write	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
is	O
show	O
'd	O
a	O
paper	O
)	O
I	O
wrote	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
Captain	O
Andrew	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
wrote	O
his	O
name	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
is	O
show	O
'd	O
another	O
)	O
The	O
body	O
of	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
clerk	O
's	O
writing	O
;	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
,	O
is	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
own	O
writing	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
sign	O
that	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
is	O
show	O
'd	O
the	O
note	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
name	O
to	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
writing	O
nor	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
different	O
as	O
any	O
two	O
hands	O
can	O
be	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Agnue	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
the	O
Captain	O
talk	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Richardson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Colonel	O
Steward	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Captain	O
Agnue	B-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
?	O
Steward	O
.	O
I	O
once	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
read	O
it	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
die	O
?	O
Steward	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
is	O
shew	O
'd	O
several	O
papers	O
.	O
)	O
Two	O
of	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
hand	O
writing	O
:	O
the	O
note	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
is	O
not	O
my	O
writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
name	O
to	O
that	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
Steward	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
like	O
his	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
it	O
like	O
his	O
writing	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
extreamly	O
intimate	O
with	O
the	O
captain	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
of	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
?	O
Steward	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
affair	O
broke	O
out	O
the	O
widow	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
a	O
person	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
thinking	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Captain	O
had	O
such	O
an	O
acquintance	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
know	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
came	O
.	O
Kenneth	B-pers
Mackenzey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Captain	O
Andrew	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
and	O
have	O
often	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Mackenzey	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
witness	O
to	O
several	O
deeds	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
also	O
here	O
two	O
letters	O
he	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
They	O
are	O
compared	O
with	O
the	O
names	O
on	O
some	O
notes	O
before	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
names	O
agree	O
,	O
he	O
looks	O
upon	O
the	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
the	O
names	O
are	O
Captain	O
Agnue	B-pers
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
shewed	O
the	O
note	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
dont	O
believe	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
:	O
I	O
dont	O
think	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
Captain	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
have	O
wrote	O
like	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
is	O
to	O
be	O
observed	O
the	O
body	O
and	O
name	O
are	O
two	O
different	O
hands	O
.	O
)	O
Neither	O
the	O
body	O
or	O
name	O
are	O
like	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
writing	O
,	O
far	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Agnue	O
,	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Steward	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Captain	O
give	O
a	O
petition	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Cumberland	O
for	O
me	O
?	O
Steward	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Agnue	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
not	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
petition	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mackenzey	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
Captain	O
Agnue	B-pers
die	O
?	O
Mackenzey	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
is	O
his	O
lawful	O
executrix	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Agnue	O
from	O
March	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Agnue	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
last	O
May	O
with	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
Mrs.	O
Agnue	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
is	O
shewed	O
a	O
letter	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
mistress	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
give	O
that	O
letter	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
read	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
for	O
an	O
answer	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Dunbar	O
,	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
this	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
was	O
,	O
which	O
name	O
was	O
to	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
Spring-gardens	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Agnue	O
.	O
Did	O
that	O
witness	O
hear	O
any	O
talk	O
then	O
about	O
money	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
dont	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
said	O
than	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Agnue	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
not	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
Captain	O
Agnue	B-pers
talk	O
pretty	O
much	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
about	O
you	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Agnue	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
Captain	O
Agnue	B-pers
when	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Mincing-Lane	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
Captain	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
he	O
removed	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Casterd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dunbar	O
,	O
going	O
on	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
Captain	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Dunbar	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
Captain	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
house	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
buried	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
of	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
Captain	O
was	O
buried	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
his	O
reason	O
for	O
asking	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
relation	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Agnue	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
buried	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
vault	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Dunbar	O
,	O
near	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
heard	O
before	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
relation	O
?	O
Casterd	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
24	O
l.	O
(	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
)	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Agnue	O
,	O
had	O
of	O
his	O
on	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
law	O
suit	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
such	O
note	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Agnue	O
would	O
honourably	O
discharge	O
it	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
captain	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Dunbar	O
in	O
Mincing-lane	O
?	O
Casterd	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
moved	O
from	O
thence	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Mincing-lane	O
,	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
,	O
January	O
was	O
twelve	O
months	O
:	O
the	O
boy	O
of	O
the	O
ale-house	O
came	O
over	O
for	O
either	O
the	O
coachman	O
or	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
dressing	O
himself	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
buried	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
talk	O
of	O
being	O
related	O
that	O
first	O
time	O
?	O
Casterd	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Casterd	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
acquaint	O
your	O
master	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
?	O
Casterd	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
nor	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
To	O
prove	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
said	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
the	O
letter	O
of	O
administration	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
dated	O
August	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
wherein	O
it	O
appeared	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
relict	O
of	O
Captain	O
Andrew	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
,	O
was	O
the	O
real	O
executrix	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Mackenzey	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Agnue	O
to	O
order	O
Mr.	O
Dagg	O
,	O
to	O
enquire	O
into	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
this	O
note	O
,	O
she	O
not	O
allowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Dunbar	O
had	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
signed	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
that	O
came	O
,	O
demanding	O
payment	O
on	O
this	O
note	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Barnard	O
Agnue	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
:	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
applied	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
this	O
note	O
;	O
(	O
holding	O
up	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
recover	O
the	O
money	O
due	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
's	O
widow	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
in	O
Great-Marlborough-Street	O
:	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Dunbar	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
never	O
owed	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
a	O
shilling	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
it	O
her	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
note	O
might	O
not	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
name	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Agnue	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
money	O
upon	O
the	O
note	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
put	O
such	O
a	O
note	O
as	O
that	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
's	O
handwriting	O
:	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
bring	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
witnesses	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
the	O
money	O
lent	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Agnue	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
money	O
to	O
carry	O
or	O
a	O
law-suit	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
money	O
at	O
the	O
Lebeck's-Head	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
drawn	O
by	O
Andrew	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
:	O
I	O
desired	O
h	O
e	O
would	O
bring	O
these	O
witnesses	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
night	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
witnesses	O
.	O
which	O
were	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
parlour	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
my	O
seeing	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
of	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
's	O
lending	O
the	O
other	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
did	O
know	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
him	O
lend	O
the	O
money	O
at	O
the	O
Lebeck's-Head	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
produce	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
them	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
Fox	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
Andrew	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
sign	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
Fox	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Captain	O
Agnue	B-pers
,	O
nor	O
saw	O
him	O
sign	O
a	O
note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Gale	O
say	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
Gale	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
Fox	O
has	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Andrew	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
sign	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spectacles	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
note	O
in	O
Fox	O
's	O
hand	O
or	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
speak	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
as	O
a	O
person	O
whom	O
they	O
knew	O
before	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Agnue	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
satisfaction	O
from	O
two	O
witnesses	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
,	O
that	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
lent	O
and	O
the	O
note	O
signed	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
appoint	O
some	O
person	O
to	O
enquire	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
bring	O
an	O
action	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
After	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Dagg	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
giving	O
me	O
a	O
receipt	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
on	O
demand	O
:	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
appoint	O
the	O
three	O
persons	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
others	O
to	O
enquire	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
note	O
a	O
true	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Captain	O
Agnue	B-pers
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
:	O
I	O
appointed	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
Tavern	O
without	O
Temple-Bar	O
:	O
we	O
met	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
:	O
Mr.	O
Dagg	O
brought	O
Mackenzey	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
then	O
produced	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Dagg	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
such	O
questions	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
proper	O
:	O
then	O
it	O
seemed	O
clear	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
their	O
answers	O
agreed	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
lent	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
note	O
read	O
.	O
)	O
London	O
,	O
February	O
3	O
,	O
1751.	O
``	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
,	O
or	O
``	O
order	O
,	O
upon	O
demand	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
twenty-five	O
``	O
Pounds	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
for	O
value	O
received.	O
``	O
By	O
Andrew	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
,	O
senior	O
.	O
''	O
Q.	O
to	O
Saunders	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Mrs.	O
Agnue	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Dagg	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
appointed	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
this	O
note	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
message	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
in	O
relation	O
to	O
a	O
note	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
demanded	O
payment	O
of	O
on	O
Mrs.	O
Agnue	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
my	O
desire	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
note	O
upon	O
my	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
receipt	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
upon	O
demand	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Saunders	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
same	O
note	O
(	O
the	O
note	O
produc	O
'd	O
)	O
you	O
received	O
from	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Dagg	O
continues	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
chamber	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
Witnesses	O
Fox	O
and	O
Gale	O
,	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
their	O
names	O
,	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
thing	O
,	O
(	O
having	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
)	O
then	O
I	O
appointed	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
to	O
meet	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
Tavern	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
these	O
men	O
appeared	O
men	O
of	O
reputation	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
prove	O
that	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
advanced	O
by	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnue	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
note	O
signed	O
,	O
my	O
client	O
should	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Dunbar	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Agnue	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
an	O
information	O
against	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
;	O
he	O
granted	O
a	O
warrant	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Mackenzey	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
Tavern	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
long	O
before	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
I	O
first	O
produced	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Saunders	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
whether	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
note	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
did	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
whether	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnue	O
gave	O
him	O
that	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
value	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
some	O
protestation	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
exactly	O
recollect	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
live	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
like	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
money	O
paid	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnue	O
,	O
was	O
24	O
guineas	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
a	O
law	O
suit	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
understand	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
Dagg	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
deposited	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
expence	O
of	O
a	O
law	O
suit	O
which	O
was	O
coming	O
on	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
examin	O
'd	O
Fox	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Surgeon	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Wheat-Sheaf	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
February	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
at	O
the	O
Lebeck	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
that	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnue	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
saw	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
advance	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnue	O
24	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnue	O
sign	O
the	O
note	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
produced	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
examined	O
Gale	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
very	O
little	O
but	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Fox	O
has	O
said	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
also	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
Broker	O
,	O
and	O
liv	O
'd	O
behind	O
Guy	O
's	O
Hospital	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
shew	O
them	O
the	O
note	O
?	O
Dagg	O
I	O
think	O
Fox	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
as	O
I	O
held	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
Gale	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
he	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
signed	O
by	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnue	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
examined	O
separately	O
;	O
they	O
agreed	O
in	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
at	O
the	O
Lebeck	O
's	O
Head	O
with	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnue	O
when	O
he	O
signed	O
the	O
note	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
hot	O
red	O
wine	O
;	O
I	O
knowing	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
drank	O
red	O
wine	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
drank	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
glasses	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
gave	O
a	O
different	O
account	O
of	O
their	O
coming	O
there	O
;	O
one	O
said	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnue	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
together	O
;	O
another	O
said	O
they	O
met	O
him	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
said	O
they	O
came	O
separate	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Colonel	O
Steward	O
.	O
Had	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnue	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
drink	O
red	O
wine	O
lately	O
?	O
Col	O
.	O
Steward	O
.	O
He	O
drank	O
no	O
red	O
wine	O
for	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Gale	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
I	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnue	O
?	O
Dagg	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
owned	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnue	O
sign	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
put	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
what	O
service	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
prove	O
the	O
forgery	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
High	O
Constable	O
of	O
Holborn	O
division	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
Tavern	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Dagg	O
has	O
said	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
truth	O
.	O
Fox	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
confirmation	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
wrote	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
pocket-book	O
produced	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mackenzey	O
.	O
What	O
Mr.	O
Dagg	O
has	O
said	O
is	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
the	O
case	O
.	O
Fox	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
Captain	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
Sir	O
Andrew	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Barnard	B-pers
Agnue	I-pers
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
sent	O
an	O
account	O
into	O
Scotland	O
of	O
the	O
Captain	O
's	O
death	O
to	O
his	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
of	O
very	O
great	O
service	O
to	O
the	O
family	O
;	O
this	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
satisfy	O
us	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
Agnue	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Agnue	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
Gibraltar	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Syms	O
's	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
respects	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
being	O
acquainted	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Cumberland	O
had	O
proposed	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
rebellion	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
Captain	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
way	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
petition	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
none	O
,	O
nor	O
carry	O
any	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
friend	O
that	O
would	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
one	O
drawn	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
find	O
a	O
friend	O
who	O
would	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
petition	O
drawn	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
twenty-four	O
guineas	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
a	O
law-suit	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
thinking	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
would	O
prevail	O
on	O
an	O
attorney	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
:	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
an	O
attorney	O
,	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
kept	O
it	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
another	O
:	O
I	O
offered	O
him	O
my	O
papers	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
never	O
employed	O
any	O
attorney	O
in	O
London	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
of	O
one	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
preserve	O
this	O
money	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
do	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
favour	O
possible	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
memorandum	O
:	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
a	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
gentleman	O
with	O
him	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
a	O
memorandum	O
:	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
minded	O
it	O
more	O
till	O
he	O
handed	O
me	O
the	O
paper	O
.	O
Fox	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
As	O
Mr.	O
Gale	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Chairing-Cross	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Agnue	O
called	O
me	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Lebeck	O
's	O
Head	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
whom	O
they	O
called	O
Captain	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
busy	O
in	O
talking	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
about	O
money	O
,	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
giving	O
or	O
receving	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
money	O
deposited	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
Gale	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
money	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
twenty-four	O
guineas	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
about	O
a	O
law-suit	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
old	O
and	O
my	O
memory	O
fails	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
Captain	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
For	O
Agnue	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Agnue	O
lodged	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
one	O
time	O
either	O
in	O
April	O
or	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
very	O
much	O
surprized	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
Nanny	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
surprize	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
and	O
have	O
heard	O
Captain	O
Agnue	B-pers
is	O
dead	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
best	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fear	O
all	O
my	O
money	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
A.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
In	O
Vinegar-yard	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Scot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Agnue	O
lodge	O
there	O
?	O
A.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
A.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
come	O
from	O
sea	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
follows	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Tase	I-pers
.	O
I	O
some	O
times	O
go	O
to	O
service	O
,	O
otherwise	O
I	O
go	O
a	O
chearing	O
or	O
ironing	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
Agnue	O
,	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
kept	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
demand	O
on	O
this	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
put	O
people	O
off	O
when	O
they	O
have	O
come	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
upon	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
demanded	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
people	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
name	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
Tase	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
Captain	O
Agnue	B-pers
,	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
does	O
the	O
prisoner	O
follow	O
?	O
Tase	O
.	O
He	O
follows	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
genteely	O
and	O
decent	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Agnue	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
once	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
a	O
law-suit	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
surgeon	O
and	O
a	O
licensed	O
physician	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Agnue	O
three	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
visited	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
trial	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
his	O
cause	O
for	O
an	O
action	O
of	O
an	O
assault	O
by	O
his	O
captain	O
,	O
and	O
recovered	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
being	O
employed	O
for	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
;	O
he	O
now	O
owes	O
me	O
eight	O
guineas	O
.	O
For	O
Gale	O
.	O
Dionies	O
Denavove	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Gale	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
harm	O
by	O
him	O
while	O
he	O
lived	O
there	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Short's-Gardens	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
seven	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
little	O
knowledge	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
last	O
year	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Devon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
working	O
silversmith	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Gale	O
about	O
three	O
four	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
whatsoever	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Devon	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
wyerdrawer	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
honesty	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
Fox	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
151	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Adam	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
scarlet	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
etwee	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
Dresden	O
ruffles	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
white	O
holland	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Dec.	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
attended	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
brush	O
and	O
clean	O
his	O
cloaths	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
mornings	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
his	O
behaviour	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
him	O
taken	O
up	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
begged	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
etwee	O
and	O
scarlet	O
breeches	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
152.	O
Ann	B-pers
Walson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Ellard	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
by	O
fastening	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lift	O
about	O
her	O
neck	O
,	O
whereby	O
she	O
was	O
strangled	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
153	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
chocolate	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
154	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Allison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Masemore	I-pers
,	O
one	O
cheque	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
January	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
155	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
January	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
156.	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Bean	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
capuchine	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
No	O
prosecutor	O
appeared	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
157	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
flannel	O
petticoats	O
,	O
one	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
camblet	O
gown	O
,	O
two	O
linnen	O
aprons	O
,	O
three	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
one	O
beaver	O
hat	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
buckle	O
set	O
with	O
bristol	O
stones	O
,	O
one	O
gridiron	O
,	O
one	O
firest	O
ovel	O
,	O
and	O
seventeen	O
pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Green-Arbour-Court	B-place
,	I-place
Golden-Lane	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
13	O
th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to-bed	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
cat	O
that	O
had	O
a	O
bell	O
about	O
her	O
neck	O
,	O
she	O
flew	O
about	O
the	O
pillow	O
and	O
awaked	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
flew	O
to	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
light	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
cat	O
,	O
what	O
ails	O
you	O
?	O
she	O
still	O
flew	O
about	O
:	O
the	O
light	O
was	O
gone	O
in	O
a	O
moment	O
:	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
root	O
step	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
bed-side	O
:	O
my	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
hung	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Jemmy	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
stayed	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
than	O
ordinary	O
?	O
have	O
you	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
afright	O
me	O
?	O
(	O
I	O
thinking	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
husband	O
)	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
husband	O
:	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
make	O
no	O
resistance	O
,	O
your	O
husband	O
will	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
in	O
two	O
minutes	O
:	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
be	O
quick	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
will	O
,	O
speaking	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
vulgar	O
manner	O
:	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
blast	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
you	O
old	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
!	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
what	O
makes	O
you	O
use	O
me	O
so	O
?	O
who	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
will	O
not	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
old	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
,	O
speaking	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
vulgar	O
manner	O
:	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
hell	O
and	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
for	O
a	O
b	O
-	O
h	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
things	O
going	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
candlesticks	O
from	O
off	O
my	O
mantlepiece	O
,	O
a	O
cheque	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
a	O
hood	O
that	O
hung	O
on	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
pepperbox	O
,	O
one	O
gridiron	O
,	O
three	O
brass	O
knobs	O
off	O
a	O
stove	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
fireshovel	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
instrument	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
?	O
R.	O
Cook	O
.	O
He	O
threatened	O
me	O
and	O
affrighted	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
a	O
brandy-shop	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drawing	O
on	O
my	O
stockings	O
when	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
mad	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
came	O
once	O
before	O
with	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
were	O
all	O
the	O
times	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
)	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
such	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
:	O
my	O
husband	O
looked	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
described	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
alehouses	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
upon	O
me	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
and	O
his	O
cloaths	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
old	O
bitch	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
like	O
an	O
arrow	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
bow	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
down	O
Turk's-head-conrt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
cry	O
out	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
when	O
became	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
R.	O
Cook	O
.	O
He	O
threatened	O
me	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
affrighted	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
power	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
R.	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
sorrow	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
into	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
R.	O
Cook	O
.	O
The	O
key	O
was	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
R.	O
Cook	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
so	O
soon	O
?	O
R.	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
heaviness	O
and	O
was	O
so	O
for	O
some	O
days	O
.	O
Clarles	O
Hilton	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Green-Artour	O
court	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
door	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
lighted	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
standing	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
water	O
;	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
came	O
running	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
every	O
thing	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
standing	O
like	O
a	O
man	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
wits	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
a	O
publick-house	O
that	O
night	O
from	O
six	O
to	O
nine	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Three	O
Pigeons	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
found	O
my	O
door	O
broke	O
open	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
took	O
told	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
ragged	O
gown	O
:	O
said	O
she	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Keath	I-pers
.	O
If	O
common	O
fame	O
speaks	O
truth	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
very	O
bad	O
character	O
:	O
she	O
is	O
capable	O
of	O
swearing	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
hardly	O
a	O
worse	O
woman	O
living	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
confined	O
in	O
Newgate	O
for	O
a	O
crime	O
of	O
this	O
nature	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
nor	O
of	O
this	O
trial	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
158	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brockley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
19	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Fleet-market	B-place
going	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
snatched	O
my	O
hat	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
away	O
he	O
ran	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
anot	O
or	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
.	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
!	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
or	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
159	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jarvis	B-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Gervise	I-pers
Shay	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
thirty	O
six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
two	O
moidores	O
,	O
one	O
four	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpenny	O
piece	O
,	O
twenty-six	O
guineas	O
,	O
six	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shilling	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
14	O
.	O
||	O
Charles	B-pers
Bowden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
wine	O
and	O
brandy	O
warehouse	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
when	O
my	O
maid	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
buroe	O
open	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
and	O
the	O
warehouse	O
door	O
were	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
maid	O
,	O
my	O
man	O
,	O
taat	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
fellow-servant	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
:	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
from	O
my	O
Lord	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
fellow	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
searched	O
another	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop-by	O
the	O
Fleet-gate	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
boy	O
that	O
lodges	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
has	O
purchased	O
six	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
crackers	O
and	O
serpents	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
come	O
again	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Barnard	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
concerning	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barnard	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
Aldermen	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
picked	O
the	O
lock	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
buroe	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pigtail	O
wig	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
drank	O
some	O
green	O
usquebaugh	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
a	O
breeches-maker	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
four	O
guineas	O
left	O
:	O
when	O
going	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
himself	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
gold	O
watch	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
leads	O
on	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
breeches	O
and	O
wig	O
were	O
put	O
down	O
the	O
vault	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
spent	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
whoring	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
to	O
a	O
girl	O
,	O
in	O
drinking	O
,	O
in	O
birds	O
and	O
cages	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
eight	O
guineas	O
to	O
girls	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
about	O
ten	O
pounds	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
hole	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
generally	O
drove	O
it	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lent	O
five	O
guineas	O
to	O
a	O
cheer-woman	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
curing	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
clap	O
.	O
William	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
Martialmen	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Bowden	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
spent	O
it	O
all	O
on	O
women	O
,	O
coach-hire	O
,	O
and	O
plays	O
:	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
in	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Edward	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
first	O
accused	O
a	O
breeches-maker	O
with	O
being	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Bowden	O
's	O
money	O
himself	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
nor	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
perriwig	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
two	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
which	O
not	O
being	O
laid	O
capital	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
on	O
that	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
160	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Alice	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wig	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
two	O
coats	O
,	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shag	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
three	O
sheets	O
,	O
twelve	O
napkins	O
,	O
three	O
damask	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
four	O
aprons	O
,	O
three	O
linnen	O
stocks	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
linnen	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
Nov.	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
