TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
25th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Thomas	B-pers
Winterbottom	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1752	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
THOMAS	B-pers
WINTERBOTTOM	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
LEE	O
*	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BURNET	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
CLIVE	O
||	O
,	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
++	O
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.B	O
.	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Snow	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Garrerd	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Collier	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dent	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Wilder	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Merryman	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Ringwood	I-pers
,	O
Paul	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Leightenhouse	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Bonham	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Piddington	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cosh	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
William	O
Cosh	O
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Church	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
in	O
his	O
stead	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Duncan	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Baugh	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gibbons	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
,	O
Jervice	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
.	O
209	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hartley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dupree	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
two	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Dupree	I-pers
I	O
live	O
near	B-place
St.	I-place
Gyles	I-place
's	I-place
pound	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
In	O
the	O
fore	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
it	O
cry	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
some	O
thing	O
forced	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
such	O
cloaths	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
when	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
his	O
person	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
casement	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
my	O
leaden	O
pipe	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
fastened	O
to	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
broke	O
or	O
cut	O
off	O
;	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
turned	O
up	O
towards	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
for	O
carrying	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
child	O
almost	O
smothered	O
in	O
the	O
blankets	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
leaden	O
pipe	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
cock	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
Dupree	O
.	O
||	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
other	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Piece	O
of	O
leaden	O
pipe	O
with	O
a	O
ball	O
cock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
fixed	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Rosingburgh	I-pers
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
||	O
Frederick	B-pers
Rosingburgh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tyburn-road	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Ann	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
last	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
gushing	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
my	O
pipe	O
was	O
cut	O
that	O
was	O
fix	O
'd	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
party-wall	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
water	O
flying	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
lodges	O
above	O
,	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
ball	O
cock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
leaden	O
pipe	O
was	O
found	O
doubled	O
up	O
near	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
210	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
with	O
a	O
chrystal	O
heart	O
set	O
with	O
eleven	O
rose	O
diamonds	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
with	O
a	O
green	O
amethist	O
,	O
four	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
one	O
garnet	O
hoop	O
ring	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
snuff	O
boxes	O
,	O
one	O
oak	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
one	O
Pinchbeck	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
stay	O
buckles	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stable	I-pers
;	O
one	O
gold	O
case	O
to	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
two	O
mourning	O
rings	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
heart	O
for	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
,	O
gent	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stable	I-pers
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
||	O
Richard	B-pers
Stable	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James's-street	I-place
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
china	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
me	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
before	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
,	O
my	O
maid	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
cabinet	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
by	O
scratches	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
got	O
over	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
a	O
funnel	O
where	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
coals	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
sent	O
my	O
sister	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
to	O
enquire	O
whether	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
she	O
returned	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
informed	O
there	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Lediard	O
;	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
knowing	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
farther	O
examination	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
my	O
sister	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodging	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
hid	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
here	O
and	O
will	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
re-examined	O
and	O
was	O
shewed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
gold	O
case	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
gold	O
case	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
:	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
a	O
gause	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
accordingly	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
alone	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
chairman	O
's	O
horse	O
on	O
which	O
they	O
carry	O
their	O
goods	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
she	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
funnel	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Stable	O
.	O
The	O
gold	O
case	O
,	O
two	O
mourning	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
silver	O
heart	O
are	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Stable	O
's	O
cabinet	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
had	O
deposed	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stables	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
sister	O
,	O
confirmed	O
that	O
of	O
his	O
evidence	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Calvert	O
,	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
and	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
watch-case	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
tick	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bed	O
,	O
sewed	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
stocks	O
and	O
feathers	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bumstead	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
that	O
of	O
her	O
confession	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
211	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Cunningham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wadsworth	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
16	O
.	O
||	O
Ann	B-pers
Wadsworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
William	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
near	O
the	O
brick	O
field	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
gown	O
,	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
line	O
in	O
my	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
shirt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
shirt	O
in	O
thieving-lane	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
knowing	O
her	O
character	O
,	O
had	O
stopped	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
that	O
again	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wadsworth	I-pers
,	O
daughter	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
evi	O
dece	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Eady	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Wadsworth	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Jermyn-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turnbolt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
that	O
of	O
her	O
confession	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
212	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Salisbury	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
house	O
,	O
called	O
the	O
turnpike-house	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Smallbury-Green	I-place
,	O
on	O
Joseph	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
12	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Feb.	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
Joseph	O
Thompson	O
.	O
On	O
Feb.	O
21	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
on	O
Smallbury-Green	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
opened	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
door	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
thrust	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
warm	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
he	O
staid	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
minutes	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
have	O
no	O
saddle	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Windsor	O
party	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
captain	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
a	O
saddle	O
:	O
it	O
being	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
orders	O
must	O
be	O
obeyed	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
hands	O
are	O
pretty	O
warm	O
now	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
me	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
strangled	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
his	O
thumb	O
in	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bit	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
get	O
it	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
4	O
s.	O
then	O
he	O
saw	O
something	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
halfpence	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
half-pence	O
)	O
then	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Gate	O
!	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
soldier	O
's	O
cockade	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
knife	O
he	O
had	O
liked	O
to	O
have	O
killed	O
me	O
with	O
;	O
this	O
cockade	O
was	O
torn	O
from	O
off	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
partner	O
's	O
studded	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cupboard	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
left	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
Never	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
lighted	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
companions	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
None	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
produces	O
a	O
watch	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
)	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
in	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
six-pences	O
.	O
(	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
six-pences	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
batter	O
'd	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
.	O
he	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
he	O
believed	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Thompson	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
watch	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Patworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
at	O
Knights	O
bridge	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
intelligence	O
about	O
five	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
cut	O
the	O
turnpike-man	O
's	O
throat	O
on	O
Smallbury	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
by	O
the	O
descriptions	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
house	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
turnpike	O
at	O
Hyde-Park-Corner	O
we	O
alarmed	O
the	O
two	O
turnpike-men	O
,	O
they	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
watch-house	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
throw	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
over	O
Hyde-park-wall	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
watch	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Alesby	I-pers
to	O
see	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
so	O
run	O
the	O
prisoner	O
down	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
turnpike-men	O
,	O
at	O
Hyde-park-corner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
duty	O
Feb.	O
21	O
,	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Hagerty	I-pers
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Smallbury-green	O
turnpike-man	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
throat	O
cut	O
by	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
we	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
from	O
towards	O
Knights	O
bridge	O
,	O
we	O
both	O
run	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
were	O
pusuing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
under	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
staff	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
you	O
sir	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
must	O
I	O
stop	O
for	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
We	O
led	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
turnpikehouse	O
;	O
we	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
pull	O
his	O
gloves	O
off	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
before	O
told	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
turnpike-man	O
had	O
bit	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
thumb	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
was	O
bit	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
St	O
George	O
's	O
round-house	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
sent	O
word	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
thumb	O
was	O
bit	O
?	O
Hoskins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
his	O
right	O
thumb	O
;	O
the	O
biggest	O
mark	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
nuckle	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Thompson	O
.	O
Which	O
thumb	O
did	O
you	O
bite	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
affrighted	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hagerty	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
duty	O
also	O
at	O
the	O
turnpike	O
,	O
at	O
Hyde-park-corner	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
guard	O
that	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
mail	O
had	O
told	O
us	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
at	O
Smallbury-green	O
turnpike	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
murdered	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
making	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
way	O
for	O
London	O
:	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
plain	O
hat	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
soon	O
after	O
pursued	O
from	O
Knights	O
bridge	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
:	O
we	O
examined	O
his	O
thumbs	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
his	O
left	O
thumb	O
willingly	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
that	O
was	O
bit	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alesby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
and	O
work	O
at	O
Brumpton	O
:	O
going	O
thither	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
getting	O
over	O
a	O
style	O
the	O
watchman	O
called	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
killed	O
on	O
Smallbury-Green	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
by	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
for	O
London	O
;	O
he	O
described	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
White-Hart	O
just	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
bridge	O
and	O
got	O
me	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
telling	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
there	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
just	O
gone	O
along	O
.	O
We	O
followed	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
hue	O
and	O
cry	O
to	O
the	O
turnpike	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
something	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
round	O
house	O
,	O
not	O
finding	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
Patworth	O
went	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
213	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Sheel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
ruby	O
stone	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ruben	B-pers
Adolphus	I-pers
,	O
secretly	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
March	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
Ruben	O
Adolphus	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
oratorio	O
in	O
Covent	B-place
Garden	I-place
,	O
March	O
11	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
besides	O
whom	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
but	O
good	O
company	O
:	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
hand	O
about	O
my	O
breeches	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
for	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
an	O
orange	O
girl	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
have	O
her	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
gallery	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
she	O
had	O
concealed	O
herself	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
purse	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
paper	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
paper	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
paper	O
the	O
ruby	O
stone	O
was	O
wrapt	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
she	O
had	O
dropped	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
my	O
ruby	O
stone	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
round	O
house	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
searched	O
her	O
will	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
loose	O
?	O
Adolphus	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
under	O
the	O
stairs	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
his	O
purse	O
with	O
the	O
gallery	O
keeper	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
fumbling	O
about	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
imagined	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
drop	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
look	O
under	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
dropt	O
something	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
and	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
ruby	O
stone	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
stone	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Joyce	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
watchouse	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
men	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
conceal	O
'd	O
in	O
her	O
mouth	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
some	O
half-pence	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
girl	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
for	O
a	O
service	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
214	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
mare	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
colour	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edling	I-pers
,	O
Octob	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Edling	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
black	O
mare	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
white	O
on	O
her	O
near	O
foot	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
off-foot	O
behind	O
,	O
to	O
Hadley	B-place
,	O
to	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
's	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
last	O
May	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
;	O
he	O
missed	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
2d	O
or	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
word	O
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
sold	O
to	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Purier	I-pers
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
mare	O
,	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
delivered	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Purier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
mare	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cotsell	O
,	O
a	O
carpenter	O
in	O
the	O
Falcon	O
Inn	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cotsell	I-pers
.	O
Going	O
to	O
Black	O
Heath	O
fair	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
with	O
this	O
mare	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Falcon	O
Inn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
mare	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
her	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
come	O
from	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
receive	O
prize	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
black	O
mare	O
about	O
14	O
hands	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
high	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
heel	O
behind	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
mare	O
at	O
Portsmouth	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
expecting	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
some	O
money	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
longer	O
than	O
my	O
time	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sold	O
my	O
mare	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
four	O
other	O
seamen	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
saw	O
me	O
buy	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
sea	O
again	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
215	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
mustard-pot	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Lionel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Lionel	O
Lee	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Sun	B-place
Tavern	I-place
at	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
;	O
the	O
things	O
lost	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
how	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Whitehall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lee	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
:	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
servants	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
behind	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
safe	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
mustard-pot	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
her	O
searched	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
another	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
opened	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
mustard	O
pot	O
and	O
spoon	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
got	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
they	O
lay	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
216	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
Spurs	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lock	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Lock	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Uxbridge	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
last	O
March	O
these	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
spurs	O
were	O
hanging	O
near	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
spurs	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
bell-man	O
coming	O
by	O
saw	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
and	O
called	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
done	O
a	O
bad	O
thing	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
them	O
under	O
some	O
hay	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
:	O
)	O
Bernard	B-pers
Elingham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
spurs	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
found	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
28	O
,	O
in	O
Calvert	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
217	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
earthern	O
jar	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
twenty-eight	O
pounds	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	I-pers
Esq	I-pers
;	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
Co	O
.	O
Mar	O
.	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
Charles	O
Batchelder	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
March	O
23	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Rawlinson	O
's	O
cellar	O
with	O
a	O
jarr	O
of	O
raisins	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
come	O
round	O
to	O
Mincing-lane	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
people	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Helaby	I-pers
.	O
That	O
boy	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
collar	O
with	O
a	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
run	O
I	O
might	O
catch	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
went	O
past	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Mincing-lane	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
White-chapel	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
water	O
side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
this	O
cellar	O
door	O
open	O
?	O
Holaby	O
.	O
It	O
opens	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
open	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
raisins	O
and	O
jarr	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Rawlinson	O
's	O
cellar	O
?	O
Helaby	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
on	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
mark	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
which	O
were	O
then	O
near	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
water	O
side	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
work	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
duskish	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
dress	O
'd	O
much	O
like	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
earn	O
3	O
d.	O
or	O
4	O
d.	O
I	O
said	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
that	O
jarr	O
to	O
White-chapel	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
there	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
Mincing-lane	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Rawlinson	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
they	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
218	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
219	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
empty	O
wine	O
vessel	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
half-hogshead	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
6	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
220	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fabre	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Goodson	B-pers
Vines	I-pers
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
Goodson	O
Vines	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
up	O
Threadneedle-street	B-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
walked	O
on	O
and	O
felt	O
something	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
looked	O
back	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
corner	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
hanging	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
left-hand	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
followed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
the	O
Change	O
;	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
round	O
directly	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
none	O
but	O
this	O
which	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
just	O
now	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Guild-hall	O
before	O
a	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
221	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
flowered	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
||	O
James	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	B-place
of	I-place
Charles-street	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linnen	O
draper	O
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
called	O
her	O
brother	O
,	O
came	O
unto	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
some	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
employed	O
herself	O
in	O
taking	O
up	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
shew-board	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
some	O
people	O
to	O
witness	O
to	O
my	O
taking	O
the	O
piece	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
had	O
she	O
gone	O
from	O
your	O
shop	O
;	O
Watson	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
kneel	O
'd	O
down	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
'd	O
forgive	O
her	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
lawn	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ashmore	I-pers
,	O
who	O
sells	O
fruit	O
near	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
whom	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
sent	O
for	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
take	O
the	O
lawn	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
arm	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
222	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
,	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tateon	I-pers
,	O
March	O
2	O
.	O
||	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
223	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Patent	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
one	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
March	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Wheeler-street	B-place
,	I-place
Spital	I-place
Fields	I-place
;	O
the	O
sheets	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
she	O
wanted	O
;	O
she	O
mentioned	O
some	O
outlandish	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
gone	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
run	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
till	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
;	O
she	O
never	O
owned	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Merrick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
white	O
and	O
red	O
colours	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
559.	O
in	O
Cokayne	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
224	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Bannel	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
one	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
||	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
225	O
,	O
226	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
O	I-pers
Brian	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Zeidenburg	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smallman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Frederick	B-pers
Zeidenburg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Great	O
Rupert-street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Fox	O
ale-house	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
use	O
that	O
house	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
countrymen	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
German	O
Q	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Zeidenburg	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
remember	O
;	O
she	O
followed	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
pint	O
and	O
drank	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
leave	O
my	O
company	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
again	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
?	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
deluded	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
countryman	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Zeidenburg	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
English	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
leave	O
your	O
companion	O
behind	O
,	O
who	O
could	O
not	O
talk	O
English	O
?	O
Zeidenburg	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
back	O
presently	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
No	B-place
.	I-place
3.	I-place
in	I-place
Orange-court	I-place
,	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smallman	I-pers
;	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
agree	O
she	O
should	O
go	O
too	O
?	O
Zeidenburg	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
that	O
O	O
Brian	O
go	O
against	O
your	O
inclination	O
?	O
Zeidenburg	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
she	O
should	O
or	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
publick-house	O
?	O
Zeidenburg	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
sell	O
liquor	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
notorious	O
bawdy-house	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
asked	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Boyle	I-pers
snatched	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
immediately	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
shewed	O
them	O
your	O
watch	O
before	O
?	O
Zeidenburg	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
might	O
see	O
the	O
string	O
hang	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
candle	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
ran	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
candle	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
way	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
down	O
I	O
asked	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Bourne	O
(	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
on	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
discharged	O
)	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
one	O
Robinson	O
a	O
thief-taker	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
describe	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Plough	O
and	O
drank	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
then	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
two	O
guineas	O
reward	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
Robinson	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
others	O
could	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
and	O
watch	O
too	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Gore	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
in	O
Orange-court	O
,	O
Drury-lane	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Plough	O
again	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
that	O
is	O
released	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
about	O
,	O
my	O
head	O
was	O
quite	O
muddled	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
women	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
keep	O
them	O
two	O
women	O
?	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
of	O
your	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
thief-takers	O
ran	O
out	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
found	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
Zeidenburg	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Zeidenburg	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Pierce	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Orange-court	O
,	O
and	O
rent	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
this	O
house	O
of	O
Smallman	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
come	O
in	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
a	O
few	O
minutes	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
O	I-pers
Brian	I-pers
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
ale	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
fetch	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
fetched	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
Mrs.	O
Smallman	O
was	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
money	O
's	O
worth	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Smallman	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
both	O
run	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
waited	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
would	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
quickly	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
minutes	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
himself	O
easy	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
O	O
Brian	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
offered	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
without	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
each	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
the	O
liquor	O
also	O
;	O
her	O
meaning	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
that	O
money	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
least	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
should	O
come	O
into	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
heavy	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
directly	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
undressed	O
myself	O
and	O
went	O
to-bed	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
12th	O
;	O
then	O
Mrs.	O
Smallman	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
give	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
could	O
sell	O
it	O
:	O
then	O
Margaret	O
O	O
Brian	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
Cutler	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
(	O
William	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
)	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
forty	O
six	O
shillings	O
;	O
she	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
M.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
this	O
?	O
M.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
prison	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
admitted	O
an	O
Evidence	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rush	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
works	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
by	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
men	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
belief	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
women	O
in	O
some	O
house	O
of	O
ill-same	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
bawdy-house	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
advertise	O
it	O
as	O
lost	O
and	O
not	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
the	O
advertisement	O
out	O
for	O
him	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
lost	O
near	O
the	O
Fox	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
)	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
Plough	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
discharged	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
saying	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
sware	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
for	O
further	O
examination	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
O	O
Brian	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
about	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Plough	O
in	O
Drury-Lane	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
;	O
he	O
looked	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
sware	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
227	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Poor	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
called	O
ducape	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Boyde	I-pers
;	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
irish	O
stuff	O
called	O
grey	O
tobine	O
,	O
and	O
thirteen	O
yards	O
of	O
scarlet	O
irish	O
stuff	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Stamford	I-pers
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Stamford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mercer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
behind	B-place
St.	I-place
Clement	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
:	O
on	O
March	O
20	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
home	O
by	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
twenty-seven	O
yards	O
of	O
ducape	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
thief	O
at	O
the	O
Cambridge	O
perriwig	O
warehouse	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
One	O
Bell	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
the	O
ducape	O
and	O
thirteen	O
yards	O
of	O
scarlet	O
irish	O
stuff	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
grey	O
tobine	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
piece	O
of	O
ducape	O
I	O
had	O
borrow	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
as	O
is	O
usual	O
in	O
our	O
trade	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
thing	O
asked	O
for	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
John	B-pers
Bellamy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stamford	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
March	O
20	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
irish	O
stuff	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pulled	O
down	O
from	O
a	O
shelf	O
about	O
eight	O
remnants	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
would	O
suit	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
running	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
maid	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
overtook	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
accuse	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
sure	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
irish	O
stust	O
that	O
would	O
suit	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
under	O
her	O
long	O
scarlet	O
cloak	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
she	O
dropped	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
dirt	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Cambridge	O
perriwig	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Master	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
down	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
,	O
another	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
borrowed	O
,	O
was	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
ready	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
Witnesses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
592.	O
in	O
Blackford	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
228	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Elizabeth	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
something	O
before	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Rotherhith	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
Highgate	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
betwixt	B-place
Islington	I-place
town	I-place
's	I-place
end	I-place
and	I-place
the	I-place
half	I-place
way	I-place
houses	I-place
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
horse	O
path	O
,	O
leading	O
two	O
saddle	O
horses	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
foot	O
causeway	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
was	O
particularly	O
little	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
not	O
very	O
large	O
:	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
they	O
were	O
dark	O
brown	O
horses	O
.	O
Something	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
nearer	O
the	O
foot	O
path	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
got	O
right	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
word	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
so	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
foot	O
path	O
with	O
his	O
horses	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
violent-hands	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
one	O
hand	O
round	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
otehr	O
on	O
my	O
petticoats	O
;	O
my	O
apron	O
he	O
slit	O
in	O
the	O
binding	O
:	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
poor	O
family	O
in	O
distress	O
with	O
the	O
smallpox	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
me	O
down	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
ends	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
damn	O
you	O
for	O
a	O
bitch	O
ca	O
n't	O
you	O
hold	O
your	O
tongue	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
my	O
mouth	O
in	O
such	O
an	O
indecent	O
manner	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
my	O
mouth	O
and	O
gums	O
a	O
bleeding	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
pass	O
by	O
on	O
foot	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
murder	O
:	O
no	O
help	O
came	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dash	O
'd	O
my	O
head	O
against	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
pulled	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
hair	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
;	O
he	O
bit	O
my	O
shoulder	O
with	O
his	O
teeth	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
bump	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
struggling	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
passed	O
by	O
in	O
light	O
colour	O
'd	O
cloaths	O
,	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
causeway	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
got	O
me	O
down	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
about	O
so	O
monstruosly	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
hardly	O
express	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
his	O
mother	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
satisfied	O
his	O
lust	O
he	O
let	O
me	O
get	O
up	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
:	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
thinks	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
villain	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
six-pence	O
in	O
my	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
six-pences	O
,	O
and	O
four-pence	O
in	O
copper	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
of	O
lobsters	O
and	O
cross-buns	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
victuals	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
mistress	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
business	O
while	O
you	O
are	O
well	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
half-way	O
houses	O
,	O
all	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Highate	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
Pyde-Bull	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
second	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
just	O
gone	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Highgate	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
overtake	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
farthest	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
before	O
hand	O
3	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
bosom	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
almost	O
to	O
the	O
Black-Dog	O
at	O
Highgate	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
back	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
no-body	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
appoint	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
Miss	O
Jeffreys	O
being	O
executed	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
Saturday	O
:	O
My	O
husband	O
being	O
come	O
from	O
the	O
pay-table	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
him	O
my	O
misfortune	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
sabbath-day	O
morning	O
I	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
particular	O
man	O
,	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
brown	O
stable	O
frock	O
,	O
an	O
hostler	O
's	O
cap	O
,	O
a	O
strip	O
'd	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
heard	O
no	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sawney	O
looking	O
whelp	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
trac	O
'd	O
the	O
road	O
he	O
might	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
sawney	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
His	O
face	O
shone	O
yellowish	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
great	O
wrath	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
head	O
at	O
Holloway	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
horses	O
,	O
he	O
there	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
the	O
horses	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Dunstable	O
waggon	O
(	O
she	O
not	O
being	O
with	O
her	O
husband	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
admitted	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
of	O
hearsay	O
)	O
after	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Easter-Monday	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
stable	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White-hart	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
hostler	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Bedfordshire	O
waggon	O
came	O
in	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
the	O
price	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Biggleswade	O
or	O
Temslord	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
came	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
might	O
see	O
the	O
waggoner	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
villian	O
that	O
used	O
me	O
ill	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
money	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
During	O
this	O
ill	O
treatment	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
grasing	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
causeway	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
the	O
horses	O
would	O
tread	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
tied	O
?	O
E	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
not	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
bridles	O
were	O
tied	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
near	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
causeway	O
near	O
the	O
high	O
road	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
was	O
he	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
horses	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Highgate	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
something	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
bridge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
any	O
house	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
houses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
people	O
passing	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no-body	O
passed	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
man	O
I	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
was	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
how	O
far	O
was	O
he	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
sessions-house	O
,	O
perhaps	O
twice	O
the	O
length	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
had	O
you	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
gone	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
this	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
stranger	O
then	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mount	O
the	O
horses	O
afterwards	O
.	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
afterwards	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
for	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
tell	O
the	O
people	O
where	O
you	O
called	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
shocked	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
tell	O
your	O
neighbours	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
late	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
such	O
an	O
affair	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
,	O
ask	O
for	O
an	O
hostler	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
farm	O
to	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
that	O
stranger	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
he	O
past	O
by	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
near	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
that	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Pointing	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
prevented	O
your	O
calling	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
call	O
out	O
murder	O
and	O
all	O
could	O
cry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
stranger	O
nearer	O
Highgate	O
or	O
Islington	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
E.	O
Humphreys	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
nearer	O
Islington	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hatton-Garden	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Holloway	O
home	O
,	O
betwixt	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
:	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
back-lane	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
woman	O
groan	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
to	O
consider	O
whether	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
forwards	O
or	O
not	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
went	O
close	O
by	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
down	O
upon	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
her	O
cloaths	O
up	O
,	O
her	O
legs	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
master	O
,	O
help	O
;	O
Murder	O
!	O
Murder	O
!	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
hold	O
your	O
tongue	O
,	O
you	O
bitch	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
horses	O
grasing	O
on	O
a	O
bank	O
close	O
by	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
foot	O
path	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
horses	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
One	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
poney	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
larger	O
,	O
I	O
judge	O
about	O
fourteen	O
hands	O
high	O
:	O
by	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
discover	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
bridles	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
halters	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
more	O
in	O
it	O
than	O
should	O
be	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
dar	O
'd	O
not	O
stay	O
to	O
assist	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
star-light	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
distinguish	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
their	O
persons	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hostler	O
's	O
frock	O
and	O
cap	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
was	O
the	O
frock	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
coloured	O
cloaths	O
had	O
you	O
on	O
.	O
Tipping	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
(	O
i.	O
e.	O
very	O
light	O
colour	O
'd	O
.	O
)	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
was	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
for	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
in	O
this	O
situation	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
assist	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
Because	O
there	O
are	O
so	O
many	O
traps	O
laid	O
to	O
draw	O
people	O
in	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
stratagems	O
of	O
women	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
this	O
appear	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
lying	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
crying	O
out	O
:	O
and	O
by	O
seeing	O
the	O
two	O
horses	O
,	O
I	O
imagined	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
more	O
hard	O
by	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
heard	O
it	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
yards	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
out	O
to	O
give	O
your	O
evidence	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
woman	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
upon	O
her	O
legs	O
?	O
Tipping	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
nor	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
up	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
relate	O
this	O
affair	O
?	O
Tipping	O
I	O
related	O
it	O
to	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
that	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
houses	O
,	O
alarm	O
the	O
people	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
came	O
riding	O
by	O
full	O
speed	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
you	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
any	O
similitude	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
an	O
idea	O
enough	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
send	O
word	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
of	O
your	O
coming	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
word	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
woman	O
before	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
letter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
meet	O
any	O
other	O
people	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Tipping	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Queen's-Head	O
at	O
Holloway	O
,	O
beyond	O
the	O
Half-way-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
eight	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Easter-eve	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
blackish	O
horses	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
saddles	O
and	O
bridles	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
small	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
cloathed	O
?	O
Fletcher	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
dark	O
fustian	O
frock	O
and	O
a	O
jockey	O
's	O
cap	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Fletcher	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
light	O
or	O
a	O
dark	O
night	O
?	O
Fletcher	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
star-light	O
evening	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
horses	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
Holloway	O
and	O
drank	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
and	O
in	O
bed	O
before	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Munns	I-pers
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
bred	O
a	O
butcher	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Fothergay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
upwards	O
of	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
harmless	O
,	O
inoffensive	O
fellow	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Comings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
White-hart	O
Inn	O
in	O
St.	O
John's-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
hostier	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
going	O
on	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
horses	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Easter	O
evening	O
?	O
Comings	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
horses	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
guest	O
,	O
two	O
carriers	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
bridled	O
and	O
saddled	O
?	O
Comings	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
one	O
less	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
Comings	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
pretty	O
deal	O
less	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
Comings	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
told	O
you	O
so	O
?	O
Comings	O
.	O
The	O
cook	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kilingly	I-pers
and	O
Mrs	O
Ruso	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Hannah	B-pers
Boroughs	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
,	O
were	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
each	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
sober	O
,	O
industrious	O
woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
rape	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
needless	O
to	O
try	O
him	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
omitted	O
.	O
229.	O
George	B-pers
Farmer	I-pers
.	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Firmer	I-pers
,	I-pers
Esq	I-pers
;	I-pers
commonly	I-pers
called	I-pers
Lord	I-pers
Lempster	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
Feb	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
Capt	O
.	O
Collingwood	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
likewise	O
of	O
the	O
unfortunate	O
deceased	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
dined	O
with	O
my	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bedford-head	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
that	O
morning	O
upon	O
guard	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
but	O
should	O
be	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
proposed	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Tilt-yard	O
coffee-house	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
captain	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
joined	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
above	O
stairs	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
had	O
once	O
at	O
a	O
masquerade	O
refused	O
to	O
lend	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
ten	O
guineas	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
words	O
after	O
supper	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
about	O
twelve	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
,	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
circumstances	O
of	O
refusing	O
,	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
particulars	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
affronting	O
words	O
I	O
heard	O
,	O
was	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
gave	O
my	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
the	O
lie	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
without	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
good	O
language	O
used	O
before	O
;	O
then	O
upon	O
this	O
my	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
called	O
him	O
rascal	O
and	O
scoundrel	O
,	O
which	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
returned	O
with	O
many	O
abusive	O
words	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
at	O
last	O
jump	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
drew	O
his	O
sword	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
had	O
not	O
his	O
sword	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
up	O
and	O
got	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
in	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
busy	O
in	O
keeping	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
,	O
no	O
advances	O
made	O
;	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
their	O
sitting	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
putting	O
up	O
their	O
swords	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
both	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
as	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
present	O
but	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
divulge	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
safe	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
they	O
stay	O
after	O
this	O
quarrel	O
?	O
Capt	O
.	O
Collingwood	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
might	O
stay	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
seemingly	O
good	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
quarrel	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q.	O
Whither	O
,	O
during	O
that	O
interval	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
?	O
Capt	O
.	O
Collingwood	O
.	O
Not	O
as	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
all	O
down	O
stairs	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
at	O
the	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Lord	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
we	O
parted	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
mine	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Tilt-yard	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
coffee	O
room	O
when	O
my	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Collingwood	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
in	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
table	O
:	O
I	O
paid	O
my	O
respects	O
to	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
them	O
a	O
bowl	O
of	O
punch	O
;	O
they	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
seemed	O
extremely	O
sociable	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
the	O
topick	O
came	O
up	O
readily	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
about	O
lending	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
seemed	O
to	O
harp	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Collingwood	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
might	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
civiller	O
answer	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
when	O
a	O
man	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
at	O
play	O
,	O
the	O
Capt	O
.	O
might	O
have	O
excused	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Lord	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
to	O
affront	O
him	O
.	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
turned	O
his	O
head	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
.	O
My	O
Ld	O
.	O
Lempster	O
turned	O
and	O
talked	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
some	O
horses	O
,	O
seemingly	O
to	O
evade	O
it	O
:	O
Then	O
my	O
Ld	O
.	O
said	O
,	O
Collingwood	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
and	O
sup	O
any	O
where	O
?	O
and	O
seemed	O
intirely	O
to	O
evade	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
at	O
several	O
intervals	O
harp	O
'd	O
upon	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
mentioned	O
the	O
Cardigan	O
;	O
said	O
Capt	O
.	O
Collingwood	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
;	O
said	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
,	O
ca	O
n't	O
you	O
as	O
well	O
sup	O
here	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
objection	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
fire	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
:	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
supper	O
and	O
more	O
punch	O
:	O
I	O
waited	O
supper	O
myself	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
they	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pack	O
of	O
cards	O
and	O
play	O
'd	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Collingwood	O
play	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
sat	O
by	O
;	O
then	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
went	O
his	O
rounds	O
,	O
and	O
returne	O
d	O
again	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
like	O
showing	O
back	O
of	O
chairs	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
their	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
say	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
blood	O
,	O
you	O
scoundrel	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
;	O
you	O
rascal	O
,	O
you	O
coward	O
,	O
you	O
dare	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
jump	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
Gray	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
put	O
up	O
with	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
room	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
cautious	O
of	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
looked	O
through	O
the	O
key-hole	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
Capt	O
.	O
Collingwood	O
standing	O
with	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
'll	O
desist	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
advanced	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
Capt	O
.	O
Collingwood	O
pacify	O
'd	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Had	O
any	O
thing	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
easily	O
have	O
gone	O
in	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
his	O
back	O
being	O
towards	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
latch	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
.	O
They	O
sat	O
down	O
after	O
this	O
seemingly	O
good	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
together	O
so	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
little	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
such	O
a	O
heighth	O
as	O
fighting	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
another	O
bowl	O
of	O
punch	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
made	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
I	O
lighted	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
was	O
over	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
my	O
Ld	O
.	O
Lempster	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
the	O
lights	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
were	O
burnt	O
out	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
;	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
shut	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
and	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
knew	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
's	O
voice	O
perfectly	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
person	O
say	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
talking	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
distinguish	O
the	O
voices	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
whispering	O
like	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
sware	O
my	O
Ld	O
.	O
Lempster	O
was	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Capt	O
.	O
Collingwood	O
one	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
sware	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
they	O
drank	O
a	O
bowl	O
of	O
punch	O
after	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
lighted	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
to	O
the	O
guard	O
room	O
about	O
five	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
about	O
eight	O
and	O
breakfasted	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
pretty-steadfastly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
that	O
little	O
dispute	O
is	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
that	O
:	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
taxed	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
hoped	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
in	O
that	O
affair	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
breakfast	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
affair	O
is	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
go	O
he	O
'll	O
take	O
it	O
amiss	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Collingwood	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
your	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
shut	O
his	O
door	O
?	O
Robert	B-pers
Fudge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barber	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
dress	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
:	O
I	O
remember	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Tilt-yard	O
guard-room	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
officer	O
on	O
guard	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Tilt-yard	O
coffee-house	O
with	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Collingwood	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
they	O
talked	O
of	O
indifferent	O
things	O
;	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
say	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
had	O
used	O
him	O
ill	O
;	O
but	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
and	O
bring	O
his	O
mourning	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Tilt-yard	O
coffee-house	O
by	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
and	O
a	O
plain	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
his	O
mourning	O
sword	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
(	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
his	O
mourning	O
sword	O
with	O
his	O
mourning	O
cloaths	O
)	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
orders	O
to	O
bring	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
black	O
ribband	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
horse	O
guards	O
as	O
the	O
clock	O
struck	O
ten	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
parade	O
,	O
I	O
waited	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
relieved	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
the	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
supposed	O
,	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
he	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
dressed	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
on	O
mourning	O
cloaths	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
a	O
mourning	O
sword	O
,	O
he	O
bound	O
the	O
ribband	O
about	O
the	O
hilt	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
mounted	O
sword	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
appear	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Fudge	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
confused	O
,	O
his	O
countenance	O
did	O
not	O
apper	O
serene	O
,	O
he	O
throwed	O
things	O
about	O
in	O
an	O
odd	O
manner	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
some	O
brandy	O
and	O
milk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
drink	O
such	O
liquor	O
?	O
Fudge	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coffee	O
house	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Cross	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Whiy	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-Market	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
lodged	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
servant	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
tell	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Gray	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
wainscot	O
for	O
his	O
servant	O
and	O
called	O
Robert	O
:	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
servant	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
my	O
Lord	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
the	O
gentleman	O
up	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
servant	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
walked	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
and	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
nor	O
he	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
servant	O
a	O
more	O
proper	O
person	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
than	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
gentleman	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
you	O
saw	O
my	O
Lord	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
go	O
out	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
E.	O
Cross	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
E.	O
Cross	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
before	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
gentleman	O
say	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
?	O
E.	O
Cross	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Gray	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
servant	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
E.	O
Cross	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
coat	O
mended	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
's	O
voice	O
.	O
E.	O
Cross	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
answered	O
through	O
the	O
wainscot	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
might	O
hear	O
the	O
knock	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
spoke	O
low	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
musician	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Marybone-fields	B-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
left-hand	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
then	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
walking	O
side	O
by	O
side	O
very	O
amicably	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
my	O
walk	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
field	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
fine	O
day	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
that	O
field	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
mile	O
or	O
better	O
;	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
walked	O
above	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
turn	O
my	O
head	O
by	O
accident	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
engaged	O
with	O
swords	O
,	O
both	O
naked	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
had	O
turn	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
face	O
toward	O
London	O
,	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
stood	O
in	O
a	O
line	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
walked	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
side	O
view	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
immediately	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
kill	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
towards	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
before	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
dropp	O
'd	O
on	O
his	O
knee	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
advanced	O
a	O
step	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
rose	O
more	O
:	O
while	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
advanc	O
'd	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
,	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
stood	O
then	O
upon	O
a	O
retreat	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
point	O
of	O
his	O
sword	O
dropt	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
Captain	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
!	O
O	O
God	O
!	O
What	O
is	O
this	O
!	O
in	O
a	O
mournful	O
voice	O
like	O
surpriz	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
vomiting	O
blood	O
as	O
he	O
lay	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
kneeled	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
head	O
with	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
his	O
eyes	O
very	O
wide	O
,	O
and	O
fix	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
vomited	O
a	O
torrent	O
of	O
blood	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
instantly	O
;	O
I	O
wiped	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
hop	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
spoke	O
,	O
I	O
open	O
'd	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
up	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
small	O
wound	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
small	O
effusion	O
of	O
blood	O
:	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
went	O
off	O
hastily	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
him	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
entrance	O
in	O
the	O
town	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
Capt	O
.	O
Gray	O
had	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
on	O
this	O
occasion	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
Captain	O
was	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
what	O
could	O
I	O
do	O
?	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
help	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
forced	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
thrust	O
after	O
the	O
Capt	O
.	O
was	O
fallen	O
upon	O
his	O
face	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
Capt	O
.	O
advanced	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
before	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
out	O
his	O
sword	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
confused	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
a	O
minute	O
's	O
observation	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
my	O
Lord	O
return	O
a	O
thrust	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
putting	O
out	O
his	O
sword	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Powell	O
.	O
He	O
stopp	O
'd	O
and	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
rather	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
entered	O
into	O
talk	O
of	O
this	O
unhappy	O
subject	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Captain	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
wound	O
on	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
which	O
penetrated	O
between	O
the	O
third	O
and	O
fourth	O
rib	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
cavity	O
;	O
and	O
without	O
doubt	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
live	O
.	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
being	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
court	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
following	O
purport	O
.	O
Lord	O
Lempster	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
extreamly	O
sorry	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
unhappy	O
occasion	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
's	O
death	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
of	O
great	O
honour	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
great	O
regard	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
arguments	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
dissuade	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
intentions	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
fight	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
our	O
way	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
he	O
drew	O
first	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
under	O
a	O
necessity	O
of	O
killing	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
defence	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
verily	O
sorry	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
it	O
had	O
never	O
happened	O
.	O
The	O
council	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
rested	O
it	O
here	O
,	O
without	O
calling	O
any	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
230	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Stephen	B-pers
Baget	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hollingworth	I-pers
,	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Hollingworth	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
coming	O
up	O
Ludgate	B-place
hill	I-place
,	I-place
opposite	I-place
the	I-place
Bell-savage	I-place
Inn	I-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
somebody	O
pull	O
at	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
boy	O
close	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
hand	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
very	O
near	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
boy	O
ran	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Bell-savage	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
the	O
thief	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
they	O
shut	O
too	O
the	O
gates	O
and	O
kept	O
him	O
in	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
found	O
himself	O
inclosed	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
people	O
would	O
search	O
with	O
candles	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
far	O
guilty	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
lad	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
and	O
dropt	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Pope	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
calling	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
broom	O
stick	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
shut	O
to	O
the	O
great	O
gates	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
candle	O
while	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
gentleman	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
coach	O
wheel	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mud	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Bell-savage	O
Inn	O
yard	O
,	O
that	O
witness	O
shut	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
231	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bridle	O
for	O
a	O
chaise-horse	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
reins	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
britching	O
and	O
black	O
strap	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Barbernell	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Barbernell	I-pers
;	O
I	O
act	O
under	O
my	O
mother	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
livery	O
stable	O
,	O
the	O
White	O
Horse	O
in	O
Bury-street	O
;	O
the	O
harness	O
were	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
that	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
rails	O
at	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
harness	O
hanging	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
brick	O
wall	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Christopher	B-pers
Frampton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
buys	O
such	O
goods	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
)	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
we	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Frampton	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
having	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
six-pence	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
Christopher	B-pers
Frampton	I-pers
,	O
saying	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
went	O
himself	O
he	O
would	O
stop	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
232.	O
(	O
L	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
iron	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stroud	I-pers
,	I-pers
Esq	I-pers
,	I-pers
and	I-pers
Company	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
,	O
and	O
Company	O
April	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
This	O
key	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
London-bridge	O
Waterworks	O
to	O
turn	O
the	O
cocks	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
lodged	O
in	O
an	O
Alehouse	B-place
in	I-place
White-chapel	I-place
,	O
the	O
usual	O
place	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
watchman	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
233	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wedge	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
pounds	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
mayor	B-pers
and	I-pers
commonalty	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
city	I-pers
of	I-pers
London	I-pers
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
234	O
,	O
235	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Furnace	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Garnet	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hopkins	I-pers
.	O
++	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
236	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Oldridge	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
stew-pan	O
.	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
,	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
keeps	O
the	O
Baptist-head	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Old-Baily	I-place
;	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
pan	O
after	O
having	O
used	O
it	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
ninth	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
pan	O
to	O
William	O
Thatcher	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
doors	O
off	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Thatcher	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Baptist-head	O
,	O
Thatcher	O
's	O
wife	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
the	O
pan	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
237	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Lewis	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
brass	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Midwinter	I-pers
,	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
founder	O
;	O
one	O
Stanton	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
servants	O
had	O
brought	O
some	O
brass	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
finished	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
tool	O
which	O
founders	O
use	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
one	O
Newton	O
,	O
a	O
founder	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
at	O
Deptford	O
for	O
six	O
pence	O
;	O
then	O
Stanton	O
examined	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
founder	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
letter	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
name	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
direction	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newton	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
238	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
,	O
March	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
along	O
Grace-church	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
March	O
22d	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
yard	O
or	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
it	O
not	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
.	O
On	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
Grace-church	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisosoner	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Rowley	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
?	O
Rowley	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
from	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
