TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
19th	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
26th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1752	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Robert	B-pers
Alsop	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1752	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
ROBERT	B-pers
ALSOP	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Heley	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Cave	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bowers	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dunch	I-pers
,	O
Coles	B-pers
Fortree	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Goreham	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Filewood	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
James	B-pers
Filewood	I-pers
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
his	O
stead	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pickles	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
L.	O
and	O
M.	O
direct	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
400	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
pillowbear	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
19	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Showring	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
July	O
22	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Showring	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
work-house	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
upwards	O
of	O
5	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Red	B-place
Lion-Court	I-place
,	I-place
Fleetstreet	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
twenty	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bag	O
with	O
a	O
forty	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
nineteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
having	O
occasion	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
guinea	O
out	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
person	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
stay	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
At	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
she	O
desired	O
my	O
maid	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
up	O
at	O
6	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
call	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
book	O
case	O
,	O
I	O
likewise	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
her	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
there	O
been	O
any	O
quarrel	O
previous	O
to	O
this	O
?	O
M.	O
Showring	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Chillingworth	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
betwixt	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'clock	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
pillowbear	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
She	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
with	O
her	O
cloaths	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
pillowbear	O
?	O
M.	O
Showring	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
her	O
own	O
bed	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
where	O
she	O
lay	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Chillingworth	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
White-chapel	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
good	O
reason	O
for	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
persuaded	O
her	O
without	O
discovering	O
farther	O
to	O
return	O
;	O
so	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
bundle	O
in	O
this	O
pillowbear	O
and	O
returned	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
searched	O
?	O
Chillingworth	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
money	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
from	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
(	O
before	O
she	O
got	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Chittey	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
her	O
mistress	O
would	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
coach	O
window	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
her	O
the	O
truth	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
pulled	O
up	O
again	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
let	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
in	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
betwixt	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
book	O
case	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
gold	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
read	O
the	O
note	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
bag	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
the	O
some	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
afterwards	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
that	O
young	O
man	O
for	O
above	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
threatnings	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
her	O
confession	O
?	O
Chillingworth	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
her	O
mistress	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
confirmed	O
this	O
of	O
her	O
confession	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Edwards	O
confirmed	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
evidence	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
401	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
she	O
ass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Gimbart	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Gimbart	I-pers
keeps	O
an	O
inn	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
this	O
ass	O
to	O
grass	O
with	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
at	O
Tottenham	B-place
,	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
a	O
servant	O
lad	O
to	O
Clark	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
horse	O
from	O
the	O
field	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
the	O
lad	O
going	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
selling	O
the	O
ass	O
to	O
a	O
stranger	O
and	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
both	O
whose	O
ass	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
money	O
for	O
her	O
and	O
delivered	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
her	O
away	O
towards	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
an	O
ass	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
gave	O
him	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
402	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bacchus	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
May	B-place
's	I-place
Buildings	I-place
,	O
am	O
a	O
leather	O
breeches	O
maker	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
July	O
Mr.	O
Belgrave	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
off	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
hung	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
breeches	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
,	O
would	O
fit	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Belgrave	O
.	O
Coming	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
breeches	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
woman	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
her	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
breeches	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
fast	O
asleep	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
awake	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
403	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Dupree	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
pepper	O
box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
July	O
25	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nevil	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
market	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
I	O
missed	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
plate	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shew	O
glass	O
;	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
about	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
farther	O
Examination	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
this	O
pepper	O
box	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
German	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
the	O
pepper	O
box	O
to	O
pledge	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
27	O
s.	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
pepper	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
and	O
found	O
oil	O
and	O
rotten	O
stone	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
the	O
silversmiths	O
clean	O
their	O
plate	O
with	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nevil	O
's	O
own	O
daughter	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
pepper	O
box	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nevil	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
daughter	O
?	O
Nevil	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
about	O
15	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
mantuamaker	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
My	O
maid	O
ran	O
away	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
daughter	O
went	O
away	O
by	O
the	O
instigation	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
404	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
thread	O
purse	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
two	O
silver	O
medals	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
June	O
17	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
about	O
February	O
or	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
clerk	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Bridgewater	O
,	O
in	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
time	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
some	O
bumboe	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
three	O
six	O
penny	O
worths	O
of	O
bumboe	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
was	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
Rotherhith	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
some	O
cyder	O
and	O
brandy	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
King-street	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Cumberland	O
's	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
more	O
cyder	O
and	O
brandy	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
played	O
at	O
skittles	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Barnaby-street	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
near	O
that	O
place	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
pistol	O
off	O
the	O
mantle-piece	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
my	O
oath	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
I	O
told	O
Bridgewater	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
revenged	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
owe	O
my	O
landlord	O
rent	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
rob	O
coaches	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
shall	O
be	O
made	O
men	O
of	O
in	O
a	O
night	O
or	O
two	O
's	O
time	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
bid	O
his	O
wife	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Graunt	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
rum	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Graunt	O
to	O
change	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
close	O
by	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
one	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
empty	O
one	O
in	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
want	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
replied	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
loaded	O
one	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
any	O
danger	O
call	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
we	O
stayed	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
together	O
.	O
He	O
heard	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
now	O
is	O
your	O
time	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
near	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
in	O
either	O
Shug-lane	O
,	O
or	O
Silver-street	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
can	O
do	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
heart	O
fails	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
if	O
we	O
must	O
do	O
it	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
go	O
first	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
you	O
look	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
corner	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
off	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
the	O
coachman	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
directly	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Deliver	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
a	O
great	O
oath	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
hold	O
out	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
to	O
take	O
what	O
they	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
prize	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
some	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
shook	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
there	O
came	O
three	O
more	O
coaches	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
empty	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
coach	O
came	O
down	O
Shug-lane	O
,	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
turn	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
must	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
try	O
at	O
once	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
the	O
coachman	O
stop	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
directly	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
a	O
reel	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
heart	O
failed	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
lady	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
looked	O
very	O
cross	O
and	O
harsh	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
Piccadilly	O
into	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
after	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
a	O
chain	O
and	O
seal	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
See	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
;	O
we	O
shall	O
do	O
for	O
ourselves	O
presently	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
another	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
'd	O
not	O
go	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Darkhouse-lane	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
and	O
Bell	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
drank	O
three	O
six	O
pennyworths	O
of	O
bumboe	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
uneasy	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
Spanish	O
dollar	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
sold	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
7	O
d.	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
lady	O
he	O
robbed	O
last	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
white	O
net	O
purse	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
foreign	O
piece	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Duke	O
of	O
Cumberland	O
's	O
piece	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
keep	O
that	O
.	O
There	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
case	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
pinchbeck	O
chain	O
,	O
a	O
seal	O
and	O
key	O
.	O
We	O
stayed	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Winstanley	O
,	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
for	O
four	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
.	O
The	O
dollar	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Winstanley	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
alone	O
.	O
Question	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
go	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
Mr.	O
Garret	O
's	O
in	O
Darkhouse	O
Lane	O
,	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
supped	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Graunt	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
Head	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Vere-street	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
in	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
two	O
boys	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Spring	O
Garden	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
medals	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
silver	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
stopped	O
and	O
robbed	O
in	O
Shug-Lane	B-place
;	O
one	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
moon	O
light	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
look	O
'd	O
pale	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
deliver	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
affrighted	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
son	O
my	O
purse	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
first	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
whom	O
the	O
purse	O
was	O
delivered	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
my	O
son	O
give	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Holt	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
affrighted	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
footman	O
behind	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
man	O
a	O
rap	O
on	O
the	O
pate	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
my	O
son	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
medals	O
were	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
German	O
medal	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
Spanish	O
piece	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
advertising	O
it	O
,	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Winstanley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
cloaths	O
had	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Holt	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
striped	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
used	O
to	O
wear	O
such	O
cloaths	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
changed	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cob	I-pers
b.	O
I	O
am	O
Mrs.	O
Holt	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Shug	O
Lane	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
He	O
look	O
'd	O
more	O
on	O
the	O
coachman	O
than	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
evidence	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
a	O
great	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
deliver	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
barrel	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
shine	O
by	O
the	O
moonlight	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
colour	O
'd	O
coat	O
and	O
striped	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Winstanley	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Looks	O
at	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
,	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
.	O
This	O
watch	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
most	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
above	O
three	O
guineas	O
of	O
gold	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
weighed	O
it	O
separate	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
any	O
more	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
gave	O
him	O
four	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
chain	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
believe	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
an	O
attorney	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
he	O
lived	O
there	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
Spanish	O
dollar	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
one	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
a	O
small	O
one	O
in	O
a	O
single	O
case	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
gave	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
four	O
guineas	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
so	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
honestly	O
came	O
by	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
dispute	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
watch	O
that	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
since	O
that	O
his	O
buckles	O
were	O
gone	O
also	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
shew	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
word	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
.	O
Then	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
being	O
Friday	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Pope	O
's	O
Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
by	O
the	O
old	O
Swan	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Spring	O
Gardens	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
watch	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
affidavit	O
it	O
was	O
hers	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
desiring	O
I	O
'd	O
endeavour	O
to	O
take	O
John	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Farthing	O
Alley	O
,	O
Bermondsey-street	O
;	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
recollected	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
enquired	O
about	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
Farthing	O
Alley	O
,	O
Barnaby-street	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
the	O
little	O
gold	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
,	O
by	O
asking	O
the	O
question	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
hundred	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
fetch	O
him	O
in	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
stepped	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
so	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hankey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Smith	O
and	O
he	O
together	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
dress	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
?	O
Winstanley	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
clean	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Graunt	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
;	O
he	O
very	O
often	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
an	O
evening	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
evidence	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
generally	O
wore	O
a	O
brown	O
coat	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Gaines	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
wore	O
a	O
whitish	O
frock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
striped	O
cotton	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pale	O
blue	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
changed	O
them	O
for	O
a	O
coarse	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
and	O
other	O
prisoners	O
what	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
fool	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
that	O
boy	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
that	O
witness	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
nor	O
never	O
wore	O
a	O
white	O
coat	O
or	O
striped	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Smith	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
said	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
lay	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Graunt	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
London	O
Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
awaked	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
gold	O
watch	O
.	O
Jane	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Half	O
Moon	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
used	O
our	O
house	O
these	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
drank	O
bumboe	O
and	O
drams	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
the	O
evidence	O
before	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
drank	O
either	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
sixpennyworths	O
of	O
bumboe	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
one	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
sometimes	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
short	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
in	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
cinnamon	O
colour	O
'd	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Callow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Lane	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
exceeding	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
the	O
evidence	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
weeks	O
or	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
wear	O
a	O
brown	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
coat	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Halder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
company	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
highway	O
robbery	O
.	O
405	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
salt	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
22	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
406	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
cask	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
gallons	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
is	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
spirituous	O
liquors	O
.	O
He	O
ordered	O
this	O
cask	O
of	O
Holland	O
gin	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
vessel	O
at	O
his	O
wharf	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
captain	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
vessel	O
.	O
A	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Jennings	O
at	O
Stepney	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
he	O
was	O
refused	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
admitted	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
cask	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
empty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cow	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
cask	O
of	O
gin	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Jennings	O
for	O
three	O
half	O
crowns	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
407	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Arding	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Banes	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Aug.	O
13	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Banes	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	B-place
Royal	I-place
Exchange	I-place
.	O
Just	O
before	O
one	O
o'clock	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
A	O
R	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
B	O
in	O
another	O
place	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
intended	O
no	O
hurt	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
408	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
privily	O
and	O
secretly	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Aug.	O
15	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
near	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
going	O
from	O
Charing	O
Cross	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
House	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
St.	B-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
Park	I-place
,	O
with	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
towards	O
the	O
grass	O
plat	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
people	O
quarreling	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
bench	O
,	O
sat	O
down	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
moonlight	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sitting	O
there	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
.	O
He	O
turned	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
little	O
jostle	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
touch	O
upon	O
the	O
elbow	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
people	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
liften	O
to	O
what	O
the	O
people	O
said	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
felt	O
him	O
twitch	O
the	O
string	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
moonlight	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
fall	O
on	O
his	O
hands	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
recovered	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
Jack	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
Edward	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
guard-house	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
cloaths	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
serjeant	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
feel	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
for	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
passage	O
into	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
serjeant	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
drop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
serjeant	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
guard-house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fight	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
till	O
we	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
guard-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
attempted	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lining	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
sat	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
sit	O
by	O
you	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
In	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Westminster	O
.	O
Coming	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
seat	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
under	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
assist	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
walking	O
pretty	O
smartly	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
led	O
him	O
away	O
towards	O
the	O
guardroom	O
.	O
Going	O
through	O
the	O
passage	O
under	O
the	O
princess	O
Amelia	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
case	O
and	O
seal	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
distinguish	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
villain	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
let	O
it	O
fall	O
on	O
my	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
glass	O
;	O
the	O
case	O
flew	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
case	O
into	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
pulled	O
them	O
out	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Linn	I-pers
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Linn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
guard	O
room	O
to	O
Justice	O
Lediard	O
.	O
This	O
watch	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
that	O
lives	O
at	O
Fulham	O
.	O
We	O
parted	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
Buckingham	O
Gate	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
returning	O
,	O
this	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
fellow	O
in	O
a	O
lightish	O
coloured	O
coat	O
,	O
very	O
close	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
got	O
up	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
then	O
stood	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Did	O
you	O
sit	O
by	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
honest	O
friend	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
You	O
scoundrel	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
serjeant	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
or	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
just	O
God	O
in	O
heaven	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
87	O
in	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Hoare	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
No	O
.	O
142	O
in	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
409	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Carous	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
20	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carous	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Snow	B-place
Hill	I-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
round	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
taken	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
ten	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
running	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
stepped	O
cross	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
he	O
attempted	O
to	O
get	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
runing	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
us	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
people	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
near	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Not	O
within	O
ten	O
yards	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
up	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
at	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
Stop	O
thief	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Woodcock	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
lie	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
or	O
within	O
three	O
yards	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
not	O
above	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
people	O
come	O
up	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Carous	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
410	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
to	I-pers
Nicholas	I-pers
Brightwell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Oldershaw	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
25	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
411	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Purser	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
412	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
,	O
his	O
wife	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
saws	O
,	O
val	O
10	O
s	O
.	O
July	O
3	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
saws	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Remnant	O
sent	O
a	O
porter	O
with	O
a	O
message	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
away	O
instantly	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
two	O
saws	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
missed	O
in	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
We	O
carried	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
from	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
two	O
saws	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
think	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
prevaricated	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
court	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
stand	O
by	O
for	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Remnant	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
.	O
Going	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
standing	O
at	O
Salmon	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
Wright	O
was	O
three	O
parts	O
in	O
getting	O
over	O
the	O
window	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
gone	O
three	O
doors	O
past	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
door	O
unlock	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Hutton	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
shut	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
looking	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
bailiffs	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
great	O
sticks	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
green	O
stall	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
came	O
both	O
out	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Fleetstreet	O
.	O
I	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Hutton	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
giving	O
a	O
spring	O
took	O
hold	O
also	O
of	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
footman	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
stick	O
and	O
a	O
hand	O
saw	O
from	O
Hutton	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
took	O
another	O
saw	O
from	O
Wright	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
saws	O
under	O
their	O
coats	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
carpenter	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
saws	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Hunter	O
put	O
our	O
private	O
marks	O
on	O
them	O
;	O
here	O
they	O
are	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
again	O
.	O
There	O
Hutton	O
said	O
to	O
Wright	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
make	O
yourself	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
your	O
power	O
,	O
and	O
save	O
yourself	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
hanged	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
West	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Remnant	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
footman	O
brought	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
the	O
church	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
,	O
where	O
Mr	O
.	O
Remnant	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
now	O
.	O
There	O
I	O
heard	O
Hutton	O
say	O
to	O
Wright	O
save	O
yourself	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
get	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
saws	O
into	O
my	O
possession	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
marked	O
.	O
Here	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
called	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
two	O
saws	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
both	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
open	O
your	O
window	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
then	O
lay	O
in	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
my	O
apprentice	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
windows	O
before	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
saws	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
till	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
7	O
o'clock	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
saws	O
were	O
missed	O
.	O
Remnant	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
handle	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
saws	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
smallest	O
saw	O
.	O
Hutton	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
small	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Salmon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
something	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
saw	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
these	O
saws	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
borrow	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
tending	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Wright	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
For	O
Hutton	O
see	O
No	O
70	O
in	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pennant	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
516	O
in	O
John	O
Blachford	O
's	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
413	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
414	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Prigg	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Dulian	I-pers
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
he	O
missed	O
6	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
.	O
He	O
found	O
two	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
one	O
Henfield	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
before	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
master	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
415	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Keeley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
iron	O
bar	O
and	O
one	O
plough	O
coulter	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
18	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
lives	O
in	O
Hampstead	B-place
parish	I-place
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Aug.	O
18.	O
going	O
from	O
his	O
house	O
with	O
something	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suspected	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
assistance	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
dropped	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
stable	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
416	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fulliger	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	O
July	O
3	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
417	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Halfpenny	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
noble	O
John	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
of	I-pers
Bedford	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
418	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
It	O
appearing	O
it	O
was	O
let	O
to	O
the	O
husband	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
419	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
peny	O
halfpeny	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Phips	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
and	O
secretly	O
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
420	O
,	O
421	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Studd	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
or	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Aug.	O
17	O
.	O
Both	O
Acq	O
.	O
422	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
false	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
and	O
publishing	O
it	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
Francis	B-pers
Blare	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
9	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Blare	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
dealt	O
in	O
discounting	O
notes	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
her	O
husband	O
Joseph	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
(	O
See	O
Numb	O
.	O
369	O
in	O
last	O
paper	O
)	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
necessity	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
cash	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
Joseph	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
before	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
looked	O
like	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
fourteen	O
pound	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
bill	O
became	O
due	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
expecting	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
and	O
Co	O
.	O
But	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
appeared	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
before	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
ever	O
since	O
March	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
his	O
surviving	O
brother	O
,	O
James	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
forgery	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
'd	O
take	O
Joyce	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
town	O
upon	O
another	O
forgery	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
note	O
from	O
Jos	O
.	O
Joyce	O
,	O
drawn	O
upon	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
whom	O
you	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
?	O
Blare	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
name	O
Wilson	O
and	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
credit	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
setting	O
forth	O
the	O
difficulties	O
he	O
was	O
under	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
danger	O
of	O
trouble	O
in	O
case	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
not	O
paid	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
note	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
Newbury	O
,	O
Dec.	O
3	O
,	O
1751	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
Thirty	O
days	O
after	O
fight	O
please	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
,	O
or	O
his	O
order	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
fifteen	O
pound	O
and	O
place	O
it	O
to	O
account	O
,	O
as	O
by	O
advice	O
of	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
Your	O
humble	O
servant	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
.	O
Directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
at	O
the	O
Anchor	O
and	O
Star	O
the	O
Corner	O
of	O
White-heart	O
yard	O
,	O
Drurylane	O
,	O
London	O
.	O
Accepted	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
by	O
Edward	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
Norris	O
the	O
drawer	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
?	O
Blare	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
seen	O
several	O
of	O
his	O
bills	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
indorsed	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Joyce	I-pers
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Birham	I-pers
,	O
Deposed	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
there	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Blare	O
say	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
15	O
l.	O
upon	O
that	O
note	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
thanks	O
for	O
the	O
favour	O
done	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
money	O
paid	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Francis	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
of	O
Newbury	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
,	O
he	O
looks	O
at	O
the	O
note	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
was	O
dead	O
before	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
husband	O
had	O
bills	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Norris	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
received	O
any	O
money	O
for	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Huston	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Story	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	O
Ward	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Jennings	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Addison	O
appeared	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
423	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
38	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
being	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
charity	O
school	O
,	O
June	O
27	O
.	O
The	O
charity	O
school	O
in	O
Hatton	B-place
Garden	I-place
being	O
repairing	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
masters	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
let	O
down	O
some	O
old	O
sheet	O
lead	O
by	O
a	O
cord	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Sharp	O
's	O
son	O
to	O
untie	O
the	O
cord	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Eley	O
the	O
plumber	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
the	O
plumbing	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Susannah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Purple-lane	O
,	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
He	O
was	O
seen	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
on	O
the	O
house	O
throwing	O
down	O
more	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
lead	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
424	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susannah	B-pers
Milward	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
publishing	O
a	O
certain	O
forged	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
note	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
20	O
l.	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
,	O
Aug.	O
20	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
note	O
was	O
properly	O
drawn	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
name	O
subscribed	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
only	O
witnessed	O
by	O
Daniel	B-pers
Barnaby	I-pers
;	O
no	O
evidence	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
Acq	O
.	O
425	O
,	O
426	O
,	O
427	O
,	O
428	O
,	O
429	O
,	O
430	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lovyer	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Glovey	I-pers
,	O
Sarah	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cornhill	I-pers
,	O
Ruth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Pearvoy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Lovyer	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Glovey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
three	O
Hessian	O
wrappers	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
packing	O
sheet	O
,	O
four	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
pins	O
,	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
blue	O
silk	O
trimming	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
18	O
yards	O
of	O
Silesia	O
lawn	O
,	O
4	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
,	O
25	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
bohea	O
tea	O
,	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
gloves	O
,	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
gloves	O
,	O
16	O
yards	O
of	O
green	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
for	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
several	O
packhorses	O
that	O
go	O
betwixt	O
Preston	O
in	O
Lancashire	O
and	O
London	O
,	O
16	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
out	O
from	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
two	O
necks	O
in	O
Lad-lane	O
,	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
all	O
loaded	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
a	O
woman	O
passenger	O
rode	O
upon	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Islington	O
and	O
parted	O
with	O
them	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
was	O
the	O
driver	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
inn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
about	O
four	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Finchley	B-place
common	I-place
by	O
my	O
self	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
hay	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
drove	O
it	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
box	O
taken	O
up	O
found	O
on	O
Finchley	O
common	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
Wrestlers	O
at	O
Highgate	O
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
there	O
sent	O
people	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
woods	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
wrapper	O
found	O
,	O
marked	O
R.	O
Addison	O
,	O
Preston	O
,	O
with	O
no	O
goods	O
in	O
it	O
lying	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
a	O
garden	O
on	O
Finchley	O
common	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Swain	O
joined	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Common	O
,	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
Wrestlers	O
at	O
Highgate	O
again	O
.	O
Some	O
people	O
had	O
picked	O
up	O
some	O
goods	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
cambricks	O
,	O
one	O
box	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
taken	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
4	O
l.	O
odd	O
money	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
box	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
,	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
directed	O
for	O
Agnes	B-pers
Branthwaite	I-pers
at	O
Cartmel	O
,	O
the	O
parcel	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Bare	I-pers
,	O
at	O
Cartmel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
brought	O
them	O
there	O
?	O
Glover	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
In	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boxes	O
there	O
were	O
womens	O
black	O
everlasting	O
shoes	O
,	O
ribbons	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
particulars	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
parcel	O
there	O
were	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
goods	O
besides	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
12	O
l.	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
then	O
brought	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
bought	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
prepare	O
a	O
proper	O
advertisement	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
Finchley	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
houses	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
at	O
either	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
box	O
picked	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Common	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
hay	O
cart	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
my	O
inn	O
,	O
the	O
cord	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
box	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
opened	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
esquire	O
Bradeel	O
at	O
Preston	O
.	O
The	O
robbery	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
again	O
for	O
Lancashire	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
after	O
leaving	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
landlord	O
's	O
hands	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
spare	O
no	O
cost	O
in	O
inquiring	O
and	O
advertising	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
overtook	O
my	O
man	O
with	O
the	O
horses	O
at	O
Fenny	O
Stratford	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
fifteen	O
horses	O
without	O
a	O
pack	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
goods	O
,	O
you	O
mention	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
found	O
,	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
packs	O
which	O
were	O
on	O
these	O
fifteen	O
horses	O
?	O
Glover	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
14	O
packs	O
arrived	O
safe	O
at	O
Lancaster	O
,	O
one	O
pack	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
all	O
safe	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
London	O
at	O
their	O
going	O
out	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fenton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
driver	O
of	O
these	O
packhorses	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
from	O
Lad-lane	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
Islington	O
and	O
went	O
back	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Highgate	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
all	O
my	O
horses	O
and	O
packs	O
,	O
one	O
horse	O
carried	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
15	O
with	O
packs	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
and	O
drank	O
at	O
the	O
Wrestlers	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
told	O
the	O
horses	O
over	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
dark	O
and	O
a	O
rainy	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
them	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
above	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
with	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
beyond	O
Brown	O
's	O
Wells	O
,	O
sometimes	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
and	O
sometimes	O
behind	O
them	O
on	O
foot	O
.	O
Near	O
the	O
six	O
mile	O
stone	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
telling	O
them	O
over	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bald	O
mare	O
with	O
her	O
halter	O
about	O
her	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
pack	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
before	O
you	O
found	O
her	O
unloaded	O
?	O
Fenton	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
mistake	O
in	O
telling	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
forward	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
third	O
or	O
fourth	O
without	O
a	O
pack	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
got	O
upon	O
her	O
and	O
looked	O
about	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
for	O
almost	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
rode	O
on	O
and	O
over-took	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Barnet	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
betwixt	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
you	O
drank	O
with	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
?	O
Fenton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
my	O
inn	O
the	O
White	O
Lion	O
at	O
Coney	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
there	O
betwixt	O
12	O
and	O
one	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
dispatched	O
a	O
messenger	O
to	O
let	O
my	O
master	O
know	O
what	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
proceeded	O
for	O
Lancashire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
your	O
saddle	O
things	O
were	O
cut	O
?	O
Fenton	O
.	O
The	O
saddle	O
and	O
girt	O
were	O
safe	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
wantey	O
that	O
fastened	O
the	O
pack	O
on	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Glover	O
.	O
The	O
wantey	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
Finchley	O
common	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
plain	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Fenton	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
body	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
that	O
night	O
molest	O
you	O
?	O
Fenton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
two	O
recks	O
in	O
Lad-lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
,	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
Highgate	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Swain	O
in	O
Goswell	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
two	O
boxes	O
and	O
a	O
paper	O
parcel	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
inn	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
box	O
directed	O
to	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Dickerson	O
,	O
Lancaster	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Bare	I-pers
of	O
Cartmel	O
;	O
the	O
parcel	O
to	O
Alice	B-pers
Galter	I-pers
,	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
particular	O
things	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boxes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
bought	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
of	O
messieurs	O
Tolfrey	O
and	O
Co.	O
haberdashers	O
and	O
drapers	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
'd	O
do	O
all	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
people	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Swain	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
night	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parcel	O
brought	O
by	O
Thomas	O
Hall	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Swain	O
there	O
were	O
very	O
disorderly	O
persons	O
frequented	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Wood	O
's	O
close	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
;	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
and	O
searched	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
some	O
calico	O
wrappers	O
made	O
into	O
sheets	O
,	O
on	O
two	O
beds	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
particular	O
piece	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lovyer	I-pers
,	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
money	O
and	O
fruit	O
lying	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
were	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
particular	O
mark	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lovyer	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Pearvoy	I-pers
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
made	O
their	O
escape	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
Hessian	O
wrappers	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
directed	O
to	O
J	O
.	O
Wearing	O
,	O
Preston	O
,	O
wrote	O
with	O
ink	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
cut	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
wrapper	O
with	O
A.	O
Branthwaite	O
,	O
Cartmel	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
shed	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
a	O
tub	O
of	O
water	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
calico	O
wrappers	O
which	O
had	O
no	O
directions	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
likewise	O
Mr.	O
Glover	O
's	O
packsheet	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
safely	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
put	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
vault	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
a	O
person	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Ruth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
's	O
mother	O
lived	O
at	O
Deptford	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
new	O
callimanco	O
drab	O
coloured	O
gown	O
on	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
everlasting	O
shoes	O
on	O
her	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
green	O
satin	O
ribbon	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
?	O
she	O
knew	O
me	O
again	O
by	O
seeing	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
She	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
an	O
adjacent	O
place	O
in	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
brown	O
callimanco	O
,	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
dark	O
callimanco	O
,	O
some	O
red	O
,	O
some	O
yellow	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
remnant	O
of	O
which	O
her	O
gown	O
was	O
made	O
.	O
And	O
likewise	O
another	O
gown	O
cut	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
for	O
her	O
sister	O
.	O
Some	O
muslin	O
wrappers	O
,	O
and	O
calico	O
wrappers	O
,	O
black	O
gloves	O
,	O
white	O
gloves	O
,	O
womens	O
green	O
shoes	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
with	O
pins	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
new	O
lawn	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
.	O
(	O
These	O
all	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
at	O
they	O
were	O
named	O
over	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
town	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
ever	O
a	O
parcel	O
in	O
that	O
pack	O
marked	O
R.	O
Addison	O
,	O
Preston	O
?	O
Booth	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
quality	O
,	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
packs	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
callimancos	O
,	O
camblets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
wrapper	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
Finchley	O
common	O
,	O
marked	O
R.	O
Addison	O
,	O
Preston	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
Pearvoy	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
very	O
pale	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
said	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
He	O
knew	O
me	O
by	O
seeing	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
search	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
two	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
in	O
Wood	O
's	O
Close	O
,	O
I	O
frequently	O
used	O
to	O
see	O
John	B-pers
Cornhill	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Pearvoy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lovyer	I-pers
together	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
idling	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
skittle	O
grounds	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lovyer	I-pers
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
blanket	O
,	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
all	O
was	O
not	O
right	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
information	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Morris	O
and	O
found	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
the	O
former	O
witness	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Bride	O
's	O
parish	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Sarah	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
hers	O
be	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
Peter	B-pers
Pearvoy	I-pers
followed	O
me	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
very	O
hastily	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
box	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
again	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
callimanco	O
and	O
keep	O
till	O
her	O
sister	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
trouble	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
being	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Trotter	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
goods	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
easy	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
'd	O
come	O
and	O
seize	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
with	O
an	O
excise	O
officer	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
once	O
lived	O
fellow-servant	O
with	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lovyer	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
he	O
speak	O
English	O
?	O
(	O
Note	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
court	O
much	O
trouble	O
to	O
interpret	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
pretending	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
English	O
.	O
)	O
M.	O
Ward	O
.	O
He	O
can	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
talk	O
'd	O
good	O
English	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
some	O
questions	O
.	O
M.	O
Ward	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
I	O
live	O
where	O
you	O
did	O
?	O
Lovyer	O
.	O
About	O
seventeen	O
months	O
.	O
M.	O
Ward	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
?	O
Lovyer	O
.	O
Above	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
The	O
piece	O
of	O
callimanco	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
M.	O
Ward	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
gown	O
of	O
it	O
cut	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
her	O
brother	O
and	O
sister	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
made	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Note	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
full	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
tea	O
lost	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
pack	O
.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Philipson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Booth	O
and	O
Hall	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Morris	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
finding	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
shut	O
himself	O
in	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
my	O
little	O
girl	O
found	O
a	O
tobacco	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
cram	O
'd	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
powder	O
horn	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
brass	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Tolfrey	O
and	O
Co.	O
haberdashers	O
.	O
The	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
we	O
sent	O
boxes	O
and	O
trusses	O
,	O
in	O
number	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
about	O
twenty	O
,	O
by	O
George	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
all	O
the	O
marks	O
;	O
but	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
mark	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
wrote	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
pencil	O
when	O
I	O
looked	O
the	O
goods	O
out	O
,	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
callico	O
wrappers	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
wrote	O
:	O
Thirty	O
yards	O
of	O
this	O
put	O
up	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Wearing	I-pers
of	O
Preston	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
looks	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
plain	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
now	O
.	O
)	O
It	O
was	O
sent	O
directed	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Wearing	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Preston	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
goods	O
here	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
goods	O
we	O
sent	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
what	O
we	O
sent	O
within	O
the	O
wrapper	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
my	O
private	O
mark	O
on	O
a	O
paper	O
in	O
which	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
black	O
gloves	O
are	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
cloth	O
we	O
always	O
pack	O
our	O
goods	O
up	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
writing	O
on	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Fourder	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
here	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
(	O
These	O
goods	O
he	O
has	O
looked	O
on	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
Morris	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
now	O
looks	O
on	O
the	O
goods	O
found	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
womens	O
black	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
pins	O
,	O
mens	O
black	O
gloves	O
,	O
womens	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silk	O
gymps	O
.	O
)	O
Of	O
these	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
mark	O
on	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
gloves	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
board	O
to	O
the	O
gymps	O
.	O
The	O
gloves	O
were	O
for	O
Addison	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gymp	O
for	O
Branthwaite	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Founder	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Looks	O
at	O
the	O
wrapper	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
about	O
twenty-six	O
boxes	O
and	O
things	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
and	O
Two	O
Necks	O
in	O
Lad-lane	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Booth	O
.	O
That	O
wrapper	O
he	O
speaks	O
of	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
tub	O
of	O
water	O
at	O
Morris	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Philip	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
and	O
comp	O
.	O
near	O
the	O
Monument	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
we	O
sent	O
a	O
truss	O
,	O
directed	O
R.	O
Addison	O
,	O
Preston	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
dark	O
grey	O
Irish	O
camblets	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
looks	O
at	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
they	O
are	O
like	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
One	O
had	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Trotter	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
St.	O
Bride	O
's	O
.	O
This	O
piece	O
he	O
swears	O
to	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
box	O
where	O
the	O
tea	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
measured	O
it	O
45	O
yards	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
in	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
who	O
deals	O
in	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
some	O
tea	O
directed	O
to	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Hall	O
at	O
Poulton	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
G.	O
Glover	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
25	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Trotter	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
Mrs.	O
Ward	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
that	O
lodged	O
where	O
she	O
lives	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
information	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
goods	O
in	O
her	O
apartment	O
which	O
were	O
not	O
lawfully	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
brought	O
by	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lovyer	I-pers
.	O
She	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
thinking	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
goods	O
prohibited	O
by	O
the	O
government	O
,	O
took	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
excise	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
this	O
box	O
of	O
tea	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
warehouse	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
also	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
callimanco	O
I	O
have	O
before	O
mentioned	O
.	O
The	O
tea	O
weighted	O
30	O
pounds	O
,	O
box	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
Booth	O
.	O
Looks	O
at	O
the	O
gown	O
found	O
upon	O
Ruth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
says	O
,	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
callimanco	O
agree	O
as	O
to	O
colour	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Lovyer	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
's	O
house	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
linen	O
washed	O
by	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
sister	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
that	O
box	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ward	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Pearvoy	O
accidentally	O
met	O
with	O
me	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
accompanied	O
me	O
there	O
.	O
Pearvoy	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
searched	O
.	O
Mary	O
Lovyer	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
service	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
White	O
Friers	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
to	O
let	O
me	O
sit	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
to	O
sell	O
fruit	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
license	O
to	O
sell	O
things	O
about	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
that	O
gown	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
mantua-makers	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
for	O
what	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Overton	I-pers
and	O
Catharine	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
appeared	O
for	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lovyer	I-pers
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
attempting	O
to	O
prove	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
lodgings	O
in	O
White	O
Friers	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
lodged	O
,	O
the	O
night	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
also	O
seven	O
other	O
witnesses	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
:	O
but	O
neither	O
could	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
his	O
bread	O
for	O
a	O
year	O
or	O
two	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
ten	O
persons	O
gave	O
Pearvoy	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
One	O
appeared	O
for	O
Ruth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
but	O
could	O
speak	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
three	O
years	O
last	O
past	O
;	O
and	O
five	O
for	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lovyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ruth	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
;	O
Sarah	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Cornhill	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Pearvoy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Lovyer	I-pers
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
431	O
,	O
432	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Penprice	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hog	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joel	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
Joel	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	B-place
Mud-dock	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Rotherhith	I-place
,	O
and	O
lost	O
a	O
sow	O
pig	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
between	O
the	O
1st	O
and	O
second	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
I	O
shut	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
my	O
dog	O
bark	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
pig	O
squeak	O
,	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
pig	O
had	O
a	O
spot	O
or	O
two	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
pigs	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
cut	O
the	O
stye	O
down	O
where	O
the	O
hog	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
second	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
pig	O
of	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
stone	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
spot	O
on	O
the	O
rump	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
below	O
its	O
eye	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
fed	O
it	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
tail	O
and	O
ran	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
boat	O
;	O
we	O
then	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Penprice	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Three	O
Cups	O
near	O
the	O
bridge	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
,	O
Shadwell	O
;	O
the	O
pig	O
gave	O
a	O
squeak	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
dog	O
barked	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
kept	O
at	O
Penprice	O
's	O
house	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
stye	O
where	O
he	O
laid	O
sand	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
was	O
killed	O
by	O
Cook	O
,	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
I	O
discovered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Chapman	O
voluntarily	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
not	O
in	O
custody	O
now	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
I	O
killed	O
a	O
hog	O
for	O
Penprice	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
this	O
might	O
weigh	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
stone	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Penprice	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
known	O
me	O
buy	O
pigs	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
for	O
my	O
family	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Robertson	O
.	O
The	O
butcher	O
suspected	O
the	O
pig	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
killed	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
Perry	O
cut	O
the	O
hair	O
off	O
the	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Smithfield	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Robertson	O
,	O
Penprice	O
,	O
and	O
Perry	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
frequently	O
seen	O
them	O
all	O
three	O
together	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
off	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Penprice	O
and	O
Robertson	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
have	O
come	O
off	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Penprice	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
malicious	O
prosecution	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
;	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
quarrel	O
between	O
me	O
and	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
Far	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
seen	O
these	O
three	O
prisoners	O
together	O
.	O
Perry	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
thing	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Penprice	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hempen	O
bag	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
eighty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
ginger	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
45	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Burnhill	I-pers
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lighter	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Burnhill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
commander	O
of	O
the	O
Augustus	B-pers
Caesar	I-pers
.	O
She	O
lay	O
at	O
Bell	B-place
Wharf	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
little	I-place
below	I-place
Ratcliff	I-place
Cross	I-place
,	O
and	O
a	O
lighter	O
lay	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
bags	O
of	O
ginger	O
on	O
board	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
bags	O
,	O
one	O
marked	O
I.S.S	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
T.B.O	O
.	O
A	O
bag	O
full	O
,	O
marked	O
I.S.S	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
We	O
lost	O
one	O
with	O
this	O
mark	O
and	O
number	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
whether	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
or	O
lighter	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Chamney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
mate	O
of	O
this	O
vessel	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
many	O
hundred	O
bags	O
of	O
ginger	O
on	O
board	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
one	O
lighter	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
another	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
or	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
One	O
was	O
missed	O
about	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
marked	O
I.S.S	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
looks	O
on	O
that	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
he	O
believes	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
Thomas	O
Edwards	O
's	O
yard	O
on	O
Bell	O
Wharf	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
boat	O
betwixt	O
the	O
ship	O
Augustus	B-pers
Caesar	I-pers
and	O
a	O
lighter	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
gray	O
coat	O
take	O
a	O
bag	O
and	O
heave	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
boat	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
lighter	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
one	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
100	O
yards	O
distance	O
;	O
the	O
lighter	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
shore	O
side	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
coarse	O
bag	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
boat	O
go	O
on	O
shore	O
at	O
Storehouse	O
yard	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Owen	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
got	O
into	O
my	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
rowed	O
to	O
Storehouse	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
bag	O
marked	O
S.	O
S.	O
I	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
ginger	O
through	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
I	O
also	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
carry	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
into	O
Storehouse	O
yard	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Herrington	I-pers
followed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
Bell	O
Wharf	O
;	O
Penprice	O
came	O
there	O
in	O
another	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
as	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
that	O
flung	O
the	O
bag	O
into	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
dress	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
Storehouse	O
yard	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
bag	O
was	O
put	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
an	O
house	O
there	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
marked	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
open	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
bag	O
stood	O
on	O
its	O
end	O
,	O
he	O
hove	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
ginger	O
out	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
sort	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
fetch	O
them	O
about	O
an	O
ounce	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
then	O
who	O
would	O
stand	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Herrington	I-pers
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
William	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
said	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
Penprice	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
Robertson	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
walked	O
up	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
the	O
mark	O
and	O
number	O
lying	O
uppermost	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Penprice	O
said	O
,	O
Stop	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
turn	O
the	O
mark	O
downwards	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
Penprice	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
bag	O
was	O
carried	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
His	O
house	O
is	O
about	O
300	O
yards	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Herrington	I-pers
went	O
into	O
his	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
Penprice	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
hold	O
my	O
tongue	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
my	O
share	O
;	O
Herrington	O
and	O
Penprice	O
talked	O
together	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
going	O
along	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
and	O
bran	O
or	O
saw-dust	O
put	O
over	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
an	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
customs	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
captain	O
with	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
mark	O
and	O
number	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Herrington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
boat	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
at	O
Bell	O
Wharf	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
purpose	O
of	O
plying	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
boat	O
shove	O
from	O
between	O
the	O
ship	O
and	O
lighter	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
large	O
bundle	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
head	O
;	O
it	O
went	O
to	O
Storehouse	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
it	O
in	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
take	O
a	O
bag	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
into	O
Storehouse	O
yard	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
mark	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
No	O
.	O
3	O
,	O
such	O
a	O
bag	O
as	O
this	O
produced	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
carry	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
shoved	O
my	O
boat	O
stern	O
on	O
shore	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
bag	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
Penprice	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
a	O
boat	O
along	O
with	O
Robertson	O
;	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
rowed	O
my	O
boat	O
to	O
Bell	O
Wharf	O
,	O
and	O
stoved	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Storehouse	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
bag	O
standing	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
followed	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
Clark	O
's	O
.	O
Penprice	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
turned	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
right	O
sort	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
who	O
would	O
be	O
porter	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
asked	O
Robertson	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
Robertson	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
some	O
distance	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
mark	O
and	O
number	O
upwards	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
turned	O
it	O
downward	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Penprice	O
's	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
one	O
corner	O
,	O
with	O
saw-dust	O
or	O
bran	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
basket	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Austine	I-pers
.	O
The	O
bag	O
of	O
ginger	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
Clark	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
betwixt	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
set	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
I.	O
and	O
S.	O
S.	O
with	O
a	O
cross	O
and	O
figure	O
of	O
3	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Penprice	O
followed	O
it	O
in	O
about	O
5	O
minutes	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
2	O
witnesses	O
;	O
those	O
two	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Penprice	O
turned	O
the	O
bag	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
breaking	O
a	O
hole	O
put	O
his	O
finger	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
ginger	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
sort	O
;	O
then	O
broke	O
a	O
piece	O
and	O
flung	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
The	O
numbers	O
were	O
towards	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
first	O
set	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
this	O
produced	O
?	O
A.	O
Austine	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
and	O
whiter	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
Herrington	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
refused	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
Robertson	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
Penprice	O
stopped	O
him	O
and	O
turned	O
the	O
mark	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
downwards	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
ginger	O
is	O
worth	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
d.	O
per	O
pound	O
.	O
He	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
race	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
sorts	O
,	O
white	O
and	O
black	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
black	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Capt	O
.	O
Burnhill	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
these	O
bags	O
in	O
common	O
?	O
Burnhill	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
weight	O
;	O
some	O
weigh	O
100	O
and	O
some	O
60	O
pounds	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
this	O
ginger	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Call	O
William	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clark	O
to	O
justice	O
Bury	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Penprice	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
my	O
coming	O
to	O
give	O
information	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
a	O
warrant	O
concerning	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
ginger	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
ginger	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Taylor	O
had	O
threatened	O
to	O
do	O
some	O
bodily	O
harm	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
stopped	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
Clark	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
grant	O
this	O
warrant	O
on	O
any	O
condition	O
,	O
only	O
on	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
some	O
roguery	O
being	O
found	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
*	O
*	O
For	O
Penprice	O
,	O
see	O
No	O
.	O
541	O
,	O
also	O
546	O
,	O
547	O
,	O
and	O
548	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mayoralty	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blachford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
433	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
coach	O
door	O
glasses	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chamberlaine	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Jan.	O
14	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Gregory	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
stable-keeper	O
and	O
coach-master	O
.	O
These	O
glasses	O
were	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
coach	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Chamberlaine	O
.	O
He	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Shadrach	O
Vendam	O
produced	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
434.	O
Ellis	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
not	O
surrendering	O
himself	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
order	O
in	O
council	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
appeared	O
;	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
the	O
issues	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
435	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
24	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Nalder	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
22	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
in	O
Milk-street	B-place
market	I-place
.	O
It	O
is	O
usual	O
for	O
the	O
waggons	O
that	O
bring	O
his	O
butter	O
twice	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
to	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
in	O
flats	O
near	O
his	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
depend	O
on	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
watchman	O
till	O
the	O
shop	O
is	O
open	O
.	O
August	O
the	O
22d	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
flats	O
set	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
observ	O
'd	O
to	O
take	O
one	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
Little	O
Britain	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
sixpence	O
for	O
carrying	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
making	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
way	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
436	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
Everet	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lawrence	B-pers
McDuff	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
18	O
,	O
1751	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
intrusted	O
to	O
work	O
up	O
small	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
way	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
away	O
half	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
gold	O
without	O
his	O
knowledge	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
caster	O
to	O
be	O
cast	O
into	O
a	O
hook	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
could	O
find	O
where	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
to	O
the	O
court	O
rather	O
a	O
breach	O
of	O
trust	O
than	O
a	O
felony	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
former	O
quarrels	O
between	O
them	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
572	O
in	O
Cokayne	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
437	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6.	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Giles	B-pers
Lone	I-pers
,	O
June	O
27	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
436	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Barrington	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
saws	O
,	O
called	O
turning	O
saws	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowse	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
1	O
.	O
1750	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
439	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
wooden	O
tubs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dowse	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
13	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
440	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Wiggins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
July	O
26	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
over	O
London-bridge	B-place
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
right	O
side	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
looked	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
out	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
meet	O
or	O
follow	O
you	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
He	O
followed	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
over	O
his	O
shoulder	O
to	O
another	O
boy	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
friend	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
I	O
both	O
felt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
deliver	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
very	O
plain	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
441	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
duffle	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
7	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
is	O
a	O
pavior	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
apprentice	O
were	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
and	O
had	O
laid	O
their	O
clothes	O
near	O
the	O
foot	O
path	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
apprentice	O
's	O
coat	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
442	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Churchman	I-pers
,	I-pers
widow	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
Row	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Forbus	I-pers
,	O
July	O
18	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
chared	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
her	O
trial	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
443	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Huits	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
31	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
above	O
the	O
bars	O
,	O
this	O
day	O
7	O
night	O
about	O
6	O
o'clock	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
buy	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
my	O
wife	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
selling	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
broker	O
to	O
come	O
who	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
landlady	O
,	O
then	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
broker	O
and	O
two	O
porters	O
through	O
the	O
passage	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
broker	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
to	O
buy	O
your	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
broker	O
took	O
his	O
leave	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
harm	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
insisted	O
upon	O
staying	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
buying	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
not	O
go	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
,	O
