TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
27th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
CRISP	O
GASCOYNE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1753	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
CRISP	O
GASCOYNE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
,	O
*	O
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
++	O
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
*	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Trimmer	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tenniswood	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Remnant	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Champion	I-pers
,	O
Barnard	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Watlington	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Weedon	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
Henry	O
Hewitt	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nicoll	I-pers
,	O
jun	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Memelin	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Briant	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Haley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lightwood	I-pers
.	O
372	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Gumbleton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Salvay	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Salvay	I-pers
.	O
About	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
by	O
the	O
watch-house	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
behind	O
me	O
say	O
,	O
You	O
dog	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
follow	O
that	O
gentleman	O
;	O
you	O
mean	O
no	O
good	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
John	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
had	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
in	O
a	O
posture	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
as	O
though	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
water	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Grant	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
observed	O
him	O
to	O
follow	O
me	O
up	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
Gracechurch-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
by	O
what	O
he	O
observ	O
'd	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
pick	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
boy	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
then	O
a	O
little	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Grant	O
had	O
first	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
place	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
lay	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
where	O
he	O
stood	O
,	O
(	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
)	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Salvay	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
other	O
little	O
boy	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
might	O
drop	O
it	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
excused	O
himself	O
in	O
that	O
sort	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
Salvay	O
.	O
Two	O
shillings	O
,	O
it	O
cost	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
used	O
much	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
follow	O
you	O
?	O
Salvay	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
did	O
not	O
appear	O
when	O
call	O
'd	O
.	O
Salvay	O
.	O
He	O
intended	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
home	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Grant	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
design	O
to	O
pick	O
that	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
design	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
373	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Blackburne	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
pillowbier	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Dennis	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Dennis	B-pers
Redman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	I-place
and	I-place
keep	I-place
the	I-place
spotted	I-place
horse	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
publick-house	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
three	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
and	O
a	O
pillowbier	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
so	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
writing	O
a	O
letter	O
at	O
a	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
kept	O
writing	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
things	O
that	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Hughes	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
whether	O
the	O
things	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
Mr.	O
Redman	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
finding	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Redman	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
as	O
before	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
and	O
committed	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Robins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
wash	O
'd	O
these	O
three	O
sheets	O
and	O
pillowbier	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Redman	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
laid	O
on	O
that	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
iron	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
missed	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
evidence	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Redman	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
work	O
of	O
carding	O
and	O
spinning	O
of	O
wool	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
work	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
an	O
apron	O
with	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Magpye	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
bed	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
four	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
lay	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
them	O
and	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
into	O
Kent	O
a	O
hopping	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
374	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
July	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
375	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Frances	B-pers
Bruel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Jane	B-pers
Germain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Haynes	O
at	O
Tom	B-place
's	I-place
Coffee-house	I-place
,	I-place
Great-Russel-Street	I-place
,	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
who	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
broken	O
victuals	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wash-house	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
wash-house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
who	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
spoon	O
which	O
we	O
missed	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
spoon	O
to	O
sell	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
(	O
Produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
by	O
Jane	B-pers
Germain	I-pers
,	O
as	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
her	O
master	O
Mr.	O
Haynes	O
)	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
and	O
advertis	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
evidence	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
as	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
stopp	O
'd	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Haynes	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
demand	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
cur	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
spoon	O
facing	O
Cross-Lane	O
in	O
Long-Acre	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
shop	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
who	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
owner	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
thinking	O
to	O
have	O
some	O
reward	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
J.	O
Germain	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
spoon	O
whole	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
wash-house	O
.	O
Germain	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
376	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Henasey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mortley	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Acq	O
.	O
377	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Frances	B-pers
Pigsworth	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
ounces	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
weight	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newsham	I-pers
,	O
July	O
30	O
,	O
++	O
Acq	O
.	O
378	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Diana	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Portugal	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
val	O
.	O
27	O
s.	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Sweet	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Aug	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	O
Sweet	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
a	B-place
little	I-place
below	I-place
Ratcliff-Cross	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler's-shop	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
customer	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
lives	O
hard	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
in	O
again	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
drawer	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
27	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
upwards	O
of	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
to	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
returned	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
since	O
breakfast	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
swear	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
drawer	O
and	O
such	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
two	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
run	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
apron	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
hand	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Goldson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
five	O
doors	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Sweet	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wanted	O
her	O
husband	O
to	O
give	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
confess	O
taking	O
it	O
?	O
Goldson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
379.	O
(	O
L	O
.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rider	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
++	O
Acq	O
.	O
380	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
quilt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Aug.	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Acq	O
.	O
381	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
quilt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pillow	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Glade	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain-lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Aug.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Glade	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford	B-place
Road	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodgings	O
at	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
week	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
clean	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
foul	O
ones	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
produced	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
gimblet	O
,	O
and	O
bored	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
wainscot	O
,	O
thro	O
'	O
which	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
quilt	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
pillow	O
,	O
sheets	O
and	O
looking	O
glass	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
had	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
confessed	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
two	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
382	O
,	O
383	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
and	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Watkins	I-pers
and	O
Ann	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Ann	O
Watkins	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
worsted	O
curtains	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3s	O
.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
pillowbiers	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
window	O
curtains	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
teaster	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
head	O
cloth	O
and	O
one	O
vallens	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
July	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Price	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Ann	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linseywoolsey	O
bed	O
curtains	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pillow-biers	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Ann	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
384	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Homer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Aug.	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Esther	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
from	O
off	O
my	O
chimney-piece	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
30th	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
lads	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
kitchen	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
victuals	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
just	O
by	O
Halbourn	O
bridge	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
enquiring	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
boys	O
idling	O
about	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
same	O
tea-kettle	O
which	O
that	O
evidence	O
delivered	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
386	O
,	O
387	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
,	O
July	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cable-street	B-place
near	I-place
Well-close-Square	I-place
;	O
Mr.	O
Lloyd	O
,	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
then	O
missed	O
one	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
bowl	O
of	O
a	O
spoon	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
handle	O
from	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
bowl	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
The	O
Silversmith	O
not	O
appearing	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
both	O
aquitted	O
.	O
388	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newhouse	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newhouse	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Smithfield	B-place
,	O
being	O
Bartholomew	O
fair	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
a	O
croud	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
down	O
my	O
hand	O
side-ways	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
coat	O
open	O
,	O
or	O
buttoned	O
?	O
Newhouse	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchiefs	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
just	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
the	O
back	O
way	O
into	O
the	O
George	O
yard	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
where	O
my	O
other	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
;	O
in	O
leading	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
an	O
another	O
hung	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Newhouse	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
last	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
it	O
?	O
Newhouse	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
about	O
4	O
minutes	O
before	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Newhouse	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
;	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'clock	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
George	O
inn	O
we	O
were	O
crouded	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
his	O
pocket	O
picked	O
of	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
the	O
George	O
yard	O
,	O
bringing	O
him	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
draw	O
out	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
hung	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
your	O
brother	O
's	O
handkerchief	O
fall	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
Newhouse	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
left	O
foot	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Usherwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
his	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
just	O
by	O
his	O
foot	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
we	O
'd	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
pushing	O
through	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
dropped	O
just	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
up	O
the	O
George	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
throwed	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
pond	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
dry	O
thread	O
about	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
after	O
that	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
389	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Lindal	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Aaron	B-pers
Declevea	I-pers
,	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
No	O
prosecutor	O
appeared	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
390	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
mettle	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
silver	O
mouth	O
piece	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
3	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
391	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Reyner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
willow	O
basket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
peck	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
French	O
beans	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
392	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
2	O
++	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
parish	B-place
of	I-place
Kensington	I-place
:	O
last	O
Sunday	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Harper	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
:	O
the	O
socket	O
of	O
the	O
ladle	O
,	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
Ratcliff	B-pers
Littler	I-pers
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
a	O
drunken	O
frolick	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
.	O
Ratcliff	O
Littler	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
comrade	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
regiment	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Sept	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
cunning	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspects	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
cunning	O
devil	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
it	O
the	O
socket	O
of	O
this	O
ladle	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
for	O
his	O
landlord	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
looks	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
says	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
bit	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
other	O
part	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
landlord	O
's	O
cupboard	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
393	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tottey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
camblet	O
skirt	O
of	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
qrs	O
.	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
August	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Southen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
road	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
without	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
child	O
crying	O
very	O
much	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
telling	O
the	O
child	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
good	O
manners	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
use	O
such	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
some	O
soldiers	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
great	O
garden	O
gate	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
cry	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
again	O
and	O
observ	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
sitting	O
her	O
crying	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
child	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
woman	O
?	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
no	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
at	O
a	O
baker	O
's	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
child	O
if	O
she	O
'd	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
coming	O
by	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Tottey	O
's	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
child	O
cry	O
'd	O
for	O
its	O
skirt	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
O	O
!	O
my	O
skirt	O
,	O
my	O
skirt	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
E.	O
Southen	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Tottey	I-pers
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
ribbon	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
;	O
then	O
her	O
mother	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Dog-Row	B-place
,	I-place
Bethlem-Green	I-place
;	O
that	O
day	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
whipping	O
the	O
child	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
ribbon	O
off	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
her	O
own	O
bosom	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
her	O
cap	O
off	O
and	O
rowl	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
had	O
no	O
skirt	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
she	O
whipped	O
the	O
child	O
for	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
might	O
do	O
what	O
she	O
pleased	O
with	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
child	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
child	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
then	O
,	O
)	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
before	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
child	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tottey	I-pers
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
child	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
coats	O
,	O
about	O
4	O
years	O
old	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Children-in-the-wood	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
church	O
and	O
the	O
turnpike	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
neighbours	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
child	O
was	O
stripp	O
'd	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
child	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Southen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
your	O
child	O
dressed	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
M.	O
Tottey	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
that	O
skirt	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
ribbon	O
of	O
about	O
3	O
qrs	O
.	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
dressed	O
her	O
myself	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
she	O
had	O
neither	O
the	O
skirt	O
nor	O
the	O
ribbon	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
this	O
and	O
another	O
to	O
school	O
together	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
almshouses	O
,	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
that	O
skirt	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
coming	O
along	O
I	O
met	O
that	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
whose	O
skirt	O
it	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
child	O
has	O
no	O
skirt	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
hang	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
394	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
brass	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
twelve	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
copper	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Scoting	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
395	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
18	O
s	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mullings	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mullings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Watling-Street	B-place
,	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
a	O
vellum	O
binder	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
2	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
18	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
under	O
my	O
trunk	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
where	O
I	O
lie	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Mullings	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
that	O
same	O
night	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
others	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
spent	O
the	O
18	O
s	O
piece	O
,	O
but	O
throwed	O
the	O
2	O
guineas	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
into	O
a	O
pond	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
saying	O
his	O
conscience	O
pricked	O
him	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
fellow-servant	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
confirm	O
'd	O
that	O
of	O
the	O
confession	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
What	O
they	O
have	O
said	O
is	O
false	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
396	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Whitefield	I-pers
,	O
clerk	O
;	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cutley	I-pers
,	O
clerk	O
;	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
monies	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whitefield	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Whitefield	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
Blandford	O
stage-coach	O
,	O
and	O
proceeded	O
up	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
through	O
Hide-Park	O
turnpike	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
a	B-place
little	I-place
beyond	I-place
Knights-bridge	I-place
,	O
the	O
coach	O
stopt	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
words	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
what	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
beside	O
myself	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
heard	O
words	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
like	O
these	O
words	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
the	O
coach	O
stop	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
horsemen	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
wheel	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
discern	O
any	O
face	O
of	O
any	O
sort	O
.	O
)	O
Upon	O
my	O
saying	O
these	O
words	O
,	O
one	O
advanced	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Money	O
,	O
Sir	O
!	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
what	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
silver	O
and	O
gold	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
hat	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
held	O
it	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
doing	O
this	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
ratling	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
let	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
coach	O
window	O
:	O
the	O
next	O
words	O
I	O
heard	O
,	O
was	O
watches	O
too	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
threw	O
into	O
the	O
hat	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Horniblow	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
last	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
went	O
from	O
James	O
Southerlands	O
.	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Two	O
Browers	O
,	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Little	O
Soffron-hill	O
;	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
from	O
his	O
house	O
two	O
briddles	O
and	O
saddles	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
ground	O
at	O
Black-Mary's-Hole	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
horses	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
bridled	O
and	O
saddled	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
out	O
to	O
Hide-Park-Corner	O
,	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
rode	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
waiting	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
came	O
up	O
about	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Blandford	O
stage	O
with	O
4	O
horses	O
;	O
we	O
past	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
demanded	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hat	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
for	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
that	O
into	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
this	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
not	O
being	O
down	O
he	O
struck	O
at	O
it	O
either	O
with	O
the	O
butt	O
end	O
of	O
his	O
pistol	O
or	O
his	O
whip	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
them	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
kept	O
what	O
he	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
kept	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Horniblow	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
one	O
Rowland	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
and	O
he	O
kept	O
it	O
till	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
it	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
?	O
Horniblow	O
.	O
To	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
discovered	O
the	O
thing	O
to	O
Rowland	O
at	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
had	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
to	O
put	O
off	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
us	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
put	O
off	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
and	O
nobody	O
be	O
ne'er	O
the	O
wiser	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
gave	O
it	O
Southerland	O
and	O
he	O
pawned	O
it	O
with	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Nicolls	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
us	O
but	O
30	O
s.	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
30	O
s.	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
between	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
which	O
had	O
most	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Southerland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Horniblow	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
brewer	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nicolls	O
's	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
both	O
together	O
?	O
Southerland	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
desired	O
you	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
?	O
Southerland	O
.	O
Horniblow	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nicolls	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
:	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
and	O
put	O
all	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examin	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
your	O
wife	O
ask	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
Southerland	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
answer	O
did	O
Horniblow	O
give	O
?	O
Southerland	O
.	O
Says	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
fetch	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
pay	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
watch	O
?	O
Southerland	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
say	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
him	O
?	O
Southerland	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
friend	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Maddox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
justice	O
Lediard	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Nicholls	O
's	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Whitefield	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Whitefield	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
all	O
the	O
reason	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
to	O
believe	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
it	O
any	O
particular	O
marks	O
?	O
Whitefield	O
.	O
The	O
marks	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
is	O
No	O
.	O
7	O
,	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
Thomas	B-pers
Budge	I-pers
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
looks	O
at	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
)	O
this	O
watch	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Southerland	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Budge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cutley	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Whitefield	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
your	O
own	O
watch	O
?	O
Whitefield	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
borrowed	O
this	O
watch	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cutley	O
,	O
to	O
travel	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
my	O
gold	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Rose	O
Southerland	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Horniblow	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
Horniblow	O
owed	O
me	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
trusted	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
liquors	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
wanted	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
brewer	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
him	O
?	O
R.	O
Southerland	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
uncle	O
left	O
it	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
mother	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
R.	O
Southerland	O
.	O
Horniblow	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
claim	O
any	O
right	O
to	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
watch	O
?	O
R.	O
Southerland	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
R.	O
Southerland	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
of	O
a	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
laid	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
had	O
you	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
of	O
nights	O
?	O
R.	O
Southerland	O
.	O
At	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
not	O
he	O
go	O
out	O
after	O
you	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
?	O
R.	O
Southerland	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
sometimes	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
keys	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
not	O
.	O
Edmund	B-pers
Beeten	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Barber	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Southerland	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Horniblow	O
were	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
hearing	O
Mrs.	O
Southerland	O
demand	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
Horniblow	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
a	O
watch	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
leave	O
it	O
in	O
pawn	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
ready	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
brewer	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
without	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Nicholls	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
while	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
E.	O
Beeten	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
watch	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
you	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
then	O
Horniblow	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
just	O
a	O
lad	O
as	O
ever	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
money	O
for	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
always	O
found	O
him	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
husband	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Tower-Hill	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
was	O
tweleve	O
month	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
liberty	O
of	O
every	O
farthing	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
half-penny	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Butcher	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behav	O
'd	O
extraordinary	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Reddrop	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upwards	O
of	O
these	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
inclinable	O
to	O
any	O
harm	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
honest	O
careful	O
boy	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
very	O
intimate	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
soberly	O
and	O
honestly	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
his	O
master	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
untold	O
gold	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Edmund	O
Clifford	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
397	O
,	O
398	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
linnen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Turner	O
,	O
August	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Judith	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
my	O
husband	O
keeps	O
a	O
linnen	O
draper	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Jones	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
shew	O
her	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
cotton	O
for	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
several	O
pieces	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
that	O
she	O
lik	O
'd	O
,	O
nor	O
none	O
that	O
would	O
come	O
at	O
her	O
price	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
sets	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
fruit	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linnen	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
linnen	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
Carter	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
Carter	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examin	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Jones	O
confess	O
the	O
fact	O
?	O
J.	O
Turner	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
the	O
linnen	O
into	O
her	O
lap	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
other	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
neither	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Jones	O
's	O
lap	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Dobbings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
with	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
linnen	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
(	O
be	O
produces	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
in	O
Castle	O
Yard	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
upon	O
Saffron	O
hill	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
Castle	O
Yard	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
Jones	O
with	O
the	O
linnen	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
linnen	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Warring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sell	O
fruit	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
2	O
women	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
Jones	O
is	O
one	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
differ	O
about	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Jones	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
talk	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
,	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
bussle	O
something	O
between	O
the	O
child	O
and	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
Holborn	O
,	O
one	O
end	O
hung	O
out	O
below	O
the	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
more	O
than	O
your	O
due	O
;	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
does	O
it	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
nd	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
whether	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Warring	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
Jones	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
ye	O
hold	O
this	O
bundle	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
blue	O
cloak	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
heard	O
somebody	O
cry	O
,	O
step	O
thief	O
!	O
immediately	O
she	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Castle	O
Yard	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Turner	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
the	O
only	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
with	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Carter	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Isabella	O
James	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Margaret	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
:	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
with	O
my	O
barrow	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
Two-blue-posts	O
tavern	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Carter	O
with	O
a	O
blue	O
cloak	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
stop	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
linnen-draper	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
blue	O
cloak	O
,	O
Jones	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
another	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
Carter	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
till	O
she	O
shifted	O
the	O
child	O
on	O
her	O
other	O
arm	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
bundle	O
into	O
her	O
hand	O
and	O
stood	O
still	O
;	O
then	O
Carter	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
turning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
bundle	O
with	O
Jones	O
,	O
who	O
stood	O
talking	O
till	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
Castle	O
Yard	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
it	O
was	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Turner	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
linnen	O
in	O
the	O
blue	O
cloak	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Jones	O
lap	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
in	O
nothing	O
but	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Jones	O
about	O
3	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
a	O
year	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
behaved	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
true	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Wallace	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Jones	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
girl	O
.	O
Bryant	B-pers
Mooney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
as	O
such	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Jones	O
8	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
in	O
Dublin	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
three	O
months	O
in	O
England	O
;	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
girl	O
.	O
Jones	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Carter	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
399	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
not	O
surrendering	O
himself	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
order	O
in	O
council	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
produced	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
jury	O
found	O
the	O
issues	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
400	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Nathaniel	I-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
missed	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
it	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
401	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass	O
knocker	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peregrine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
knocker	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Peregrine	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hart-street	B-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
brass	O
knocker	O
from	O
my	O
street	O
door	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
July	O
:	O
the	O
watchman	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
The	O
knocker	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Ten-pence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
York	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
market	O
:	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
trying	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
knocker	O
off	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
person	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
off	O
.	O
He	O
shewed	O
us	O
the	O
doors	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
from	O
;	O
one	O
was	O
this	O
witness	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Ball	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
402	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Rimer	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
,	O
July	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
Ann	O
Wheatley	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
child	O
in	O
a	O
cradle	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
near	O
the	O
ditch	O
side	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
leave	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
cradle	O
,	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wheatley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
changed	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
12	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
four	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
her	O
many	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
wrong	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
girl	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
RECOMMENDED	O
.	O
403	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Esther	B-pers
Odew	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Mary	B-pers
Maun	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
one	O
stripe	O
linnen	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Maun	I-pers
,	O
her	O
father	O
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Martha	B-pers
Maun	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
the	O
cloaths	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
gown	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
holding	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
,	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
that	O
go	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
child	O
before	O
her	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
staid	O
for	O
somebody	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
petticoat	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
unlace	O
her	O
stays	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
stripping	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
her	O
mother	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
snew	O
me	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
she	O
lend	O
me	O
about	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
but	O
brought	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
the	O
mother	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
brother	O
seeing	O
her	O
,	O
owned	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
again	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
404	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
,	I-pers
Casper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
privately	O
from	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
the	O
juror	O
unknown	O
.	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
No	O
evidence	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
405	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
ounces	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baynard	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Tittcut	I-pers
,	O
August	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
It	O
appearing	O
to	O
the	O
Court	O
that	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
silk	O
belonged	O
to	O
Baynard	O
and	O
part	O
to	O
Tittcut	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
not	O
partners	O
but	O
separate	O
dealers	O
,	O
therefore	O
the	O
Indictment	O
not	O
being	O
laid	O
right	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
406	O
,	O
407	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Webley	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Cibber	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8s	O
.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Small	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
Aug.	O
16	O
.	O
No	O
prosecutor	O
appearing	O
they	O
were	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
408	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Hadlep	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Greenfield	I-pers
,	O
July	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Greenfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Brewer-street	B-place
,	I-place
Golden-Square	I-place
;	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
the	O
last	O
prisoners	O
suffered	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
twenty-third	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
girl	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
brass	O
nail	O
over	O
the	O
fire-place	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
waked	O
at	O
three	O
o'clock	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
enquiry	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
some	O
keys	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
her	O
af	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fitz	O
.	O
Henry	O
,	O
who	O
look	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
wife	O
your	O
bedfellow	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
young	O
girl	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
wife	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
an	O
hundred	O
and	O
fifty	O
miles	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
girl	O
that	O
watch	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
she	O
go	O
away	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
At	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
watch	O
there	O
then	O
?	O
Greenfield	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Fitz	I-pers
.	O
Henry	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
liquors	O
,	O
she	O
seemed	O
much	O
fuddled	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
drank	O
what	O
she	O
first	O
called	O
for	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
more	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
money	O
she	O
had	O
that	O
which	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
called	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
High	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
We	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
girl	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
that	O
night	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Coming	O
along	O
Beaver-Street	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
was	O
seven	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
woman	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
us	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
good	O
to	O
treat	O
us	O
with	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
rasberry	O
gin	O
and	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
cherry	O
brandy	O
,	O
we	O
drank	O
out	O
the	O
bottle	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
cloaths	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
look	O
tight	O
and	O
clean	O
:	O
afterwards	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
this	O
till	O
I	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
guinea	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
offer	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
harm	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
to	O
Fitz-Henry	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
I	O
told	O
a	O
story	O
,	O
in	O
saying	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
409	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Gains	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Joel	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Aug.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
Jonathan	O
Joel	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
after	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
treat	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
Joel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
I.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
pick	O
you	O
up	O
,	O
or	O
you	O
them	O
?	O
Joel	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
common	O
salutation	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
several	O
publick-houses	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
one	O
was	O
in	O
Montague-Court	B-place
,	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Stitchbury	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
each	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sit	O
down	O
?	O
Joel	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
,	O
one	O
sat	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
staid	O
some	O
considerable	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
?	O
Joel	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
how	O
long	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
your	O
watch	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Joel	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
all	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
were	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
this	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
invited	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
that	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
thing	O
?	O
Joel	O
.	O
Called	O
carnal	O
conversation	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
alley	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
carnal	O
conversation	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
swear	O
that	O
;	O
as	O
she	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
was	O
getting	O
things	O
in	O
order	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
she	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
snatch	O
'd	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
lug	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
let	O
go	O
her	O
hold	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
catch	O
her	O
again	O
?	O
Joel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
here	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
.	O
This	O
watch	O
(	O
holding	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
in	O
a	O
spunging-house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
upon	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
case	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
lend	O
him	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
we	O
were	O
got	O
for	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
easy	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
conversation	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
dropped	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
upon	O
her	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
watch	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
410	O
,	O
411	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
out	O
thence	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
twenty-three	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
and	O
one	O
tin	O
cannister	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pint	O
of	O
rum	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
glass	O
bottle	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Peterson	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Jane	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	I-pers
I	I-pers
am	I-pers
wife	I-pers
to	I-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
James	O
,	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
in	O
New-street	O
,	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
twenty-fifth	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
had	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
casement	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
yard	O
door	O
also	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
safe	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
missed	O
was	O
the	O
sugar	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
which	O
our	O
lodger	O
Peterson	O
had	O
brought	O
home	O
from	O
abroad	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hat	O
also	O
of	O
his	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
sugar	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
about	O
3	O
d.	O
per	O
pound	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
tin	O
cannister	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
missing	O
about	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
rum	O
in	O
a	O
quart	O
bottle	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
days	O
after	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
who	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
tin	O
cannister	O
and	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
justice	O
Richards	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
them	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Nicholas	O
Peterson	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Holmes	O
,	O
the	O
cannister	O
,	O
sugar	O
,	O
hat	O
and	O
rum	O
were	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
eleven	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
were	O
safe	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
seven	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
broke	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
casement	O
open	O
and	O
back	O
door	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
things	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
a	O
thieving	O
together	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
broke	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
Philip	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
lifted	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
back	O
yard	O
door	O
and	O
let	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
casement	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
handed	O
them	O
out	O
the	O
sugar	O
in	O
a	O
tin	O
cannister	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
rum	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
casement	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Caherine	O
Murphy	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
us	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
we	O
sold	O
the	O
hat	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
whom	O
;	O
we	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
betwixt	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
the	O
rum	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
begin	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Brian	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
C.	O
Murphy	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
lads	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
twenty-three	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
rum	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
three	O
pence	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
5	O
s.	O
9	O
d	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
may	O
be	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
bring	O
the	O
sugar	O
in	O
?	O
C.	O
Murphy	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
coarse	O
cloth	O
,	O
(	O
She	O
produced	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
sugar	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
like	O
that	O
sugar	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
too	O
dark	O
colour	O
'd	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brebrook	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
second	O
or	O
third	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
the	O
turnkey	O
of	O
Bridewell	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
evidence	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
Brian	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
inform	O
'd	O
against	O
two	O
fellows	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Brian	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
in	O
Sun-Tavern-Fields	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
we	O
looked	O
about	O
we	O
should	O
find	O
a	O
tin	O
cannister	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Elwall	I-pers
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
a	O
lower	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
tin	O
cannister	O
near	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
Brian	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
hat	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
with	O
Brian	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Peterson	O
;	O
Brian	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
you	O
bought	O
a	O
hat	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
Peterson	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
several	O
hats	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
,	O
(	O
holding	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
hat	O
he	O
lost	O
;	O
we	O
would	O
have	O
subpaened	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Peterson	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
cannister	O
?	O
Peterson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
hat	O
.	O
Peterson	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoners	O
ever	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Brebrook	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Elwall	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
empty	O
house	O
along	O
with	O
Brebrook	O
;	O
he	O
exactly	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
Brebrook	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
;	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
they	O
confessed	O
nothing	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
,	O
Brian	O
brought	O
the	O
tin	O
cannister	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
412	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Abraham	I-pers
Enslow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
camblet	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
one	O
holland	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
cambrick	O
hoods	O
laced	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
linnen	O
rags	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
missing	O
also	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
easy	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
me	O
them	O
all	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
the	O
petticoat	O
on	O
her	O
now	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
hired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
full	O
charge	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
young	O
child	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
things	O
gone	O
;	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
surrendered	O
herself	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
then	O
in	O
his	O
and	O
my	O
hearing	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
in	O
her	O
mind	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
character	O
being	O
talked	O
on	O
so	O
much	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
work	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
She	O
lent	O
me	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
413	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Fury	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
yarn	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
buckles	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Terrance	B-pers
Rorke	I-pers
,	O
August	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Terrance	B-pers
Rorke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	B-place
of	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
with	O
one	O
Catherine	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
and	O
asleep	O
when	O
these	O
thing	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
shoes	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
word	O
sent	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
other	O
cloaths	O
of	O
a	O
friend	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
my	O
things	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Rorke	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
gave	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
who	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Catherine	O
Robertson	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
market	O
woman	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
how	O
his	O
cloaths	O
were	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
them	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
shoes	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
person	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
on	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
old	O
cloaths	O
and	O
was	O
crying	O
them	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
hung	O
them	O
on	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
going	O
along	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
lost	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
414	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Bignall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
portugal	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
May	O
21	O
,	O
1752	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Poulter	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Limehouse	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
was	O
a	O
twelve	O
month	O
;	O
he	O
pretended	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
he	O
pitch	O
'd	O
upon	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
begged	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
my	O
father	O
to	O
oblige	O
him	O
in	O
changing	O
a	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
my	O
father	O
had	O
some	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
sum	O
'd	O
up	O
:	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
one	O
,	O
my	O
father	O
drawed	O
his	O
hand	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
forwards	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
so	O
again	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
what	O
my	O
father	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
afterwards	O
*	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
just	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
father	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
ever	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
look	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
guinea	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
much	O
desac	O
'd	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
missed	O
while	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
my	O
father	O
missed	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
miss	O
the	O
18	O
s	O
piece	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
our	O
servant	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
my	O
father	O
accused	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
my	O
father	O
whether	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
his	O
oath	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
half	O
pence	O
and	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
so	O
strict	O
as	O
to	O
observe	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
robbed	O
you	O
of	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
then	O
here	O
they	O
are	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
are	O
satisfied	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
I	O
may	O
go	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
answer	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
satisfied	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
like	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
neighbours	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
father	O
charging	O
an	O
officer	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
for	O
a	O
fraud	O
.	O
*	O
This	O
here-say	O
is	O
not	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
printed	O
;	O
but	O
only	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
introductory	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
avoided	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
acknowledge	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
E.	O
Poulter	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
was	O
bail	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
on	O
bail	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Maxwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
called	O
me	O
from	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
overtook	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
my	O
master	O
whether	O
he	O
could	O
sware	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
half-pence	O
and	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
three	O
guineas	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
your	O
three	O
guineas	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
other	O
gold	O
amongst	O
his	O
money	O
?	O
Maxwell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
him	O
.	O
Maxwell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
missed	O
the	O
18	O
s.	O
piece	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Newgate	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
charged	O
him	O
there	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
master	O
would	O
admit	O
him	O
to	O
bad	O
he	O
'd	O
make	O
it	O
all	O
good	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
Let	O
me	O
see	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
hats	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
price	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
one	O
upon	O
your	O
word	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
chose	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
line	O
and	O
loop	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
call	O
tomorrow	O
morning	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
could	O
you	O
oblige	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
Queen	O
ANN	O
's	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
chest	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
very	O
welcome	O
if	O
there	O
are	O
any	O
here	O
,	O
your	O
eyes	O
are	O
better	O
than	O
mine	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
look	O
and	O
see	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
;	O
the	O
daughter	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
any	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
down	O
a	O
Queen	O
ANN	O
's	O
guinea	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
his	O
money	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
rag	O
as	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
chest	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
,	O
a	O
boy	O
came	O
running	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
was	O
not	O
you	O
at	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
master	O
desires	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
wants	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
running	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
mistake	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
looking	O
over	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
three	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
miss	O
twenty	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
a	O
reason	O
that	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
all	O
my	O
halfpence	O
and	O
some	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
here	O
is	O
any	O
money	O
which	O
you	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
punish	O
'd	O
according	O
to	O
law	O
,	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
three	O
guineas	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
go	O
about	O
your	O
business	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
an	O
officer	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
rightly	O
swear	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
all	O
the	O
work	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
now	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
that	O
informs	O
against	O
the	O
bawdy-houses	O
and	O
my	O
friends	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
are	O
trie	O
d	O
you	O
'	O
l	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
shall	O
give	O
you	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
trouble	O
about	O
it	O
till	O
now	O
,	O
nor	O
should	O
have	O
now	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
five	O
guineas	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Rose-and-Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Church-lane	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
an	O
India-Man	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Hardey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Adam	O
and	O
Eve	O
,	O
in	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Whitechapel	O
officer	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
arrested	O
people	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
ever	O
stole	O
three	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
securities	O
.	O
Catherine	O
Wilkerson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
well	O
belov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
bears	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
life	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
three	O
guineas	O
.	O
Barbara	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Church-lane	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
415	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Oliver	B-pers
Mac	I-pers
Allister	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
bushels	O
of	O
pease	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
eight	O
wooden	O
posts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bucknell	I-pers
,	O
doctor	O
in	O
physic	O
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
produc	O
'd	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
either	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
his	O
indictment	O
granted	O
him	O
.	O
416	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Lydia	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
to	I-pers
Oliver	I-pers
Mac	I-pers
Allister	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Lydia	I-pers
Roach	I-pers
,	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Lydia	O
Roach	O
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
pistol	O
loaded	O
with	O
gunpowder	O
and	O
leaden	O
shot	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
held	O
in	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
did	O
shoot	O
off	O
at	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
to	O
kill	O
and	O
murder	O
,	O
Jan.	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
shot	O
at	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
chamber	O
window	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
hurt	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
ball	O
,	O
or	O
shot	O
,	O
were	O
not	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
to	O
be	O
leaden	O
shot	O
;	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
prov	O
'd	O
in	O
order	O
for	O
conviction	O
;	O
this	O
came	O
short	O
of	O
proof	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
her	O
indictment	O
granted	O
.	O
417	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
,	O
(	O
knowing	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
)	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
of	O
plate	O
,	O
stolen	O
by	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Hoad	O
,	O
by	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Anderton	I-pers
,	O
Aug	O
1	O
.	O
who	O
were	O
tried	O
,	O
cast	O
,	O
and	O
executed	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
Chelmsford	O
assizes	O
last	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
The	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
record	O
of	O
their	O
conviction	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Anderton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
prosecutor	O
of	O
Benson	O
,	O
and	O
Wood	O
,	O
at	O
Chelmsford	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
cast	O
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
plate	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
West	O
Ham	O
Abbey	O
,	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
Spring-Gardens	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
goods	O
were	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
She	O
knew	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
stole	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
told	O
her	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
rob	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
return	O
'd	O
they	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
over	O
her	O
head	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
'd	O
fire	O
it	O
thro	O
'	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
awake	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
a	O
prize	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
plate	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
quart	O
silver	O
tankard	O
and	O
two	O
spoons	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Parnell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Mr.	O
Anderton	O
,	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
two	O
Sailors	O
who	O
dined	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
prov	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Benson	O
and	O
Wood	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
describ	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
pale-fac	O
'd	O
men	O
in	O
blue	O
jackets	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
neighbours	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
printed	O
bills	O
given	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
lost	O
from	O
Goldsmith	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
was	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
Two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
shoe	O
and	O
knee	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
in	O
Benson	O
's	O
shoes	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
which	O
increas	O
'd	O
my	O
suspicion	O
.	O
We	O
agreed	O
to	O
meet	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
morning	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
,	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
room	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
Wood	O
,	O
we	O
observ	O
'd	O
his	O
hand	O
go	O
towards	O
the	O
pillow	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
pillow	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
large	O
horse	O
pistol	O
loaded	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Anderton	O
's	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
dark	O
lanthorn	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
powder	O
and	O
shot	O
:	O
this	O
woman	O
and	O
Benson	O
were	O
both	O
out	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
hire	O
a	O
house	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
silver	O
strainer	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
describ	O
'd	O
.	O
Wood	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Benson	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
their	O
being	O
concerned	O
in	O
robberies	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Deptford	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
known	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
return	O
'd	O
from	O
transportation	O
before	O
his	O
time	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
gave	O
no	O
attention	O
to	O
his	O
being	O
an	O
evidence	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1749	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
to	O
Cock-Hill	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
Benson	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
household	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
putting	O
them	O
to	O
rights	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Benson	O
had	O
got	O
intelligence	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
.	O
We	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
penny-worth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
a	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
two	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
strainer	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Anderton	O
swore	O
to	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
took	O
and	O
her	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
shoes	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
to	O
gaol	O
,	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
2	O
s.	O
each	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Richley	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
a	O
quart	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
large	O
spoons	O
there	O
for	O
five	O
guineas	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Anderton	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
tankard	O
and	O
spoons	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Anderton	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Parnell	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
another	O
quart	O
tankard	O
,	O
23	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
pepper	O
boxes	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
salts	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
punch	O
ladles	O
,	O
all	O
silver	O
,	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Waite	O
,	O
a	O
silversmith	O
in	O
Wapping	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Anderton	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Waite	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
small	O
parcel	O
of	O
plate	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
more	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
she	O
came	O
four	O
times	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
2	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
3	O
pepper	O
boxes	O
,	O
3	O
salts	O
,	O
some	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
punch	O
ladles	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
she	O
had	O
for	O
them	O
12	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
at	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
ounce	O
.	O
She	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Edwards	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Anderton	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Richley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
quart	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
large	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
five	O
guineas	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Anderton	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
demanded	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
brought	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
accordingly	O
I	O
denied	O
going	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
cock	O
'd	O
a	O
pistol	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
418	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
corner	B-place
of	I-place
Water-lane	I-place
,	I-place
out	I-place
of	I-place
Thames	I-place
street	I-place
,	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
something	O
touch	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
Water-lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
boys	O
come	O
rusling	O
along	O
,	O
going	O
farther	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
not	O
as	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
419	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
August	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
W.	O
Whittle	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
12	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Orange-Court	B-place
near	I-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
catch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
man	O
?	O
Whittle	O
.	O
I	O
