TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
27th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Eighth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
CRISP	O
GASCOYNE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1753	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
CRISP	O
GASCOYNE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
*	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
LEGGE	I-pers
+	O
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
:	O
++	O
,	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
,	O
L.M	O
.	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Tomlyn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sibley	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Meakins	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chettle	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Box	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Nevill	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Abraham	B-pers
Atterbury	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mount	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Man	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Layton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bartholamew	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burrell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Linell	I-pers
.	O
439	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Lydia	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lydia	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lydia	O
.	O
++	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
except	O
what	O
Edward	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
had	O
said	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
tried	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
fact	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
executed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Action	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
he	O
was	O
Acq	O
.	O
See	O
his	O
trial	O
No	O
.	O
429	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
paper	O
.	O
440	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Bunion	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
linlin	O
shift	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
seven	O
linnen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
check	O
aprons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
beaver	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
Oct.10	O
Richard	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
a	O
fortnight	O
and	O
three	O
days	O
from	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
October	O
to	O
the	O
19th	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
other	O
servants	O
were	O
milking	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
having	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
Hanover-square	O
Parish	O
;	O
last	O
Friday	O
morning	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
hour	O
four	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
drest	O
in	O
a	O
linnen	O
night	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
goes	O
a	O
butterfly	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
way	O
amongst	O
some	O
timber	O
and	O
met	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
turnpike	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
waggon	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
goods	O
down	O
to	O
Edgar	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
box	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
full	O
besides	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
service	O
by	O
seeing	O
her	O
tremble	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
shall	O
go	O
back	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Mitchel	O
in	O
North	O
Audley-street	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
going	O
along	O
she	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
and	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
secured	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
were	O
his	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
441	O
,	O
442	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
ducks	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
turkey	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Shakespear	I-pers
.	O
Sept.	O
16	O
.	O
George	O
Shakespear	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Knights	B-place
bridge	I-place
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
two	O
ducks	O
and	O
turkey	O
mentioned	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Holt	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Spike	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
gardener	O
to	O
the	O
duke	O
of	O
Rutland	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
at	O
Knights	O
bridge	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Levit	I-pers
informed	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
stealing	O
Mr.	O
Shakespear	O
's	O
sowls	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
next	O
to	O
ours	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
gun	O
and	O
we	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
Holt	O
had	O
two	O
ducks	O
and	O
a	O
turkey	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Shakespear	O
own	O
'd	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Levit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
under	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
at	O
the	O
duke	O
of	O
Rutland	O
's	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
turkey	O
cry	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
grounds	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
some	O
people	O
whisper	O
,	O
I	O
imagined	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
some	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Shakespear	O
's	O
people	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
stand	O
upon	O
a	O
mount	O
in	O
that	O
field	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
hard	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
surprize	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
Holt	O
look	O
up	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
signal	O
not	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
sight	O
yet	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
pursued	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
together	O
,	O
he	O
that	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
watch	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
hang	O
from	O
him	O
like	O
a	O
turkey	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
lost	O
two	O
turkeys	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
lay	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
Holt	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
Evans	O
surrendered	O
.	O
Holt	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
ducks	O
and	O
turkey	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Evan	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
walking	O
along	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
the	O
men	O
were	O
upon	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
in	O
their	O
company	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
hand	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
surrendered	O
.	O
Holt	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
fowls	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
that	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Lomax	I-pers
.	O
Evans	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Holt	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
443	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Lay	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
two	O
check	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
linnen	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
ivory	O
comb	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Eliot	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
444	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bickerton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
stuff	O
jacket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elisha	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
one	O
stuff	O
body	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
lining	O
of	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Isaacs	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Oct.	O
13	O
*	O
Elizabeth	O
Isaacs	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Brunett	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Gerrard-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
my	O
bundle	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
take	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bundle	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
Goods	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Brunett	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
set	O
her	O
bundle	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
facing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
parcel	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
bundle	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
near	O
where	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brunett	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
leaning	O
over	O
the	O
rails	O
looking	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
445	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Hanford	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
camblet	O
gown	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
one	O
check	O
apron	O
and	O
one	O
horsehair	O
hat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Judson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Sept.	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
446	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
linnen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Oct.	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Steward	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linnen-draper	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
New	B-place
Bond-street	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
towards	O
dusk	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
frock	O
for	O
her	O
child	O
;	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
for	O
another	O
woman	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
bought	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linnen	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
at	O
another	O
shop	O
higher	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
where	O
she	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
first	O
offence	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
I	O
'd	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
nor	O
call	O
'd	O
any	O
witness	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
447	O
,	O
448	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Maine	I-pers
and	I-pers
Margaret	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
feather	O
bed	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
bolstor	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
bed	O
quilt	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
one	O
blue	O
harrateen	O
bed	O
curtain	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Jethroh	B-pers
Vaeker	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
and	O
Margaret	O
,	O
Sept.	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Margaret	O
,	O
Acq	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
449	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brown	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
42	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Steff	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
450	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
brass	O
hinges	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
brass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fairchild	I-pers
,	O
Sept	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
452	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Alice	B-pers
Mc	I-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
16	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
453	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
snuffers	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
copper	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jasper	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
454	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sidaway	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Oct.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Richardson	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
agent	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
Downing-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
likewise	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
October	O
we	O
missed	O
seven	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
desk	O
in	O
the	O
Office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
kept	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
that	O
desk	O
?	O
Barber	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
we	O
having	O
miss	O
'd	O
money	O
since	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
justice	O
Ledland	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
seven	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
desk	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
desk	O
lock	O
'd	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Barber	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
desk	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
seven	O
guineas	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
desk	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
more	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
desk	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Barber	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
hundred	O
and	O
six	O
pounds	O
,	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
ten-pence	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
back	O
the	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
office	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
?	O
Barber	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
455	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Reice	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
stolen	O
by	O
Jane	O
Brooks	O
,	O
widow	O
,	O
May	O
20	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Oxom	I-pers
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
that	O
Reice	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
her	O
a	O
silk	O
capuchine	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
blue	O
sattin	O
,	O
two	O
childrens	O
caps	O
and	O
two	O
little	O
shirts	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
by	O
Brooks	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
convicted	O
and	O
transported	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Reice	O
,	O
by	O
reading	O
the	O
advertisement	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
being	O
stolen	O
,	O
apprehended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Brooks	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
she	O
came	O
.	O
The	O
Record	O
of	O
her	O
Conviction	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
known	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
nor	O
where	O
to	O
have	O
found	O
Brooks	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
Reice	O
stopped	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
informed	O
her	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
No	O
.	O
284	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
of	O
Brooks	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
read	O
the	O
advertisement	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
honourably	O
Acq	O
.	O
456	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Darby	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Jeffereys	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Jeffereys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hemlock-court	B-place
,	I-place
Temple	I-place
Bar	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
woman	O
used	O
to	O
meet	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
sometimes	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
three	O
half-penny	O
glass	O
of	O
brandy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
expected	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
again	O
at	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
room	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
that	O
tankard	O
lost	O
?	O
Jeffereys	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
that	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
she	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Jeffereys	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
three	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
on	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
woman	O
came	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
meet	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
her	O
till	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
in	O
Magpye-alley	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
denied	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
insisted	O
on	O
seeing	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
concealed	O
amongst	O
some	O
curtains	O
to	O
a	O
turn-up	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
hid	O
herself	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
heard	O
my	O
voice	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
to	O
talk	O
with	O
me	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
into	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
hoped	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
merciful	O
unto	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Cursiter-street	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
alderman	O
Bethell	O
at	O
Guild-hall	O
,	O
who	O
granted	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
tankard	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
(	O
the	O
name	O
she	O
went	O
by	O
)	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
a	O
tankard	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
tankard	O
I	O
delivered	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
other	O
things	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
this	O
tankard	O
several	O
times	O
between	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
and	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
describ	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Marsh	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
read	O
the	O
advertisement	O
while	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
custody	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
Indeed	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
usually	O
read	O
the	O
advertisements	O
in	O
the	O
papers	O
.	O
Marsh	O
.	O
I	O
generally	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
seeing	O
this	O
advertisement	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
her	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
letters	O
on	O
the	O
handle	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
tankard	O
here	O
produc	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Marsh	O
.	O
It	O
weigh	O
'd	O
twenty-one	O
ounces	O
and	O
odd	O
penny	O
weights	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
weighs	O
twenty-one	O
ounces	O
fifteen	O
penny	O
weights	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Martingale	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
and	O
her	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
well	O
brought	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
debauched	O
by	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
apprentice	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
necessity	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
committing	O
this	O
action	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
457	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Rolt	I-pers
,	O
Sept	O
,	O
8	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
458	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sabati	B-pers
Israel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
13	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
Returning	O
from	O
'Change	O
about	O
a	O
Quarter	O
after	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
one	O
Capt	O
.	O
Castleton	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
beliv	O
'd	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
shewing	O
me	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
going	O
abroad	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
seized	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
Dineley	O
Wardman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
'Change	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
Mr.	O
Freeman	O
's	O
pocket	O
of	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
Capt	O
.	O
Castleton	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Freeman	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
459	O
,	O
460	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Bridges	I-pers
and	O
Alexander	B-pers
Bisset	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
saddle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
bridle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
.	O
Dec	O
,	O
17	O
James	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
saddle	O
and	O
bridle	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
girth	O
,	O
sursingle	O
,	O
and	O
saddle	O
cloth	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
broker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Bridges	O
brought	O
the	O
saddle	O
and	O
bridle	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
;	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
price	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
stopped	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
an	O
alderman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
compter	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
the	O
landlord	O
at	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
partner	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Bisset	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
here	O
produced	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
what	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
wrap	O
himself	O
up	O
in	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
both	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
fact	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Haile	I-pers
.	O
I	O
look	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Davison	O
's	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
these	O
things	O
here	O
produced	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
all	O
was	O
fast	O
at	O
the	O
stable	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
a	O
casement	O
was	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
iron	O
wrenched	O
out	O
that	O
went	O
across	O
.	O
Bridges	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
leather	O
apron	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
Bridges	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
saddle	O
and	O
the	O
bridle	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
in	O
Leicester	O
Fields	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
advertise	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
461	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Parkinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Overel	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Overel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Heydon-square	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
returning	O
home	O
,	O
just	O
by	B-place
the	I-place
postern	I-place
in	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
I	O
stood	O
still	O
in	O
a	O
pause	O
whether	O
I	O
should	O
call	O
on	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
your	O
pocket	O
is	O
pick	O
'd	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
by	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
an	O
offer	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
another	O
person	O
that	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
person	O
said	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
pick	O
'd	O
,	O
there	O
lay	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
that	O
person	O
that	O
inform	O
'd	O
you	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Overal	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Millet	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Ireland	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
not	O
return	O
'd	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Shoemaker-Row	O
,	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
blue	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
your	O
pocket	O
is	O
pick	O
'd	O
of	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
gentleman	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
arm	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
gentleman	O
that	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
or	O
not	O
that	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
462	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
McPhearson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Oct.	O
22	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
McPhearson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Philadelphia	O
in	O
Pensylvania	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
present	O
lodge	O
near	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
'Change	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
people	O
call	O
out	O
a	O
pickpocket	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
some	O
people	O
engaged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
many	O
of	O
his	O
friends	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
people	O
could	O
do	O
to	O
hold	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
and	O
received	O
several	O
blows	O
;	O
however	O
we	O
at	O
last	O
tied	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
proposed	O
searching	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
searched	O
his	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
,	O
among	O
many	O
others	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
found	O
mine	O
gone	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
silk	O
India	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
sort	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
before	O
?	O
McPhearson	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
that	O
day	O
you	O
lost	O
it	O
?	O
McPhearson	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
chiefly	O
that	O
day	O
on	O
'Change	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
tied	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
about	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
.	O
James	B-pers
McCulloch	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
'Change	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
mob	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
towards	O
the	O
people	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
people	O
say	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
fellow	O
and	O
duck	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
a	O
blow	O
from	O
some	O
by-stander	O
that	O
drew	O
blood	O
on	O
both	O
my	O
hands	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
and	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
handkerchiefs	O
I	O
believe	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
gentlemen	O
got	O
hold	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
another	O
this	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
went	O
their	O
way	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
ducking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
save	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
.	O
This	O
he	O
spoke	O
on	O
the	O
open	O
'Change	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
nor	O
call	O
'd	O
any	O
witness	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
463	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Mullings	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Joseph	B-pers
Broad	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
pillowbier	O
,	O
twenty-eight	O
yards	O
of	O
linnen	O
cloth	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
grey	O
coat	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
bags	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
drawers	O
,	O
Aug.	O
11	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
appearing	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
464	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Dyston	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
pillowbiers	O
,	O
one	O
diaper	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Jolley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Sept.	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Acq	O
.	O
465	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Coultis	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Oct.	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Coultis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Chequer-Alley	O
,	O
White-cross-street	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
a	O
friend	O
's	O
house	O
home	O
at	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
along	O
Whitecross	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Coultis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
packthread	O
ground	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
'd	O
knock	O
me	O
down	O
if	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
touch	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
's	O
house	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
this	O
account	O
?	O
Coultis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
last	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
beef	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
shop	O
that	O
very	O
night	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Coultis	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
but	O
once	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
moon-light	O
night	O
?	O
Coultis	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
star-light	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
light	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
endeavour	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Coultis	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
information	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
forc	O
'd	O
to	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
information	O
against	O
you	O
?	O
Coultis	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
against	O
me	O
and	O
three	O
more	O
for	O
,	O
stealing	O
this	O
beef	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
warrant	O
granted	O
against	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
the	O
three	O
persons	O
?	O
Coultis	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
mentioned	O
your	O
name	O
?	O
Coultis	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
beef	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
any	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
missed	O
him	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
your	O
hat	O
again	O
?	O
Coultis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
your	O
hat	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
charg	O
'd	O
you	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
beef	O
?	O
Coultis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Whitecross-street	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
deals	O
in	O
old	O
cloaths	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Marshalsea	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
collect	O
rents	O
for	O
'squire	O
Jenkenson	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
his	O
accounts	O
to	O
this	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
Cotton	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
I	O
settle	O
his	O
books	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
in	O
a	O
week	O
are	O
you	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
?	O
Cotton	O
.	O
Two	O
days	O
in	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
per	O
day	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Cotton	O
.	O
He	O
pays	O
me	O
after	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
last	O
sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Cotton	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
with	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
buttock	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
wipes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
wipes	O
?	O
Coultis	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
what	O
are	O
commonly	O
called	O
handkerchiefs	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
buy	O
nothing	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
offered	O
a	O
hat	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
that	O
hat	O
worth	O
?	O
Cotton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
worth	O
about	O
2	O
s.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Goodyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Beach-lane	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
cook	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Whaley	I-pers
,	O
whose	O
father	O
keeps	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Featherstone-street	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
out	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
Coultis	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
in	O
Bunhill-Row	O
,	O
there	O
before	O
several	O
people	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
an	O
information	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
my	O
beef	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
;	O
and	O
swore	O
many	O
bad	O
oaths	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Goodyer	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
Friday	O
morning	O
last	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
made	O
information	O
against	O
four	O
persons	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Coultis	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
of	O
stealing	O
Coultis	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
information	O
?	O
Goodyer	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
upon	O
an	O
information	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-four	O
pounds	O
of	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Goodyer	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
cap	O
.	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Goodyer	O
deposed	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Coultis	O
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
supp	O
'd	O
on	O
two	O
fowls	O
he	O
dressed	O
for	O
them	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
first	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
them	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
beef	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
Cotton	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
stealing	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
:	O
The	O
linnen	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
Cotton	O
was	O
on	O
his	O
recognizance	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estrcated	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawksworth	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
about	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
pounds	O
of	O
beef	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
buttock	O
boil	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
describ	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
stuffing	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
stayed	O
and	O
played	O
at	O
cards	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
plentifully	O
,	O
being	O
late	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
into	O
their	O
lodgings	O
,	O
they	O
all	O
concluded	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
fishing	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
beef	O
to	O
eat	O
the	O
while	O
,	O
Clark	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
466	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Clendon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
five	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
fustian	O
frock	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Abel	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
Abel	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
earl	O
of	O
Scarborough	O
in	O
Grosvenor-square	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
stables	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
to	O
the	O
rax	O
at	O
Hungerford-market	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
box	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
but	O
return	O
'd	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Leevas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
beedle	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
information	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
advertised	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
twenty-five	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
lord	O
Scarborough	O
's	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
shirt	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
box	O
and	O
goods	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lees	I-pers
.	O
This	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
shirt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
on	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Frost	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Frost	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
of	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
coach	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
coach-hire	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
467	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Darwent	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Joseph	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
October	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
Joseph	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Throgmorton-street	O
,	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
supp	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lady	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
return	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
Parliament-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
;	O
he	O
was	O
stooping	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
go	O
along	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
love	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
enemies	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
like	O
you	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
on	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
200	O
yards	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
now	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
I	O
will	O
do	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
fist	O
,	O
he	O
staggered	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
my	O
stick	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
fight	O
now	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
kill	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
this	O
man	O
is	O
too	O
much	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
thought	O
we	O
were	O
too	O
powerful	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
wig	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
to	O
Privy-garden-gate	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
's	O
man	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Lediard	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
round-house	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
Gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
answerable	O
for	O
my	O
appearance	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
fighting	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
better	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
attempt	O
to	O
pick	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
ask	O
me	O
for	O
any	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
round-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
mention	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
your	O
wig	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
mention	O
'd	O
my	O
wig	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
my	O
hat	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
first	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
first	O
attack	O
you	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
when	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stooping	O
down	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
pass	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
us	O
,	O
neither	O
one	O
way	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
man	O
behind	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
an	O
ill-looking	O
fellow	O
behind	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
notion	O
they	O
want	O
to	O
rob	O
us	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
fellow	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
then	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
rob	O
us	O
?	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
come	O
a	O
little	O
further	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
want	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
both	O
sticks	O
in	O
our	O
hands	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
before	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
on	O
about	O
150	O
yards	O
towards	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
by	O
he	O
started	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
my	O
eyes	O
and	O
limbs	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
do	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
then	O
my	O
brother	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
my	O
brother	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
knees	O
upon	O
his	O
belly	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
cried	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
struck	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
my	O
stick	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
wig	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
hat	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Privy-garden-wall	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
dropp	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
we	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
came	O
,	O
we	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
round-house	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
damn	O
'd	O
us	O
for	O
scoundrels	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
2	O
s	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
or	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
d.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
the	O
Justice	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Abby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Plaisterer	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
squabble	O
,	O
man	O
come	O
running	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
in	O
at	O
Privy-garden-gate	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
himself	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
dropp	O
'd	O
it	O
down	O
beside	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
round	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
searched	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
clasp	O
knife	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
taking	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mob	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
hat	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
'till	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
lieutenant	O
to	O
the	O
company	O
the	O
prisoner	O
belongs	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
soldier	O
in	O
the	O
regiment	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
never	O
suspected	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
ensign	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
extremely	O
well	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Hog	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
serjeant	O
to	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
serjeant-major	O
to	O
the	O
regiment	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
almost	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
himself	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
best	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
regiment	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
,	O
neglected	O
any	O
duty	O
,	O
nor	O
came	O
drunk	O
or	O
dirty	O
to	O
the	O
regiment	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
received	O
his	O
pay	O
of	O
me	O
these	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
always	O
esteemed	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
just	O
man	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
has	O
a	O
better	O
character	O
than	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
neither	O
do	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Car	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
twelvemonth	O
last	O
year	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
fellow	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
lain	O
where	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
money	O
and	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
farthing	O
.	O
I	O
lik	O
'd	O
him	O
so	O
well	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bargain	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
another	O
year	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
never	O
desire	O
a	O
better	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
468	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Isabella	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Daniel	I-pers
Lynch	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
six	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
thimble	O
;	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Portress	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
6	O
*	O
Mary	O
Hodges	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
alms-houses	O
in	O
the	O
foot-way	O
going	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Portress	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
bedridden	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
appear	O
herself	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
nurse	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Portress	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
why	O
she	O
thought	O
so	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
these	O
spoons	O
(	O
producing	O
four	O
)	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
the	O
marrow	O
spoon	O
came	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
last	O
September	O
,	O
another	O
of	O
the	O
large	O
spoons	O
came	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
another	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
twenty-nine	O
shillings	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
spoons	O
she	O
pawned	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
mistress	O
sent	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
acquainted	O
Mrs.	O
Portress	O
with	O
the	O
affair	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
marrow	O
spoon	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
then	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
was	O
ailing	O
a-bed	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
support	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
for	O
us	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
but	O
four	O
shillings	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
was	O
drove	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
469	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Stampy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
Samuel	B-pers
Manton	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
razor	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Sept.	O
12	O
*	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Manton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Castle	O
,	O
in	O
Borustreet	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
behind	O
a	O
coach	O
;	O
coming	O
along	O
the	B-place
King	I-place
's	I-place
Road	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Bloody	I-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
two	O
persons	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
stopt	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
empty	O
,	O
they	O
then	O
came	O
behind	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
jumped	O
down	O
,	O
then	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
clapt	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
of	O
value	O
about	O
you	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
six-pence	O
:	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
giving	O
one	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
kept	O
repeating	O
these	O
words	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
shoot	O
you	O
!	O
I	O
will	O
shoot	O
you	O
!	O
and	O
held	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
shoot	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
searched	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
the	O
razor	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
moonlight	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
shoot	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
my	O
neck	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
turnpike	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
people	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Kite	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Norden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
for	O
another	O
fact	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
advertised	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
we	O
took	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Manton	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
picked	O
him	O
out	O
from	O
among	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Adam	B-pers
Henly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
these	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
a	O
coachman	O
,	O
he	O
drove	O
for	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drove	O
for	O
me	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
industrious	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
470	O
,	O
471	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Mooney	I-pers
and	I-pers
Joyce	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
and	O
Joyce	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
one	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
val	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
val	O
4	O
d.	O
one	O
feather	O
bolster	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
seven	O
lb	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
feathers	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
Oct.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	O
,	O
Acq	O
.	O
Joyce	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
472	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brocade	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silk-damask	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
a	O
tabby	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
four	O
linnen	O
caps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
linnen	O
bedgowns	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
four	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
beaver	O
hat	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
buckle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Alice	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Thomas	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
the	I-place
hospital	I-place
,	I-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
other	I-place
side	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
water	I-place
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
barr	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Sept.	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
mist	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
searched	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
advertised	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
tavern	O
facing	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
.	O
There	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Alderman	O
Scott	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
confest	O
all	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
the	O
holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Gun	O
Yard	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Halcomb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry-Compter	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
Sept.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
here	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
her	O
own	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
got	O
them	O
?	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
mistress	O
sent	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
husband	O
was	O
arrested	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
goal	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
somebody	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
or	O
no	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
one	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
quite	O
a	O
contrary	O
place	O
to	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
mistress	O
lived	O
:	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
while	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
473	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Baxter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6000	O
of	O
lillikin	O
pins	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
474	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cullingham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pewter	O
plates	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
11	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oswin	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
475	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
kid	O
gloves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
August	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
476	O
,	O
477	O
,	O
478	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Fairbrother	I-pers
and	I-pers
Jane	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
and	O
Jane	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Monger	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
four	O
awls	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
pinchers	O
,	O
one	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
knives	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Poarch	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Monger	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
twenty	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
Oct.	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
Samuel	B-pers
Poarch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
upon	O
Ludgate-hill	O
;	O
my	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
things	O
took	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
,	O
having	O
but	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
mist	O
about	O
forty	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
and	O
pumps	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
tools	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Degen	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
evidence	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Fairbrother	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Sarah	O
Monger	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
in	O
Shoe	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
too	O
;	O
Degen	O
confest	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
Monger	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
under	O
her	O
bed	O
.	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Degen	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Fairbrother	I-pers
brought	O
me	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
last	O
Friday	O
night	O
upon	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
break	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
watchman	O
before	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
stocking	O
shop	O
,	O
upon	O
Clerkenwell	O
Green	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
iron	O
pocker	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
stall	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Poarch	I-pers
open	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
arm	O
full	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
her	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
shoes	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
lap	O
:	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Elizabeth	O
-	O
's	O
room	O
upon	O
Addle-hill	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
lodged	O
there	O
:	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
carried	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Monger	I-pers
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
sometimes	O
,	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
we	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
them	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
a	O
girl	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
knew	O
what	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
seen	O
what	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
her	O
we	O
did	O
steal	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
told	O
her	O
so	O
?	O
Degen	O
.	O
He	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Fairbrother	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
so	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
bed	O
;	O
we	O
threw	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
shoes	O
over	O
Bridwell	O
Bridge	O
;	O
and	O
sold	O
an	O
apron	O
full	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
all	O
shoes	O
?	O
Degen	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
himself	O
upon	O
his	O
feet	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
evidence	O
was	O
apprehended	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
;	O
Fairbrother	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
Alderman	O
;	O
the	O
receiver	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Fairbrother	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
Monger	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fairbrother	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Jane	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Monger	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
young	O
man	O
brought	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
Fairbrother	O
,	O
Guilty	O
;	O
Jane	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
Acq	O
.	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Monger	I-pers
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Monger	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Fairbrother	O
:	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Fairbrother	I-pers
,	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Shelling	I-pers
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
1	O
b.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
d.	O
five	O
loav	O
s	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
d	O
.	O
one	O
earthen	O
dish	O
and	O
a	O
stone	O
jar	O
,	O
val	O
3	O
d.	O
one	O
half	O
1b	O
.	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
Aarch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
one	O
dozen	O
of	O
pickle	O
cucumbers	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
Oct.	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
keeps	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
New-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
sash	O
lifted	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Monger	I-pers
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
by	O
setting	O
fire	O
to	O
some	O
straw	O
,	O
which	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chimney	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
secreted	O
himself	O
.	O
Degen	O
the	O
accomplice	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
directions	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
that	O
keeps	O
the	O
cellar	O
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
two	O
men	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
describing	O
their	O
size	O
like	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
evidence	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
their	O
faces	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
having	O
any	O
knowledge	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
479	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Mackensie	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
yards	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
3	O
yards	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
diaper	O
napkin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Slowman	I-pers
,	O
May	O
26	O
*	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
480	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Coulster	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
481	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
stew	O
pan	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pillowbier	O
,	O
val	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Rossiter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
Sept.	O
8	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
482	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Wale	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribband	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fladgate	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
Stephen	B-pers
Fladgate	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Conduit-street	O
,	O
Hanover-square	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
hosier	O
's	O
and	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
dinner	O
with	O
my	O
son	O
and	O
daughter	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
6	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
ribband	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
ribband	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fladgate	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
then	O
;	O
my	O
sister	O
look	O
'd	O
and	O
missed	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
and	O
the	O
black	O
ribband	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
make	O
a	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
coming	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
ribband	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
stockings	O
she	O
held	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
483	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
leather	O
pocket	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
thimble	O
,	O
two	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
one	O
iron	O
snuff-box	O
and	O
two	O
pence	O
halfpence	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Acq	O
.	O
484	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Bunce	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chavace	I-pers
,	O
he	O
stood	O
charg	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
,	O
August	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Claud	B-pers
Chavace	I-pers
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
was	O
my	O
son	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
was	O
he	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
had	O
he	O
lived	O
till	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
May-fair-market	O
,	O
am	O
a	O
Chairman	O
in	O
the	O
winter	O
,	O
and	O
labourer	O
in	O
summer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
upon	O
a	O
scaffold	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
word	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
chairmen	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
kill	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
son	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
hospital	O
at	O
Hide	O
park	O
Corner	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
son	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
laid	O
in	O
bed	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
bloody	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
blood	O
running	O
down	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
chairmen	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
from	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
fifty	O
or	O
sixty	O
yards	O
within	O
Grosvenor-gate	B-place
,	O
between	O
the	O
walnut-trees	O
and	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
where	O
lay	O
some	O
blood	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
enquir	O
'd	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
his	O
hurt	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
had	O
spoke	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
told	O
several	O
people	O
that	O
the	O
park-keeper	O
had	O
beat	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
for	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
justice	O
would	O
not	O
grant	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
except	O
I	O
would	O
bring	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
heard	O
the	O
child	O
say	O
so	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
infirmary	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
doctor	O
that	O
examin	O
'd	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
,	O
possibly	O
the	O
child	O
may	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
senses	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
tell	O
who	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
till	O
we	O
saw	O
whether	O
he	O
would	O
live	O
or	O
die	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
child	O
speak	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
sensible	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
rightly	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Chavace	I-pers
.	O
My	O
child	O
received	O
his	O
hurt	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
him	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
partly	O
sensible	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
judge	O
him	O
partly	O
sensible	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
knowing	O
me	O
and	O
calling	O
me	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
ail	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
Pray	O
mother	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
tea	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
park-keeper	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
at	O
what	O
gate	O
he	O
stood	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
hurt	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
describe	O
any	O
place	O
else	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
repeated	O
the	O
same	O
words	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
the	O
park-keeper	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pray	O
mother	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
his	O
head	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
hurt	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
wound	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
his	O
senses	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
short	O
while	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
sensible	O
he	O
'd	O
cry	O
for	O
mercy	O
in	O
these	O
words	O
,	O
Pray	O
forgive	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
staff	O
is	O
too	O
big	O
;	O
oftentimes	O
he	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examin	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
said	O
at	O
first	O
setting	O
out	O
,	O
you	O
thought	O
him	O
partly	O
sensible	O
;	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
think	O
him	O
partly	O
insensible	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
counted	O
him	O
sensible	O
for	O
so	O
long	O
a	O
time	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
not	O
judg	O
'd	O
insensible	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
hospital	O
to	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
Chavace	O
.	O
At	O
times	O
he	O
was	O
sensible	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
child	O
to	O
be	O
sensible	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
forgive	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
staff	O
is	O
too	O
big	O
.	O
Chavace	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
imagine	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
ever	O
a	O
staff	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
No	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
done	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
affrighted	O
him	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
asked	O
you	O
forgiveness	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
pray	O
forgive	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
mother	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Upper	O
Brook-street	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
major	O
Burton	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
passed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
beating	O
a	O
boy	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
Brook-Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
into	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
the	O
minute	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
lying	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
dead	O
.	O
Q.	O
Whereabout	O
did	O
he	O
lie	O
?	O
Wells	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
under	O
the	O
walnut-trees	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
park-keeper	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
and	O
he	O
groan	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
lie	O
easy	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
again	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
wip	O
'd	O
the	O
blood	O
and	O
froth	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
mouth	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
who	O
had	O
beat	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
round	O
the	O
park	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
park-keeper	O
's	O
house	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
windows	O
above	O
and	O
below	O
are	O
all	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
,	O
the	O
master	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
his	O
servants	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
the	O
parkkeeper	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
boy	O
lay	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
washing	O
him	O
with	O
heartshorn	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
some	O
people	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
the	O
infirmary	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
woman	O
here	O
that	O
gave	O
this	O
information	O
?	O
Wells	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
patient	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
deceased	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
his	O
mother	O
ask	O
him	O
who	O
beat	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
park-keeper	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
back	O
:	O
I	O
also	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
Pray	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
forgive	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
stick	O
is	O
too	O
long	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
then	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
then	O
,	O
than	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
how	O
long	O
?	O
Q.	O
to	O
Jane	B-pers
Chavace	I-pers
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
die	O
?	O
Chavace	O
.	O
He	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
fortnight	O
after	O
he	O
received	O
his	O
hurt	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
being	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hardyman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
riding	O
on	O
my	O
mare	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
at	O
that	O
very	O
time	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
a	O
boy	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
walnut-tree	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
a	O
pole	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
held	O
much	O
about	O
over	O
his	O
head	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
for	O
striking	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
:	O
The	O
boy	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
do	O
n't	O
strike	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
Almighty	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
n't	O
strike	O
me	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
saw	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
galloping	O
along	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
boy	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examin	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Hardyman	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hanover-square	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
coachman	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
after	O
some	O
equl	O
page	O
belonging	O
to	O
my	O
lord	O
Powis	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
abroad	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
chariot	O
and	O
harness	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
steward	O
's	O
mare	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
her	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
on	O
this	O
occasion	O
?	O
Hardyman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
attend	O
there	O
?	O
Hardyman	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
bring	O
myself	O
into	O
a	O
preminary	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
tell	O
it	O
to	O
?	O
Hardyman	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
chairman	O
last	O
Sunday	O
in	O
a	O
publick-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
that	O
a	O
chairman	O
's	O
son	O
was	O
found	O
murdered	O
in	O
Hyde-Park	O
?	O
Hardyman	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
neither	O
write	O
nor	O
read	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
hear	O
that	O
a	O
child	O
had	O
been	O
kill	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
?	O
Hardyman	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
it	O
till	O
last	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
came	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
reason	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
talk	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
fearing	O
being	O
brought	O
into	O
a	O
preminary	O
?	O
Hardyman	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
last	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
swear	O
you	O
saw	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
day	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
?	O
Hardyman	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
what	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
my	O
mare	O
and	O
was	O
rubbing	O
her	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
boy	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
park-keeper	O
had	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
walnut-tree	O
;	O
upon	O
my	O
word	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
since	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Hardyman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
park-keeper	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
being	O
committed	O
to	O
New-prison	O
for	O
perjury	O
on	O
this	O
account	O
,	O
was	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
brought	O
into	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
his	O
mittimus	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
first	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
He	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
being	O
guilty	O
of	O
first	O
making	O
information	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
many	O
Circumstances	O
,	O
tending	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
prisoner	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
since	O
had	O
declared	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
that	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
was	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
committed	O
perjury	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
S	O
ign	O
'd	O
by	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
between	O
fifteen	O
and	O
sixteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
about	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
being	O
kill	O
'd	O
?	O
Warner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
a	O
heard	O
others	O
talk	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
landlady	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
consider	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
sad	O
thing	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
life	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
said	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Warner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
on	O
oath	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
and	O
hope	O
God	O
will	O
forgive	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
committed	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
?	O
Warner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
the	O
following	O
witnesses	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
master	O
or	O
keeper	O
of	O
Grosvenor's-Gate	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
work	O
below	O
stairs	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
that	O
looks	O
into	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
casement	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
boy	O
killed	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
help	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
were	O
Richard	O
was	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
that	O
person	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Spinneys	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Richard	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
with	O
his	O
linnen	O
to	O
wash	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
;	O
he	O
usually	O
carried	O
it	O
once	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
does	O
he	O
commonly	O
stay	O
when	O
he	O
goes	O
with	O
his	O
linnen	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
He	O
commonly	O
stays	O
two	O
hours	O
,	O
his	O
sister	O
washes	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
what	O
time	O
do	O
you	O
judge	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
before	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
his	O
sister	O
live	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
She	O
lives	O
in	O
Portland-street	O
,	O
beyond	O
Chandois-square	O
;	O
the	O
way	O
there	O
is	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
through	O
Grosvenor's-gate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
bundle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
does	O
he	O
do	O
with	O
his	O
staff	O
at	O
such	O
times	O
.	O
Turner	O
.	O
He	O
lays	O
that	O
down	O
sometimes	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
without	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
his	O
nearest	O
way	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
walnut-trees	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
be	O
almost	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
park	O
about	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
return	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Turner	O
.	O
He	O
returned	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
very	O
seldom	O
worked	O
with	O
his	O
chair	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
(	O
being	O
a	O
chairman	O
)	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
church	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
continued	O
that	O
practice	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
for	O
natural	O
temper	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
the	O
best	O
behaved	O
man	O
I	O
ever	O
had	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
swearer	O
or	O
drunkard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
Catherine	O
Wells	O
talking	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Turner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
slipp	O
'd	O
my	O
memory	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Catherine	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
man	O
you	O
talk	O
'd	O
to	O
,	O
that	O
gave	O
you	O
no	O
answer	O
?	O
C.	O
Wells	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
pulling	O
hair	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
head	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
where	O
are	O
all	O
the	O
park-keepers	O
gone	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
boy	O
lies	O
murdered	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
!	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
said	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
a	O
footman	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
footman	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
;	O
then	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Turner	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
upon	O
this	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
accident	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
just	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
croud	O
of	O
people	O
.	O
and	O
it	O
shocked	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
again	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
The	O
day	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
murdered	O
I	O
rode	O
into	O
the	O
park	O
by	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
from	O
Crosvenor	O
's	O
Gate	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
twelve	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
gate	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
going	O
toward	O
.	O
Tyburn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
a	O
staff	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Carter	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
and	O
over	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
murdered	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
boy	O
there	O
then	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
y	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-lion	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
opposite	O
to	O
Grosvenor	O
's	O
Gate	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
in	O
it	O
like	O
linnen	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cane	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
under	O
the	O
wall	O
towards	O
Tyburn	O
:	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
lying	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
between	O
a	O
post	O
and	O
a	O
wallnut-tree	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
two	O
horses	O
and	O
a	O
boy	O
with	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
help	O
the	O
boy	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
assisted	O
him	O
and	O
undid	O
his	O
stock-buckle	O
and	O
collar	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
drops	O
of	O
blood	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
more	O
or	O
less	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cut	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
were	O
the	O
blood	O
came	O
from	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
bread	O
and	O
butter	O
lay	O
behind	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
sensible	O
?	O
Mills	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
park	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
my	O
hearing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Mills	O
.	O
Six	O
or	O
seven	O
months	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Turner	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
servants	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
only	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
the	O
other	O
keepers	O
keep	O
servants	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
They	O
do	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
attend	O
their	O
own	O
gates	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Bunce	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sister	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
:	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
when	O
the	O
accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
.	O
I	O
wash	O
for	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Portland-street	O
,	O
Oxford	O
Market	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
Grosvenor	O
's	O
Gate	O
.	O
Bunce	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
usual	O
way	O
is	O
to	O
bring	O
his	O
linnen	O
once	O
a	O
week	O
to	O
be	O
washed	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
that	O
very	O
28th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
turned	O
of	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
after	O
eight	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
or	O
about	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
past	O
eight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
stay	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
might	O
stay	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ducey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
almost	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
his	O
sister	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
day	O
this	O
lad	O
got	O
his	O
death	O
in	O
Hide	O
park	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
twice	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
was	O
at	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
his	O
cane	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Lucas	B-pers
Everard	I-pers
Greenhead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
assistant	O
apothecary	O
and	O
belong	O
to	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
hospital	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
deceased	O
being	O
brought	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
own	O
satisfaction	O
,	O
sometimes	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
state	O
of	O
delirium	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
venture	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pupil	O
at	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
hospital	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
lad	O
's	O
being	O
brought	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
and	O
dressed	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
sensible	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
good-natured	O
,	O
humane	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
alive	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
that	O
day	O
and	O
I	O
joked	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
eating	O
bread	O
and	O
butter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Cotton	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
neither	O
going	O
nor	O
coming	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
in	O
the	O
park	O
was	O
the	O
boy	O
?	O
Cotton	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
wallnut-trees	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
?	O
Cotton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
clock	O
had	O
struck	O
eight	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
wallnut-trees	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
nobody	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
?	O
Cotton	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lodge	O
door	O
shut	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remember	O
that	O
day	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
killed	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
but	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
soldier	O
walking	O
together	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
fall	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
wallnut-tree	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
riding	O
by	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
a	O
black	O
horse	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
a	O
gray	O
one	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
smack	O
'd	O
his	O
whip	O
;	O
we	O
conceived	O
that	O
assrighted	O
the	O
boy	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
fall	O
down	O
:	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
ran	O
towards	O
the	O
gateway	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
