TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
of	O
DECEMBER	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
27th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1753	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1753	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RAWLINSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
*	O
,	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DENNISON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
Sir	O
SIDNEY	B-pers
STAFFORD	I-pers
SMYTH	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
||	O
HENRY	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
teh	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
that	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noel	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bodicote	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Chandler	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boyce	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Basdine	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Collison	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wriglesworth	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Huson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Basands	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Astee	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Parminster	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lowrey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Blinkhorne	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sugg	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Nightingale	I-pers
,	O
Stephen	B-pers
Hore	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Coulson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Leach	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
Rice	B-pers
Evers	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hand	I-pers
.	O
1	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Emott	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Things	O
mentioned	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
Property	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
Witness	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pedley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
House	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
does	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
Door	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
this	O
Coat	O
and	O
Cloak	O
in	O
his	O
Apron	O
.	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
Cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
and	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
Liquor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
Money	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3	O
,	O
4	O
,	O
5	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Buye	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Pair	O
of	O
Leather	O
Gloves	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
.	O
Oct.	O
25	O
.	O
||	O
All	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Alley	O
or	O
open	O
Place	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Highway	O
,	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Venesal	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
Assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
Fear	O
,	O
and	O
Danger	O
of	O
her	O
Life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
one	O
Cloth	O
Cloak	O
,	O
Value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gilham	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
;	O
one	O
linen	O
Apron	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
Hat	O
,	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Shoes	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Venesal	I-pers
,	O
Dec	O
,	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Venesal	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Charles	O
Court	O
,	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Clavering	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
Night	O
last	O
about	O
Eleven	O
o'Clock	O
,	O
in	O
One	B-place
Tun	I-place
Alley	I-place
by	I-place
Hungerford	I-place
Market	I-place
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
with	O
his	O
Fist	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
my	O
Apron	O
and	O
Handkerchief	O
,	O
Hat	O
,	O
Cloak	O
and	O
Shoes	O
from	O
off	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Round	O
House	O
on	O
the	O
Watchman	O
's	O
Back	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
One	O
Tun	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
Tussel	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
Woman	O
down	O
,	O
stripping	O
her	O
of	O
her	O
Petticoats	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Watch	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
Wife	O
and	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
no	O
Business	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
Watchman	O
took	O
Charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
Woman	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
without	O
her	O
Shoes	O
,	O
Hat	O
,	O
Cloak	O
,	O
or	O
Apron	O
;	O
a	O
Watchman	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watchouse	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
have	O
any	O
Thing	O
in	O
his	O
Custody	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
Things	O
taken	O
away	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
or	O
after	O
?	O
E.	O
Venesal	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
on	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
this	O
Man	O
took	O
them	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
his	O
Wife	O
?	O
E.	O
Venesal	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
Life	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
Evidences	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
House	O
drunk	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
Woman	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
drunken	O
Condition	O
standing	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
Window	O
,	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
One	O
Tun	O
Alley	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
sensible	O
Word	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Hour	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
also	O
saw	O
her	O
after	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
Hours	O
10	O
,	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
.	O
At	O
half	O
an	O
Hour	O
after	O
12	O
o'Clock	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
sent	O
a	O
Watchman	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
to	O
his	O
Assistance	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hulit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Watchman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
Witness	O
's	O
Stand	O
when	O
Hudson	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
lay	O
the	O
Woman	O
on	O
the	O
Ground	O
,	O
and	O
Hudson	O
had	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Woman	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Cloak	O
lay	O
under	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
about	O
her	O
Shoulders	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
any	O
Goods	O
?	O
Hulit	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Monk	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
Spoon	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
Gown	O
,	O
Value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
Pair	O
of	O
Stays	O
,	O
one	O
Apron	O
,	O
one	O
Petticoat	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
Caps	O
,	O
one	O
Woman	O
's	O
Beaver	O
Hat	O
,	O
one	O
Yard	O
of	O
silk	O
Ribbon	O
,	O
one	O
Child	O
's	O
Dimitty	O
Waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Publican	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
Servant	O
about	O
five	O
Days	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
2nd	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
Hour	O
's	O
Time	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
People	O
come	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
one	O
Morgan	O
,	O
a	O
Lodging	O
House	O
in	O
Golden	O
Lane	O
.	O
There	O
lay	O
all	O
the	O
Goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
two	O
Chairs	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
burst	O
out	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
Forgiveness	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
Things	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Things	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
Officer	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
before	O
him	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
an	O
Alderman	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Morgan	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
own	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
Things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
Liquor	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
Things	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
8	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
Murder	O
of	O
Brian	B-pers
Henlen	I-pers
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Inquisition	O
for	O
Manslaughter	O
,	O
Oct.	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Kernan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Sign	O
of	O
the	O
Two	O
Chairmen	O
in	O
Old	B-place
Paved	I-place
Alley	I-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
James	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
Wife	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Pint	O
of	O
Beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
Dispute	O
arose	O
between	O
one	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
House	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
Deceased	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
Halfpennyworth	O
of	O
Gin	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
to	O
Potts	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
such	O
Company	O
as	O
this	O
?	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
he	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
damned	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
Bitch	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
struck	O
first	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
Falls	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
the	O
Deceased	O
's	O
Head	O
fell	O
against	O
the	O
Fender	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Hospital	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
three	O
Weeks	O
and	O
two	O
Days	O
after	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
Days	O
after	O
this	O
happened	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
thank	O
'd	O
God	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
better	O
than	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
(	O
only	O
for	O
his	O
Head	O
)	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
well	O
in	O
a	O
Week	O
or	O
ten	O
Days	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
any	O
Animosity	O
against	O
the	O
Man	O
that	O
hurt	O
you	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
assure	O
you	O
;	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
Liquor	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
meddled	O
with	O
any	O
Body	O
whatsoever	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
Liquor	O
?	O
Kernan	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
known	O
each	O
other	O
some	O
Time	O
.	O
The	O
Deceased	O
said	O
he	O
freely	O
forgave	O
every	O
one	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Gready	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Time	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Potts	O
had	O
some	O
Words	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Wife	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
Husband	O
's	O
Part	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Deceased	O
coming	O
in	O
he	O
took	O
Potts	O
's	O
Part	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
Woman	O
Bitch	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
Deceased	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
Business	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
call	O
my	O
Wife	O
Bitch	O
?	O
Then	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
three	O
Falls	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Head	O
came	O
against	O
the	O
Fender	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
Blows	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
which	O
struck	O
first	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
Fall	O
they	O
fell	O
both	O
together	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Potts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
Words	O
first	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
only	O
some	O
words	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
struggle	O
that	O
ensued	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
together	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
have	O
said	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gowan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
at	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
hospital	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
being	O
brought	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wound	O
about	O
an	O
inch	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
long	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
probably	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
his	O
falling	O
on	O
the	O
sender	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
hurt	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Gowan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
should	O
rather	O
think	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
other	O
bad	O
symptoms	O
;	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
attacked	O
with	O
a	O
fever	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
that	O
arise	O
from	O
the	O
wound	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Gowan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
bone	O
was	O
not	O
defected	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
coagulated	O
blood	O
after	O
the	O
skull	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
fracture	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wound	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
healing	O
state	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
attend	O
him	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Brian	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
visited	O
the	O
deceased	O
almost	O
every	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
till	O
he	O
died	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
they	O
cut	O
his	O
flesh	O
,	O
they	O
cut	O
much	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
wound	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
bed	O
immediately	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
the	O
witnesses	O
have	O
said	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
quarrel	O
is	O
truth	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scofield	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pewter	O
plates	O
value	O
15	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Monday	I-pers
,	O
November	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Monday	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
plates	O
here	O
produced	O
are	O
my	O
plates	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
often	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Joseph	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
these	O
two	O
plates	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seeing	O
the	O
letters	O
and	O
mark	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
it	O
,	O
suspected	O
her	O
and	O
stopped	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
being	O
informed	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Monday	O
's	O
house	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Monday	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
plates	O
,	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
do	O
of	O
my	O
dying	O
hour	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
four	O
witnesses	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Peter	I-pers
Lenard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
three	O
shifts	O
,	O
three	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
November	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Stephen	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Purford	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Purford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Sunbury	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
work	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
want	O
victuals	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
some	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
dropped	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
we	O
saw	O
somebody	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
at	O
our	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
after	O
we	O
left	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
cupboard	O
door	O
open	O
with	O
his	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
only	O
one	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Bever	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
continued	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
story	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
at	O
Twickenham	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
odd	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
rest	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
,	O
except	O
four	O
shillings	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Purford	I-pers
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
from	O
church	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
dust	O
lying	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
looked	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
lain	O
in	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
one	O
guinea	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
that	O
day	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
waiting	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Purford	O
came	O
from	O
church	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bonnit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
golden	O
guinea	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
by	O
him	O
at	O
Hampton	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
that	O
same	O
day	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
changed	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Barnfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
as	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Oxland	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
arms	O
at	O
Isleworth	O
;	O
he	O
inquired	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
boy	O
confess	O
the	O
breaking	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
taking	O
one	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cupboard	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
a	O
hair	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
13	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
.	O
12	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Jeremiah	I-pers
Foreman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
cotton	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
muslin	O
cap	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
hood	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
December	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Spittle-fields	B-place
;	O
my	O
wife	O
informed	O
me	O
that	O
last	O
Sunday	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
o'clock	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
woman	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
street	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
garret	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
hanging	O
up	O
to	O
day	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
December	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fetherstone	O
buildings	O
;	O
Holborn	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
again	O
at	O
Spencer	O
's	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
pawned	O
it	O
informed	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
Cassandra	B-pers
Mold	I-pers
with	O
it	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
fourteen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Cassandra	B-pers
Mold	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
employed	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
's	O
in	O
Holborn	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Diana	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
hanging	O
upon	O
a	O
nail	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
and	O
cut	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
missed	O
it	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
who	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
and	O
his	O
recognisance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Cradock	I-pers
Spinster	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
silver	O
buckle	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
November	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Ann	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
.	O
We	O
live	O
in	O
Drury	B-place
lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
daughter	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
.	O
She	O
produces	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
stockbuckle	O
which	O
is	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
John	B-pers
Ishar	I-pers
take	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
stock	O
buckles	O
?	O
A.	O
Whitehead	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
stock	O
buckle	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Spinsters	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
cloth	O
cloaks	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
ten	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
three	O
silk	O
ribands	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
four	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
tuckers	O
,	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
linen	O
worked	O
with	O
needlework	O
,	O
one	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
calimancoe	O
skirt	O
of	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilkin	I-pers
,	O
October	O
26	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilkin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sell	O
milk	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
upon	O
liking	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
workhouse	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
apprentice	O
in	O
last	O
October	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
employment	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
milk	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
returned	O
about	O
six	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
doors	O
all	O
open	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
they	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
at	O
James	O
M'Daniel	O
's	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
at	O
the	O
three	O
blue	O
balls	O
in	O
Denmark	O
street	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
October	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
and	O
James	O
M'Daniel	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
offered	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
pledge	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
cap	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
shirt	O
,	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
them	O
8	O
s	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
before	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
afterwards	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
about	O
eleven	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Guilty	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Walter	B-pers
Bedford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
,	O
October	O
27	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
high	B-place
Holborn	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
sheets	O
off	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
ordered	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
sheets	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
he	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
sheets	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
several	O
small	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
no	O
money	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
hopes	O
soon	O
to	O
have	O
money	O
to	O
redeem	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Stowman	I-pers
widow	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
camblet	O
gown	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
double	O
laced	O
cap	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
one	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
,	O
November	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
my	O
brother	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
drest	O
in	O
my	O
cloaths	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
parcel	O
she	O
had	O
bundled	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
.	O
No	O
never	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
the	O
cloaths	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
bundle	O
the	O
cloaths	O
up	O
which	O
you	O
found	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kempster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
my	O
mistress	O
sent	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
my	O
mistress	O
if	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
cloaths	O
on	O
her	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Owres	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
made	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
duffel	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Curtis	I-pers
widow	O
;	O
four	O
printed	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
book	O
of	O
common	O
prayer	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
November	O
1st	O
.	O
No	O
evidences	O
appearing	O
,	O
their	O
recognizances	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
20	O
,	O
21	O
,	O
22	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Briant	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Plastow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
perriwig	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burdett	I-pers
,	O
one	O
perriwig	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
one	O
perriwig	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jonas	B-pers
Hannoway	I-pers
,	O
one	O
perriwig	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Bickham	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Tench	I-pers
,	O
November	O
1st	O
.	O
||	O
Richard	B-pers
Tench	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
perriwig-maker	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
perriwigs	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burdet	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Jonas	B-pers
Hannoway	I-pers
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Bickham	I-pers
;	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
Burdet	O
's	O
and	O
Hannoway	O
's	O
again	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
Elmose	O
's	O
possession	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
one	O
Gordon	O
's	O
possession	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
John	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
one	O
concerned	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
Briant	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
Plastow	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
Ann	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
Briant	O
took	O
four	O
perriwigs	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Rag-fair	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
Gaol	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
they	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Bryant	O
's	O
Defence	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
Hall	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
things	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
||	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Briant	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
Value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
Goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Hoyles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
11	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Hyan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
the	O
Money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cockerill	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cockerill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
Betty	B-pers
Mountague	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
almost	O
starved	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
victuals	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
in	O
the	O
loft	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
chamber	O
joining	O
to	O
the	O
lost	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
One	O
morning	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
key	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
help	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
up	O
he	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
inform	O
'd	O
his	O
father	O
at	O
Hampstead	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
brother	O
after	O
him	O
towards	O
Stratford-upon-Avon	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
quite	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
father	O
return	O
'd	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
this	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
again	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
had	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
There	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
clerk	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Bingham	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
recognisance	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
open	O
any	O
lock	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Denton	I-pers
Peat	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
doors	O
from	O
Catharine-street	B-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
talking	O
to	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
my	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
my	O
right	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
others	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
till	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
strand	O
,	O
and	O
neither	O
touch	O
'd	O
or	O
saw	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
eight	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Sopp	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pewter	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
fifty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
December	O
the	O
1st	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
merry-making	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Cross	O
,	O
facing	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
I	O
overtook	O
two	O
women	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	O
Bed	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Fleet	B-place
Market	I-place
;	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
them	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
stopping	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
what	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
cold	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
three	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
three	O
halfpence	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Poplin	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
and	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
going	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
after	O
heard	O
somebody	O
cry	O
halloo	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
.	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
touch	O
or	O
no	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
three	O
pence	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
!	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Well	O
come	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
toss	O
off	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
fumbling	O
up	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
directly	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
you	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Cross	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
for	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Cross	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
it	O
?	O
Cross	O
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
and	O
rumbled	O
her	O
about	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
witness	O
that	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
big	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
her	O
alone	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
leave	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
thinking	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
exposed	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
witness	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Young	O
man	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
drop	O
from	O
between	O
her	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
fall	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Leaver	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
and	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
laying	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
elbow	O
the	O
watch	O
dropt	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
witness	O
Priest	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
watch	O
drop	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
from	O
between	O
her	O
feet	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Leaver	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
apprehend	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
fall	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mears	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
witnesses	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
watch-house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
He	O
produces	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Cross	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Cross	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
Fleet	O
Market	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
in	O
my	O
head	O
than	O
one	O
should	O
have	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
standing	O
up	O
making	O
water	O
;	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
he	O
'd	O
on	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
skirt	O
of	O
my	O
gown	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
out	O
again	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
He	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
all	O
came	O
to	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
one	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
his	O
watch	O
to	O
hold	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28	O
,	O
29	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
29	O
gallons	O
of	O
Brandy	O
,	O
val	O
11	O
l.	O
and	O
24	O
gallons	O
of	O
rum	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
in	O
his	O
warehouse	O
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
wherein	O
these	O
liquors	O
were	O
was	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
to	O
let	O
for	O
his	O
landlord	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
were	O
deposited	O
divers	O
things	O
for	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
carpenters	O
and	O
bricklayers	O
that	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
estate	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
frequently	O
had	O
the	O
keys	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
for	O
their	O
tools	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
positive	O
proof	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
liquors	O
,	O
(	O
there	O
being	O
others	O
that	O
constantly	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
)	O
they	O
were	O
acquitted	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Christopher	B-pers
Woodland	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gahagan	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
;	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
blankets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
counterpane	O
,	O
two	O
smoothing	O
irons	O
,	O
four	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
four	O
plates	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
metal	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
||	O
James	B-pers
Gahagan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Saffron	B-place
Hill	I-place
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
night	O
last	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
in	O
again	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
ten	O
found	O
the	O
padlock	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stock	O
lock	O
broke	O
;	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
fast	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
strong	O
chissel	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
One	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
that	O
keeps	O
a	O
broker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Broker	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
received	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
some	O
other	O
company	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
bag	O
while	O
they	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
buckles	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Broker	O
's	O
Alley	O
by	O
Drury	O
Lane	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
with	O
him	O
came	O
on	O
Monday	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
bring	O
them	O
presently	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
again	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
or	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
them	O
go	O
to	O
some	O
place	O
and	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
by	O
Long	O
Acre	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
stopt	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
stopt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
a	O
house	O
on	O
Little	O
Saffron	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fellow	O
that	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
afterwards	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
Saffron	O
Hill	O
to	O
inquire	O
what	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
He	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
talking	O
that	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Justice	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Tis	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
this	O
for	O
want	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Crawley	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Flood	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
stock	O
bed	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
boulster	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
rug	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Bryan	B-pers
M'Gaughlan	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
2	O
.	O
||	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
evidence	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
brother	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
husband	O
,	O
all	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
part	O
by	O
agreement	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
one	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
lodgings	O
for	O
herself	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
by	O
mistake	O
took	O
the	O
wrong	O
bed	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
no	O
proof	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
32	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jacob	B-pers
Harbutt	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hog	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Forrest	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
5	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
33	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Rebecca	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Handford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
spurs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
diaper	O
napkin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
chattels	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
34	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Markham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
November	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
35	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Rudd	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
ginger	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
November	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
36	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
table	O
cloth	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Sunderland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
green	O
stuff	O
petticoat	O
and	O
a	O
bonnet	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Togin	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
November	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
37	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Stephen	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
copper	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
November	O
22	O
d.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
38	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Luke	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Willet	I-pers
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
for	O
manslaughter	O
,	O
November	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Clarage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
High	O
Holbourn	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
deceased	O
agreed	O
to	O
meet	O
at	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
in	I-place
Tottenham	I-place
Court	I-place
Road	I-place
,	O
where	O
they	O
met	O
and	O
fought	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
to	O
fight	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
each	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
shook	O
hands	O
before	O
they	O
began	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
they	O
had	O
malice	O
against	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
money	O
to	O
be	O
spent	O
?	O
Clarage	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
agreement	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
their	O
fighting	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
died	O
in	O
about	O
nine	O
hours	O
after	O
the	O
battle	O
.	O
They	O
fought	O
at	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
died	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
sober	O
when	O
they	O
fought	O
?	O
Clarage	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
death	O
owing	O
to	O
any	O
bruises	O
he	O
received	O
?	O
Clarage	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
bruised	O
very	O
much	O
about	O
his	O
breast	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
bruised	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
near	O
of	O
an	O
age	O
?	O
Clarage	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
two	O
strong	O
young	O
fellows	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
before	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
fight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
agreement	O
made	O
to	O
fight	O
?	O
Clarage	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
morning	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
battle	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
was	O
very	O
hearty	O
and	O
well	O
before	O
they	O
fought	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fix	O
'd	O
battle	O
.	O
They	O
shook	O
hands	O
before	O
they	O
sought	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
deceased	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
they	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
appearance	O
of	O
malice	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
striving	O
to	O
beat	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
deceased	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
field	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
they	O
fought	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
.	O
Willet	O
said	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
punch	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
fight	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
throw	O
him	O
behind	O
the	O
fire	O
and	O
burn	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
battle	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
deceased	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
the	O
battle	O
;	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
he	O
died	O
of	O
his	O
bruises	O
then	O
received	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
challenged	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rowbottom	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
battle	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
the	O
deceased	O
died	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
that	O
battle	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
turn	O
and	O
shake	O
his	O
hand	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
threaten	O
me	O
?	O
The	O
deceased	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
quarrelsome	O
man	O
;	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
stones	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
threw	O
him	O
fifty	O
times	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
39.	O
John	B-pers
Rimes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
gilding	O
,	O
washing	O
and	O
colouring	O
over	O
a	O
six-pence	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
pass	O
for	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
coin	O
of	O
this	O
realm	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
No	O
prosecutor	O
appearing	O
against	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
40	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
blankets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
11	O
s.	O
two	O
pillow	O
cases	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
in	O
his	O
ready	O
furnish	O
'd	O
lodgings	O
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
41	O
,	O
42	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Keyes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Grace	B-pers
Grannet	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
Nov.	O
10	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Great	O
Warner-street	O
,	O
Cold	O
Bath	O
Fields	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
Mount	B-place
Pleasant	I-place
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
'd	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
Between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
my	O
way	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
just	O
the	O
contrary	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
towards	O
Sir	O
John	O
Oldcastle	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
wrong	O
way	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Keyes	O
tripp	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
heels	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
a	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
half	O
crowns	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
had	O
their	O
hands	O
in	O
my	O
pockets	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
his	O
buckles	O
are	O
silver	O
,	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
Keyes	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
knock	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
if	O
you	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
that	O
night	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
the	O
woman	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Black	O
Mary	O
's	O
Hole	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
also	O
running	O
when	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Chamberlaine	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
The	O
man	O
has	O
got	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
watchmen	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Sir	O
John	O
Oldcastle	O
's	O
;	O
just	O
after	O
one	O
o'clock	O
he	O
assisted	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
bringing	O
Grace	B-pers
Grannet	I-pers
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
neither	O
hat	O
,	O
wig	O
,	O
or	O
shoes	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
things	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
rude	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
His	O
hat	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
watchmen	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
they	O
found	O
a	O
shoe	O
without	O
a	O
buckle	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
And	O
on	O
the	O
bridge	O
near	O
the	O
dead	O
wall	O
they	O
found	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
When	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
then	O
?	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
her	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Bob	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
his	O
other	O
name	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
but	O
a	O
fortnight	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
we	O
found	O
Keyes	O
at	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
directed	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Justice	O
Chamberlaine	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
both	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
and	O
three	O
half	O
crowns	O
sealed	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
tobacco	O
box	O
which	O
Keyes	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Buckingham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Justice	O
Chamberlaine	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
the	O
examinations	O
and	O
voluntary	O
confessions	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
in	O
which	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
robbery	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
before	O
deposed	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Elmore	I-pers
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
back	O
from	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
Grannet	O
said	O
she	O
unbuckled	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Bob	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
pull	O
off	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
buckles	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
are	O
silver	O
.	O
Scarbrow	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
Elmore	O
,	O
being	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Keyes	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Grace	B-pers
Grannet	I-pers
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
laid	O
down	O
a	O
shilling	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
her	O
bosom	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
did	O
that	O
for	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
dear	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
fire	O
and	O
candle	O
.	O
They	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
lie	O
together	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
down	O
another	O
shilling	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
more	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Bob	B-pers
Keyes	I-pers
,	O
he	O
has	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
have	O
none	O
to	O
buy	O
us	O
any	O
victuals	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
had	O
better	O
let	O
it	O
alone	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
Spaw	O
Fields	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
we	O
went	O
she	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
rob	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Grannet	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
birth-day	O
at	O
night	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
bargain	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
he	O
there	O
made	O
a	O
bargain	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
down	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
offered	O
Keyes	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
carried	O
him	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
foot	O
between	O
his	O
feet	O
and	O
tripped	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
behind	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
he	O
took	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
together	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
To	O
Keyes	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Keyes	O
a	O
summer	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
hard	O
working	O
lad	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
year	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Rober	O
Vandermine	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Browning	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
were	O
Keyes	O
did	O
last	O
June	O
and	O
July	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
sent	O
him	O
of	O
errands	O
,	O
and	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
money	O
and	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
christening	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
had	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
43	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pocket	O
book	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
promissory	O
signed	O
under	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Galley	I-pers
,	O
value	O
11	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
it	O
being	O
due	O
and	O
unsatisfied	O
for	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
Hubert	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
October	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
Hubert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
Lothbury	O
;	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
at	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
near	O
home	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
letters	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
note	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
11	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
home	O
?	O
Hubert	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
then	O
almost	O
day-light	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Hubert	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
quite	O
sober	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
call	O
any	O
where	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
?	O
Hubert	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Poarch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
,	O
that	O
he	O
stopped	O
the	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
arm	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
pocket	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
he	O
when	O
he	O
confessed	O
this	O
?	O
Poarch	O
.	O
In	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Blackwell	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
testament	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
:	O
On	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
one	O
Plank	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
lodgings	O
this	O
book	O
and	O
note	O
here	O
mentioned	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
as	O
Plank	O
had	O
before	O
informed	O
us	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
note	O
dated	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
dated	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
payable	O
six	O
months	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
book	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
44	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
transportation	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
records	O
of	O
his	O
conviction	O
were	O
produced	O
and	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
See	O
Number	O
412.	O
in	O
alderman	O
Alsop	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
;	O
his	O
former	O
trial	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
in	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
saws	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
found	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
ordered	O
for	O
transportation	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Aylomer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
turnkey	O
of	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
attending	O
this	O
court	O
when	O
he	O
received	O
sentence	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
come	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
particular	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Aylomer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
locked	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
the	O
Friday	O
in	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sentence	O
of	O
transportation	O
passed	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
abroad	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
apprehended	O
him	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Aylomer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
yard	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Baily	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
that	O
had	O
come	O
from	O
transportation	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Norden	O
who	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
Hutton	O
was	O
returned	O
from	O
transportation	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
directly	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
Creed	O
lane	O
,	O
then	O
into	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
directed	O
you	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Aylomer	I-pers
.	O
A	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thumb	O
screws	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
for	O
safety	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Wood-street	O
Compter	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Norden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
apprehending	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
court	O
when	O
he	O
received	O
sentence	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
saws	O
from	O
a	O
carpenter	O
's	O
in	O
Chancery-lane	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
carried	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Peale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
here	O
at	O
the	O
trial	O
,	O
nor	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
received	O
sentence	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
transportation	O
before	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
cost	O
his	O
father	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
ship	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Penprice	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
died	O
in	O
the	O
voyage	O
.	O
William	O
Palmer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Peale	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
once	O
before	O
by	O
Brebrook	O
and	O
young	O
Pinchell	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
father	O
raised	O
thirteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
having	O
seen	O
him	O
once	O
tried	O
in	O
this	O
court	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
these	O
people	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
accused	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
raise	O
a	O
friend	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
my	O
father	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
gaol	O
.	O
Norden	O
said	O
before	O
my	O
lord-mayor	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
of	O
my	O
being	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
Number	O
70.	O
in	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Pennant	I-pers
's	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
and	O
516.	O
in	O
alderman	O
Blachford	O
's	O
.	O
45	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
table	O
spoons	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
six	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
covered	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
game	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Decima	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
October	O
25	O
.	O
||	O
Decima	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Dashwood	I-pers
's	O
family	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
spoons	O
of	O
mine	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
rolled	O
up	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
shoes	O
mentioned	O
were	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
drawer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
?	O
Decima	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
May	O
and	O
returned	O
in	O
October	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
drawers	O
locked	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
so	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Upon	O
missing	O
a	O
petticoat	O
,	O
in	O
searching	O
about	O
I	O
missed	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
amongst	O
them	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gauze	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
drawers	O
were	O
the	O
spoons	O
in	O
?	O
Decima	O
Davis	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
Sir	O
James	O
's	O
drawers	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
spoons	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stonehouse	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
a	O
house-maid	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Searle	O
,	O
who	O
lived	O
in	O
Sir	O
James	B-pers
Dashwood	I-pers
's	O
house	O
:	O
The	O
spoons	O
mentioned	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
strictly	O
honest	O
;	O
we	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
we	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
the	O
spoons	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
satin	O
shoes	O
and	O
a	O
gauze	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
spoons	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
curiosity	O
;	O
but	O
hearing	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
,	O
surprized	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
shoes	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
My	O
Lady	O
Boyer	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
a	O
year	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
she	O
behaved	O
very	O
soberly	O
and	O
honestly	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
servant	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dandridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
she	O
always	O
bore	O
an	O
exceeding	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
young	O
woman	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Sherwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
she	O
bore	O
an	O
extreme	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Herbert	B-pers
Jefferys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
industrious	O
honest	O
girl	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
46	O
,	O
47	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	O
Welch	O
the	O
younger	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
dead	O
pig	O
,	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
farthing	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
September	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
John	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
September	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
Islington	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
bad	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
and	O
he	O
me	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
walked	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
and	O
met	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
fire-arms	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
collared	O
him	O
and	O
threw	O
him	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
:	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
tussling	O
with	O
him	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
another	O
man	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
he	O
followed	O
his	O
blows	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
imagined	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
me	O
in	O
four	O
places	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
that	O
attacked	O
me	O
first	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
middle	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
stunned	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
rifled	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
then	O
my	O
watch	O
from	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
three	O
farthings	O
,	O
a	O
tobacco-box	O
,	O
spectacles	O
and	O
case	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
dead	O
pig	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
for	O
my	O
Sunday	O
's	O
dinner	O
.	O
There	O
I	O
lay	O
some	O
considerable	O
time	O
in	O
a	O
gore	O
of	O
blood	O
,	O
feeling	O
it	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
knee	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
into	O
my	O
shoe	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
upon	O
the	O
causeway	O
very	O
faint	O
,	O
and	O
scrambled	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
hundred	O
yards	O
met	O
three	O
men	O
coming	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
their	O
assistance	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
habitation	O
though	O
they	O
were	O
strangers	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
abused	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
evidence	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
first	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Kirvan	I-pers
Kirby	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
myself	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
junior	O
,	O
met	O
according	O
to	O
our	O
appointment	O
at	O
the	O
Blue	O
Anchor	O
in	O
Bunhill-row	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
Welches	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
committed	O
divers	O
robberies	O
together	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
Mason	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Newgate	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
some	O
idle	O
things	O
together	O
before	O
;	O
we	O
four	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
between	O
Islington	O
and	O
London	O
;	O
there	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
Welch	O
junior	O
and	O
Mason	O
changed	O
coats	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
ladder-bridge	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
we	O
agreed	O
two	O
of	O
us	O
should	O
stay	O
there	O
;	O
so	O
Welch	O
senior	O
and	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
went	O
in	O
the	O
path	O
Moorfield	O
's	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
Welch	O
junior	O
went	O
Islington	O
way	O
,	O
both	O
to	O
be	O
within	O
our	O
hearing	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
if	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
Islington	O
way	O
,	O
Welch	O
junior	O
was	O
to	O
speak	O
aloud	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
a	O
hearty	O
good	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Moorfield	O
's	O
way	O
was	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
if	O
he	O
met	O
any	O
body	O
:	O
This	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
signal	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
bridge	O
to	O
know	O
who	O
to	O
rob	O
.	O
Mason	O
met	O
Humphrys	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
him	O
a	O
hearty	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
with	O
a	O
chearful	O
voice	O
that	O
we	O
might	O
hear	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
a	O
lame	O
hand	O
,	O
having	O
had	O
it	O
run	O
through	O
with	O
a	O
sword	O
,	O
so	O
could	O
not	O
do	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
me	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
causeway	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
his	O
silver	O
watch	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
struggle	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
up	O
his	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
Welch	O
took	O
a	O
hanger	O
and	O
pushed	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
which	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
chin	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
,	O
then	O
Welch	O
bid	O
me	O
cut	O
his	O
throat	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
occasion	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
easy	O
enough	O
;	O
then	O
Welch	O
junior	O
said	O
,	O
two	O
old	O
women	O
could	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
business	O
sooner	O
than	O
you	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Kirby	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
in	O
his	O
place	O
;	O
then	O
Welch	O
senior	O
gave	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
a	O
stroke	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
first	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
stick	O
and	O
left	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
;	O
Welch	O
took	O
his	O
money	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
acknowledge	O
it	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pig	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
two	O
cloths	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
next	O
robbery	O
Welch	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
us	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
in	O
Maynard	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
come	O
home	O
asked	O
a	O
soldier	O
who	O
drawed	O
beer	O
there	O
,	O
where	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
ask	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
Harvey	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
Mason	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
ask	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
another	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
more	O
money	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
lent	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
with	O
some	O
steaks	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
more	O
money	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
after	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
Kirby	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
him	O
Welch	O
the	O
younger	O
;	O
Kirby	O
desired	O
Mason	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
Mason	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
heard	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
pig	O
roasted	O
at	O
one	O
Sparrey	O
's	O
opposite	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mason	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
twenty-second	O
of	O
September	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
in	O
Maynard-street	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
that	O
woman	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
landlady	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
some	O
things	O
which	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
pledge	O
in	O
some	O
other	O
place	O
for	O
more	O
money	O
;	O
this	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
sent	O
the	O
soldier	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
it	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
West-street	O
,	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bibby	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
they	O
lay	O
for	O
thirteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bibby	O
lent	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Clare	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
breast	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
pork	O
steaks	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Reding	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
steaks	O
dress	O
'd	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
borrowed	O
the	O
money	O
about	O
seven	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
S.	O
Harvey	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
mention	O
?	O
S.	O
Harvey	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
was	O
sick	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Reding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
watch	O
to	O
see	O
about	O
its	O
time	O
to	O
take	O
physick	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
ten	O
when	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
lent	O
Mason	O
.	O
For	O
Mason	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bibby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Stanhope-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Mason	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
twenty-second	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
some	O
things	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
lighted	O
candles	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
be	O
exact	O
to	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
light	O
candles	O
then	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
eight	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
fun	O
does	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
till	O
about	O
six	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
light	O
candles	O
before	O
the	O
sun	O
goes	O
down	O
?	O
Bibby	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
exact	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Nathan	B-pers
Patterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mason	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
Nine	O
months	O
ago	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
in	O
May	O
Fair	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
for	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
we	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Welch	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
company	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
this	O
man	O
says	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
Welch	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
.	O
Welch	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
twenty-second	O
of	O
September	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Church-lane	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
there	O
till	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
,	O
we	O
drank	O
three	O
single	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
three	O
quarters	O
after	O
nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
Blake	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Blake	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
trifle	O
coming	O
in	O
from	O
a	O
relation	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
upon	O
my	O
earnings	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
my	O
character	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Leonard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
Welch	O
two	O
years	O
last	O
February	O
at	O
times	O
in	O
mending	O
sacks	O
and	O
filling	O
coals	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
that	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
his	O
attendance	O
daily	O
when	O
there	O
was	O
work	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
money	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
employed	O
him	O
in	O
mending	O
sacks	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Irons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
in	O
filling	O
coals	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
bushels	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
brought	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
Welch	O
used	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
and	O
civilly	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
above	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
yet	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
highway	O
robberies	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
cast	O
upon	O
this	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
48	O
,	O
49	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Aubury	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
linen	O
ruffles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
linen	O
ruffles	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
vest	O
embroidered	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
locket	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
with	O
a	O
Mocha	O
stone	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
small	O
diamonds	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Fraizer	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Nov.	O
13	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
+	O
Alexander	B-pers
Wetherburn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Pump	O
Court	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Clark	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
linen	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
under	O
his	O
care	O
;	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
heard	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
many	O
things	O
by	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
injury	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
;	O
some	O
wearing	O
cloaths	O
,	O
some	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
laced	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
laced	O
and	O
plain	O
,	O
a	O
vest	O
embroidered	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
divers	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Fraizer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
who	O
granted	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbrokers	O
will	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
One	O
Margaret	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
Aubury	O
's	O
,	O
brought	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
and	O
eighth	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
old	O
silk	O
stockings	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Murford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
in	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
18	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Wetherburn	O
.	O
This	O
waistcoat	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Fraizer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
Simon	B-pers
Fraizer	I-pers
.	O
That	O
waistcoat	O
is	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
in	O
October	O
Aubury	O
brought	O
a	O
gold	O
locket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
hair	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
Lord	O
Lovat	O
's	O
hair	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
lent	O
her	O
5	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
her	O
which	O
way	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Middleton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Both	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Archibald	B-pers
Fraizer	I-pers
.	O
These	O
goods	O
produced	O
are	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Aubury	O
.	O
Whether	O
or	O
not	O
that	O
gentleman	O
has	O
had	O
money	O
of	O
Clark	O
after	O
I	O
have	O
pawn	O
'd	O
things	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Cooper	O
's	O
in	O
Clare	O
Market	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
use	O
?	O
Fraizer	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Young	B-pers
Mr	I-pers
.	O
Fraizer	O
first	O
brought	O
me	O
into	O
all	O
bad	O
company	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Neal	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Clark	O
from	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
misbehaved	O
thing	O
till	O
this	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Sturdey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
behaved	O
soberly	O
,	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
civilly	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Welch	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
and	O
pay	O
money	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
post	O
my	O
accounts	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Uriah	B-pers
Boote	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
dutiful	O
to	O
his	O
parents	O
,	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wetherburn	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
do	O
him	O
justice	O
,	O
before	O
this	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Aubury	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
What	O
I	O
say	O
will	O
have	O
no	O
great	O
weight	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
'll	O
say	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
Clark	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
things	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
have	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
.	O
Once	O
he	O
said	O
Mr.	O
Fraizer	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
some	O
silver	O
lace	O
which	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
having	O
seen	O
them	O
in	O
company	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
Mr.	O
Fraizer	O
had	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
Clark	O
guilty	O
,	O
Aubury	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
50	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Nov.	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hodgson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	B-place
Minories	I-place
at	O
the	O
Peacock	O
,	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
losing	O
it	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
witnesses	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
set	O
the	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
anniseed	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
enough	O
above	O
,	O
so	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
to	O
fill	O
a	O
bottle	O
,	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
served	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Missing	O
the	O
mug	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
lived	O
hard	O
by	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
with	O
other	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
a	O
chimney	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
pull	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
he	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
closet	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
,	O
who	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Madding	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Madding	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
myself	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
amongst	O
some	O
straw	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
(	O
who	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
going	O
by	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
so	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
us	O
)	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
mug	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hodgson	O
's	O
bar	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
51	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Magee	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
29	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Alexander	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
sale	O
shop	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
into	O
my	O
parlour	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
that	O
laid	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
on	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
then	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
two	O
minutes	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
detain	O
him	O
without	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
very	O
bad	O
words	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
took	O
off	O
his	O
right	O
foot	O
shoe	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
money	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
board	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Carnagey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
return	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
the	O
woman	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
shoe	O
.	O
He	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
his	O
shoe	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
a	O
half-guinea	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
piece	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
bureau	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
half-guinea	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
mortally	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
52	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Frances	B-pers
Ellice	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Humphry	B-pers
Grudgworthy	I-pers
and	I-pers
company	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
20	O
.	O
||	O
Timothy	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
partner	O
with	O
Humphry	O
Grudgworthy	O
.	O
We	O
keep	O
the	O
Fountain	O
Tavern	O
,	O
Catharine-street	B-place
.	O
About	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
spoon	O
and	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
the	O
bowl	O
end	O
broke	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
handle	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
fellow	O
spoon	O
to	O
compare	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
silversmith	O
's	O
mark	O
on	O
one	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
marked	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
difficult	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
poor	O
woman	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Marshal	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lovel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
She	O
looks	O
at	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
spoon	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
spoon	O
belongs	O
to	O
my	O
two	O
masters	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
silversmith	O
's	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
piece	O
broke	O
off	O
should	O
have	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
Fountain	O
Tavern	O
,	O
Catharine-street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
own	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
masters	O
house	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
spoon	O
in	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
mistress	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
by	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
found	O
it	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
fountain	O
tavern	O
Catharine-street	O
;	O
he	O
stopt	O
it	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Grudgworthy	O
:	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
discovered	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lemon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
spoon	O
in	O
the	O
seller	O
,	O
all	O
over	O
dirt	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
spoon	O
in	O
the	O
seller	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
black	O
and	O
I	O
cleaned	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
53	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
