TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
26th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
CRISP	O
GASCOYNE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1753	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
CRISP	O
GASCOYNE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WRIGHT	O
*	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
GUNDREY	O
+	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
BARON	O
ADAMS	O
||	O
,	O
WILLIAM	O
MORETON	O
++	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Allinson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gill	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Baynton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Manning	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Gerrard	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Spleer	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Love	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
Collin	B-pers
Dollinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Darwood	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ranby	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ballard	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Vear	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Trisler	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Friday	I-pers
.	O
98	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
washing	O
tub	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
woman	O
's	O
clogs	O
;	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Morton	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Lad-Lane	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
clogs	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
pulled	O
off	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
)	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Parrock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Morton	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
tub	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
cellar	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
near	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
shehad	O
got	O
a	O
washing	O
tub	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Morton	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
clogs	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
those	O
things	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
2	O
d.	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
Alderman-bury	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
since	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
M.	O
Parrock	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
things	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
M.	O
Parrock	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
99	O
,	O
100	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Hermitage	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Vineyard	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
bushels	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
||	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
103	O
,	O
104	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Vincent	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Grelby	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
56	O
horse-shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
and	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Mading	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
105	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Robert	I-pers
Heap	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
wooden	O
box	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
two	O
Portugal	O
pieces	O
,	O
forty-nine	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Skuce	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Skuce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
White's-alley	B-place
,	I-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
back	I-place
of	I-place
Bond	I-place
's	I-place
stables	I-place
;	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
a	O
fortnight	O
my	O
wife	O
missed	O
a	O
cloak	O
and	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
they	O
owed	O
me	O
a	O
year	O
's	O
rent	O
,	O
3	O
l.	O
15	O
s.	O
then	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
time	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
box	O
which	O
used	O
to	O
stand	O
under	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
in	O
it	O
were	O
fifty	O
guineas	O
,	O
five	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
eight	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
crown	O
;	O
these	O
,	O
box	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
were	O
missing	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
liquor	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
paying	O
some	O
money	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
due	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
her	O
behaviour	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
twenty-two	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
thirty	O
six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
eight	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
crown	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Skuce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
money	O
in	O
this	O
box	O
under	O
our	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
my	O
cloak	O
and	O
apron	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
paid	O
another	O
person	O
another	O
debt	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
by	O
searching	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
stocking	O
,	O
thirty	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
8	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
crown	O
loose	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
had	O
found	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
we	O
must	O
carry	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
cloak	O
in	O
her	O
wash	O
tub	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
was	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
wash.	O
George	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
twenty-six	O
shillings	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
halfpence	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
order	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
amongst	O
some	O
coals	O
,	O
twenty-three	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
thirty	O
six	O
shillings	O
pieces	O
,	O
eight	O
crowns	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
crown	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
the	O
Morning	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
five	O
Guineas	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
his	O
rent	O
;	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
returned	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
only	O
I	O
am	O
told	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
borrow	O
'd	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
lent	O
her	O
any	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
constable	O
take	O
the	O
money	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coal-hole	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
chimney	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
cloak	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
washing	O
tub	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
paid	O
me	O
a	O
debt	O
of	O
15	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
.	O
Gasper	O
Cayton	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
paid	O
me	O
a	O
debt	O
1	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
single	O
half-penny	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
worth	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witness	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
trouble	O
my	O
friends	O
about	O
such	O
a	O
frivilous	O
affair	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
brought	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
money	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
106	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
,	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
Henry	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	B-place
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
wet-day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Exchange	O
was	O
crowded	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
seiz	O
'd	O
him	O
immediately	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Rawlins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
under	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
prejudice	O
mankind	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
change	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
wine	O
merchant	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
pressing	O
of	O
the	O
croud	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
came	O
upon	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
107	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Blundell	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
twenty	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
privately	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
guinea	O
wages	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Dabbs	O
,	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
changed	O
the	O
guinea	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
,	O
in	O
Rose-court	O
;	O
and	O
put	O
20	O
s.	O
into	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
going	O
by	O
Bishop's-gate	O
church	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
could	O
tell	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
lodging	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
just	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
consider	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
betwixt	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Pump	O
Court	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
lodged	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
another	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
rather	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
breakfast	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
desire	O
for	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Ship	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
one	O
there	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
also	O
;	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
halfpence	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
change	O
sixpence	O
for	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Pump	B-place
Court	I-place
;	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
stay	O
there	O
till	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
stood	O
talking	O
together	O
I	O
thought	O
something	O
pulled	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
apprehend	O
she	O
was	O
picking	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
according	O
to	O
her	O
promise	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
where	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
the	O
slip	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
a	O
passage	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
landlady	O
whether	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
her	O
husband	O
and	O
brother	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
changed	O
her	O
dress	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
dress	O
had	O
she	O
when	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
E.	O
Hunter	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
jacket	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
blue	O
cloak	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
blue	O
flowered	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
camblet	O
one	O
upon	O
that	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Before	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
alehouse	O
the	O
landlady	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
swear	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
treated	O
with	O
a	O
dram	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
strip	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
pocket	O
off	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
nobody	O
's	O
company	O
but	O
her	O
's	O
till	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
you	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
to	O
a	O
lodging	O
?	O
E.	O
Hunter	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
acquaintance	O
at	O
that	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Torrent	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
last	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
E.	O
Hunter	O
before	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
nine	O
.	O
E.	O
Hunter	O
went	O
to	O
seel	O
in	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
halfpence	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
penny	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
returned	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
to	O
E.	O
Hunter	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
E.	O
Hunter	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
a	O
dram	O
there	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
by	O
sight	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
of	O
20	O
s.	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
returned	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
E.	O
Hunter	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Deoonshire	O
steps	O
by	O
the	O
square	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
husband	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
E.	O
Hunter	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
old	O
blue	O
cloak	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
alehouse	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
linnen	O
bed	O
gown	O
on	O
under	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
E.	O
Torrent	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
how	O
often	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
before	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Meading	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
last	O
Thursday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
E.	O
Hunter	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
dealt	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
in	O
what	O
,	O
or	O
with	O
whom	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dabbs	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
night	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
a	O
guinea	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
my	O
service	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Three	O
Tons	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
nurse	O
maid	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
woman	O
days	O
of	O
my	O
breath	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
with	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
its	O
mother	O
's	O
womb	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
108	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
February	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
Ship	B-place
tavern	I-place
,	I-place
Bishopsgate-street	I-place
,	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
in	O
Spitalfields	B-place
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
ladies	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
the	O
wall	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
pass	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
my	O
coat	O
aside	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
women	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
tried	O
to	O
catch	O
at	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
shifted	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
my	O
stick	O
kept	O
the	O
women	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pull	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Helmet	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
something	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
Both	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
marked	O
N.	O
S.	O
)	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
is	O
the	O
next	O
evidence	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Elicourt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
these	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
Helmet	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
silk	O
one	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shepherd	O
had	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
name	O
upon	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
mine	O
is	O
a	O
brown	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
is	O
N.	O
S.	O
upon	O
it	O
before	O
he	O
shewed	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
109	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
funnel	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
and	I-pers
James	I-pers
Islewood	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
||	O
James	B-pers
Islewood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
this	O
copper	O
funnel	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
funnel	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
brother	O
Thomas	O
's	O
and	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Etheridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hind	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
last	O
Monday	O
morning	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
sack	O
with	O
this	O
funnel	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
sack	O
.	O
As	O
they	O
were	O
swearing	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
dispute	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
the	O
funnel	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
sack	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
but	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
hide	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
bench	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
first	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
as	O
I	O
remember	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
he	O
'd	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
me	O
in	O
Fore	O
Street	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
there	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
110	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
saw	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Derbyeal	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
7	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Derbyeal	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
worked	O
both	O
for	O
one	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Grundy	O
,	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
.	O
At	O
night	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
saw	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
pad	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
confessed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
directed	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
justice	O
Chamberlain	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
robbing	O
his	O
shopmate	O
of	O
a	O
saw	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Moor-fields	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
saw	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
man	O
(	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
)	O
who	O
owned	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Before	O
we	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
must	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
I	O
really	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
saw	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
saw	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
four	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
that	O
saw	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
necessity	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Philip	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
(	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
or	O
known	O
)	O
young	O
fellow	O
:	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
five	O
months	O
and	O
upwards	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
12	O
years	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
knew	O
or	O
saw	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cover	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
fellow-apprentices	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pateman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
111	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Room	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
offensive	O
weapon	O
called	O
a	O
razor	O
,	O
on	O
Richard	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
attempt	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
to	O
steal	O
,	O
November	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
13	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
last	O
Dec	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
out	O
news-papers	O
for	O
my	O
father	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
delivered	O
a	O
wrong	O
paper	O
in	O
Hornsey-lane	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Crouch-End	O
,	O
that	O
leads	O
down	O
to	O
Hornsey	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
any	O
harm	O
.	O
At	O
Crouch-End	O
he	O
shaved	O
a	O
gentleman	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
barber	O
)	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
a	O
gate	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
field	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
bricklayers	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
mortar	O
and	O
stuff	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
which	O
come	O
out	O
to	O
Holloway	B-place
.	O
We	O
got	O
over	O
a	O
hedge	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
money	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
money	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
nor	O
should	O
have	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
the	O
hedge	O
to	O
escape	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
me	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
skirt	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
suffered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
hedge	O
and	O
went	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
along	O
the	O
field	O
;	O
he	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
hedge	O
and	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
come	O
his	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
his	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
hedge	O
and	O
said	O
again	O
,	O
money	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
and	O
money	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
answer	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
sure	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
I	O
'd	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Haycock	O
in	O
Devils-lane	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
money	O
he	O
wanted	O
and	O
money	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
;	O
I	O
answered	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
his	O
razor	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
neck	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
cut	O
me	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
feel	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
chin	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
the	O
razor	O
along	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
cut	O
them	O
so	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
when	O
we	O
shave	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Haycock	O
(	O
I	O
bled	O
much	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
hollow	O
out	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
or	O
woman	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
which	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
where	O
were	O
two	O
horses	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
thumb	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
my	O
mouth	O
and	O
finger	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
calling	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
laid	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
haycock	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
hay	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
haycock	O
,	O
and	O
covered	O
me	O
over	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
lie	O
there	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
Holloway	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
borrow	O
me	O
a	O
crown	O
or	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
somebody	O
else	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
for	O
fear	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
drovers	O
coming	O
along	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
with	O
my	O
wound	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
Dennis	O
.	O
Because	O
when	O
Dr.	O
Coleman	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sew	O
my	O
wound	O
up	O
he	O
shewed	O
a	O
large	O
scar	O
on	O
his	O
throat	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
my	O
money	O
home	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
7	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
farthing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
senses	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
112	O
,	O
113	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Bannister	I-pers
,	O
the	O
first	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pecks	O
of	O
flour	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Short	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
13	O
.	O
||	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
lives	O
at	O
Limehouse	B-place
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
baker	O
.	O
The	O
principal	O
evidence	O
was	O
Peter	B-pers
Whitwell	I-pers
,	O
the	O
journeyman	O
,	O
whose	O
evidence	O
was	O
only	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
given	O
Fletcher	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
flour	O
,	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
about	O
five	O
pecks	O
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
Both	O
Acq	O
.	O
114	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edmund	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Roger	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
and	O
Beston	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Esqrs	O
.	O
February	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Ferguson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
buildings	O
,	O
or	O
warehouses	O
,	O
at	O
Young's-Key	B-place
,	O
he	O
had	O
18	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
in	O
a	O
lump	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
done	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Messrs.	O
Drake	O
and	O
Long	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Winterbourne	I-pers
.	O
Ferguson	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
with	O
the	O
sugar	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
tub	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
Drake	O
and	O
Long	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
there	O
for	O
some	O
hoop-sticks	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
sugar	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
apron	O
.	O
They	O
met	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
the	O
hogshead	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
115	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
beaten	O
hemp	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
,	O
February	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
George	B-pers
Gardiner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
send	O
my	O
hemp	O
to	O
the	O
London	O
workhouse	O
to	O
be	O
beaten	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
times	O
as	O
I	O
want	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
as	O
journeyman	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3	O
d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
returned	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
and	O
fetched	O
away	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
that	O
afternoon	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
send	O
him	O
there	O
for	O
any	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
hemp	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
East	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
London	O
workhouse	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
for	O
a	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
hemp	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
he	O
worked	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Veal	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
hemp	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
116	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Gerrard	B-pers
Levy	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hat	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dias	I-pers
Fanandus	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Jan.	O
14	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	O
Lake	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
optical	O
shop	O
in	O
Leaden-hall-street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
by	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
from	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
without	O
a	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
what	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
hat	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Fenchurch	O
Buildings	O
,	O
another	O
witness	O
then	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
hat	O
under	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
;	O
we	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
without	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Fanandus	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
another	O
Jew	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
whispered	O
together	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
hat	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
but	O
still	O
he	O
kept	O
pulling	O
it	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
hat	O
to	O
be	O
cleaned	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
hat	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Cray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
near	O
Bouker	O
's	O
Gardens	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
without	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
thief	O
take	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
gone	O
through	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
hat	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
stopt	O
him	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Dias	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
old	O
gentleman	O
without	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
six	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Dias	O
Fanandus	O
(	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
)	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
water	O
against	O
a	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
Leadenhall	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
up	O
Sugar-Loof	O
Court	O
with	O
the	O
hat	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
gentleman	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
presently	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
hat	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Motloe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
shutting	O
up	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
men	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
minute	O
's	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
returned	O
again	O
presently	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
black	O
without	O
a	O
hat	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Dias	I-pers
Fanandus	I-pers
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Crutched	O
Friers	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
found	O
that	O
hat	O
,	O
so	O
those	O
fellows	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
me	O
,	O
pulled	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
117	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pewter	O
plates	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
February	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
118	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Haws	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
71	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
for	O
breeches	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
February	O
1	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
119.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
And	O
,	O
120.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
42	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
.	O
And	O
.	O
121.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
24	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Haws	I-pers
came	O
to	O
Puddle	O
Dock	O
on	O
Thursday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
and	O
I.	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
a	O
brownish	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Newgate-Market	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
linnen	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
silk	O
stockings	O
and	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
believe	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
?	O
E.	O
Moor	O
.	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
now	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
?	O
E.	O
Moor	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
us	O
all	O
above	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
pair	O
that	O
we	O
sold	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
took	O
four	O
pair	O
and	O
pawned	O
one	O
pair	O
in	O
Bride-lane	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
upon	O
Snow	O
Hill	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
asked	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
where	O
she	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
mother	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
wedding	O
stockings	O
;	O
he	O
stopped	O
them	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Field-lane	O
,	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Ridge	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
pair	O
for	O
three	O
shillings	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
pair	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
trades	O
in	O
women	O
's	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Pearce	O
who	O
lives	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
doors	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
room	O
and	O
fetched	O
4	O
pair	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
us	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
three	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
shop	O
Mrs.	O
Ridge	O
called	O
us	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
stockings	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
bring	O
them	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
pair	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
more	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
14	O
pair	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
we	O
carried	O
40	O
pair	O
;	O
she	O
paid	O
us	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
32	O
or	O
13	O
s.	O
more	O
.	O
She	O
bid	O
us	O
come	O
o	O
n	O
the	O
next	O
Sunday	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
did	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
us	O
3	O
s.	O
then	O
she	O
bid	O
us	O
come	O
the	O
next	O
Sunday	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
,	O
paid	O
us	O
5	O
s.	O
we	O
bought	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
came	O
to	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Pearce	O
's	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
that	O
we	O
carried	O
the	O
40	O
pair	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
we	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
we	O
might	O
bring	O
them	O
down	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
carried	O
20	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
lend	O
us	O
20	O
s.	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
we	O
'd	O
fetch	O
them	O
away	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
her	O
we	O
would	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
found	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
more	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
Mrs.	O
Ridge	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
long	O
silk	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
long	O
,	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Pearce	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Haws	I-pers
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
linnen	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
stockings	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
My	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
prisoners	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
(	O
Haws	O
)	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Haws	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
Moor	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Whitacre	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
parcel	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Towcester	O
waggon	O
,	O
which	O
unloads	O
every	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
Newgate-Market	O
;	O
the	O
bag	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
lading	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bag	O
was	O
missing	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
unloaded	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	O
Hookham	O
in	O
liread	O
street	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
a	O
letter	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
3	O
guineas	O
reward	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
information	O
I	O
had	O
was	O
from	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
stopped	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
this	O
bag	O
of	O
stockings	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bag	O
of	O
halfpence	O
which	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
carry	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
(	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bag	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
with	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
in	O
it	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Moor	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
burned	O
two	O
pocket	O
books	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
apron	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hookham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
workmen	O
that	O
make	O
stockings	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
Northamptonshire	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
John	O
Shepherd	O
of	O
Hertford	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
me	O
71	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
hose	O
.	O
and	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
for	O
breeches	O
by	O
the	O
Towcester	O
waggon	O
,	O
which	O
never	O
came	O
to	O
hand	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
advertisement	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
on	O
Snow	O
hill	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
hose	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stopped	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
crimson	O
silk	O
stockings	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
and	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
advertisement	O
of	O
two	O
pair	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
stopped	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
pair	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
workmen	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
general	O
account	O
of	O
,	O
(	O
for	O
these	O
in	O
the	O
parcel	O
were	O
from	O
several	O
workmen	O
)	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
by	O
the	O
clocks	O
and	O
colour	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
of	O
them	O
42	O
in	O
one	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
24	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
besides	O
this	O
pair	O
which	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Newel	I-pers
produced	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
?	O
Hookham	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
46	O
l.	O
there	O
are	O
different	O
prices	O
to	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
best	O
worth	O
a	O
pair	O
?	O
Hookham	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
15	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
lowest	O
value	O
?	O
Hookham	O
.	O
None	O
under	O
9	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
the	O
real	O
value	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
selling	O
price	O
?	O
Hookham	O
.	O
I	O
mean	O
the	O
real	O
value	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Haws	O
say	O
the	O
apron	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
outside	O
wrapper	O
or	O
bag	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
Mary	O
Ridge	O
own	O
she	O
had	O
lodged	O
some	O
stockings	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
in	O
Shoemaker	O
Row	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
away	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
,	O
were	O
42	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
for	O
breeches	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
brought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
stockings	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
leave	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
was	O
7	O
nights	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
many	O
there	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
necessitated	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
opened	O
them	O
and	O
took	O
two	O
pair	O
out	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
might	O
make	O
free	O
with	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
10	O
s.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
upon	O
Snow-hill	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
stockings	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
my	O
name	O
and	O
place	O
of	O
abode	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
without	O
the	O
stockings	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
pawn	O
two	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
stopped	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seared	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
so	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
no	O
longer	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
followed	O
me	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
persons	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
of	O
these	O
two	O
pair	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
their	O
being	O
advertised	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
laughed	O
at	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
stockings	O
that	O
were	O
advertised	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
first	O
brought	O
them	O
,	O
did	O
she	O
give	O
any	O
reason	O
why	O
she	O
desired	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
left	O
there	O
?	O
C.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
stockings	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
were	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
principal	O
owner	O
and	O
get	O
the	O
reward	O
;	O
the	O
answered	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
three	O
guineas	O
reward	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
money	O
was	O
not	O
sufficient	O
to	O
destay	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
dropped	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Masters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Catharine	O
Taylor	O
brought	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
and	O
her	O
own	O
use	O
in	O
Chick	O
Lane	O
last	O
summer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
gave	O
16	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
in	O
Field	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
a	O
cloaths	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
some	O
stockings	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
improbable	O
but	O
these	O
might	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
look	O
into	O
the	O
advertisement	O
and	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
persons	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
safe	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
hurry	O
to	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
shop	O
alone	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
(	O
the	O
stockings	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
lived	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
directed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Masters	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
about	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
s.	O
per	O
pair	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
these	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
,	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
40	O
pair	O
more	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Horrocks	O
in	O
Dunnings	O
Alley	O
,	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
brought	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
herself	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
just	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
and	O
one	O
Brebrook	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
a	O
stone-cutter	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Pratt	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
out	O
24	O
pair	O
and	O
two	O
pieces	O
for	O
breeches	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Emmery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
made	O
nine	O
pair	O
of	O
these	O
stockings	O
here	O
produced	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parcel	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
stone-cutter	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
up	O
amongst	O
others	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
by	O
the	O
Towcester	O
waggon	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
(	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
)	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
Clark	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Moor	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
mother	O
gave	O
them	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
Puddle	O
Dock	O
.	O
Moor	O
said	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
of	O
taking	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
Clark	O
's	O
wedding-stockings	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
Clark	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
ever	O
wore	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
they	O
had	O
neither	O
been	O
wore	O
nor	O
pressed	O
,	O
stopped	O
them	O
till	O
she	O
brought	O
somebody	O
to	O
testify	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
not	O
coming	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
Haws	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
stockings	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
which	O
comes	O
out	O
into	O
Newgate-street	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
upon	O
Ludgate	O
hill	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Haws	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
He	O
lodged	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
pawned	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
another	O
house	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
stopped	O
.	O
Haws	O
told	O
us	O
what	O
we	O
made	O
above	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
pair	O
we	O
should	O
have	O
.	O
Ridge	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
and	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
any	O
stockings	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
two	O
pair	O
and	O
asked	O
8	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
maker	O
and	O
was	O
distressed	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
6	O
s.	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
away	O
they	O
went	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
following	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
them	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
upon	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
proper	O
time	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
I	O
lent	O
them	O
10	O
s.	O
upon	O
20	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
and	O
desired	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
them	O
10	O
s.	O
more	O
on	O
20	O
pair	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
which	O
appeared	O
afterwards	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
so	O
seeing	O
the	O
stockings	O
advertised	O
,	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
trouble	O
,	O
therefore	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
stockings	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Pearce	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Moor	I-pers
came	O
one	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
stockings	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
at	O
night	O
she	O
came	O
again	O
and	O
brought	O
20	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
some	O
money	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
them	O
away	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
could	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
the	O
advertisement	O
I	O
was	O
affrighted	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
left	O
there	O
.	O
For	O
Mary	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Chapeman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mrs.	O
Ridge	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
was	O
extremely	O
good	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
she	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
your	O
service	O
?	O
Chapman	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
but	O
little	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
this	O
last	O
year	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dayle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
when	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
above	O
twice	O
this	O
last	O
half	O
year	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
once	O
lived	O
servant	O
in	O
York	O
Buildings	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
trusted	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
three	O
years	O
down	O
to	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
woman	O
.	O
All	O
four	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
122	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
29	O
s.	O
one	O
dimity	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
shag-green	O
case	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
linnen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
12	O
horn	O
buttons	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Wilkerson	I-pers
,	O
September	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Wilkerson	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Oak	I-place
in	I-place
North-street	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Red	I-place
Lion	I-place
Square	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
for	O
a	O
lodging	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
landlord	O
let	O
him	O
he	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
September	O
at	O
night	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
six	O
o'clock	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
box	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
some	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
from	O
other	O
parts	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
names	O
them	O
all	O
over	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Upon	O
missing	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
landlord	O
up	O
,	O
who	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
afterwards	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
another	O
account	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
paper	O
whereon	O
I	O
had	O
set	O
down	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
landlord	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
every	O
thing	O
mentioned	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dying	O
man	O
(	O
meaning	O
for	O
his	O
other	O
offence	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
do	O
as	O
I	O
pleased	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
come	O
another	O
day	O
he	O
'd	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
put	O
me	O
off	O
from	O
time	O
to	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
an	O
old	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
cost	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
value	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
at	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
At	O
6	O
l.	O
or	O
upwards	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Wilkerson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
day	O
of	O
September	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
for	O
a	O
jeweller	O
in	O
Turnstile	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
might	O
lodge	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
enquire	O
after	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
this	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
be	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
intending	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
enquire	O
after	O
his	O
character	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
directed	O
me	O
.	O
John	O
Cooper	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
to	O
work	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
as	O
a	O
jeweller	O
near	O
Turnstile	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
porter	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
enquired	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
lived	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
unhappy	O
young	O
lad	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
fortnight	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Scotland	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
mother	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
,	O
and	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
chose	O
him	O
out	O
from	O
among	O
15	O
or	O
16	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
rob	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dying	O
man	O
for	O
the	O
thing	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
be	O
easy	O
he	O
'd	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
come	O
again	O
any	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
read	O
over	O
the	O
paper	O
of	O
things-lost	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
all	O
except	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
the	O
box	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
John	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
called	O
me	O
up	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
boxes	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
cloaths	O
mentioned	O
,	O
Cooper	O
had	O
on	O
that	O
Sunday	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
up	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
jeweller	O
and	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Turnstile	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
want	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
in	O
Foster-lane	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
work	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Gravesend	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
five	O
nights	O
and	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Wilkerson	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
his	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
worsted	O
waistcoat	O
trimmed	O
with	O
silver	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hardwick	I-pers
,	O
one	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
nankeen	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hustenson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
July	O
31	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hustenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Queen-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
lodging	O
of	O
me	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
agreed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
lawyer	O
's	O
clerk	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
above	O
stairs	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
writing	O
immediately	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
crimson	O
waistcoat	O
laced	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
flashy	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
who	O
does	O
it	O
be	O
long	O
to	O
?	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
think	O
we	O
write	O
very	O
strangely	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
write	O
that	O
which	O
people	O
ca	O
n't	O
understand	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
we	O
are	O
doing	O
;	O
he	O
sealed	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
another	O
sheet	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
recommend	O
me	O
to	O
an	O
honest	O
person	O
that	O
can	O
carry	O
this	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
in	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
them	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
Morris	O
,	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Salisbury	O
Court	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
earn	O
that	O
shilling	O
myself	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
could	O
call	O
on	O
his	O
father	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
his	O
character	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
unclosed	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
rogue	O
has	O
sent	O
this	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
he	O
tells	O
me	O
he	O
is	O
your	O
clerk	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
rogue	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
be	O
what	O
he	O
will	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
home	O
again	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
absent	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
missed	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
made	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
chest	O
locked	O
before	O
?	O
Hustenson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
there	O
found	O
an	O
old	O
hat	O
and	O
mine	O
gone	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
said	O
waistcoat	O
before	O
mentioned	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
nankeen	O
breeches	O
;	O
the	O
worsted	O
waistcoat	O
trimm	O
'd	O
with	O
silver	O
belonged	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hardwick	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
after	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
prison	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
be	O
easy	O
and	O
make	O
no	O
disturbance	O
he	O
'd	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Hustenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
to	O
take	O
lodgings	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
opposite	O
the	O
stair-foot	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
his	O
cloaths	O
seemed	O
more	O
bulky	O
behind	O
than	O
they	O
did	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
nobody	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
till	O
my	O
husband	O
returned	O
,	O
having	O
fight	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
at	O
going	O
out	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
quire	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
a	O
stationer	O
lived	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
directed	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Holborn	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Randalph	I-pers
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
confessed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
when	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
meddled	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
These	O
people	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
wicked	O
design	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
life	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
25	O
s	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
third	O
indictment	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
laid	O
capital	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
that	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
515	O
,	O
in	O
alderman	O
Alsop	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
123	O
,	O
124	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hinds	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Pound	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomason	B-pers
Clegg	I-pers
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
iron	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
cock	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
beer	O
steins	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Whitacre	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
September	O
8	O
.	O
||	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
125	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joshua	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
brass	O
pottage	O
pot	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
cover	O
,	O
one	O
saucepan	O
,	O
one	O
stew-pan	O
,	O
one	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Holt	I-pers
,	O
January	O
9	O
.	O
||	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
126	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
January	O
14	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
127	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
not	O
surrendering	O
himself	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
order	O
in	O
council	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
evidence	O
produced	O
in	O
support	O
of	O
the	O
prosecution	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
issues	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
128	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Silvester	B-pers
Eager	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
spade	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
February	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
gardener	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
to	O
call	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
returning	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
this	O
spade	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
shed	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
cost	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
custody	O
at	O
his	O
brother-in-law	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
spade	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
129	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anthony	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
iron	O
gun	O
barrels	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
28	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
18	O
.	O
||	O
Joseph	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
a	O
gunsmith	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
a	O
workman	O
of	O
our	O
,	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
two	O
gun	O
barrels	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
gun-maker	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
Bond	B-place
street	I-place
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
They	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
pardon	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
journeyman	O
with	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Thomson	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
gunsmith	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
two	O
gun	O
barrels	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
agreed	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
his	O
money	O
I	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
maker	O
of	O
these	O
gun	O
barrels	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
know	O
they	O
are	O
of	O
your	O
make	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
who	O
for	O
?	O
Brian	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
trade	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
never	O
a	O
gun	O
barrel	O
maker	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Brian	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Griffin	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
these	O
barrels	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Griffin	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
short	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
these	O
two	O
barrels	O
worth	O
?	O
Griffin	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
28	O
s.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
missed	O
these	O
barrels	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
two	O
barrels	O
of	O
my	O
Brother	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
Spain	O
;	O
who	O
left	O
me	O
also	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
gun-stocks	O
;	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Griffin	O
the	O
stocks	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Griffin	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
offer	O
you	O
any	O
stocks	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
?	O
Griffin	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
for	O
us	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
130	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Blundell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty-six	O
knives	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
thirty-six	O
forks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Slathford	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
||	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cutler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Russel	B-place
street	I-place
Covent-Garden	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
some	O
,	O
he	O
pitched	O
upon	O
three	O
dozen	O
,	O
he	O
chose	O
one	O
dozen	O
of	O
china	O
handles	O
,	O
one	O
dozen	O
of	O
ebony	O
handles	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
dozen	O
of	O
pistol	O
ivory	O
handles	O
with	O
silver	O
ferrels	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
in	O
Duke-street	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
6	O
l.	O
17	O
s.	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
write	O
a	O
receipt	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
Williams	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
should	O
want	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
boy	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hichcock	I-pers
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
crazy	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bill	O
and	O
receipt	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
how	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
bilk	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
following	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
one	O
in	O
German	O
street	O
,	O
named	O
Gunston	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
dozen	O
of	O
ebony	O
ones	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Colling	I-pers
's	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
seek	O
after	O
Colling	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
Blundell	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
since	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
2	O
Chairmen	O
on	O
the	O
Southwark-side	O
near	O
Westminster-Bridge-foot	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
and	O
intended	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
dozen	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
person	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
had	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
three	O
dozen	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
sell	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
?	O
Dawson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
a	O
receipt	O
in	O
Sir	O
Robert	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
's	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
bill	O
and	O
receipt	O
,	O
but	O
suppose	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
should	O
be	O
at	O
dinner	O
,	O
may	O
the	O
boy	O
leave	O
them	O
for	O
an	O
hour	O
?	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
knives	O
into	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
expected	O
my	O
boy	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
Sir	O
Robert	O
William	O
's	O
liv	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hichcock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
these	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
suppose	O
his	O
master	O
should	O
be	O
at	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
want	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
left	O
for	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
or	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
objection	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
bid	O
me	O
not	O
deliver	O
the	O
bill	O
with	O
the	O
receipt	O
till	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
paid	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
long	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
that	O
kept	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
good	O
customer	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
come	O
so	O
far	O
for	O
the	O
knives	O
,	O
for	O
here	O
are	O
several	O
hard-ware	O
shops	O
nearer	O
;	O
coming	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
St.	O
James's-Park	O
,	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
knives	O
under	O
my	O
coat	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
stopped	O
by	O
the	O
centinels	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
knew	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
Park	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
hide	O
them	O
all	O
conveniently	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
dozen	O
to	O
put	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
the	O
dozens	O
did	O
you	O
deliver	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Hichcock	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
done	O
up	O
in	O
papers	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
a	O
chapel	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
much	O
in	O
a	O
fright	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
dinner	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
stay	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
himself	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
I	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
fool	O
to	O
stay	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
refused	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
try	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
wen	O
into	O
Duke	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
dit	O
not	O
push	O
,	O
but	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
caused	O
the	O
porter	O
for	O
not	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
ad	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
round	O
to	O
the	O
Pare	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
livery	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
push	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
tea	O
try	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
both	O
locked	O
out	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
,	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
proposed	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
an	O
she	O
could	O
just	O
by	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
I	O
consented	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
near	O
to	O
Story's-Gate	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
parlour	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
are	O
people	O
about	O
business	O
;	O
they	O
answered	O
our	O
business	O
will	O
soon	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
down	O
the	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
knives	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
as	O
well	O
lay	O
mine	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
impatient	O
for	O
the	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
landlord	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
it	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
drank	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
twice	O
,	O
I	O
proposed	O
going	O
just	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
the	O
gate	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
return	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Hichcock	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
his	O
Slathford	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
bill	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
The	O
China	O
handles	O
,	O
3	O
guineas	O
;	O
The	O
ebony	O
,	O
2	O
guineas	O
;	O
The	O
pistol	O
ivory	O
,	O
32	O
shillings	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
Evidence	O
continues	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gate	O
and	O
rang	O
for	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
came	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Hichcock	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
the	O
having	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
defraud	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
intended	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
year	O
's	O
time	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Sparling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cutler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
ivory	O
and	O
China	O
handles	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
James's-Market	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
them	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
three	O
dozen	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
for	O
some	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
dozen	O
?	O
Sparling	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
bought	O
any	O
china	O
handles	O
before	O
now	O
;	O
I	O
understand	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
what	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
says	O
;	O
had	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
ebony	O
ones	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
directly	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
are	O
marked	O
on	O
the	O
blades	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
accidentally	O
met	O
a	O
person	O
named	O
Edward	O
's	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
knew	O
in	O
North-Wales	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
order	O
from	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
3	O
dozen	O
of	O
genteel	O
knives	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
receive	O
some	O
money	O
in	O
town	O
and	O
was	O
disappointed	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
'd	O
return	O
it	O
me	O
from	O
Westchester	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
acquai	O
nted	O
with	O
any	O
cutler	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
credit	O
for	O
him	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
did	O
know	O
one	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
dealt	O
with	O
eight	O
or	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
try	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
wanted	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
wanted	O
some	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
dead	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
remember	O
'd	O
my	O
using	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
person	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
giving	O
me	O
credit	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
two	O
dozen	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
take	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
china	O
handles	O
I	O
refused	O
three	O
times	O
over	O
,	O
he	O
perswaded	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
might	O
put	O
them	O
up	O
if	O
he	O
pleased	O
,	O
we	O
agreed	O
for	O
price	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
parcelled	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
bill	O
to	O
;	O
but	O
first	O
of	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
mentioned	O
I	O
asked	O
this	O
Edwards	O
,	O
who	O
these	O
knives	O
were	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
one	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
some	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
near	O
Harding	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
seat	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
set	O
every	O
thing	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
bill	O
by	O
itself	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
must	O
they	O
be	O
cast	O
up	O
in	O
three	O
places	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
sum	O
cast	O
up	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
shall	O
I	O
write	O
a	O
receipt	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
not	O
write	O
a	O
receipt	O
?	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
money	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
paid	O
upon	O
the	O
delivery	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
write	O
it	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
torn	O
off	O
without	O
blemishing	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
wrote	O
the	O
receipt	O
two	O
inches	O
below	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
the	O
money	O
is	O
not	O
paid	O
directly	O
,	O
may	O
your	O
servant	O
leave	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
till	O
another	O
time	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
provided	O
the	O
receipt	O
be	O
torn	O
off	O
the	O
bill	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Spring-Gardens	O
,	O
the	O
servant	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
dozens	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
had	O
them	O
after	O
,	O
or	O
came	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
waited	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
just	O
within	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
further	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
sat	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
other	O
dozen	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
may	O
put	O
them	O
with	O
these	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
touch	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
we	O
said	O
the	O
space	O
of	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
proposed	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
matter	O
was	O
not	O
material	O
whether	O
I	O
waited	O
his	O
coming	O
back	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
inn	O
where	O
this	O
Edwards	O
said	O
he	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
people	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
certainly	O
mistaken	O
the	O
sign	O
,	O
I	O
inquired	O
at	O
several	O
other	O
inn	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
harm	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
knives	O
and	O
forks	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
disposing	O
of	O
them	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
was	O
to	O
wait	O
a	O
little	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
's	O
sight	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
raise	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Lamb	O
at	O
Lamb's-Conduit	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Foundling	O
Hospital	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
almost	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
been	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
chose	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
look	O
'd	O
after	O
my	O
affairs	O
till	O
my	O
return	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
known	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
that-time	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
thirty-nine	O
shillings	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
131	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
dimity	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
camblet	O
riding	O
hood	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
coat	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
velvet	O
hoods	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
one	O
child	O
's	O
corral	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Winifred	B-pers
Verney	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
132	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
iron	O
hammer	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Purcer	I-pers
,	O
Jan	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
133	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gamble	I-pers
,	O
January	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
134	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Blundall	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stickney	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
William	O
Stickney	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
young	O
men	O
very	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
thought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
picking	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
kennel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Stickney	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
fall	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
young	O
men	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
135	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Patrick	I-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
yard	O
of	O
alapeen	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
fustian	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
February	O
6	O
.	O
||	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
master	O
taylor	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
worked	O
journey-work	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
discharged	O
his	O
service	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
before	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
day	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
heard	O
somebody	O
on	O
his	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
hours	O
before	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
136	O
,	O
137	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Kite	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Hugh	B-pers
Field	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Bass	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
did	O
steal	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
watch	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
Stephen	O
Bass	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
(	O
name	O
Rose	O
Manning	O
)	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
(	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Bess	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
)	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
used	O
to	O
drink	O
beer	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
hot	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
hot	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
for	O
another	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
had	O
five	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
have	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
silver	O
,	O
so	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
hungry	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
victuals	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
or	O
fled	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
drinking	O
with	O
those	O
two	O
till	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
after	O
supper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
Bass	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Bass	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
actually	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
last	O
pot	O
of	O
hot	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
Summers	O
)	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
pots	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
?	O
Bass	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
judge	O
,	O
but	O
believe	O
about	O
15	O
or	O
16	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
pints	O
,	O
or	O
quarts	O
?	O
Bass	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
quarts	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
it	O
was	O
too	O
late	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Rose	O
Manning	O
's	O
bed	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
Hugh	B-pers
Field	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Cross-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
lodge	O
?	O
Bass	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Bow-street	O
,	O
Bloomsbury	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Rose	O
Manning	O
lodges	O
at	O
a	O
lodging-house	O
,	O
and	O
sells	O
fish	O
,	O
oranges	O
,	O
and	O
apples	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
about	O
20	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
rum	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
Golden	O
Boot	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
paid	O
for	O
your	O
eating	O
and	O
drinking	O
?	O
Bass	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
all	O
.	O
Rose	O
Manning	O
was	O
so	O
fuddled	O
that	O
the	O
waiter	O
of	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
lead	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
but	O
about	O
50	O
yards	O
to	O
walk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
walk	O
without	O
help	O
?	O
Bass	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
having	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
brought	O
,	O
fearing	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
dry	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
brought	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Summers	O
.	O
Rose	O
Manning	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
then	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Bass	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
instead	O
of	O
both	O
going	O
into	O
bed	O
we	O
were	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
that	O
we	O
were	O
neither	O
of	O
us	O
able	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
bed	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
our	O
cloaths	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
awaked	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
some	O
considerable	O
time	O
before	O
day-light	O
,	O
and	O
awaked	O
her	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
must	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
with	O
our	O
cloaths	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
undress	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
silver	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
two	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
three	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
I	O
