TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
26th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
CRISP	O
GASCOYNE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1753	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
CRISP	O
GASCOYNE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
DENNISON	O
*	O
,	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
BARON	O
SMYTH	O
+	O
,	O
WILLIAM	O
MORETON	O
++	O
.	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
which	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pascoe	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Daniel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bonnett	I-pers
,	O
Abel	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Fern	I-pers
,	O
Lockyer	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Driver	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Foddy	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Luttman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Timbrell	I-pers
,	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Vanderslop	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Perritt	I-pers
,	O
Morgan	B-pers
Gwynn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Glegg	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cobbett	I-pers
.	O
258	O
.	O
259	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	B-pers
Collard	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
,	O
June	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Limehouse	B-place
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
my	O
maid	O
was	O
serving	O
them	O
,	O
another	O
took	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
apron	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
round	O
Limehouse	O
church	O
,	O
they	O
dropt	O
the	O
sugar	O
in	O
the	O
churchyard	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
evidence	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
,	O
he	O
granted	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
Hall	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
where	O
Underwood	O
confest	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
sugar	O
.	O
-	O
Hall	O
.	O
One	O
Jack	O
went	O
to	O
Arnold	O
's	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
halfpennyworth	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
then	O
one	O
Ben	O
.	O
Ball	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Underwood	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
through	O
a	O
Street	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
run	O
through	O
the	O
church-yard	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
follow	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
servant	O
maid	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Arnold	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
sugar	O
loaf	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
robbing	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
swim	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Collard	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
six	O
of	O
us	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
mention	O
of	O
getting	O
money	O
in	O
any	O
unlawful	O
way	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
indeed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
way	O
of	O
living	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
spinner	O
.	O
Underwood	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
church-yard	O
.	O
Underwood	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
,	O
Collard	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
260	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
calve	O
skins	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
thirty-five	O
pieces	O
of	O
leather	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
and	I-pers
John	I-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
May	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
261	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Simon	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Mibous	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mibous	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Change-court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
May	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
Twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
coming	O
home	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
soldiers	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
distance	O
from	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
yards	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
met	O
me	O
and	O
took	O
fast	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
light	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lamp	O
burnt	O
bright	O
just	O
opposite	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
?	O
Mibous	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
bosom	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
arm	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
you	O
be	O
at	O
,	O
immediately	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
arm	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
thieves	O
and	O
watch	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
loosed	O
his	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
:	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursu	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
calling	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Mibous	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
any	O
weapon	O
?	O
Mibous	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
near	O
the	O
Savoy	O
steps	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
quitted	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
towards	O
Savoy-hill	O
:	O
at	O
the	O
alley	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
catch	O
me	O
now	O
if	O
you	O
can	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
soldier	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
:	O
then	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
threatening	O
language	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
kick	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
ran	O
into	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
barracks	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
corporal	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
who	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
two	O
other	O
soldiers	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
corporal	O
,	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Exeter-street	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
near	O
the	O
New-Church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
New	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
and	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
your	O
's	O
off	O
your	O
head	O
?	O
Mibous	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
soldiers	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
resisted	O
and	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hat	O
fell	O
off	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
cockade	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
an	O
area	O
,	O
which	O
hat	O
is	O
mine	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
describ	O
'd	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
particular	O
mark	O
in	O
the	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
mark	O
withinside	O
:	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
prison	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
hat	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woolfe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
corporal	O
in	O
the	O
Third	O
Regiment	O
on	O
the	O
Barrack-guard	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Second	O
Regiment	O
:	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Mibous	O
came	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
opening	O
it	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
by	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
down	O
towards	O
the	O
barracks	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
centinel	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
any	O
person	O
go	O
past	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Mibous	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
any	O
place	O
he	O
thought	O
proper	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
soldiers	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
of	O
ill	O
same	O
in	O
that	O
neighbourhood	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
no	O
body	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
going	O
up	O
Exeter-street	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
seeming	O
to	O
call	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
with	O
us	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
likewise	O
seen	O
Mibous	O
pursuing	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
:	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Mibous	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
till	O
I	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
so	O
a	O
soldier	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
us	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
refused	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
light	O
,	O
Mibous	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
hanger	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
soldiers	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
on	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
neck	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
murder	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
the	O
hat	O
fell	O
off	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
soldiers	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
soldier	O
took	O
up	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
on	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
steps	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
tossed	O
his	O
hat	O
off	O
into	O
an	O
Area	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
hand	O
at	O
liberty	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
conducted	O
him	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
we	O
concluded	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
area	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
this	O
hat	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
soldiers	O
got	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mibous	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
description	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mibous	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
hat	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
yours	O
?	O
Mibous	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
one	O
without	O
a	O
lace	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
mettle	O
button	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hobbins	I-pers
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
English	I-pers
,	O
the	O
two	O
soldiers	O
that	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
Woolfe	O
;	O
the	O
latter	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
at	O
an	O
alehouse	O
with	O
two	O
shoemakers	O
(	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
not	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
)	O
and	O
two	O
soldiers	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
parted	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
towards	O
Savoy	O
Hill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
and	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
parted	O
with	O
them	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
centinel	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
was	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
soldiers	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
there	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
it	O
the	O
prisoner	O
got	O
from	O
the	O
centinel	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
in	O
Exeter-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
struggle	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
hat	O
fell	O
off	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
observed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
too	O
good	O
for	O
a	O
regimental	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cockade	O
being	O
loose	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
area	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
were	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
toss	O
it	O
from	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
this	O
hat	O
produced	O
here	O
,	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
;	O
my	O
hat	O
had	O
a	O
lace	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
these	O
soldiers	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
returned	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Eagen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Eagen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
14	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
town	O
in	O
Ireland	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Malouday	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
by	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
262	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Martha	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Hoadman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
copper	O
stew	O
pan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
two	O
stone	O
flower	O
pots	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
knee	O
bucks	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
May	O
18	O
++	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Swallow-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
day	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
my	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
hid	O
herself	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
I	O
stept	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
here	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
stept	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
to	O
prevent	O
any	O
body	O
from	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
coors	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
enquired	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
waiting	O
for	O
her	O
below	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
her	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
down	O
John	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
stopt	O
her	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
with	O
things	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
on	O
searching	O
her	O
further	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
stew	O
pan	O
tied	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
your	O
own	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
All	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
have	O
mentioned	O
were	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
.	O
John	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
above	O
stairs	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
bundles	O
upon	O
the	O
top	O
stair	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
open	O
the	O
bundles	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
things	O
before	O
mentioned	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
stew	O
pan	O
which	O
dropt	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
defence	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
263	O
.	O
264	O
.	O
265	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
David	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Aukels	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Benian	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
stick	O
,	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Milbourn	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
May	O
31	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
There	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
any	O
intention	O
to	O
rob	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
acquited	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
them	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
only	O
.	O
266	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
13	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
thimble	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
recognizance	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
267	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Andrew	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloath	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
stuff	O
damask	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
cloath	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
,	O
June	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
night	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
cloath	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
lying	O
off	O
New	B-place
Crane	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
parish	I-place
of	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
again	O
at	O
Dennis	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
's	O
,	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
belong	O
to	O
your	O
vessel	O
?	O
Beard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
further	O
account	O
.	O
Dennis	B-pers
Murphey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
coat	O
and	O
2	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hermitage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
directly	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cabin	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
cast	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
from	O
Dever	O
in	O
a	O
Gravesend	O
boat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
at	O
New	O
Crane	O
Stairs	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
asleep	O
;	O
I	O
awaked	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
myself	O
very	O
cold	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
these	O
cloaths	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
cask	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
about	O
till	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
not	O
being	O
laid	O
capital	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
that	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
268	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
scythes	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
May	O
30	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
269	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Pursley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pail	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
iron	O
pot	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
May	O
26	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
270	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Christophers	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
promissory	O
note	O
under	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
bearing	O
date	O
April	O
29	O
,	O
1751	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
l.	O
by	O
which	O
note	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
promised	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
50	O
l.	O
six	O
months	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1751	O
,	O
William	O
Hulls	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
hood	O
and	O
judgment	O
of	O
one	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
sign	O
to	O
Hays	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
owe	O
him	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
sign	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
arrest	O
me	O
for	O
16	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
goal	O
.	O
I	O
consulted	O
with	O
Christophers	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
his	O
advice	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
John	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
I	O
should	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
bond	O
and	O
judgment	O
for	O
100	O
l.	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
with	O
the	O
bond	O
and	O
judgment	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
mortgage	O
upon	O
my	O
estate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
this	O
Hays	O
?	O
Garret	O
.	O
He	O
keeps	O
the	O
earl	O
of	O
Stair	O
's	O
head	O
in	O
Vine-street	O
.	O
In	O
July	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
note	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
which	O
Hays	O
gave	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
my	O
order	O
,	O
50	O
l.	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
me	O
April	O
29	O
,	O
1751	O
,	O
payable	O
6	O
months	O
after	O
date	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
missed	O
it	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Garret	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Hays	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
50	O
l.	O
note	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
what	O
signifies	O
50	O
l.	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
I.	O
Ann	O
Boon	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
September	O
51	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
by	O
poor	O
Garret	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
bond	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
given	O
to	O
Hays	O
from	O
Garret	O
.	O
Hays	O
gave	O
to	O
Garret	O
a	O
promissory	O
note	O
for	O
50	O
l.	O
that	O
as	O
Hays	O
could	O
get	O
nothing	O
on	O
the	O
bond	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
note	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
lay	O
together	O
)	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Hays	O
,	O
and	O
Hays	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
presence	O
,	O
flung	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
fire	O
and	O
destroy	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
getting	O
all	O
Garret	O
's	O
estate	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
60	O
or	O
70	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
conversation	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Boon	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Chandos-street	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
by	O
at	O
this	O
conversation	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Boon	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
William	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bohus	I-pers
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
.	O
On	O
December	O
,	O
1751	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
to	O
the	O
evidence	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
excuse	O
him	O
some	O
little	O
incumbrance	O
(	O
what	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
justly	O
say	O
)	O
he	O
'd	O
open	O
to	O
her	O
the	O
whole	O
scene	O
of	O
villainy	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
this	O
50	O
l.	O
note	O
out	O
of	O
Garret	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
delivering	O
it	O
to	O
Hays	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bohus	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
above	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
neither	O
the	O
month	O
nor	O
year	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Hays	O
and	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Boon	O
have	O
both	O
been	O
at	O
law	O
for	O
the	O
fellow	O
's	O
estate	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
serve	O
their	O
ends	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
am	O
now	O
prosecuted	O
out	O
of	O
spight	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Whitewood	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
near	O
London-Wall	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
they	O
behaved	O
like	O
brothers	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
each	O
other	O
so	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
got	O
among	O
a	O
bad	O
set	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
but	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
This	O
very	O
woman	O
(	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Boon	O
)	O
once	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
friend	O
,	O
about	O
making	O
up	O
an	O
affair	O
of	O
a	O
bastard	O
child	O
that	O
was	O
laid	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
she	O
wants	O
to	O
hang	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
drinking	O
together	O
often	O
since	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
call	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
in	O
good	O
friendship	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Olsinbrook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
facing	O
Cripplegate	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
Hays	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
52	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
like	O
brothers	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
Garret	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
note	O
or	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Olsinbrook	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'd	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
untold	O
gold	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
near	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
and	O
Garret	O
together	O
an	O
hundred	O
times	O
since	O
the	O
year	O
51	O
in	O
good	O
friendship	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
also	O
know	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
together	O
since	O
the	O
year	O
51	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
Hays	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
they	O
lodged	O
together	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
appeared	O
very	O
friendly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
them	O
talk	O
about	O
the	O
note	O
?	O
Bourne	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
near	O
16	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hays	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
together	O
several	O
times	O
since	O
the	O
year	O
51	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
Garret	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Greenwood	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
they	O
always	O
appeared	O
like	O
brothers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
Mr.	O
Hays	O
live	O
?	O
Greenwood	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Vine-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Round-Court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Woodruff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Man-in-the-Moon	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
once	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
his	O
leaving	O
me	O
was	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
employment	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wadsworth	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Yowel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
very	O
well	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
behaved	O
exceeding	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
untold	O
gold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
opinion	O
of	O
him	O
after	O
hearing	O
what	O
has	O
has	O
been	O
said	O
here	O
?	O
Wadsworth	O
.	O
I	O
now	O
have	O
the	O
same	O
opinion	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
271	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Corbee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
did	O
put	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
,	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
thread	O
purse	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
one	O
Spanish	O
dollar	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
shilling	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
Feb.	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Stubbs	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
,	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
closet-keeper	O
,	O
his	O
daughter	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Buckmire	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
playhouse	O
,	O
coming	O
home	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
through	O
the	O
field	O
leading	O
to	O
Chelsea	B-place
,	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
past	O
and	O
went	O
before	O
us	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
narrow	O
lane	O
they	O
turned	O
back	O
upon	O
us	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
hanger	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
his	O
money	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
so	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
our	O
money	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Buckmire	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
leading	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
had	O
a	O
cut-and-thrust	O
sword	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Buckmire	O
,	O
he	O
pointed	O
out	O
the	O
sword	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
an	O
inch	O
further	O
he	O
'd	O
run	O
me	O
through	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
no	O
further	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Buckmire	O
,	O
he	O
catch	O
'd	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
then	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
my	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
white	O
net	O
purse	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
went	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
three	O
half	O
crowns	O
,	O
a	O
queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
pocket	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
small	O
pocket	O
pieces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
that	O
person	O
robb	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
Stubbs	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
3	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taking	O
Mr.	O
Hart	O
's	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
down	O
on	O
one	O
knee	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Stubbs	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
dress	O
was	O
I	O
in	O
?	O
Stubbs	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
flapp	O
'd	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
brownish	O
horseman	O
's	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
soldiers	O
cloaths	O
underneath	O
as	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
red	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Stubbs	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
as	O
light	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
moon	O
shine	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
examination	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
griev	O
'd	O
much	O
after	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
rings	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
valued	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
with	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
feared	O
the	O
consequence	O
would	O
be	O
bad	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
get	O
you	O
the	O
ring	O
again	O
.	O
Since	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
accomplice	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
evidence	O
)	O
sent	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
mother-in-law	O
's	O
name	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
date	O
she	O
died	O
on	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
.	O
Corbee	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
Westminster	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
to	O
Hide-Park	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
somebody	O
,	O
we	O
staid	O
there	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
and	O
saw	O
nobody	O
,	O
but	O
going	O
under	O
the	O
wall	O
we	O
saw	O
these	O
gentlemen	O
coming	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
5-fields	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
followed	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Ayres	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
we	O
passed	O
them	O
some	O
way	O
and	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
there	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Ayres	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
3	O
gentlemen	O
and	O
2	O
women	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stopp	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
a	O
net	O
purse	O
,	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
a	O
Spanish	O
dollar	O
,	O
a	O
queen	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
two	O
silver	O
groats	O
and	O
about	O
16	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
some	O
silver	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
,	O
but	O
how	O
much	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
buckles	O
also	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
fields	O
making	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
our	O
way	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
shar	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
one	O
ring	O
to	O
pawn	O
by	O
his	O
washer-woman	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
share	O
?	O
Ayres	O
.	O
My	O
share	O
came	O
to	O
about	O
15	O
s.	O
with	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
(	O
he	O
looks	O
at	O
the	O
ring	O
produced	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
rings	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
mourning	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
thread	O
purse	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
Stubbs	O
.	O
This	O
ring	O
was	O
pawned	O
for	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
other	O
ring	O
he	O
sold	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
where	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
whom	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Peal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Durham	O
with	O
some	O
others	O
on	O
the	O
information	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
Ayres	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
by	O
shipping	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
of	O
this	O
very	O
robbery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
confess	O
this	O
?	O
Peal	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
5	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Sunday	O
,	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
us	O
what	O
Ayres	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
some	O
robberies	O
,	O
but	O
Ayres	O
had	O
not	O
mentioned	O
this	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
we	O
robb	O
'd	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
in	O
the	O
5	O
fields	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
search	O
Ayres	O
's	O
wife	O
we	O
should	O
find	O
a	O
white	O
net	O
purse	O
with	O
a	O
pocket	O
piece	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
The	O
purse	O
produced	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
purse	O
?	O
Ayres	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
purse	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Corbee	O
had	O
it	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
mentioned	O
this	O
robbery	O
first	O
,	O
you	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
ship	O
?	O
Peal	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
we	O
there	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
Peal	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
robberies	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
reason	O
of	O
my	O
mentioning	O
that	O
robbery	O
was	O
they	O
said	O
Ayres	O
was	O
not	O
submitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
receive	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
mercy	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
clear	O
my	O
conscience	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Ayres	O
were	O
both	O
soldiers	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
their	O
trial	O
No	O
69	O
,	O
70	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
272	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Ayliff	I-pers
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
.	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
paper	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
stock	O
one	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
stopp	O
'd	O
between	O
Pancras	B-place
and	O
the	O
Turnpike	B-place
about	O
Nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
thing	O
I	O
heard	O
was	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
snapping	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
Then	O
came	O
up	O
one	O
man	O
and	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
near	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
in	O
rifling	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
paper	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
my	O
stock	O
and	O
stock-buckle	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
all	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
to	O
distinguish	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
their	O
faces	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but-one	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
brother	O
here	O
?	O
Clifton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
a	O
chaise	O
you	O
drove	O
yourselves	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
it	O
drove	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
?	O
Clifton	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
four-wheel	O
chaise	O
and	O
a	O
coachman	O
to	O
drive	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
that	O
snapping	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
the	O
coachman	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
patience	O
I	O
'll	O
make	O
my	O
horses	O
stand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
person	O
stand	O
at	O
the	O
horses	O
heads	O
?	O
Clifton	B-pers
It	I-pers
was	O
so	O
dark	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
what	O
there	O
were	O
:	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
threaten	O
you	O
or	O
demand	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Clifton	O
.	O
They	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
and	O
swore	O
they	O
would	O
mains	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
deliver	O
our	O
watches	O
and	O
:	O
the	O
evidence	O
Ayres	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
stock	O
buckle	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
were	O
pawned	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
sent	O
he	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
light	O
enough	O
to	O
discern	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
their	O
own	O
hair	O
or	O
wigs	O
?	O
Clifton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
observed	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
distinguish	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
their	O
cloaths	O
?	O
Clifton	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
ch	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
less	O
man	O
than	O
Ayres	O
the	O
evidence	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Corbee	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
crossing	O
the	O
fields	O
we	O
met	O
Ayliff	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
naked	O
knife	O
and	O
a	O
broomstick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
bad	O
luck	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
together	O
he	O
dared	O
not	O
attack	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
standing	O
together	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
four-wheel	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
Corbee	O
took	O
a	O
pistol	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Ayres	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
above	O
Pancras	O
Church-yard	O
in	O
the	O
hollow	O
way	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
me	O
rifle	O
it	O
.	O
Ayliff	O
went	O
first	O
by	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
hit	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
lifted	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
stand	O
still	O
he	O
'd	O
shoot	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
strike	O
him	O
across	O
the	O
nose	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
C	O
lifton	O
for	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
me	O
half-a-crown	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
got	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
stock	O
and	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
men	O
were	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
chaise	O
?	O
Ayees	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
stock	O
and	O
stock	O
buckle	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
Ayliff	O
pull	O
'd	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
chaise	O
by	O
my	O
heels	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
thought	O
they	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
coming	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
a-cross	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
Ayliff	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
over	O
a	O
bank	O
,	O
but	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pistol	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
shot	O
Corbee	O
,	O
but	O
stepping	O
back	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
harm	O
done	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Holloway	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
somebody	O
,	O
but	O
met	O
with	O
none	O
to	O
rob	O
:	O
Ayliff	O
had	O
one	O
shilling	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
us	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
?	O
Ayres	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
six	O
shillings	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
Corbee	O
sent	O
the	O
stock-buckles	O
to	O
pawn	O
by	O
his	O
washer-woman	O
,	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Alice	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
of	O
them	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
Ayliff	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
coach	O
before	O
the	O
horse	O
bit	O
him	O
?	O
Ayres	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
bid	O
the	O
coachman	O
stop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
intention	O
in	O
stopping	O
them	O
?	O
Ayres	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
all	O
dispose	O
of	O
yourselves	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
horses	O
?	O
Ayres	O
.	O
One	O
went	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
whether	O
Corbee	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
pistol	O
snapp	O
'd	O
?	O
Ayres	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
a	O
blow	O
cross	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
nose	O
:	O
the	O
stock-buckle	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
we	O
had	O
six-pence	O
each	O
of	O
that	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
hats	O
Corbee	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
from	O
off	O
his	O
head	O
in	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
commit	O
a	O
robbery	O
near	O
Cranbury	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
sold	O
:	O
in	O
our	O
sharing	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
other	O
hat	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
Corbee	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
half-crown	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
Corbee	O
and	O
you	O
meet	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Ayres	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
first	O
at	O
a	O
publick-house	O
in	O
Pye-street	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
pistol	O
's	O
going	O
off	O
the	O
flint	O
fell	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shilling	O
that	O
Ayliff	O
had	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
screw	O
it	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
bent	O
in	O
so	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Speller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
having	O
been	O
attack	O
'd	O
and	O
shot	O
at	O
by	O
Ayres	O
and	O
Corbee	O
near	O
Cranbury	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
in	O
the	O
struggle	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
lost	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
keepers	O
there	O
they	O
were	O
soldiers	O
:	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
sure	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
two	O
soldiers	O
that	O
were	O
tried	O
and	O
acquitted	O
in	O
January	O
sessions	O
last	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
and	O
took	O
Ayres	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
hat	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
hat	O
the	O
person	O
had	O
on	O
that	O
shot	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clifton	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
hat	O
?	O
Clifton	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
hat	O
that	O
he	O
lost	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Ayres	O
.	O
The	O
hat	O
we	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
gentleman	O
had	O
a	O
cockade	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Clifton	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
brother	O
an	O
officer	O
in	O
the	O
army	O
?	O
Clifton	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
cockade	O
on	O
his	O
hat	O
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
hat	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
cockade	O
.	O
Speller	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
on	O
Easter-Tuesday	O
,	O
Ayliff	O
was	O
under	O
examination	O
:	O
the	O
justice	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
followed	O
that	O
course	O
of	O
life	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
answered	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
robbing	O
a	O
four-wheel	O
chaise	O
near	O
Pancras-Wash	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
horse	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
bit	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
pistol	O
went	O
off	O
going	O
over	O
a	O
bank	O
,	O
by	O
accident	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
shilling	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
after	O
some	O
talk	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
Clerk	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
signing	O
the	O
confession	O
,	O
Mind	O
what	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
that	O
may	O
be	O
hurtful	O
to	O
you	O
on	O
your	O
trial	O
:	O
then	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
evidence	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
sign	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Ayliff	O
confess	O
at	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
mentioned	O
several	O
robberies	O
besides	O
this	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
publick-house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
horse	O
bit	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
in	O
getting	O
over	O
a	O
bank	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
pistol	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Philipson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
He	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
confession	O
of	O
Ayliff	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Peal	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
being	O
there	O
also	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
.	O
Corbee	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
Ayres	O
has	O
sworn	O
very	O
falsely	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
buckles	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dying	O
man	O
.	O
Ayliff	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
time	O
that	O
they	O
say	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Maidenhead	O
in	O
Berkshire	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
christening	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
children	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
with	O
Ayres	O
but	O
once	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
Hollaway	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
me	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
coming	O
back	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
in	O
robbing	O
a	O
waggon	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
agree	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
been	O
better	O
for	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
drunk	O
with	O
him	O
above	O
five	O
times	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
273	O
,	O
274	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
and	I-pers
Catharine	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
and	O
Catharine	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
one	O
pillow	O
bier	O
,	O
one	O
pewter	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Both	O
Acq	O
.	O
275	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Davley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
iron	O
bar	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
checks	O
to	O
a	O
grate	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Agate	I-pers
,	O
May	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
276	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Cypher	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Cypherwood	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Cypherroot	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kew	I-pers
,	O
her	O
former	O
husband	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
,	O
Aug.	O
27	O
,	O
1727	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
200.	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
paper	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
277	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Harley	I-pers
,	O
May	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
278	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
forty-two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Targoose	I-pers
.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	O
Targoose	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Whittington-and-Cat	B-place
in	I-place
White-Chapel	I-place
,	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lie	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
I	O
forgot	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
March	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Hearing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
sold	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
)	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
he	O
that	O
took	O
mine	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Wapping	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
watch	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
here	O
?	O
Targoose	O
.	O
Not	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
:	O
upon	O
my	O
taxing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Targoose	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
joyner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
lodged	O
any	O
time	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Targoose	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
hear	O
this	O
confession	O
?	O
Targoose	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Billington	I-pers
by	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Billington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
Whettington-and-Cat	O
the	O
chamber	O
door	O
standing	O
open	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
behave	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
279	O
,	O
280	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Onyon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Esther	B-pers
Onyon	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
brass	O
bottoms	O
of	O
warming	O
pans	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
four	O
brass	O
covers	O
for	O
warming	O
pans	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
May	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Pitman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brazier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Mulberry-court	B-place
near	I-place
Moore-fields	I-place
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Onyon	I-pers
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
examin	O
'd	O
all	O
these	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Lamb-alley	O
,	O
others	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Hone	O
who	O
had	O
stopp	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
missed	O
them	O
where	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
large	O
quantity	O
together	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
found	O
the	O
four	O
covers	O
and	O
sack	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
lad	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
mother	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
one	O
Emmerton	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Emmerton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Beach	O
Lane	O
,	O
I	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
brass	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
some	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
fourteen	O
bottoms	O
for	O
warming-pans	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
per	O
pound	O
?	O
M.	O
Emmerton	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
9	O
d.	O
per	O
pound	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
brass	O
worth	O
per	O
pound	O
?	O
Pittman	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
buy	O
500	O
pounds	O
weight	O
together	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
have	O
it	O
under	O
thirteen-pence	O
halfpenny	O
per	O
pound	O
.	O
M.	O
Emmerton	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
usual	O
price	O
I	O
give	O
for	O
old	O
brass	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
were	O
doubled	O
up	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ask	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
M.	O
Emmerton	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
me	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
?	O
M.	O
Emmerton	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
brazier	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
own	O
affairs	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
brass	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
?	O
M.	O
Emmerton	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
where	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
M.	O
Emmerton	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
5	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
in	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
her	O
the	O
remainder	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
brass	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hone	O
,	O
who	O
I	O
sell	O
mettal	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Onyon	I-pers
?	O
M.	O
Emmerton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
the	O
brass	O
was	O
all	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
founder	O
,	O
and	O
buy	O
brass	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
Emmerton	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
we	O
call	O
scurff	O
brass	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
chippings	O
of	O
brass	O
that	O
is	O
trimm	O
'd	O
off	O
round	O
the	O
edges	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
might	O
perhaps	O
come	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
;	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
expected	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
accordingly	O
on	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'ennight	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
with	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
night	O
these	O
plates	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
determined	O
,	O
if	O
possible	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
mentioning	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
whose	O
husband	O
happened	O
to	O
mention	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pitman	O
it	O
was	O
discover	O
'd	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pitman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
these	O
14	O
bottoms	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
woman	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Emmerton	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
knowing	O
her	O
son	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wale	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Thomas	B-pers
Onyon	I-pers
confess	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
fourteen	O
brass	O
bottoms	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
mother	O
had	O
inveigled	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Pitman	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
your	O
apprentice	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Pitman	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
20th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
age	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Onyon	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
brass	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
neither	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Onyon	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
M.	O
Emmerton	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
son	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
tops	O
of	O
warming	O
pans	O
which	O
he	O
designed	O
to	O
chase	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
carry	O
them	O
home	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
box	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Pitman	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
box	O
lock	O
'd	O
at	O
Onyon	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
tops	O
?	O
Pitman	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
broke	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
box	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
the	O
key	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
their	O
Character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Town	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
woman	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
employed	O
her	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
quilting	O
way	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
or	O
the	O
boy	O
wrong	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Twitchel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Rumley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Thomas	B-pers
Onyon	I-pers
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
boy	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
James	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
dealt	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Rumley	O
when	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
errand	O
boy	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
James	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
errand-boy	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
opinion	O
of	O
his	O
fidelity	O
.	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
apprentice	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
when	O
the	O
boy	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
errand-boy	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
extremely	O
well	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
saw	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
281	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hand	O
saw	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pond	I-pers
.	O
April	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Pond	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
after	O
Easter	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
saw	O
,	O
producing	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brewin	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Pond	O
's	O
apprentice	O
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
this	O
saw	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
following	O
I	O
wanted	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
:	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
he	O
returned	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
advertis	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Mead	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brewin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hosiar-lane	O
,	O
Snow-hill	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
saw	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
saw	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
longer	O
than	O
ordinary	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
choose	O
to	O
stoop	O
at	O
his	O
work	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
three	O
shillings	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Some	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
advertisement	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
answered	O
the	O
descriptions	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pond	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
in	O
case	O
the	O
prisoner	O
should	O
come	O
again	O
to	O
secure	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
another	O
saw	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
I	O
jumped	O
over	O
the	O
compter	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Coming	O
up	O
Coleman-street	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
will	O
you	O
buy	O
this	O
saw	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
one	O
of	O
White	O
's	O
make	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
4	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
Half-a-crown	O
and	O
three	O
half-pence	O
;	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
befor	O
e	O
No	O
.	O
496.	O
in	O
alderman	O
Blachford	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
282	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Cornhill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman-baker	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Southwark	O
,	O
on	O
Friday	O
was	O
se'ennight	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Exchange	B-place
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
there	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
had	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
hanging	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
hold	O
on	O
it	O
and	O
pull	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
lord-mayor	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
and	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Preston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman-baker	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
four	O
shillings	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
before	O
for	O
robbing	O
a	O
pack-horse	O
on	O
Finchley	O
Common	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
425	O
,	O
426	O
,	O
427	O
,	O
428	O
,	O
429	O
and	O
430.	O
in	O
alderman	O
Winterbottom	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
283	O
,	O
284	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Perkinson	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Plastow	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
gartering	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Daniel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
*	O
Daniel	O
Kennedy	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Little	B-place
Tower	I-place
hill	I-place
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
victualling	O
office	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
slop	O
and	O
hosier	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
as	O
they	O
hung	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
window	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Burrier	I-pers
.	O
Betwixt	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
victualling-office	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Perkinson	I-pers
went	O
and	O
lifted	O
up	O
a	O
sash	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Carlow	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
which	O
were	O
eight	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
for	O
your	O
share	O
?	O
Burrier	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
20	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
and	O
they	O
meet	O
first	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Burrier	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
them	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Perkinson	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
me	O
first	O
?	O
Burrier	O
.	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
White	O
Chapel	O
,	O
where	O
Perkinson	O
worked	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
together	O
often	O
,	O
picking	O
of	O
pockets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Burrier	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
Mistress	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
opposite	O
to	O
Kennedy	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
three	O
boys	O
together	O
down	O
from	O
towards	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
;	O
they	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
of	O
Kennedy	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Kennedy	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
servant	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
catch	O
'd	O
Plastow	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Richards	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
assist	O
in	O
finding	O
the	O
others	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
the	O
slip	O
.	O
Perkinson	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Plastow	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
but	O
twelve	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
had	O
neither	O
father	O
or	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
Both	O
Acq	O
.	O
285	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silk	O
gowns	O
,	O
two	O
quilted	O
petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
capuchin	O
,	O
two	O
linnen	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
large	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
six	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
strainer	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
dimitty	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
two	O
linnen	O
frocks	O
,	O
five	O
linnen	O
children	O
's	O
coats	O
,	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
sattin	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
linnen	O
caps	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Oxon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
.	O
May	O
20	O
*	O
Rhodam	B-pers
Oxon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
William	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
hosier	O
and	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
White-chapel	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
one	O
week	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
dinner	O
at	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
returned	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
put	O
our	O
boy	O
in	O
backward	O
,	O
who	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
not	O
been	O
double	O
lock	O
'd	O
:	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
half	O
before	O
we	O
missed	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
searching	O
about	O
afterwards	O
we	O
found	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
not	O
mentioned	O
,	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
She	O
names	O
them	O
over	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
,	O
we	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
we	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
William	O
Reice	O
a	O
falseman	O
in	O
Tothill	O
fields	O
,	O
who	O
upon	O
seeing	O
the	O
advertisement	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
Here	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
capuchin	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
blue	O
sattin	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
I	O
found	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
lodgings	O
where	O
she	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
pink	O
silk	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
three	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
tongs	O
,	O
strainer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
3	O
little	O
children	O
's	O
shirts	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
remaining	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
sattin	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
silversmiths	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
three	O
tea-spoons	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
one	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Birkingham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
and	O
live	O
near	O
Charing-cross	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
large	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
tea	O
spoons	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
the	O
23rd	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
appearing	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
clean	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Tomb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
Parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
a	O
warrant	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
Lediard	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
brown	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
also	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
broker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
the	O
plate	O
at	O
the	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
my	O
husband	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
that	O
Sunday	O
and	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
be	O
quiet	O
he	O
'd	O
knock	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
pawn	O
them	O
to	O
raise	O
money	O
to	O
give	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
that	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
cozen	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
character	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
286	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Rex	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Rix	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
six	O
linnen	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
five	O
caps	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
three	O
other	O
petticoats	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
David	O
.	O
*	O
David	O
Thomas	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
I	O
went	O
to-bed	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
under	O
my	O
compter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
upwards	O
of	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
half-pence	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
till	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
cellar	O
window	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
mentioned	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Godson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
a	O
draught	O
of	O
beer	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Pear-tree	O
alley	O
,	O
right	O
against	O
the	O
gun	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
some	O
half-pence	O
scatter	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
friend	O
you	O
are	O
full	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
help	O
you	O
to	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
himself	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
his	O
voice	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lately	O
drawn	O
beer	O
at	O
the	O
black	O
dog	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Godson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
distance	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
this	O
money	O
to	O
his	O
mistress	O
's	O
summer-house	O
at	O
Hogsdon	O
,	O
there	O
lay	O
a	O
bundle	O
by	O
him	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Parrot	O
in	O
the	O
Land	O
of	O
Promise	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
see	O
where	O
you	O
go	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
till	O
we	O
pass	O
'd	O
the	O
Parrot	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
committed	O
a	O
robbery	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
indeed	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
near	O
the	O
Carlisle	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
clock	O
strike	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
bundle	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Rawlinson	O
Armstrong	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
twelve	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
down	O
to	O
this	O
present	O
time	O
?	O
Armstrong	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
this	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
John	B-pers
Widson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
these	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
5	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
sewing	O
thread	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bominear	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Abraham	O
.	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
Abraham	B-pers
Bominear	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Spittal	B-place
fields	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
sewing	O
thread	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
back	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Bominear	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
about	O
seven	O
days	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Bominear	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Bominear	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
our	O
people	O
saw	O
him	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
warehouse	O
backwards	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Bominear	O
.	O
He	O
formerly	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
seven	O
months	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cash	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
affair	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
having	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
months	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
lost	O
goods	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
sewing	O
thread	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
him	O
any	O
promise	O
previous	O
to	O
this	O
confession	O
?	O
Cash	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
on	O
Mr.	O
Bominear	O
's	O
affair	O
?	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
make	O
this	O
confession	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
him	O
any	O
promise	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
where	O
he	O
sold	O
it	O
(	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
receiver	O
)	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
confessed	O
before	O
justice	O
Gower	O
,	O
he	O
bound	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
287	O
,	O
288	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
widow	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
May	O
4	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bricklayer	B-place
's	I-place
Arms	I-place
in	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
road	I-place
,	O
and	O
hired	O
Anne	O
Ellis	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
May	O
9	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
rooms	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
about	O
six	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
necessary	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
people	O
in	O
our	O
yard	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
drawer	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
some	O
guineas	O
missing	O
(	O
she	O
is	O
sick	O
at	O
home	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
attend	O
)	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
her	O
mother	O
lodged	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
my	O
servant	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
but	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Six	O
or	O
7	O
of	O
us	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
her	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
a	O
neighbour	O
accidentally	O
seeing	O
her	O
getting	O
into	O
the	O
Barnet	O
stage	O
coach	O
came	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
took	O
horses	O
,	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
Whetstone	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
carried	O
,	O
them	O
to	O
Barnet	O
,	O
and	O
tax	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
directly	O
owned	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
forced	O
open	O
the	O
drawer	O
with	O
an	O
old	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
14	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
safely	O
say	O
there	O
were	O
17	O
missing	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
six	O
behind	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
six	O
guineas	O
in	O
gold	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
woman	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
daughter	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
They	O
had	O
bought	O
themselves	O
cloaths	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
being	O
now	O
both	O
very	O
tight	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
very	O
ragged	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
into	O
Bedfordshire	O
to	O
the	O
mother	O
's	O
sister	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
?	O
Hudson	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
7	O
s.	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
girt	O
said	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
woman	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
what	O
my	O
daughter	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
John	O
Collier	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hudson	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
We	O
overtook	O
them	O
about	O
,	O
3	O
miles	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
,	O
Barnet	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
daughter	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
base	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
master	O
of	O
17	O
or	O
18	O
guineas	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
14	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Barnet	O
before	O
justice	O
Haswell	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
a	O
key	O
in	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
under	O
drawer	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
she	O
forc	O
'd	O
open	O
the	O
drawer	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
14	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
devil	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
her	O
head	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
coach	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
She	O
deliver	O
'd	O
7	O
s.	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
money	O
her	O
daughter	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
officer	O
that	O
lives	O
at	O
Barnet	O
has	O
got	O
the	O
cloaths	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
bought	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Anne	O
Ellis	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
the	O
lock	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
7	O
s.	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
Acquitted	I-pers
.	O
289	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Birt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
snuff	O
box	O
value	O
7	O
s	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buttons	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
;	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
May	O
31	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cow	B-place
Cross	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
had	O
for	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buck	O
skin	O
breeches	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
in	O
his	O
bed	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
two	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
lock	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
lodger	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
him	O
,	O
so	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Chamberlain	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
lock	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
sides	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
He	O
delivered	O
them	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
rent	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
of	O
mine	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
also	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
their	O
respective	O
owners	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Briscodine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
charge	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
I	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
also	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
goods	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
290	O
,	O
291	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Burgin	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
to	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
103	O
yards	O
of	O
ribband	O
.	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
May	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Russel	B-place
street	I-place
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
hats	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
the	O
looks	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
some	O
ribbands	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
boxes	O
with	O
some	O
;	O
Evans	O
bought	O
a	O
little	O
remnant	O
for	O
her	O
child	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
Perkins	O
took	O
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
take	O
4	O
pieces	O
of	O
coloured	O
ribband	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
shall	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
hereafter	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
,	O
with	O
black	O
ribbands	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
way	O
.	O
Perkins	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
have	O
no	O
hats	O
,	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
some	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
fit	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
'll	O
take	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
fetched	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
more	O
in	O
that	O
case	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
chose	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
black	O
ribband	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
this	O
black	O
ribband	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
moving	O
a	O
small	O
curtain	O
could	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
this	O
ribband	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
Perkins	O
took	O
these	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
coloured	O
ribband	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
box	O
amongst	O
the	O
black	O
ones	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
black	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
black	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
there	O
they	O
both	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
themselves	O
.	O
Perkins	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Evans	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
292	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barrow	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
china	O
bowl	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Liberten	I-pers
,	O
March	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
293	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margret	B-pers
Monroe	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Wiseman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stocking	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
holland	O
sleeves	O
for	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
3	O
ells	O
of	O
holland	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
punch-ladle	O
,	O
4	O
silver	O
medals	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
May	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
Ann	O
Wynn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
George	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
We	O
live	O
in	O
Chiswell-street	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
four	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
silver	O
medals	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
a	O
queen	O
Anne	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
Friday	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
portmantua	O
of	O
ours	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
,	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
missed	O
three	O
ells	O
of	O
holland	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
(	O
the	O
shirt	O
is	O
not	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
)	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
punch-laddle	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
scrutore	O
by	O
her	O
bed-side	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
some	O
days	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
spoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
hers	O
in	O
Lombard-street	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
missed	O
more	O
things	O
;	O
having	O
mentioned	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
supposed	O
they	O
that	O
took	O
one	O
took	O
all	O
.	O
She	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
fine	O
brussels	O
lace	O
tucker	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
cousin	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
;	O
this	O
being	O
so	O
exceeding	O
good	O
a	O
lace	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
suspicon	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
my	O
business	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
her	O
cousin	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
never	O
gave	O
her	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
my	O
stockings	O
and	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
advertised	O
the	O
other	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Catch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
last	O
,	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
the	O
sleeves	O
and	O
stockings	O
were	O
mine	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Catch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
wash	O
the	O
sleeves	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
the	O
stockings	O
mended	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Broom	I-pers
I	O
wash	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Catch	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
sleeves	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
and	O
stockings	O
to	O
be	O
mended	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
as	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
stockings	O
out	O
to	O
mend	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sleeves	O
to	O
wash	O
for	O
my	O
mistress	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
9	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
always	O
had	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
just	O
person	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Monroe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
her	O
brother	O
?	O
Robert	B-pers
Monroe	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
related	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
service	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
The	O
lady	O
which	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
character	O
to	O
this	O
place	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
294	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
2	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
24	O
silver	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
clasps	O
,	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
studs	O
,	O
I	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	O
Atkins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
We	O
live	O
at	O
Gravesend	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
too	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
about	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
the	O
alehouses	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
here	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
parish	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
son-in-law	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Saturday	O
last	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
together	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
faceing	O
my	O
stand	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
2	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
the	O
snuff	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
mentioned	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse-keeper	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carey	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
watchouse-keeper	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
parish	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
more	O
things	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
some	O
buttons	O
,	O
two	O
spoons	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
brother	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
My	O
landlady	O
generally	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
drawer	O
about	O
an	O
inch	O
out	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
robbed	O
,	O
so	O
took	O
them	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
preserve	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
neighbours	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
295	O
,	O
296	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Longman	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
camblet	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
eleven	O
linnen	O
caps	O
,	O
three	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
hood	O
,	O
one	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
one	O
gause	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
two	O
muslin	O
aprons	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wadley	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
.	O
May	O
17	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Wadley	I-pers
