TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
MAY	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
In	O
the	O
27th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1754	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1754	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Kings	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RAWLINSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Baron	O
CLIVE	O
*	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Baron	O
LEGGE	O
+	O
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
.	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Vaugh	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Froome	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Witherby	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Evered	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Leightenhouse	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Bonham	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Piddington	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Durham	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bosworth	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Covey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pyke	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cross	I-pers
,	O
Duncan	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Baugh	I-pers
.	O
229	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Lapham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Weight	I-pers
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
ten	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
27	O
s.	O
and	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
horsehair	O
,	O
glove-tops	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Weight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
behind	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
boy	O
had	O
stole	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
horsehair	O
glove-tops	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
behind	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
four	O
were	O
dropped	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
;	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Atterbury	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Fleet-street	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
window	O
;	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
glass	O
break	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mr	O
.	O
Weight	O
a	O
boy	O
had	O
broke	O
his	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Salisbury-Court	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
and	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
dropped	O
near	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
along	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
other	O
place	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
but	O
my	O
bosom	O
and	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
230	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Tombs	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
March	O
9	O
*	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
tripeshop	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
the	O
money	O
mentioned	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
shopboard	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
for	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
shutters	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
him	O
back	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
ply	O
in	O
Westminster-market	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
shop-windows	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
called	O
out	O
basket	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
earned	O
a	O
penny	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
231	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Page	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
an	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
coach-house	O
and	O
stable	O
.	O
Feb.	O
15	O
*	O
George	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
Cavendish-square	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
mason	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
lead	O
off	O
my	O
coach-house	O
and	O
stable	O
;	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
the	O
watchman	O
had	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
I	O
compared	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
place	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
fitted	O
.	O
Webb	O
deposed	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
stopping	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
comparing	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
place	O
from	O
whence	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
watchman	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
232	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Pippen	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Pepper	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
pieces	O
of	O
fir	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Blagrave	I-pers
.	O
April	O
the	O
5th	O
*	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blagrave	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
watchman	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
nine	O
pieces	O
of	O
fir	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
next	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Road	O
,	O
Gray's-Inn	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Pryer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
with	O
the	O
wood	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Blagrave	O
,	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
his	O
man	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Blagrave	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
forgive	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
so	O
before	O
,	O
nor	O
will	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
233	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Beardsmore	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
,	O
lett	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
March	O
8	O
++	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
234	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Need	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
.	O
April	O
17	O
++	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
.	O
Coming	O
along	O
Cheapside	B-place
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
dropped	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
King-street	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
accused	O
me	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
till	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
235	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Gunnell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Salkeld	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
pillowbear	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
++	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Salkeld	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	B-place
Cross-Keys	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Gracechurch-street	I-place
,	O
throwed	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
one	O
pillowbear	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
napkin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
sash	O
fastened	O
down	O
?	O
Fox	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
near	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Fox	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
upon	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
shew	O
us	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
sheet	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Rosemary-Branch	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Salkeld	I-pers
,	O
marked	O
with	O
the	O
initial	O
letters	O
of	O
his	O
name	O
]	O
I	O
am	O
chamberlain	O
there	O
.	O
William	O
Cauthery	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
has	O
mentioned	O
in	O
finding	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
his	O
confession	O
.	O
Conner	O
,	O
another	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	O
Salkeld	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
thence	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Salkeld	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lawson	I-pers
++	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
:	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
facts	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
sheet	O
and	O
pumps	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
sheet	O
again	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
,	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
Did	O
he	O
confess	O
what	O
hour	O
he	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
latch	O
?	O
Fox	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
236	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Dunmal	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Braidey	I-pers
,	O
March	O
8	O
++	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Braldey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ivy-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
journeyman	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
missed	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
scale-beam	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
stamp	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
with	O
a	O
cypher	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
twenty-pence	O
of	O
the	O
halfpence	O
that	O
was	O
marked	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
paper	O
with	O
the	O
letter	O
G	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
his	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
237	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Walter	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
marrying	O
Martha	B-pers
Stowel	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
his	O
former	O
wife	O
being	O
then	O
living	O
.	O
Oct.	O
20	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
one	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
wedding	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
ceremony	O
performed	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Zarrant	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
the	O
New-Chappel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Welch	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
May	O
or	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
positive	O
which	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
ring	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
finger	O
?	O
Welch	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
.	O
This	O
woman	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
points	O
to	O
,	O
is	O
Mary	B-pers
Braiswell	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
wedding	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Stowel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
married	O
at	O
St.	O
Bride	O
's	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
got	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
cohabited	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
about	O
six	O
score	O
pounds	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
ring	O
put	O
on	O
your	O
finger	O
?	O
Martha	B-pers
Stowel	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
consented	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
as	O
my	O
lawful	O
husband	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
a	O
bond	O
and	O
judgment	O
for	O
an	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
goods	O
were	O
seized	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
friend	O
who	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Neal	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
living	O
with	O
the	O
first	O
wife	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
brought	O
several	O
persons	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
all	O
her	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
Stowel	I-pers
married	O
at	O
St.	O
Bride	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
clergyman	O
's	O
habit	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
words	O
mentioned	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
wedded	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
ring	O
put	O
on	O
her	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bailiffs	O
put	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
after	O
the	O
marriage	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Martha	B-pers
Stowel	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
wife	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
regard	O
that	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Martha	O
Stowel	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
before	O
I	O
married	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
about	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
I	O
married	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
contents	O
were	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
about	O
town	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
marry	O
women	O
to	O
ruin	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
widow	O
?	O
Stowel	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
this	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
myself	O
:	O
This	O
woman	O
that	O
they	O
call	O
my	O
first	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
out	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
married	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
drunken	O
frolick	O
at	O
Welch	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
man	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
last	O
wife	O
be	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
hours	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
before	O
we	O
were	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
a	O
wedding	O
dinner	O
there	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
wife	O
living	O
.	O
This	O
old	O
woman	O
gave	O
it	O
out	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
Welch	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
5	O
l.	O
I	O
should	O
hear	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
my	O
selling	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
goods	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pay	O
Welch	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
expended	O
in	O
beer	O
.	O
The	O
old	O
woman	O
said	O
after	O
this	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
any	O
remote	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
with	O
her	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
ashamed	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
known	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
so	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
This	O
Welch	O
will	O
forswear	O
himself	O
presently	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
his	O
part	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Simon	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Braiswell	O
went	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
minister	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
so	O
drunk	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
make	O
this	O
up	O
for	O
5	O
l.	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
said	O
?	O
Welch	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
238	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Rose	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Martin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pier	O
glass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
March	O
23.	O
*	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Blue-Cross-Street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
neighbours	O
had	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
pier-glass	O
,	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
]	O
which	O
before	O
hung	O
in	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
in	O
my	O
parlour	O
on	O
the	O
wainscot	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Revear	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
but	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
Blue-Cross-Street	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
with	O
this	O
glass	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
called	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
workmen	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
marks	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
glass	O
by	O
?	O
Revear	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
places	O
that	O
were	O
broke	O
off	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
pieces	O
were	O
broke	O
off	O
the	O
frame	O
by	O
wrenching	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
wainscot	O
[	O
producing	O
some	O
pieces	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
fixing	O
the	O
goods	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
just	O
removed	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Being	O
called	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
glass	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
before	O
screwed	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
wainscot	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
walked	O
off	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
shavings	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
my	O
going	O
out	O
that	O
evidence	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
was	O
this	O
glass	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
.	O
They	O
bid	O
me	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
that	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
glass	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
hurried	O
me	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
directly	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Revear	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
glass	O
in	O
her	O
possession	O
?	O
Revear	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Mary	B-pers
Showles	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Shon	I-pers
,	O
Susannah	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Dormoot	I-pers
,	O
William	O
Cowley	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
to	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
fifteen	O
,	O
the	O
third	O
twelve	O
,	O
the	O
fourth	O
sixteen	O
,	O
the	O
fifth	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
eighteen	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
239	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Croshew	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
camblet	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
April	O
2	O
+	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
in	O
Wardour-Street	B-place
.	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
in	O
a	O
garret	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
by	O
whom	O
,	O
or	O
when	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
husband	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Bow-Street	O
.	O
Having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
had	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
a	O
son	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
paid	O
her	O
wages	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
away	O
missed	O
her	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
all	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
to	O
clear	O
herself	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
40	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
goods	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Bow-Street	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
the	O
man	O
a	O
paper	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
there	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Melvell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
in	O
Bow-Street	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
another	O
young	O
woman	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
gone	O
away	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
240	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hugh	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Henry	I-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
tenant	O
saw	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jos	B-pers
Plat	I-pers
;	O
eight	O
planes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
oil-stone	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
March	O
16.	O
*	O
.	O
The	O
tools	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
building	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	B-place
,	O
betwixt	O
Saturday	O
night	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
and	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
going	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
missed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
violins	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
goal	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
tools	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Singleton	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
respective	O
owners	O
.	O
]	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Singleton	O
deposed	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
violins	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
laid	O
for	O
single	O
felony	O
only	O
be	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
241	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Amey	B-pers
Bright	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
teakettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
was	O
coming	O
towards	O
her	O
own	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
suspected	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
a	O
teakettle	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
hers	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
242.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
three	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
lawn	O
ruffles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
two	O
lawn	O
tuckers	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Catharine	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
March	O
13	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
243	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
++	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
watch	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
and	O
told	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
inquire	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Bury	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
nail	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
Field-Lane	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Brown	O
.	O
His	O
man	O
Thomas	B-pers
Slayter	I-pers
,	O
that	O
should	O
have	O
given	O
his	O
evidence	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Coombs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
eating	O
my	O
supper	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
.	O
Sanders	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
and	O
beckoned	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
pawn	O
this	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Balls	O
,	O
on	O
Snow-Hill	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
standing	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
it	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
that	O
kept	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
drunk	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
244	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Selbey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
copper	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Blackbourne	I-pers
,	O
March	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Trent	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
spent	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
bag	O
to	O
a	O
fish-woman	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
245	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
West	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gunpowder	O
flask	O
mounted	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
val	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
spring	O
saw	O
,	O
one	O
glass	O
mug	O
,	O
one	O
drinking	O
glass	O
,	O
one	O
gardener	O
's	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
tinder-box	O
,	O
one	O
trowel	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
,	O
December	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
James-Street	B-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Margaret	I-place
's	I-place
parish	I-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
garden	O
at	O
a	O
small	O
Distance	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
greenhouse	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
only	O
laid	O
those	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
last	O
there	O
?	O
Hays	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
December	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
them	O
the	O
13th	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
goods	O
here	O
produced	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
or	O
cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hains	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
when	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
all	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
described	O
them	O
all	O
before	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
One	O
John	B-pers
Putlock	I-pers
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
coachman	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
these	O
goods	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
should	O
soon	O
receive	O
my	O
pension	O
money	O
at	O
Chelsea	O
College	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Borroughs	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Christmas	O
eve	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Chelsea	O
to	O
his	O
usurer	O
whose	O
name	O
is	O
Cammel	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Coming	O
back	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
guineas	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
disguised	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
quarrel	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Cross	O
in	O
Tothil-Street	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Dick	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
in	O
a	O
cloth	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
had	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
case	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
5	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
business	O
?	O
Borroughs	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
trade	O
in	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
larger	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
these	O
goods	O
to	O
furnish	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
246	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Mayne	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
set	O
with	O
chrystal	O
stones	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s.	O
two	O
cambrick	O
aprons	O
with	O
laced	O
borders	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
eight	O
China	O
cups	O
and	O
eight	O
China	O
saucers	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
fans	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
four	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
cambrick	O
caps	O
laced	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
mittens	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
mussatees	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
silver	O
lace	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Purshall	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charlotte	O
,	O
April	O
2.	O
*	O
.	O
Charlotte	B-pers
Purshall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
suspecting	O
her	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
constable	O
fetcht	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
trunk	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
recommended	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
complained	O
to	O
me	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
there	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
several	O
things	O
and	O
suspected	O
her	O
honesty	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
trunk	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
things	O
produced	O
taken	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
that	O
the	O
three	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
her	O
mistress	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Camm	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
a	O
capuchin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Gray	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
they	O
tumbled	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
pocket	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
delivered	O
that	O
again	O
to	O
her	O
mistress	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
trunk	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
lady	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
these	O
other	O
things	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
parish	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
untold	O
gold	O
.	O
She	O
behaved	O
exceedingly	O
well	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Wells	O
.	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
behaved	O
just	O
and	O
honestly	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
247	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Maxwell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
callicoe	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
.	O
March	O
5	O
++	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Old-Bailey-Gate	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
being	O
busy	O
she	O
staid	O
and	O
assisted	O
me	O
in	O
making-up	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
all	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
bed-gown	O
and	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Newtoner	O
's	O
Lane	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
gown	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
designed	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
a	O
justice	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
[	O
the	O
bedgown	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
:	O
and	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
deposed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
there	O
and	O
pledged	O
it	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
delivered	O
the	O
bedgown	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
248	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hitchman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
.	O
March	O
26	O
*	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
had	O
hung	O
my	O
watch	O
on	O
a	O
brass	O
knob	O
,	O
as	O
usually	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Portal	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
near	O
Hungerford-Market	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
silversmith	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Portal	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
twenty-seven	O
shillings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
A	O
soldier	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
regiment	O
with	O
me	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
doors	O
below	O
Hungerford-Market	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
since	O
deserted	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
249	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Ralph	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
mahogany	O
plank	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
23	O
++	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Abbot	O
's	O
at	O
Wapping	O
,	O
to	O
measure	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
plank	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
plank	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
measured	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
mark	O
T.	O
A.	O
and	O
our	O
own	O
mark	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
put	O
on	O
planks	O
when	O
we	O
measure	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
particularly	O
remember	O
this	O
plank	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
we	O
then	O
measured	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
made	O
several	O
impressions	O
on	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
gouge	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
my	O
book	O
about	O
me	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
answered	O
in	O
every	O
particular	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
's	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Abbot	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Abbot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
plank	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Cole	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
here	O
;	O
but	O
from	O
among	O
so	O
many	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
particular	O
plank	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Abbot	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Abbot	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Cole	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
in	O
a	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
heard	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
250	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
harrateen	O
val	O
.	O
necs	O
o	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
sattin	O
hat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
March	O
26	O
*	O
.	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
live	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Watts	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stakeman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
knowing	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shove	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
near	O
Russel-Court	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
251	O
,	O
252	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
China	O
bason	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
fourpence	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Black	I-place
Horse	I-place
in	I-place
Barbican	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pint	O
China	O
bason	O
of	O
halfpence	O
and	O
farthings	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
two	O
full	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
them	O
by	O
my	O
girl	O
;	O
she	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
on	O
a	O
jar	O
to	O
let	O
herself	O
in	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
in	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
bason	O
and	O
halfpence	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
by	O
enquiring	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
that	O
night	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
confessed	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
bason	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
seven	O
shillings	O
and	O
fourpence	O
halfpenny	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
about	O
them	O
both	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
eightpence	O
in	O
halfpence	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
bason	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
and	O
thrown	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Main	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
[	O
he	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
]	O
The	O
prisoners	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
253	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fourteen	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
two	O
sheep	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
April	O
20	O
++	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
254	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
five	O
other	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Lockyer	I-pers
in	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
April	O
10	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lockyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	O
;	O
coming	O
through	O
the	O
Fleet-Market	B-place
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
more	O
together	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
w	O
did	O
that	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Lockyer	I-pers
.	O
Not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
after	O
him	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
my	O
hat	O
he	O
turned	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
market-house	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
near	O
the	O
Harrow	O
alehouse	O
;	O
there	O
stood	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
(	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
confederate	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
my	O
hat	O
again	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
suspected	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
things	O
as	O
is	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
charge	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
dishonest	O
action	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
255	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Timothy	B-pers
Carrol	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
.	O
April	O
16	O
++	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Piccadilley	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
an	O
oil	O
and	O
colour	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
parcels	O
out	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
my	O
till	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
April	O
16.	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
left	O
;	O
the	O
till	O
was	O
not	O
locked	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
shoe-blacker	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
carried	O
out	O
some	O
parcels	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
to	O
his	O
customers	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
warehouse	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
till	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Looking	O
into	O
it	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
till	O
too	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
insisted	O
on	O
knowing	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
heart	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
put	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
4	O
s.	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
nigh	O
the	O
till	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
255	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
saw	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Morton	I-pers
,	O
April	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
256	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Too	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
shag	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tailor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
with	O
the	O
shag	O
under	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
lost	O
my	O
shag	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
against	O
her	O
than	O
the	O
watchman	O
told	O
me	O
afterwards	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Huit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
calling	O
the	O
hour	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
at	O
the	O
Star	O
Inn	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
accusing	O
the	O
people	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
shag	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
persuade	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
presently	O
after	O
it	O
dropped	O
from	O
her	O
cloaths	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
257	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Blackston	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
ox	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Harris	B-pers
Roughton	I-pers
,	O
March	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Harris	O
Roughton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
On	O
March	O
the	O
25th	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
and	O
my	O
lad	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
a	O
lad	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
an	O
ox	O
's	O
head	O
from	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
the	O
head	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
James	O
Purchase	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
minding	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
ox	O
's	O
head	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
stall	O
,	O
but	O
presently	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
behind	O
the	O
shop	O
saw	O
two	O
lads	O
walking	O
up	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
head	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
no	O
assistance	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
only	O
.	O
He	O
afterwards	O
owned	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
lad	O
took	O
the	O
head	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
lad	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
258	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hugh	B-pers
M'kave	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
an	O
infant	O
not	O
five	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
mother	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
[	O
She	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
.	O
]	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
was	O
going	O
wriggling	O
about	O
in	O
a	O
strange	O
manner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
petticoats	O
were	O
not	O
tied	O
tight	O
enough	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
tied	O
them	O
tighter	O
;	O
but	O
still	O
she	O
went	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
setting	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
lap	O
looked	O
at	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
shift	O
was	O
spotted	O
as	O
though	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
spit	O
upon	O
it	O
who	O
had	O
a	O
consumption	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
as	O
raw	O
about	O
the	O
private	O
parts	O
as	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
skinned	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
a	O
porter	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
surgeon	O
in	O
Pallmall	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
servant	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
suspected	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
used	O
her	O
ill	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
foul	O
disease	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
his	O
opinion	O
the	O
child	O
had	O
the	O
foul	O
disease	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pinkstone	O
in	O
St.	O
Alban's-Street	O
;	O
he	O
examined	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
very	O
ill	O
used	O
by	O
some	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
M.	O
Holmes	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
born	O
Jan.	O
3	O
,	O
1750	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
tailor	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
On	O
going	O
out	O
myself	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
the	O
child	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
care	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
house	O
being	O
down	O
through	O
an	O
entry	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
by	O
place	O
,	O
very	O
few	O
people	O
come	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
child	O
cured	O
now	O
?	O
M.	O
Holmes	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pinkstone	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
unction	O
to	O
anoint	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
wash	O
the	O
part	O
with	O
warm	O
milk	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
still	O
continue	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
surgeon	O
here	O
?	O
M.	O
Holmes	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
gone	O
to-day	O
to	O
set	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
leg	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
Jane	O
Thomas	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
midwife	O
.	O
The	O
mother	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
child	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
condition	O
,	O
unless	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
ill	O
used	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
who	O
had	O
forced	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
this	O
child	O
had	O
and	O
has	O
now	O
the	O
foul	O
distemper	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
though	O
the	O
ointment	O
has	O
done	O
her	O
some	O
good	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
acknowledge	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
clerk	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
foul	O
distemper	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
aunt	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
My	O
sister	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
feared	O
her	O
child	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
ill	O
by	O
some	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
's	O
,	O
whose	O
servant	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
ill	O
by	O
some	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
private	O
parts	O
were	O
as	O
raw	O
as	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
thighs	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
a	O
stone	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
like	O
a	O
tap	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
shift	O
was	O
black	O
and	O
yellow	O
with	O
the	O
filth	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
worked	O
with	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
husband	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
owed	O
me	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
believe	O
myself	O
clear	O
of	O
that	O
distemper	O
now	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
259	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
steal	O
out	O
thence	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
nine	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
three	O
halfpence	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Serjeant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
parish	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barber	O
and	O
periwig	O
maker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
dinner	O
;	O
the	O
lodgers	O
being	O
all	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
made	O
all	O
fast	O
below	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
a	O
door	O
that	O
goes	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
was	O
wrenched	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
window	O
shutter	O
that	O
before	O
was	O
nailed	O
up	O
at	O
a	O
back	O
window	O
was	O
pulled	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
window	O
left	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
twelve	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
three	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Mayfield	O
's	O
in	O
Poplar	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
eight	O
pair	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
He	O
begged	O
his	O
master	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lenham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
last	O
evidence	O
in	O
finding	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
stockings	O
I	O
had	O
nobody	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witness	O
to	O
call	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
260	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Silas	B-pers
Dowling	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
March	O
28	O
++	O
.	O
Nathanael	O
Stent	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brownless	O
,	O
a	O
merchant	O
,	O
in	O
Fetter-Lane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
an	O
advertisement	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jenour	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
printer	O
of	O
the	O
Daily	O
Advertiser	O
,	O
near	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
an	O
auction	O
of	O
books	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
;	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
then	O
too	O
fast	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
walked	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Lombard-Street	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
letters	O
at	O
the	O
post-office	O
,	O
we	O
there	O
wished	O
each	O
other	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
.	O
Having	O
done	O
my	O
business	O
there	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
St	O
.	O
Miles's-Lane	O
to	O
inquire	O
at	O
a	O
coffee-house	O
when	O
the	O
ship	O
Phillis	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Jamaica	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
there	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
From	O
thence	O
I	O
came	O
directly	O
homewards	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Fetter-Lane	B-place
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
behind	O
me	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
leaned	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
strike	O
you	O
with	O
?	O
Stent	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
he	O
spoke	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
understood	O
hi	O
m	O
,	O
You	O
dog	O
,	O
deliver	O
,	O
or	O
such	O
like	O
words	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
before	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
you	O
lived	O
?	O
Stent	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
far	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
walking	O
together	O
?	O
Stent	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
switch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
apprehend	O
the	O
blow	O
was	O
given	O
with	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Stent	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
he	O
stood	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
holding	O
his	O
hands	O
out	O
towards	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
in	O
a	O
posture	O
of	O
defence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Stent	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
lamps	O
near	O
you	O
?	O
Stent	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
none	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
discern	O
his	O
face	O
?	O
Stent	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
him	O
standing	O
before	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
dress	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
walked	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
recollected	O
him	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
walked	O
together	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
Stent	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Fenchurch-street	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
across	O
Fleetstreet	O
:	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
Mitre	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
watchman	O
?	O
Stent	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
[	O
That	O
whereas	O
a	O
young	O
gentleman	O
in	O
a	O
laced	O
hat	O
was	O
assaulted	O
by	O
a	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
,	O
by	O
applying	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
might	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
]	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
examined	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
[	O
the	O
watch	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hine	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Cross-Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
the	O
exact	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
Stent	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Stent	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
swear	O
directly	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
him	O
speak	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
litle	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
positive	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
brought	O
in	O
amongst	O
others	O
,	O
or	O
singly	O
?	O
Stent	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
single	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
stood	O
before	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
?	O
Stent	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
voice	O
and	O
his	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
have	O
on	O
now	O
?	O
Stent	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
white	O
fustian	O
William	B-pers
Hine	I-pers
One	O
Richard	B-pers
Nokes	I-pers
told	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
that	O
over	O
night	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Taylor	O
's	O
Arms	O
,	O
in	O
Wych-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
Nokes	O
?	O
Hine	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
convicted	O
for	O
perjury	O
,	O
and	O
discovered	O
that	O
gang	O
of	O
Harley	O
and	O
Mark	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
and	O
others	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
which	O
all	O
those	O
people	O
resort	O
to	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
What	O
about	O
this	O
watch	O
?	O
Hine	O
.	O
Nokes	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
him	O
off	O
for	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
at	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
we	O
called	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Norden	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Nokes	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
follow	O
you	O
;	O
Nokes	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
left	O
us	O
:	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
we	O
saw	O
Nokes	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
together	O
,	O
going	O
towards	O
the	O
New	O
Church	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
we	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
him	O
there	O
,	O
found	O
this	O
silver	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
terrified	O
that	O
his	O
water	O
came	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Barley-Mow	O
,	O
near	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
him	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
we	O
thought	O
proper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
sign	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Barwell	O
Smith	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
what	O
sized	O
young	O
man	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
laced	O
hat	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
advertisement	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
description	O
he	O
gave	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
owned	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
at	O
an	O
auction	O
of	O
books	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
going	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
post-office	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Norden	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
Hines	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
be	O
ever	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
'till	O
Richard	B-pers
Nokes	I-pers
gave	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
hold	O
while	O
he	O
tied	O
up	O
his	O
garter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
witness	O
to	O
prove	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
when	O
this	O
thing	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Baptist's-Court	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
from	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
over-night	O
'till	O
seven	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Richard	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
after	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
paviour	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Matthews	O
,	O
in	O
Butcherhall-Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stay	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
there	O
and	O
slept	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
asleep	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
his	O
business	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
just	O
removed	O
from	O
one	O
room	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
washes	O
for	O
gentlemens	O
servants	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
an	O
house-warming	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
one	O
we	O
wash	O
for	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
who	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
mother	O
Harding	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
that	O
other	O
man	O
is	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
now	O
.	O
Here	O
the	O
court	O
ordered	O
the	O
evidence	O
's	O
wife	O
out	O
of	O
court	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
drink	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
Beer	O
;	O
about	O
twelve	O
or	O
thirteen	O
full-pots	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
there	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
Five	O
or	O
six	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
sat	O
down	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
sleep	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
had	O
you	O
your	O
beer	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
We	O
drank	O
from	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
place	O
we	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
gallon	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
that	O
was	O
out	O
we	O
had	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
successively	O
'till	O
near	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
we	O
pour	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
into	O
full	O
pots	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
all	O
the	O
company	O
stay	O
'till	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
went	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
service	O
(	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
the	O
Red-Cross	O
in	O
Newgate-market	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
Scotch	O
girl	O
)	O
sat	O
and	O
slept	O
'till	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
One	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
lives	O
at	O
the	O
Saracen's-Head	O
,	O
in	O
Friday-street	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
a	O
boy-like	O
person	O
that	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
stay	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Scotch	O
girl	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
staid	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
rooms	O
have	O
you	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
utter	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Consider	O
what	O
you	O
say	O
.	O
Harding	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
I	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
here	O
on	O
purpose	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
has	O
your	O
wife	O
washed	O
for	O
that	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
him	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
About	O
twice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dressed	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
fustian	O
frock	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
with	O
mohair	O
buttons	O
on	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
colour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
what	O
colour	O
was	O
the	O
frock	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
lightish	O
brown	O
or	O
drab	O
colour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
it	O
a	O
cape	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
lived	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
there	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Stent	O
.	O
What	O
cloaths	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
walked	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Stent	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
white	O
fustian	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
dirtyish	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
trimmed	O
with	O
black	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
it	O
a	O
cape	O
?	O
Stent	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
had	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Hines	O
.	O
What	O
cloaths	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
him	O
?	O
Hines	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
fustian	O
frock	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
white	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
dirtyish	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
buttons	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
colour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
cape	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Hines	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
to	O
Harding	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
wife	O
with	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
,	O
excepting	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
fetched	O
a	O
pot	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
beer	O
Q	O
Who	O
fetched	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
beer	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
No	O
body	O
fetched	O
any	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
I	O
wash	O
for	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Jane	O
Harding	O
.	O
Not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
'till	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
also	O
three	O
other	O
acquaintances	O
I	O
wash	O
for	O
.	O
Cross-Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
liquor	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
We	O
had	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
with	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
He	O
came	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
they	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
night	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
staid	O
pretty	O
late	O
then	O
they	O
begged	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
came	O
first	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
company	O
or	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
young	O
woman	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
The	O
others	O
came	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
quite	O
sober	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
They	O
were	O
very	O
sober	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
fetched	O
the	O
beer	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
the	O
coach-and-horses	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
all	O
you	O
had	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
that	O
lasted	O
them	O
'till	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
no	O
more	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
We	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
two	O
full	O
pots	O
before	O
the	O
others	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
beer	O
might	O
you	O
have	O
in	O
all	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
Four	O
or	O
five	O
full	O
pots	O
were	O
all	O
we	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
no	O
body	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
No	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
set	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
slept	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
'till	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
went	O
away	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
light	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
awake	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
hour	O
did	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
go	O
away	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
At	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
six	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
there	O
of	O
you	O
in	O
company	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
besides	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
in	O
time	O
to	O
the	O
inn	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
waggon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
About	O
what	O
time	O
did	O
they	O
go	O
away	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
About	O
five	O
,	O
or	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
that	O
woman	O
that	O
staid	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
name	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
Betty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
washed	O
for	O
her	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
washed	O
for	O
her	O
above	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
might	O
you	O
have	O
washed	O
for	O
her	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
She	O
brought	O
caps	O
and	O
aprons	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
Were	O
you	O
all	O
sober	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
We	O
were	O
all	O
very	O
sober	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
cloaths	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
much	O
notice	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
nor	O
since	O
,	O
'till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
not	O
a	O
man	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
fetched	O
the	O
beer	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
,	O
who	O
fetched	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
fetched	O
none	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
was	O
it	O
fetched	O
?	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
In	O
single	O
quarts	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Baynham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
turner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
turn-over	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
apprenticeship	O
?	O
Baynham	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
continued	O
with	O
you	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Baynham	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
one	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
that	O
ago	O
?	O
Baynham	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
week	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Baynham	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
sixteen	O
or	O
seventeen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Curtice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
apprentice	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
was	O
he	O
then	O
?	O
Curtice	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
fourteen	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Baynham	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
frequently	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
he	O
free	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
court	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
this	O
trial	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
what	O
is	O
sworn	O
against	O
him	O
?	O
Wingfield	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Tomlinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
our	O
ward-school	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
within	O
two	O
doors	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
messages	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
for	O
his	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
lad	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Maridow	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
as	O
an	O
errant	O
boy	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
many	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
fulfilled	O
his	O
trust	O
faithfully	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Ruth	B-pers
Blyer	I-pers
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
memory	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
trusted	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
and	O
plate	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
relation	O
's	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
too	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Tompson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
sober	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Liblong	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
court	O
committed	O
Harding	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
Newgate	O
for	O
perjury	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
receive	O
sentence	O
,	O
he	O
declared	O
what	O
those	O
two	O
witnesses	O
had	O
swore	O
on	O
his	O
trial	O
was	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cknowledged	O
the	O
committing	O
the	O
fact	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
cast	O
.	O
261	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Kenady	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
compasses	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
24	O
++	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
262	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Plumton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
.	O
April	O
17	O
++	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
263	O
,	O
264	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Rachael	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
chain-ring	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
crystal	O
stone	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
locket	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
one	O
fork	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
agate	O
handle	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Barrot	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
coral	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
April	O
21	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
locket	O
,	O
and	O
fork	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
*	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Barrot	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
within	O
two	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
,	O
not	O
liking	O
her	O
behaviour	O
,	O
turned	O
her	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Powel	O
,	O
at	O
Kensington-Gore	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Barrot	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
near	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
those	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Powel	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
chain	O
,	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
coral	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
when	O
Clark	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
the	O
coral	O
is	O
not	O
properly	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
named	O
Chambers	O
,	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
small	O
matter	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
gold	O
watch	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
Lucas	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
gold	O
locket	O
in	O
Denmark-Court	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
locket	O
delivered	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
then	O
by	O
Clark	O
's	O
direction	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Walter	B-pers
Rochford	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Russel-Court	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
spoon	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
delivered	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
.	O
Clark	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
Sunday	O
before	O
Easter	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
returned	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
coral	O
and	O
chain	O
ring	O
that	O
hung	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
to	O
sell	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
advertised	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Holebourne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Denmark-Court	O
.	O
Rachael	O
Lucas	O
brought	O
this	O
gold	O
locket	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
4	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Rochford	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
one	O
spoon	O
and	O
one	O
ring	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
then	O
.	O
Lucas	O
once	O
before	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
same	O
gold	O
locket	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cuthbert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
Last	O
Saturday	O
night	O
Mr.	O
Barrot	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
Mary	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
that	O
Lucas	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
her	O
master	O
Barrot	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Lucas	O
had	O
inticed	O
her	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
agat-handled	O
fork	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
Lucas	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
Clark	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
mentioned	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Lucas	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
Clark	O
's	O
coming	O
away	O
till	O
she	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
For	O
Clark	O
.	O
Barnaby	O
M'Atee	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Clark	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
green	O
grocer	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
served	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barrot	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
his	O
wife	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Kingham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
three	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
.	O
She	O
worked	O
hard	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
For	O
Lucas	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Lucas	O
upwards	O
of	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
her	O
lately	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Lucas	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
frequently	O
in	O
my	O
apartments	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
her	O
of	O
being	O
a	O
bad	O
woman	O
,	O
or	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
now	O
was	O
she	O
at	O
liberty	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Herd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Holebourne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Lucas	O
these	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
265	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Harwood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Arabella	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
one	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
March	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Merrit	I-pers
Slipper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Kingsland	O
Road	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
my	O
fireside	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
turned	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
an	O
arm	O
reaching	O
cross	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
My	O
child	O
said	O
,	O
Mamma	O
,	O
mamma	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
reaching	O
two	O
gowns	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
iron	O
fork	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
something	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
but	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
gowns	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
gowns	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
's	O
house	O
of	O
office	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
this	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
these	O
gowns	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Slipper	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
:	O
John	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
our	O
house	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
sister	O
between	O
that	O
time	O
and	O
the	O
finding	O
of	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stay	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
your	O
yard	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
She	O
staid	O
about	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
is	O
common	O
for	O
persons	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
before	O
she	O
returned	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
She	O
lives	O
about	O
100	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
business	O
she	O
followed	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
sister	O
straitening	O
an	O
iron	O
fork	O
at	O
my	O
fire	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
that	O
fork	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
had	O
streightened	O
the	O
tines	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
sister	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
here	O
go	O
along	O
,	O
you	O
bitch	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
do	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
sister	O
never	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
only	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Whose	O
gown	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
pledge	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
pawned	O
a	O
gown	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Slipper	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
away	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Ann	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
;	O
also	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
deposed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
pledge	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Fitzgerald	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
sister	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
's	O
yard	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
in	O
the	O
necessary-house	O
,	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Martin	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
gowns	O
were	O
any	O
where	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
they	O
must	O
be	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
gown	O
,	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
seat	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
necessary-house	O
?	O
Fitzgerald	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
near	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
that	O
they	O
alledge	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
near	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
above	O
four	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cook	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
money	O
for	O
almost	O
a	O
day	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
ever	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
character	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
as	O
soon	O
take	O
her	O
in	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
does	O
she	O
follow	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
mend	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
like	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
twenty-six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
does	O
she	O
follow	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
She	O
sews	O
,	O
makes	O
caps	O
,	O
foots	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
,	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
266	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Christian	B-pers
Douglass	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linnen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
April	O
the	O
18	O
th	O
*	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
such	O
things	O
.	O
Some	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
detained	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
brought	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchiefs	O
to	O
pawn	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
with	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
from	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
in	O
Whitechapple	O
parish	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
Mr.	O
West	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
robbing	O
him	O
of	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
those	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
from	O
her	O
pocket	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
Mr.	O
West	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
and	O
committed	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
267	O
,	O
268	O
,	O
269	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Paul	B-pers
Kenady	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Fitch	I-pers
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Carlow	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rich	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
[	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
from	O
Lincoln's-inn-fields	B-place
playhouse	I-place
,	O
and	O
that	O
forty	O
pounds	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
good	O
the	O
damage	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
principal	O
evidence	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Carty	I-pers
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
with	O
Carlow	O
stole	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
evidence	O
standing	O
unsupported	O
by	O
any	O
evidence	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
acquitted	O
]	O
270	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Fitch	I-pers
,	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Tarrant	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
hundred	O
and	O
twenty-eight	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
33	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Goddard	I-pers
.	O
April	O
2	O
+	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
271	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	I-pers
single	I-pers
woman	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Aubury	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
March	O
4	O
.	O
She	O
stood	O
