TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
27th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1754	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1754	O
;	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Kings	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RAWLINSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BATHURST	O
*	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
ADAMS	O
+	O
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justice	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Bickerton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Aaron	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Hall	O
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Simons	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pittman	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Sheffield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Westley	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
,	O
*	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
for	O
John	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Cornwell	I-pers
.	O
413	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susannah	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Pennel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
coffee	O
pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
August	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
broker	O
in	O
Morefields	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
coffee	O
pot	O
from	O
his	O
shop	O
door	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
about	O
five	O
doors	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
stopped	O
her	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
coffee	O
pot	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
alone	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Nelson	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Lovan	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lefeaver	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Portrow	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
,	O
Michael	B-pers
Vear	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
,	O
Badley	O
Navaugh	O
,	O
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Cathel	I-pers
;	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
exclusive	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
414	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hare	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
415	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixteen	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
on	O
Summers	B-place
's	I-place
Key	I-place
.	O
I	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
hole	O
under	O
a	O
gate	O
and	O
handed	O
me	O
out	O
this	O
tobacco	O
.	O
Producing	O
some	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
is	O
there	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Symonds	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
sixteen	O
pounds	O
weight	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Symonds	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
it	O
in	O
two	O
parcels	O
to	O
one	O
Cosgrave	O
near	O
the	O
Victualing	O
Office	O
on	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
we	O
knocked	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
along	O
time	O
in	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Cosgrave	O
know	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
tobacco	O
?	O
Symonds	O
.	O
He	O
must	O
know	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
others	O
concerned	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
you	O
?	O
Symonds	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
none	O
else	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
beat	O
the	O
hour	O
one	O
this	O
night	O
and	O
past	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
evidence	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
knocking	O
at	O
Cosgrave	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
on	O
the	O
inside	O
unlocking	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
myself	O
saw	O
the	O
evidence	O
lying	O
on	O
this	O
tobacco	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
man	O
within	O
heard	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
evidence	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
officer	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
when	O
the	O
evidence	O
and	O
the	O
tobacco	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
his	O
accomplice	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
information	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
a	O
warrant	O
was	O
granted	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
evidence	O
's	O
direction	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
confessed	O
also	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
tobacco	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
accomplice	O
had	O
mentioned	O
before	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
concerned	O
upon	O
the	O
key	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hunt	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
only	O
he	O
had	O
tobacco	O
that	O
night	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
accomplice	O
say	O
they	O
took	O
this	O
from	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
rolled	O
up	O
under	O
the	O
gateway	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
safe	O
there	O
till	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
fetched	O
away	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hole	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
gate	O
where	O
a	O
person	O
might	O
creep	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
duty	O
paid	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
evidence	O
going	O
over	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
stopped	O
against	O
this	O
door	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Friend	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
stop	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
for	O
keeping	O
disorderly	O
hours	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
fearing	O
he	O
should	O
lay	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
warrant	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
just	O
come	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
Huntingtonshire	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
stranger	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
416	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Walters	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Staple	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
*	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Staple	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
Lombard-Street	B-place
,	O
and	O
apprehending	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
clapp	O
'd	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
near	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
falling	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
desired	O
I	O
'd	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
near	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Staple	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
near	O
me	O
as	O
she	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
Staple	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
2	O
s.	O
it	O
is	O
almost	O
new	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
many	O
other	O
persons	O
going	O
along	O
besides	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
417	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Davies	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
violin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
,	O
Aug	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Duke	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
[	O
a	O
musick	O
shop	O
,	O
Red-Lion	B-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Holbourn	I-place
]	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
a	O
violin	O
which	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
stealing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
not	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
violin	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Duke	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
about	O
15	O
s.	O
George	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
violin	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
Stop	O
him	O
,	O
Stop	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
taken	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
bring	O
him	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
violin	O
produced	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
saw	O
before	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
.	O
When	O
they	O
cried	O
,	O
Stop	O
Thief	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
violin	O
and	O
a	O
bow	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
A	O
porter	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
violin	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
being	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
mob	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Duke	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
violin	O
produced	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
that	O
which	O
fell	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Red	O
Lion	O
passage	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
siddle	O
dropp	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
by	O
trade	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
418	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Martha	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Ralph	I-pers
Lomack	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
two-quart	O
pewter	O
pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lomas	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
8	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
keeps	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
two-quart	O
pot	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
bench	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
just	O
before	O
set	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
observed	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Cooley	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
informed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
after	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
borrowed	O
it	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
husband	O
some	O
drink	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
419	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
North	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
pillow	O
cases	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
saucepan	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Bartlet	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
420	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Young	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
two	O
moidores	O
,	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
three	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
pocket	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pitten	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pitten	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cook	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
King	B-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
on	I-place
Tower-hill	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
chest	O
in	O
my	O
bedchamber	O
in	O
which	O
was	O
money	O
and	O
plate	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
two	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
two	O
27	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
some	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
and	O
guineas	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
how	O
many	O
,	O
besides	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
in	O
all	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
inquiring	O
about	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
that	O
day	O
in	O
Monmouth	O
Street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Round-house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
chest	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
rings	O
mentioned	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
them	O
?	O
Pitten	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
rings	O
and	O
buckles	O
about	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Pitten	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
about	O
seventeen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Flannegan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Monmouth	O
Street	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
searching	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
back	O
kitchen	O
found	O
two	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
two	O
moidores	O
,	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
three	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
pocket	O
piece	O
,	O
three	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
17	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
rings	O
and	O
buckles	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
chest	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Flannegan	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
chest	O
either	O
with	O
a	O
poker	O
or	O
tongs	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
taking	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
rings	O
?	O
Flannegan	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
other	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
leaving	O
them	O
together	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dorton	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Monmouth	O
Street	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pitten	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
describing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
him	O
word	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
In	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
shop	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
young	O
fellow	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
another	O
person	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Young	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
who	O
have	O
robbed	O
your	O
master	O
of	O
40	O
l.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
half	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
sober	O
?	O
Dorton	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
person	O
with	O
him	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
some	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
returned	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
things	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
the	O
constable	O
mentioned	O
,	O
including	O
the	O
guinea	O
that	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
.	O
He	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
His	O
master	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
disorderly	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
spent	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
nothing	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
break	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
421	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
Mary	O
,	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
,	O
July	O
27	O
++	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
stall	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Evening	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
snatch	O
'd	O
his	O
hand	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
money	O
directly	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
followed	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
he	O
jostled	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
near	O
my	O
stall	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
just	O
before	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
husband	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Green	O
the	O
Constable	O
,	O
who	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
on	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
My	O
wife	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
her	O
pocket	O
of	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
s.	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
money	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
searched	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
halfpence	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
old	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
another	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
thing	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
422	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Varron	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Sylvester	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Beconsfield	O
Waggon	O
out	O
of	O
the	B-place
Bell	I-place
Inn	I-place
in	I-place
Warwick-lane	I-place
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
porter	O
that	O
carried	O
parcels	O
from	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
The	O
coat	O
was	O
advertis	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
coat	O
there	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
another	O
person	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
see	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
that	O
day	O
after	O
3	O
o'clock	O
?	O
Sylvester	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
upon	O
the	O
waggon	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
tied	O
upon	O
a	O
hamper	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Old	O
Fish-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
July	O
Mr.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Monmouth-street	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
that	O
coat	O
that	O
was	O
advertis	O
'd	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
made	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
charges	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
stop	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
being	O
stolen	O
.	O
C	O
-	O
Dawson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
coat	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
made	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
me	O
for	O
18	O
s.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
fetch	O
the	O
taylor	O
that	O
made	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
advertis	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
coat	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
Monmouth-street	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
person	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
I	O
worked	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
5	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
an	O
infant	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
423	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
July	O
26	O
++	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lancaster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Summer's-key	B-place
near	I-place
Billingsgate	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Fletcher	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
.	O
Fletcher	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
drinking	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
eight	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
The	O
tankard	O
was	O
not	O
missed	O
till	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
my	O
tankard	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
examined	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Cockayne	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
counter	O
,	O
upon	O
Fletcher	O
's	O
confession	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
tankard	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
evening	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Taylor	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
Not	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
was	O
Fletcher	O
in	O
?	O
Lancaster	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
bred	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
sea	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
reputable	O
family	O
at	O
Norwich	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shot	I-pers
Clark	O
.	O
This	O
tankard	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dealer	O
and	O
chapman	O
)	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sale	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
night	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
.	O
Taylor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
friend	O
that	O
had	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
to	O
sell	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
walk	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
Fletcher	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
tankard	O
out	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
buying	O
it	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
never	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
candle	O
light	O
;	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
it	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
by	O
day-light	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
give	O
them	O
more	O
than	O
they	O
asked	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
Taylor	O
came	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
refused	O
paying	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
officer	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
Fletcher	O
was	O
either	O
gone	O
or	O
going	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
vessel	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
officer	O
came	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
Taylor	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
directly	O
said	O
that	O
Captain	O
Fletcher	O
(	O
the	O
Name	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
)	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
in	O
some	O
court	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
Am	O
I	O
safe	O
to	O
keep	O
Taylor	O
till	O
I	O
take	O
Fletcher	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
officer	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
Fletcher	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
carried	O
before	O
alderman	O
Cockayne	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
Fletcher	O
confessed	O
the	O
thing	O
and	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
his	O
exact	O
words	O
.	O
Taylor	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
met	O
Fletcher	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
and	O
he	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
The	O
tankard	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
tankard	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Fletcher	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
friend	O
from	O
Norwich	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
six	O
at	O
Night	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
again	O
about	O
seven	O
upon	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
Going	O
away	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
tankard	O
standing	O
under	O
the	O
gateway	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
a	O
little	O
poverty-struck	O
(	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
advertis	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
brother-prisoner	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
I	O
could	O
sell	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
To	O
Fletcher	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bradley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Fletcher	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Bradley	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
spent	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
too	O
and	O
again	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stanton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
any	O
robbery	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
and	O
never	O
could	O
have	O
thought	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
before	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
For	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Badman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Taylor	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
pay	O
and	O
receive	O
money	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
several	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
mast-makers	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
dight	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Story	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
fellow	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Prodey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
civil	O
fellow	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
fifteen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
apprentices	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
contrary	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
years	O
;	O
we	O
both	O
serv	O
'd	O
one	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
lad	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Fletcher	B-pers
Guilty	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
Taylor	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
424	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
Deadot	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Quane	I-pers
did	O
rob	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
with	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Deadot	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
Aug.	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
Deadot	O
Quane	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Windsor	O
in	O
my	O
carrot	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
between	O
Hounslow	B-place
Heath	I-place
and	O
Cranford	B-place
Bridge	I-place
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
hot	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
blinds	O
being	O
down	O
:	O
When	O
my	O
chariot	O
stopp	O
'd	O
I	O
fancied	O
my	O
coachman	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
water	O
the	O
horses	O
.	O
I	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
bd	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
to	O
look	O
out	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
horseback	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
pointing	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
His	O
hand	O
shook	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
expected	O
by	O
the	O
motion	O
of	O
it	O
the	O
pistol	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
off	O
every	O
minutes	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Deliver	O
up	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
How	O
your	O
bins	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
off	O
a	O
bracelet	O
from	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
spring	O
being	O
very	O
difficult	O
to	O
undo	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
it	O
off	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
blue	O
silk	O
purse	O
and	O
gave	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
were	O
nine	O
guineas	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
eight	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
,	O
Monsieur	O
Debreau	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
Windsor	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
returned	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
thought	O
,	O
about	O
26	O
s.	O
He	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
angry	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
shoot	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
of	O
this	O
business	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
robbing	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
arrested	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
hoped	O
I	O
'd	O
do	O
him	O
no	O
harm	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
should	O
do	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
as	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
examine	O
his	O
horse	O
in	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
lame	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
he	O
turned	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
lane	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
easy	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
stopped	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
chariot	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
a	O
coach	O
and	O
fix	O
with	O
some	O
servants	O
on	O
horseback	O
coming	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Sir	O
Kendal	O
Clayton	O
's	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
gentleman	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
'd	O
let	O
his	O
servants	O
go	O
to	O
help	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
highwayman	O
.	O
He	O
consented	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
horse	O
for	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
mount	O
;	O
till	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
happening	O
to	O
come	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
he	O
'd	O
lend	O
me	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
mounted	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
servants	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
Cranford	O
Bridge	O
and	O
ordered	O
my	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
hour	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
at	O
Cranford	O
Bridge	O
Bridge	O
was	O
asked	O
what	O
could	O
induce	O
him	O
to	O
vous	O
a	O
practice	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
children	O
in	O
necessity	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
know	O
you	O
in	O
?	O
D.	O
Quane	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
instantly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
but	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Justice	O
Birkhead	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
having	O
the	O
purse	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
impudence	O
to	O
deny	O
it	O
?	O
be	O
honest	O
once	O
in	O
your	O
life	O
before	O
you	O
are	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
than	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
saddle	O
upon	O
his	O
horse	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
told	O
your	O
Lordship	O
,	O
that	O
going	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
faint	O
,	O
and	O
tumbled	O
from	O
his	O
horse	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
a	O
chaise	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
his	O
chaise	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
soldier	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
stable	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
purse	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
the	O
soldier	O
play	O
'd	O
a	O
trick	O
upon	O
the	O
highwayman	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
purse	O
empty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carlton	I-pers
produces	O
a	O
purse	O
.	O
D.	O
Quane	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
purse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
own	O
the	O
robbery	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
D.	O
Quane	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
arms	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
D.	O
Quane	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
pistol	O
prodigiously	O
loaded	O
.	O
and	O
some	O
shot	O
and	O
powder	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
masked	O
or	O
unmasked	O
?	O
D.	O
Quane	O
.	O
Unmasked	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
certain	O
that	O
man	O
who	O
stands	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
might	O
he	O
be	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
your	O
chariot	O
?	O
D.	O
Quane	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
be	O
there	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
footman	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
behind	O
the	O
chariot	O
on	O
Hounslow	O
Heath	O
.	O
I	O
first	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
pretty	O
near	O
he	O
looked	O
round	O
me	O
and	O
went	O
past	O
the	O
chariot	O
,	O
and	O
peep	O
'd	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
sell	O
back	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
yards	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
very	O
strict	O
eye	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
coming	O
out	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
chariot	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
stop	O
.	O
The	O
coachman	O
said	O
,	O
ha	O
!	O
Stop	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
coachman	O
seeing	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
stopped	O
.	O
My	O
lady	O
looked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pistol	O
was	O
presented	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
the	O
chariot	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
within	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
then	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
money	O
.	O
My	O
lady	O
said	O
,	O
ha	O
!	O
Your	O
money	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
directly	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
My	O
lady	O
said	O
,	O
Very	O
well	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
blue	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
gold	O
shine	O
through	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
given	O
him	O
afterwards	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
it	O
he	O
put	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
pistol	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
on	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
chariot	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
got	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
heaths	O
he	O
turned	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
towards	O
Butchers	O
Grove	O
.	O
I	O
begged	O
of	O
my	O
lady	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pistols	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chariot	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pursue	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
coach	O
and	O
six	O
coming	O
behind	O
.	O
My	O
lady	O
desired	O
the	O
gentleman	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
horse	O
to	O
pursue	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
sent	O
his	O
two	O
servants	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
gentleman	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
my	O
lady	O
begged	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
mounted	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
a	O
brace	O
of	O
pistols	O
,	O
followed	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
and	O
half	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
servants	O
had	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
rode	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
telling	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
resign	O
I	O
would	O
blow	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
directly	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
resigned	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
tied	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Cranford	O
Bridge	O
to	O
my	O
lady	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
where	O
the	O
purse	O
was	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clayton	O
's	O
servant	O
and	O
a	O
soldier	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
purse	O
taken	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
saddle	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
again	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gascoyne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
driving	O
the	O
chariot	O
with	O
my	O
lady	O
in	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
aboat	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Hounslow	O
Heath	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
first	O
came	O
opposite	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
drew	O
his	O
horse	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
biding	O
me	O
stop	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
ha	O
!	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
stop	O
coachman	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
lady	O
putting	O
her	O
head	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
chariot	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Your	O
money	O
,	O
madam	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
his	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
cocking	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
turned	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
chariot	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
necessity	O
that	O
drove	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
done	O
this	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
gone	O
to	O
prison	O
.	O
He	O
rode	O
on	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
before	O
the	O
chariot	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
turning	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
he	O
struck	O
off	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
stopped	O
and	O
my	O
lady	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chariot	O
,	O
and	O
Sir	O
Kendal	O
Clayton	O
coming	O
by	O
with	O
two	O
servants	O
-	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
did	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
Gascoyne	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
was	O
his	O
periwig	O
?	O
Gascoyne	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
a	O
grey	O
wig	O
on	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
(	O
Which	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
one	O
)	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carlton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
,	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
coach	O
and	O
horses	O
,	O
not	O
Sir	O
Kendal	O
's	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
almost	O
to	O
the	O
eleventh	O
mile	O
stone	O
upon	O
Hounslow	O
Heath	O
some	O
people	O
on	O
foot	O
told	O
us	O
a	O
lady	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
might	O
be	O
soon	O
taken	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
chariot	O
and	O
the	O
lady	O
standing	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
stop	O
'd	O
his	O
coach	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
told	O
she	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
shewn	O
which	O
way	O
the	O
highwayman	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
They	O
desired	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
horses	O
to	O
pursue	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
accordingly	O
ordered	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
to	O
go	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dismounted	O
standing	O
by	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
robbed	O
a	O
lady	O
in	O
a	O
chariot	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
necessity	O
drove	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
we	O
'd	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
must	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
lady	O
at	O
Cranford	O
Bridge	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
there	O
?	O
Carlton	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
Reading	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
being	O
very	O
hot	O
,	O
I	O
denied	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
at	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
places	O
besides	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
some	O
cyder	O
mixed	O
,	O
what	O
we	O
call	O
on	O
board	O
shangaree	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
down	O
this	O
lane	O
thought	O
of	O
easing	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
off	O
my	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
consider	O
,	O
whether	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
so	O
great	O
a	O
crime	O
as	O
laid	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
stupid	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
off	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
blow	O
out	O
my	O
brains	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
surrender	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
by	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
horse	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
pistols	O
cock	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
at	O
once	O
.	O
The	O
reason	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
confined	O
in	O
a	O
mad	O
house	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
carried	O
that	O
every	O
day	O
to	O
defend	O
myself	O
.	O
prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Svn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
May	O
Fair	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
some	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
;	O
his	O
right	O
name	O
is	O
Savage	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
him	O
b.	O
Elizabeth	O
nton	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
L.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
drunken	O
mad	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
four	O
time	O
in	O
a	O
mad	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
this	O
affair	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
nothing	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lenton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
almost	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
mad	O
house	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
certainly	O
lost	O
his	O
reason	O
,	O
but	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
is	O
to	O
honesty	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
425	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Verity	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
quart	O
mug	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Mixter	I-pers
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Peter	O
.	O
Aug.	O
10	O
*	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Mixter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Green	I-place
Dragon	I-place
,	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
,	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
till	O
near	O
eight	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
lost	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
About	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
after	O
my	O
tankard	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
came	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
my	O
tankard	O
again	O
,	O
begging	O
of	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
the	O
tankard	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
brought	O
this	O
silver	O
mug	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
having	O
found	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
instructions	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lock	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Mixter	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
prisoner	O
either	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lock	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
received	O
two	O
letters	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
there	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
Mr.	O
Mixter	O
,	O
tankard	O
under	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
go	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Mixter	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
for	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
charged	O
us	O
with	O
being	O
privy	O
to	O
the	O
talking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
two	O
nights	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
and	O
a	O
toast	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
another	O
pint	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
another	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pewter	O
pint	O
mug	O
.	O
Then	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
to	O
enquire	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
shook	O
hands	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
call	O
again	O
another	O
time	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
come	O
that	O
way	O
I	O
will	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
man	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
at	O
present	O
waiter	O
at	O
the	O
Queen	O
's	O
Hand	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
into	O
Mr	O
.	O
Lock	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lodg	O
'd	O
;	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
called	O
,	O
Hip	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Verity	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
Mr.	O
More	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
obliged	O
to	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
tankard	O
and	O
keep	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
till	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
then	O
being	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Horshoe	O
and	O
Magpie	O
,	O
in	O
Clare-Market	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
farther	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
room	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
a	O
tankard	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
near	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
nine	O
months	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
collected	O
many	O
thousands	O
of	O
pounds	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
behav	O
'd	O
honest	O
to	O
me	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
absent	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
servant	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
behav	O
'd	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Cope	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
near	O
neighbour	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
near	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
by	O
all	O
appearance	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
then	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
behave	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bozley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
rented	O
a	O
house	O
of	O
me	O
in	O
Clothfair	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
then	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hewlet	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
I	O
trusted	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
every	O
thing	O
safe	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
letter	O
carrier	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
foreign	O
letter	O
directed	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Verity	I-pers
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
upon	O
it	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
carried	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
shew	O
'd	O
a	O
letter	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
Boulogne	O
,	O
Aug.	O
17	O
,	O
1754	O
.	O
SIR	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
bringing	O
you	O
under	O
misfortune	O
on	O
my	O
account	O
,	O
in	O
giving	O
you	O
a	O
tankard	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
this	O
opportunity	O
of	O
giving	O
you	O
a	O
line	O
,	O
certifying	O
to	O
whom	O
it	O
may	O
concern	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
Thomas	B-pers
More	I-pers
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
from	O
the	O
Green-Dragon	O
,	O
Fleetstreet	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
&	O
c.	O
Signed	O
Your	O
affectionate	O
Servant	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
426	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
July	O
19	O
+	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
427	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirteen	O
pewter	O
plates	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
August	O
.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Coleman-street	B-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
Blue	I-place
Anchor	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
London-Wall	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
thirteen	O
plates	O
in	O
July	O
,	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
particularly	O
the	O
days	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
for	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
Skinner-street	O
,	O
at	O
one	O
Wells	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
them	O
herself	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
still	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
such	O
things	O
she	O
would	O
deliver	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
the	O
plates	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
search	O
'd	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
by	O
persuading	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
girl	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
them	O
up	O
(	O
thirteen	O
plates	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
)	O
the	O
girl	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
my	O
kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
linnen	O
apron	O
at	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
one	O
Hughs	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Long-Alley	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
plates	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
4	O
d.	O
a	O
plate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
plates	O
worth	O
a-piece	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
They	O
weigh	O
'd	O
above	O
a	O
pound	O
a	O
plate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Wells	O
here	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
apron	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
apron	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
8	O
d.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
creature	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
but	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
428.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Knott	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bed	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
August	O
23	O
.	O
No	O
prosecutor	O
appear	O
'd	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
429	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Cadman	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
iron	O
bars	O
to	O
a	O
copper	O
,	O
3	O
iron	O
hinges	O
,	O
one	O
iron	O
bolt	O
and	O
ring	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
July	O
23	O
+	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Knightsbridge	B-place
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
away	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
whom	O
;	O
by	O
his	O
directions	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
and	O
sell	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
denied	O
by	O
the	O
prosecuter	O
upon	O
his	O
being	O
asked	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
430	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	O
Pollard	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
2	O
+	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pollard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Lumbert	B-place
Court	I-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	O
Adcock	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
with	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
by	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
for	O
stealing	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
breeches	O
again	O
that	O
afternoon	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
(	O
Produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
)	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Pollard	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
breeches	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
had	O
them	O
?	O
Pollard	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
them	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
there	O
?	O
Pollard	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
always	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
breeches	O
last	O
?	O
Pollard	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
hanging	O
on	O
a	O
pin	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
Mr.	O
Lediall	O
,	O
a	O
salesman	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
breeches	O
were	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
his	O
money	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
half	O
crowns	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
then	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
before	O
Justice	O
Withers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
declared	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
in	O
Lumbert-Court	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
directions	O
to	O
the	O
owner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
acknowledged	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
that	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
himself	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
acknowledge	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
breeches	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Marchant	I-pers
,	O
who	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bridgewater-Garden	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
6	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Comfort	O
Aubury	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
lately	O
?	O
Webb	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
any	O
relation	O
of	O
his	O
?	O
Webb	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
relation	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Seley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
Herefordshire	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
lately	O
?	O
Seley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
a	O
twelve-month	O
ago	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
within	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
then	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
431	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Aug.	O
27	O
++	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White-Horse	O
,	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
I	O
drive	O
post	O
chaise	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
going	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
to	O
Dartford	O
,	O
her	O
mother	O
was	O
cook	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
?	O
Roe	O
.	O
I	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Portobello	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
five	O
fields	O
,	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
August	B-pers
There	I-pers
I	O
got	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
sat	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
sat	O
by	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
?	O
Roe	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Roe	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Howard	O
awak	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Roe	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
own	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
?	O
Roe	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
she	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
there	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
recollect	O
what	O
passed	O
,	O
or	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
her	O
company	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
suspect	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Marshall	O
Court	O
officer	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
have	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
property	O
being	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
awaked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
did	O
for	O
security	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
432	O
,	O
433	O
,	O
434	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Everard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Lightholder	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
July	O
27	O
,	O
30	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Reading	I-pers
,	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
did	O
,	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
James	I-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
++	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Reading	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Clare-Market	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
look	O
about	O
I	O
should	O
miss	O
some	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
stole	O
it	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
in	O
Clement's-Lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
was	O
missing	O
near	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
still	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Lightholder	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Lightholder	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
he	O
'd	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
?	O
Reading	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Maypole-Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Wich-street	O
.	O
There	O
I	O
found	O
lead	O
that	O
answered	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
woman	O
and	O
Lightholder	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Justice	O
Bedwell	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
Everard	O
was	O
there	O
also	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
confessed	O
they	O
stole	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
owned	O
before	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
13	O
d.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
them	O
at	O
any	O
other	O
time	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
?	O
Reading	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
sign	O
a	O
petition	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
guilty	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
after	O
they	O
had	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
declare	O
the	O
only	O
carrying	O
on	O
the	O
prosecution	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
vict	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
Reading	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
woman	O
is	O
more	O
to	O
be	O
than	O
they	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
neighbours	O
desiring	O
me	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
not	O
have	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
Eliot	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
July	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
go	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Lightholder	O
had	O
a	O
tool	O
bag	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
he	O
it	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
shoulder	O
,	O
it	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
pretty	O
heavy	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
E.	O
Shepherd	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
throw	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
without	O
asking	O
any	O
questions	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
empty	O
,	O
putting	O
money	O
into	O
their	O
pockets	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Rising	O
there	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
landlord	O
where	O
hey	O
work	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Barnard	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
distiller	O
,	O
in	O
Clare-Market	O
:	O
thinking	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Barnard	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
informed	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Everard	O
's	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
30	O
pounds	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
Lightholder	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
gave	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
and	O
two	O
pence	O
half	O
penny	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
men	O
the	O
look	O
of	O
thieves	O
?	O
Eliot	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
journeymen	O
carpenters	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
tell	O
it	O
look	O
'd	O
weighty	O
?	O
Eliot	O
.	O
Because	O
lead	O
lies	O
closer	O
than	O
tools	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
a	O
custom	O
among	O
carpenters	O
to	O
have	O
lead	O
that	O
is	O
cut	O
up	O
?	O
Eliot	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Everard	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
lead	O
from	O
there	O
.	O
Lightholder	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
lead	O
among	O
some	O
old	O
rubbish	O
.	O
Shepherd	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
These	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
with	O
this	O
lead	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
old	O
lead	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
if	O
they	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
a	O
penny	O
a	O
pound	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
weighed	O
it	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
For	O
Everard	O
.	O
Kinton	O
Couse	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Everard	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
fellow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
you	O
trust	O
him	O
now	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
?	O
Reading	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
question	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Everard	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
quarter	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
near	O
the	O
Mews	O
Gate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
frequented	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
civil	O
man	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Glanvile	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Everard	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
worked	O
under	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Egerton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Evan	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Everard	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
ever	O
shall	O
esteem	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
cloaths	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
received	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
forced	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
promise	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
suspected	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
fact	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Everard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
father	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
need	O
not	O
want	O
money	O
if	O
he	O
asks	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Brian	B-pers
Dunn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Everard	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
Lightholder	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Abington	O
Buildings	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
They	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
under	O
my	O
master	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
trusted	O
my	O
life	O
in	O
either	O
of	O
their	O
hands	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
them	O
confess	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
lead	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
handed	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
evidence	O
Miles	O
there	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
Miles	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
the	O
examination	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
say	O
they	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
rubbish	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
say	O
so	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
hearing	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
before	O
they	O
confessed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
lead	O
ever	O
fitted	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
answered	O
in	O
length	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
breadth	O
,	O
that	O
being	O
altered	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Titeridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
joyner	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
Lightholder	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Titeridge	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
For	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lack	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Shepherd	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Reyner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
,	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shutlock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
six	O
Months	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
just	O
,	O
fair-dealing	O
woman	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Reyner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Drinkworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
for	O
her	O
these	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
above	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
just	O
woman	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
435	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
sixty	O
fathom	O
of	O
rope	O
,	O
called	O
tow-line	O
,	O
value	O
45	O
s.	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
ship	O
called	O
the	O
Richard	O
and	O
Jane	O
,	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
,	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
Ship	O
Richard	O
and	O
Jane	O
;	O
on	O
last	O
Monday	O
we	O
had	O
this	O
tow-line	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
Morning	O
we	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
45	O
or	O
50	O
s.	O
At	O
least	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
45	O
s.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Waterman	O
.	O
On	O
last	O
Monday	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
drinking	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
After	O
that	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Stairs	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
boat	O
and	O
pair	O
of	O
sculls	O
without	O
leave	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
at	O
King	O
James	O
's	O
Stairs	O
.	O
He	O
handed	O
down	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
tow-line	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
fathom	O
of	O
them	O
both	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
board	O
capt	O
.	O
Simpson	O
's	O
ship	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
tow-line	O
of	O
the	O
forecastle	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
sixty	O
fathom	O
;	O
we	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
down	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
's	O
just	O
before	O
Limehouse-Bridge	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
we	O
knocked	O
at	O
her	O
door	O
.	O
She	O
sent	O
her	O
servant	O
down	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
weighed	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
eight	O
hundred	O
three	O
quarters	O
and	O
fourteen	O
pound	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
30	O
s.	O
which	O
she	O
paid	O
us	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Lee	O
was	O
the	O
means	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
admitted	O
king	O
's	O
evidence	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Lee	O
sent	O
her	O
daughter	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
her	O
mother	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
for	O
receiving	O
some	O
stolen	O
rope	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
man	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
means	O
of	O
clearing	O
her	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
voluntary	O
confession	O
.	O
He	O
mentioned	O
this	O
evidence	O
as	O
being	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
stealing	O
the	O
rope	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
weighed	O
eight	O
hundred	O
three	O
quarters	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
paid	O
,	O
and	O
fourteen	O
pounds	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
paid	O
for	O
.	O
The	O
rope	O
is	O
in	O
custody	O
of	O
a	O
headborough	O
at	O
Limehouse	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
has	O
given	O
information	O
of	O
several	O
other	O
facts	O
committed	O
.	O
Ralph	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
mate	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
this	O
rope	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Lee	O
's	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Phillips	O
.	O
Twenty	O
eight	O
fathom	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
rope	O
that	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
Phillips	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
All	O
the	O
rope	O
I	O
had	O
I	O
left	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Lee	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
hatchet	O
and	O
cut	O
it	O
in	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
436	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
Money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dobbins	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
August	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Dobbins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Swallow-street	O
,	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
,	O
and	O
ply	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Gate	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
Highgate	O
from	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
and	O
another	O
were	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
life-guard	O
stables	O
in	O
Oxford-road	B-place
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
called	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
christian	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
;	O
are	O
not	O
you	O
a	O
chairman	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
winter	O
time	O
.	O
She	O
begged	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Wheatsheaf	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
they	O
chose	O
that	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
us	O
another	O
quartern	O
,	O
that	O
will	O
serve	O
us	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
buss	O
before	O
you	O
go	O
?	O
and	O
held	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
buss	O
to	O
get	O
shut	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
held	O
to	O
my	O
belly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
stirred	O
or	O
resisted	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
rip	O
me	O
open	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
?	O
Dobbins	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
away	O
towards	O
the	O
fields	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
a	O
man	O
brought	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
reward	O
to	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
reward	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
thief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
you	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Dobbins	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Stevens	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
oath	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
19th	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
taking	O
the	O
watch	O
or	O
money	O
,	O
only	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Dobbins	O
.	O
It	O
cost	O
me	O
5	O
l.	O
new	O
;	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
4	O
l.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
I	O
thanked	O
him	O
and	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
court'sy	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
good	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
nigh	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
saw	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
single	O
Felony	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
437	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
studds	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Eliz	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
+	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
twenty	O
pieces	O
of	O
pickled	O
pork	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
3	O
;	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Grigg	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
ten	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
pork	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
linen	O
cloth	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Dumbline	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
pickled	O
pork	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Leather	B-place
Lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
pork	O
butcher	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
,	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
nine	O
weeks	O
.	O
'T	O
is	O
usual	O
in	O
our	O
business	O
to	O
pickle	O
up	O
pork	O
for	O
the	O
summer	O
season	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
ten	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
pork	O
,	O
without	O
knowing	O
how	O
.	O
I	O
taxed	O
the	O
girl	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
had	O
had	O
of	O
her	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
or	O
two	O
pounds	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
of	O
pork	O
stickings	O
,	O
hogs	O
faces	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
given	O
her	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
likewise	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
two	O
other	O
pieces	O
and	O
one	O
sticking	O
to	O
Duncomb	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
pieces	O
to	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
whom	O
we	O
have	O
not	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
Clark	O
a	O
linen	O
cloth	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
heard	O
Slaughter	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
she	O
absconded	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
at	O
Battle	O
Bridge	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
she	O
grumbled	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Duncomb	O
had	O
had	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
more	O
pieces	O
than	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
pork	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
Slaughter	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
my	O
complaint	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Creech	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
pieces	O
did	O
she	O
confess	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
name	O
that	O
great	O
many	O
by	O
any	O
number	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
six	O
pieces	O
or	O
more	O
and	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
Slaughter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
lost	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wished	O
the	O
others	O
that	O
had	O
received	O
other	O
pieces	O
were	O
there	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Duncomb	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
her	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
Slaughter	O
any	O
promises	O
of	O
favour	O
before	O
she	O
confessed	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
threaten	O
before	O
she	O
did	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Josiah	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Slaughter	O
say	O
she	O
stole	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
pork	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
also	O
heard	O
Clark	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
receive	O
some	O
pork	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
Duncomb	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Gardner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
William	O
Cramplin	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Slaughter	O
say	O
,	O
She	O
has	O
stole	O
pork	O
from	O
her	O
master	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Cramplin	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
them	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Manwaring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
to	O
Newgate	O
to	O
see	O
Mary	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
;	O
she	O
there	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
meat	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pounds	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Meat	O
?	O
Manwaring	O
.	O
Pickled	O
pork	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
receivers	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
heard	O
Clark	O
or	O
Duncomb	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Manwaring	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Rose	O
Sutherland	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
has	O
often	O
offered	O
pork	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
Duncomb	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Whitall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Peg	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
's	O
house	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
three	O
Stickings	O
of	O
pork	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
which	O
way	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Whitall	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
mother-in-law	O
gave	O
her	O
them	O
.	O
Slaughter	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
sent	O
a	O
woman	O
for	O
some	O
pork	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
.	O
Clark	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
sent	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
for	O
pork	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
went	O
always	O
of	O
her	O
own	O
accord	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
sent	O
for	O
any	O
.	O
Slaughter	O
and	O
Clark	O
guilty	O
,	O
Duncomb	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
438	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jer	B-pers
.	I-pers
Main	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
passage	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Mary	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
two	O
calicoe	O
window-curtains	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Crush	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
,	O
August	O
17	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
marsh	O
wall	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
mill	O
,	O
at	O
Poplar	B-place
,	O
walking	O
along	O
I	O
was	O
alone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
place	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
Is	O
it	O
a	O
lone	O
place	O
,	O
or	O
among	O
houses	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
no	O
houses	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
an	O
open	O
field	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
calicoe	O
curtains	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crush	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
and	O
stopped	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
a	O
boat	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
rushes	O
,	O
betwixt	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
and	O
the	O
bank	O
,	O
without	O
saying	O
another	O
word	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
used	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
indecent	O
manner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
continue	O
there	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
both	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
rushes	O
together	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crush	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
did	O
he	O
walk	O
with	O
you	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
yards	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
threw	O
me	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
at	O
getting	O
over	O
a	O
stile	O
,	O
my	O
bundle	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
it	O
would	O
tire	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
did	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
after	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crush	O
's	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
pull	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
up	O
an	O
alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
betwixt	O
the	O
rushes	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Crush	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
No	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crush	O
's	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
complaint	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
curtains	O
,	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
refused	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
three	O
pence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
just	O
after	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ditch	O
;	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
tied	O
round	O
the	O
curtains	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
Bundle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
pistol	O
he	O
had	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
strike	O
you	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
'd	O
treat	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
myself	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
look	O
odd	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
treat	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Crush	O
's	O
sister	O
in	O
East-Lane	O
,	O
Greenwich	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
been	O
of	O
that	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
did	O
he	O
throw	O
you	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
stile	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
and	O
pulled	O
me	O
in	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
wet	O
or	O
dry	O
ditch	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
muddy	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
both	O
very	O
dirty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
fuddled	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
Really	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
miller	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
by	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
miller	O
at	O
his	O
gate	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Hallow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
call	O
to	O
the	O
miller	O
to	O
assist	O
you	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
as	O
bad	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crush	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
not	O
ask	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
publick	O
house	O
to	O
drink	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
several	O
alehouses	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
farthest	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
before	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
pretty	O
long	O
street	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
singing	O
and	O
whistling	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
Mr.	O
Crush	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Foster	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
past	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Crush	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
this	O
girl	O
was	O
sent	O
from	O
her	O
mistress	O
,	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
for	O
two	O
callicoe	O
curtains	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
Foxes	O
in	O
Narrow-street	O
,	O
Ratcliff	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
made	O
her	O
sit	O
down	O
and	O
eat	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
butter	O
,	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
dish	O
of	O
tea	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
way	O
she	O
has	O
here	O
mentioned	O
,	O
for	O
Greenwich	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
curtains	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
crying	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
stop	O
'd	O
and	O
used	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
that	O
stop	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
betwixt	O
a	O
shed	O
and	O
a	O
necessary	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
We	O
seized	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
design	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
?	O
Crush	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
understand	O
by	O
her	O
complaint	O
?	O
Crush	O
.	O
I	O
understood	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
used	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
robbery	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Crush	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
her	O
losing	O
the	O
curtains	O
or	O
3	O
d	O
?	O
Crush	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Crush	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
bundle	O
?	O
Hone	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dropped	O
the	O
bundle	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
girl	O
came	O
over	O
the	O
stile	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a-dry	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
3	O
d.	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
returned	O
her	O
her	O
3	O
d.	O
again	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
return	O
you	O
your	O
3	O
d.	O
again	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Crush	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
18	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
6	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
that	O
ago	O
?	O
Gibson	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
year	O
or	O
ten	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
he	O
behaved	O
since	O
?	O
Gibson	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
?	O
Sarah	B-pers
Powers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
keep	O
the	O
Foxes	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
now	O
Mr.	O
Crush	O
has	O
.	O
The	O
same	O
night	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
came	O
into	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
seemingly	O
in	O
a	O
civil	O
manner	O
;	O
no	O
man	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
bundle	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
man	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Crush	O
and	O
other	O
people	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
declared	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
bundle	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
helping	O
her	O
over	O
the	O
stile	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
fol	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
'd	O
carry	O
it	O
,	O
fearing	O
it	O
should	O
tire	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
consented	O
to	O
his	O
carrying	O
it	O
?	O
S.	O
Powers	O
.	O
