TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
2d	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
and	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
MARCH	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
27th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1754	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1754	O
,	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Kings	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RAWLINSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
MARTIN	O
WRIGHT	O
*	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	O
ADAMS	O
+	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
Country	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
,	O
Andrew	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Westwood	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stent	I-pers
,	O
Josiah	B-pers
Seal	I-pers
,	O
Gregory	B-pers
Pember	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Belden	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bagshaw	I-pers
,	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Poulter	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bagnell	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Dechamps	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jumard	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sarsfield	I-pers
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Pearce	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
,	O
Moses	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Roby	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bramell	I-pers
.	O
152	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Twigg	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Barnard	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
Barnard	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Ludgate-Hill	B-place
,	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
suspected	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
open	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
gloves	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
:	O
The	O
lace	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
another	O
servant	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
nor	O
can	O
I	O
tell	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
[	O
the	O
gloves	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
]	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
parcel	O
which	O
was	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
dining-room	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
at	O
a	O
funeral	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
floor	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Appleyard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
trusted	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
living	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Appleyard	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
behaved	O
herself	O
well	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
fellow	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Appleyard	O
's	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
behaved	O
well	O
then	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
153	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Talwood	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Talwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Leonard	I-place
's	I-place
,	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Hackney	I-place
Road	I-place
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
great	O
parcel	O
of	O
hay	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
litter	O
which	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Bethnal-Green	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
hay	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
watchmen	O
had	O
taken	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
there	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
hay	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
bundles	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
two	O
trusses	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Ass	O
and	O
Fowl	O
in	O
Hog-Lane	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Alavine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bethnal-Green	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
with	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
hay	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
Going	O
farther	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
bundles	O
more	O
lying	O
within	O
some	O
rails	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
come	O
back	O
from	O
carrying	O
that	O
bundle	O
to	O
Hog-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
,	O
by	O
following	O
the	O
track	O
of	O
the	O
hay	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
a	O
bed	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
154	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Braines	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
quilt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
pottage	O
pot	O
with	O
a	O
copper	O
cover	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Belsey	I-pers
,	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Feb.	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
155	O
,	O
156	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Purney	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bradlen	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
salver	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holles	I-pers
,	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
his	O
Grace	O
the	O
Duke	O
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
butler	O
to	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
are	O
chimney-sweepers	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
sweep	O
the	O
chimnies	O
up	O
stairs	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
silver	O
salver	O
,	O
it	O
had	O
his	O
grace	O
's	O
arms	O
and	O
crest	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
Bradley	O
,	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
broke	O
it	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
by	O
this	O
means	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
that	O
part	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
arms	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
these	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
confession	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
constable	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
salver	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
From	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
butler	O
's	O
pantry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
chimney	O
swept	O
in	O
the	O
butler	O
's	O
pantry	O
?	O
Turner	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
or	O
9th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
's	O
boy	O
brought	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
pieces	O
to	O
me	O
all	O
dirty	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
what	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
by	O
weight	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
they	O
have	O
all	O
black	O
faces	O
alike	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Burchel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
piece	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
's	O
boy	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
[	O
holding	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
]	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
cleaned	O
the	O
blackness	O
off	O
,	O
weighed	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
comes	O
to	O
eight	O
penny	O
weight	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
his	O
stature	O
and	O
voice	O
answers	O
to	O
his	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
,	O
[	O
he	O
takes	O
up	O
the	O
foot	O
]	O
a	O
woman	O
brought	O
this	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Grace	B-pers
Walford	I-pers
.	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
son	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
has	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
salver	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
does	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
.	O
About	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
a	O
chimney-sweeper	O
's	O
boy	O
brought	O
this	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
all	O
over	O
dirt	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
,	O
weighed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
3	O
s.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
buy	O
himself	O
a	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
then	O
in	O
his	O
shirt	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hinemarsh	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
[	O
she	O
takes	O
up	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
]	O
this	O
seems	O
to	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
salver	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Purney	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
other	O
piece	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
little	O
chimney-sweeper	O
's	O
boy	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
his	O
behind	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
boy	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
his	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
Purney	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Duke	O
of	O
Newcastle	O
's	O
sweeping	O
some	O
chimnies	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
little	O
boy	O
took	O
the	O
salver	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pantry	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
concealed	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
broke	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
disposed	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
shew	O
where	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
concealed	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
Scotland-Yard	O
below	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
common	O
shore	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
piece	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
mud	O
,	O
that	O
has	O
the	O
arms	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
disposed	O
of	O
?	O
Burnet	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hinemarsh	O
's	O
facing	O
Durham-Yard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
piece	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Purney	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
thing	O
being	O
taken	O
.	O
Purney	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
Bradley	O
acquit	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
157	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Martha	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
shift	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Martha	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
My	I-pers
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
James	B-pers
Clay	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Crutched-Friars	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
charity	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Humerton	O
last	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
strict	O
order	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
designing	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
turnpike	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
there	O
,	O
or	O
come	O
near	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
my	O
son	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
my	O
London	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
some	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
given	O
away	O
.	O
Fanny	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Clay	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
bid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
to	O
White-Chapel	O
turnpike	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
bundle	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
bundle	O
was	O
gone	O
likewise	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
about	O
her	O
neck	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
then	O
own	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Clay	O
,	O
and	O
accidentally	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
about	O
her	O
neck	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
there	O
was	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
two	O
creatures	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Castle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wardley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
who	O
delivered	O
the	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
shift	O
and	O
two	O
coloured	O
aprons	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
them	O
without	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
here	O
?	O
Wardley	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
158	O
,	O
159	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Wessbrook	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Isaac	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
Richard	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
January	O
26	O
,	O
1753	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cloth-Fair	O
,	O
am	O
of	O
no	O
business	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
5th	O
,	O
or	O
6th	O
was	O
twelvemonth	O
,	O
just	O
past	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Old-street	O
from	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
office	O
;	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
middle	O
walk	O
in	O
Moor-Fields	B-place
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
past	O
eight	O
;	O
then	O
three	O
men	O
more	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
money	O
,	O
(	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
sticks	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
else	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sticks	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
ever	O
since	O
)	O
[	O
holding	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
]	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
me	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
stunned	O
down	O
with	O
one	O
blow	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
rifle	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
glove	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
)	O
then	O
one	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
somebody	O
coming	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
will	O
cut	O
all	O
the	O
cloaths	O
off	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
have	O
almost	O
killed	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
speak	O
another	O
word	O
we	O
will	O
kill	O
you	O
quite	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
by	O
cutting	O
the	O
glove	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
string	O
,	O
seal	O
,	O
and	O
key	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Then	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
drive	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
call	O
after	O
them	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
back	O
and	O
murder	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
evidence	O
was	O
taken	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
confessed	O
nothing	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
Harper	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
remember	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
partly	O
of	O
a	O
size	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Palace	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale-shop	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
January	O
53	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
George	B-pers
Hose	I-pers
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
(	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
an	O
afternoon	O
)	O
he	O
asked	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
l.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
worth	O
above	O
50	O
s.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
an	O
old	O
watch	O
that	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
fetch	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
saying	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
family	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
old	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
A	O
night	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
I	O
read	O
in	O
the	O
Advertiser	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
name	O
Ingraham	O
,	O
describing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
the	O
advertisement	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
him	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
as	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
mentioned	O
]	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
him	O
:	O
But	O
it	O
past	O
on	O
till	O
the	O
same	O
month	O
the	O
next	O
year	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
George	B-pers
Hore	I-pers
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
cheapened	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
pistols	O
in	O
my	O
glass-case	O
of	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
did	O
not	O
recollect	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
Hore	O
said	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
your	O
servant	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
you	O
should	O
use	O
me	O
well	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
before	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
think	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
sold	O
you	O
a	O
watch	O
once	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
instead	O
of	O
selling	O
you	O
one	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
an	O
exchange	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
very	O
right	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
buy	O
my	O
own	O
watch	O
of	O
you	O
again	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
his	O
heart	O
.	O
Then	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
two	O
men	O
that	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
trade	O
with	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
case	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
and	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
then	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
desire	O
you	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
is	O
a	O
robber	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
produce	O
pe	O
ople	O
enough	O
to	O
his	O
honesty	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
not	O
expose	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
his	O
friends	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Rickards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
till	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Justices	O
sit	O
in	O
White-Chapel	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Westbrook	O
and	O
Arnold	O
were	O
brought	O
there	O
.	O
Hore	O
looked	O
Westbrook	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Justices	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
heartily	O
sorry	O
for	O
Westbrook	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
know	O
of	O
our	O
robbing	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
having	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
by	O
chance	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Westbrook	O
went	O
from	O
them	O
in	O
fifteen	O
minutes	O
after	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
whoever	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
booty	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
old	O
watch	O
he	O
kept	O
himself	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hore	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
January	O
53	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
met	O
Isaac	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
some	O
purl	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
low	O
,	O
they	O
offered	O
to	O
treat	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
and	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pints	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
Arnold	O
promising	O
to	O
call	O
on	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
some	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
get	O
no	O
business	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
startled	O
me	O
very	O
much	O
:	O
I	O
refused	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
as	O
night	O
was	O
coming	O
on	O
,	O
with	O
Isaac	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
.	O
We	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
we	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
Westbrook	O
together	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
four	O
agreed	O
to	O
drink	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
's	O
Head	O
in	O
Bull-and-Mouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
Summers	O
and	O
Arnold	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
started	O
the	O
question	O
to	O
Westbrook	O
and	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
rob	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
we	O
met	O
.	O
Being	O
in	O
liquor	O
we	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
Summers	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
Arnold	O
had	O
a	O
screw	O
barrel	O
pistol	O
.	O
We	O
walked	O
about	O
to	O
where	O
Summers	O
and	O
Arnold	O
took	O
us	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
into	O
Gough	O
Square	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
.	O
Summers	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
see	O
a	O
servant	O
maid	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
cup	O
or	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
people	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
for	O
beer	O
with	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
knock	O
her	O
down	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
Summers	O
proposed	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
Moor-Fields	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
we	O
met	O
.	O
Westbrook	O
agreed	O
as	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
together	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
whom	O
we	O
past	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Westbrook	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
others	O
insisted	O
on	O
our	O
staying	O
.	O
So	O
we	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
the	O
middle	O
quarter	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Harper	O
;	O
Arnold	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
had	O
just	O
struck	O
eight	O
;	O
then	O
Arnold	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
then	O
Summers	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
him	O
against	O
the	O
pales	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
insisted	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
they	O
felt	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
clapped	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
drawing	O
it	O
down	O
felt	O
something	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
Then	O
Arnold	O
pulled	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
cut	O
all	O
the	O
cloths	O
off	O
his	O
back	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
glove	O
and	O
string	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
slip	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
thought	O
nobody	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
the	O
fingers	O
of	O
the	O
glove	O
to	O
Summers	O
,	O
and	O
Westbrook	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
money	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
walked	O
up	O
Houndsditch	O
and	O
into	O
White	O
Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
all	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
Minories	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
?	O
Hore	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
all	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Friday-street	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Isaac	B-pers
Summers	I-pers
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
Arnold	O
and	O
Summers	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Arnold	O
where	O
Summers	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
Summers	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
it	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Then	O
Arnold	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
both	O
refused	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
it	O
was	O
proposed	O
,	O
whoever	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
should	O
have	O
Westbrook	O
's	O
part	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
25	O
s	O
and	O
a	O
shagreen	O
watch	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
18	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Palace	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
true	O
?	O
Palace	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
an	O
18	O
s.	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Evidence	O
continues	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Summers	O
the	O
18	O
s.	O
piece	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
to	O
be	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
had	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
shagreen	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
together	O
.	O
Cross-Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
declared	O
Westbrook	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
you	O
were	O
about	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Hore	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
before	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
declared	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
Westbrook	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
sight	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Hore	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
discovered	O
?	O
Hore	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
year	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
discovered	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
robbery	O
?	O
[	O
To	O
this	O
question	O
be	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
direct	O
answer	O
,	O
although	O
asked	O
him	O
three	O
times	O
over	O
,	O
but	O
prevaricated	O
,	O
and	O
talked	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
fuddled	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Your	O
art	O
is	O
seen	O
in	O
evading	O
this	O
question	O
:	O
Pray	O
answer	O
this	O
plain	O
question	O
,	O
on	O
what	O
occasion	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Castle	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
January	O
last	O
?	O
Hore	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
pistols	O
for	O
Arnold	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
providenc	O
it	O
was	O
prevented	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
should	O
very	O
likely	O
have	O
done	O
some	O
mischief	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
tell	O
them	O
you	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
watch	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
but	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
watch	O
?	O
Hore	O
.	O
Summers	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
offered	O
two	O
guineas	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Briscoe	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
an	O
account	O
you	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
?	O
Hore	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Westbrook	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Arnold	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Westbrook	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
under	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
.	O
I	O
also	O
have	O
known	O
George	O
Hore	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
bedfellow	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
he	O
related	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
Westbrook	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
met	O
him	O
very	O
promiscuously	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
their	O
design	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
cocks	O
fight	O
in	O
Moor-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
because	O
Summers	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
mention	O
two	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
own	O
life	O
.	O
Westbrook	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Best	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Westbrook	O
by	O
sight	O
,	O
his	O
brother	O
is	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
this	O
Hore	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
Westbrook	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
either	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
fuddled	O
he	O
knew	O
not	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
from	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wynne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Best	O
and	O
Westbrook	O
's	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
Hore	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Westbrook	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
your	O
brother	O
Frank	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
innocent	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
much	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
they	O
attacked	O
the	O
man	O
Westbrook	O
was	O
gone	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
working	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
loses	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
can	O
get	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
him	O
innocent	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cleaver	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Westbrook	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
diligent	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Steed	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
sixteen	O
or	O
seventeen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
character	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Parnel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
industrious	O
fellow	O
.	O
Hore	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
he	O
received	O
no	O
benefit	O
by	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
being	O
an	O
apprentice	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
or	O
privy	O
to	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Westbrook	O
in	O
Town	O
and	O
Country	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
soberest	O
of	O
the	O
sort	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pretty	O
workman	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Whitton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
industrious	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
imagine	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
as	O
is	O
laid	O
to	O
his	O
charge	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Edan	O
.	O
He	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
other	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
from	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lambeth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Arnold	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
;	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
near	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Hotskins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
good	O
boy	O
in	O
working	O
for	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Arnold	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
his	O
mother	O
where	O
he	O
lives	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
far	O
from	O
doing	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
John	B-pers
How	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
well-behaved	O
lad	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
fourteen	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
'till	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
street-robbery	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Angel-street	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
Arnold	O
three	O
summers	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
three	O
winters	O
at	O
several	O
houses	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
industrious	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Arnold	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
industrious	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
sober	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cruff	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Arnold	O
upwards	O
of	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
industrious	O
:	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
wholly	O
maintained	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
brother	O
and	O
sister	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
him	O
any	O
way	O
inclinable	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Green-Arbour-Court	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Arnold	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sober	O
and	O
hard	O
working	O
fellow	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
commit	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Hartle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Arnold	O
sixteen	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
lad	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
committing	O
a	O
street-robbery	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Neel	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Arnold	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
:	O
I	O
always	O
believed	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
lad	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
commit	O
a	O
street-robbery	O
.	O
Agnes	B-pers
Rockall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Arnold	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
industrious	O
lad	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
word	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
street-robbery	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Willet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Arnold	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
getting	O
a	O
livelihood	O
for	O
himself	O
and	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
Westbrook	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Arnold	B-pers
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
160	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Finsley	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
linnen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
About	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
linnen	O
check	O
aprons	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
hedge	O
at	O
Barnet	B-place
;	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
my	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
nobody	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
:	O
she	O
being	O
a	O
loose	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
we	O
looked	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
barn	O
at	O
Finchley	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
aprons	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
hedge	O
and	O
had	O
hid	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
she	O
mentioned	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
aprons	O
were	O
these	O
?	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
was	O
laid	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
161	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Humphreys	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
twenty-five	O
Shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
.	O
Jan.	O
29	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
sawyer	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
saw	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
saw	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
yard	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
about	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
Thomas	O
Quick	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
the	O
turnpike	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
marks	O
were	O
on	O
it	O
?	O
Sharp	O
.	O
The	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
Billicom	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
slaw	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
last	O
summer	O
,	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Quick	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
some	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Quick	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Quick	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
saw	O
into	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
owner	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
and	O
afraid	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
saw	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
owner	O
before	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
inquiry	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
owner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
saw	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Quick	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
saw	O
,	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
Bellicom	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Sharp	O
claimed	O
it	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Culom	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
saw	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
Quick	O
.	O
Quick	O
and	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
worked	O
together	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
must	O
have	O
the	O
saw	O
or	O
money	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
agreed	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
Quick	O
gave	O
him	O
his	O
half	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
saw	O
,	O
and	O
Quick	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
half	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Unwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
fourteen	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
drawn	O
beer	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
ever	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pallit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
kept	O
very	O
good	O
hours	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
worthy	O
,	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
162	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Tobin	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Woods	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Tobin	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Woods	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
returning	O
from	O
transportation	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
her	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
record	O
of	O
her	O
conviction	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
the	O
purport	O
of	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
1748	O
,	O
was	O
in	O
due	O
course	O
of	O
law	O
tried	O
for	O
a	O
capital	O
felony	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
goal-delivery	O
for	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
convicted	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
death	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
it	O
appeared	O
,	O
she	O
received	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
royal	O
mercy	O
,	O
upon	O
condition	O
of	O
transportation	O
for	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
which	O
she	O
accepted	O
upon	O
that	O
condition	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Court	O
did	O
award	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
following	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
town-clerk	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
tried	O
and	O
convicted	O
as	O
here	O
mentioned	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
the	O
Court	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bristol	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
near	O
two	O
years	O
in	O
Newgate	O
in	O
Bristol	O
at	O
or	O
about	O
1748	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
custody	O
of	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Court	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
a	O
capital	O
felony	O
before	O
Sir	O
Michael	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
remember	O
her	O
being	O
under	O
sentence	O
of	O
transportation	O
afterwards	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
vessel	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
Whitare	O
;	O
the	O
ship	O
belonged	O
to	O
Benson	O
of	O
Biddeford	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Perrit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
night	O
constable	O
in	O
Bristol	O
when	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
convicted	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
tried	O
there	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
near	O
five	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
for	O
picking	O
one	O
farmer	O
Hewit	O
's	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
death	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
and	O
desired	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
receive	O
sentence	O
of	O
transportation	O
for	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
I	O
had	O
business	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
Bridges-street	O
,	O
I	O
there	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
large	O
;	O
I	O
apprehended	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
name	O
is	O
not	O
Conner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Captain	O
Lancey	B-pers
,	O
now	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
named	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
drowned	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
ship	O
Nightingale	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
captain	O
.	O
Lancey	O
being	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
at	O
the	O
sessions	O
of	O
admiralty	O
,	O
held	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
this	O
inst	O
.	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
the	O
remarkable	O
trial	O
of	O
Lancey	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
admiralty-paper	O
,	O
published	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church-yard	O
.	O
162	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Richard	B-pers
Parham	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
bodily	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one-silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
.	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Parham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cold-bath-fields	O
,	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
her	O
aunt	O
at	O
the	O
Half-moon	O
Tavern	O
,	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
below	O
the	O
Bars	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
o'clock	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
ordered	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Hockley-in-the-Hole	B-place
the	O
coach	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
fired	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
words	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
we	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
lean	O
'd	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
drive	O
on	O
coachman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
three	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
th	O
ey	O
were	O
on	O
foot	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
and	O
advertised	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
two	O
guineas	O
reward	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
Feb.	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
and	O
another	O
gentleman	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
Kimbershaw	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
small	O
crystal	O
stone	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
,	O
at	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
about	O
two	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
plaid	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
blue-grey	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
over	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
keep	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
secure	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
business	O
at	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
:	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
stood	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
on	O
his	O
examination	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
with	O
one	O
Wilson	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
the	O
description	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
had	O
given	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
his	O
dress	O
that	O
pawned	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
clerk	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
to	O
come	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
my	O
watch	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
and	O
Wilson	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
again	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
and	O
examined	O
about	O
my	O
robbery	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Davison	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
,	O
Wilson	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
Dean	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Can	O
he	O
swear	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
?	O
Parham	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
his	O
voice	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
His	O
is	O
like	O
the	O
voice	O
that	O
said	O
,	O
Drive	O
on	O
coachman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lamp	O
by	O
us	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Parham	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
took	O
Mr.	O
Parham	O
's	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
New-Prison	O
afterwards	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
overagainst	O
a	O
lamp	O
in	O
Hockley-in-the-Hole	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
were	O
stopped	O
by	O
three	O
fellows	O
;	O
one	O
fired	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
oath	O
said	O
,	O
Deliver	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
said	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
my	O
husband	O
for	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
said	O
we	O
were	O
dead	O
people	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Parham	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
use	O
us	O
ill	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
all	O
we	O
have	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
gave	O
him	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
answered	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
giving	O
me	O
half-pence	O
,	O
or	O
three	O
halfpence	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
no	O
half-pence	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
coach-door	O
was	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lean	O
'd	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
of	O
seeing	O
his	O
face	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
lamp	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
dark	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
pistol	O
loaded	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Parham	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
had	O
nothing	O
but	O
powder	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
took	O
your	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
keeper	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
leave	O
to	O
drink	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
rob	O
us	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
fire	O
a	O
pistol	O
?	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
me	O
:	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
amongst	O
a	O
hundred	O
persons	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
picked	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
blue	O
grey	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
plaid	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
over	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
every	O
thing	O
then	O
on	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
described	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Davison	O
.	O
Thirty-six	O
shillings	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Chatham	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
well	O
known	O
in	O
Bishopsgate	O
street	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
inquired	O
at	O
such	O
an	O
inn	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
pressed	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
pawn	O
his	O
watch	O
to	O
get	O
down	O
another	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
have	O
distinguished	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
multitude	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Davison	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
I	O
could	O
amongst	O
an	O
hundred	O
men	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
six	O
nights	O
locked	O
down	O
under	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
admitted	O
to	O
come	O
between	O
the	O
gates	O
;	O
so	O
the	O
woman	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
the	O
night	O
they	O
were	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
supper	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Nicholas	O
's	O
in	O
Old-street	O
,	O
from	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
'till	O
three	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farrier	O
in	O
Goswell	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
ten	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
he	O
drove	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
undertaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Old-street	O
;	O
I	O
imploy	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
drove	O
many	O
times	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
character	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
blemish	O
on	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
last	O
man	O
I	O
should	O
think	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
highway-robbery	O
.	O
Isaac	O
Dimsdel	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
coaches	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
bore	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
as	O
faithfully	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
of	O
his	O
profession	O
ever	O
did	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Frances	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
seen	O
him	O
every	O
day	O
almost	O
,	O
except	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carrier	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
years	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
bore	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
character	O
as	O
any	O
young	O
fellow	O
on	O
earth	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rearsby	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
in	O
the	O
Marshal	O
's	O
Court	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
money	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
a-robbing	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
coach	O
and	O
horses	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
nine	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
as	O
soon	O
have	O
suspected	O
my	O
own	O
brother	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
as	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nolton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
coaches	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
good	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
much	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
wronged	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
or	O
used	O
horses	O
bad	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
these	O
last	O
three	O
months	O
?	O
Nolton	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Weoley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
master	O
coachman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
I	O
believe	O
thirteen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
eight	O
months	O
and	O
two	O
days	O
he	O
behaved	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
servant	O
I	O
ever	O
had	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
eleven	O
years	O
ago	O
since	O
he	O
drove	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dunsdale	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
honestly	O
and	O
justly	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
an	O
ill	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachmaster	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
near	O
twenty	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
'till	O
this	O
happened	O
:	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
George	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Clerk	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
.	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Wiltshire	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
present	O
I	O
am	O
at	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Feb.	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
to	O
Cavendish-square	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
Old	B-place
Pound	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
we	O
were	O
sitting	O
with	O
our	O
backs	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
the	O
shutter	O
was	O
up	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
or	O
off-side	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
shutter	O
was	O
down	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
Dean	O
pass	O
by	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
moon	O
shone	O
so	O
very	O
bright	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
fair	O
view	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
then	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
horses	O
head	O
,	O
by	O
reaching	O
over	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
perceived	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
long	O
horse-pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
coach	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
immediately	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
coach-door	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
and	O
behave	O
quietly	O
,	O
for	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
endeavouring	O
to	O
get	O
out	O
at	O
that	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
use	O
us	O
like	O
gentlemen	O
;	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
shutter	O
on	O
my	O
side	O
was	O
let	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Wilson	O
looked	O
in	O
and	O
presented	O
a	O
small	O
pistol	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
motion	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
from	O
my	O
breast	O
:	O
he	O
demanded	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
shillings	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
to	O
feel	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
although	O
then	O
in	O
my	O
fob	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
after	O
eleven	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
they	O
in	O
rifling	O
you	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
by	O
their	O
shape	O
,	O
their	O
voices	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
eyes	O
or	O
ears	O
can	O
tell	O
by	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
being	O
so	O
soon	O
after	O
taken	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lost	O
the	O
idea	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Wilson	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
patch	O
under	O
his	O
left	O
eye	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
also	O
remarked	O
the	O
horse	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
one	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
brass	O
barrel	O
.	O
Dean	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
rifled	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
.	O
He	O
leaving	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
we	O
both	O
got	O
out	O
.	O
Immediately	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
we	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
run	O
down	O
a	O
narrow	O
street	O
.	O
We	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
secured	O
under	O
a	O
lamp	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
the	O
high	O
constable	O
and	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
other	O
constables	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
four	O
minutes	O
after	O
they	O
left	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
called	O
out	O
thieves	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
described	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
them	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
answered	O
our	O
descriptions	O
perfectly	O
.	O
The	O
black	O
patch	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
fallen	O
off	O
Wilson	O
's	O
face	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
constables	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
fresh	O
knocked	O
off	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
lodged	O
in	O
New	O
Prison	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
February	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Dean	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
awaked	O
by	O
his	O
opening	O
the	O
coach	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
a	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
observed	O
a	O
long	O
brass	O
barrel	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
moon	O
)	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
drew	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
light-coloured	O
coat	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
am	O
positively	O
sure	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
demand	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
,	O
being	O
entirely	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
Dean	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
plainly	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
the	O
moon	O
,	O
I	O
imagine	O
they	O
were	O
with	O
us	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
minutes	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
we	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
exciseman	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
we	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
went	O
down	O
a	O
narrow	O
street	O
.	O
We	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
positive	O
to	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
particularly	O
described	O
Dean	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
January	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
was	O
out	O
with	O
several	O
of	O
us	O
to	O
search	O
bad	O
houses	O
for	O
disorderly	O
people	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
Puckeridge-street	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
being	O
foremost	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
coming	O
along	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
asked	O
who	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
they	O
gave	O
no	O
answer	O
,	O
but	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
;	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
I	O
saw	O
they	O
had	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Dean	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
said	O
this	O
fellow	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
pistol	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
Wilson	O
)	O
I	O
left	O
Dean	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
two	O
other	O
constables	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Wilson	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
then	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
he	O
put	O
this	O
pistol	O
to	O
my	O
breast	O
[	O
producing	O
a	O
small	O
pocket	O
pistol	O
]	O
and	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
examining	O
it	O
afterwards	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
loaded	O
with	O
powder	O
and	O
ball	O
,	O
and	O
primed	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
constable	O
that	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
found	O
another	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
came	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
with	O
a	O
sword	O
drawn	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
stopped	O
them	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
minutes	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
describe	O
Dean	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Hen	O
.	O
Flanerkin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
given	O
by	O
Smith	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
deposed	O
to	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
where	O
Dean	O
was	O
first	O
stopped	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
Wilson	O
was	O
first	O
stopped	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
patch	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
found	O
afterwards	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
headborough	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
and	O
others	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
]	O
Joshua	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
evidences	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
one	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
sung	O
a	O
good	O
song	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
(	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
)	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
meant	O
me	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
lady	O
,	O
who	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
they	O
stopped	O
us	O
we	O
were	O
singing	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Murphy	O
farther	O
added	O
,	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
stopped	O
Dean	O
he	O
heard	O
something	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
secured	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
long	O
pistol	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
produced	O
]	O
Dean	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
having	O
offended	O
no	O
body	O
,	O
was	O
stopped	O
by	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
Wilson	O
tried	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
479	O
,	O
in	O
Alderman	O
Blackford	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
them	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Lane	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
capitally	O
convicted	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
on	O
that	O
.	O
164	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
scissers	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fry	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
evidence	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
candles	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
scissers	O
were	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
ground	O
at	O
the	O
cutler	O
's	O
who	O
before	O
had	O
ground	O
them	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
intelligence	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
and	O
committed	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
165	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Winter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Blackey	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Holborn	B-place
,	O
one	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
told	O
him	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
person	O
pick	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
this	O
be	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
his	O
wife	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
166	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Feb.	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Fleet-street	B-place
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
near	O
me	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
immediately	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
evidence	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
me	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
the	O
fact	O
being	O
committed	O
there	O
.	O
Coming	O
along	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
stick	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
retook	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
[	O
producing	O
it	O
in	O
court	O
]	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
if	O
ever	O
he	O
got	O
his	O
liberty	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
meet	O
me	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
field	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
fine	O
sport	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
and	O
dragged	O
me	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
prisoner	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
,	O
he	O
thanked	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
staid	O
at	O
home	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
hanged	O
in	O
three	O
sessions	O
more	O
.	O
167	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
Mackansey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
February	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Catharine	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
ribbon	O
for	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
staid	O
on	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
found	O
fault	O
with	O
the	O
colour	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
dark	O
blue	O
ribbon	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
worth	O
of	O
green	O
silk	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
mazarine	O
blue	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
I	O
immediately	O
sent	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
she	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
ribbon	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
denied	O
having	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
child	O
with	O
her	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
mamma	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
your	O
lap	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
there	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
C.	O
Johnson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
exactly	O
tell	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
yards	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
safely	O
say	O
there	O
was	O
above	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
is	O
my	O
mamma	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
[	O
She	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
her	O
mamma	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whilst	O
her	O
mamma	O
was	O
reaching	O
the	O
green	O
silk	O
,	O
slide	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
mazarine	O
blue	O
ribbon	O
into	O
her	O
lap	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
asked	O
the	O
man	O
whether	O
it	O
should	O
b	O
e	O
dark	O
green	O
ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
laid	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
ribbon	O
,	O
nor	O
had	O
any	O
man	O
there	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
168	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
stone	O
weight	O
of	O
rough	O
tallow	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
February	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
169	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
pewter	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
pewterer	O
's	O
plate	O
block	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Newham	I-pers
.	O
January	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Newham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New	B-place
street	I-place
by	I-place
Shoe-lane	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
pewterer	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Having	O
missed	O
some	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
suspected	O
my	O
apprentice	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
staid	O
out	O
late	O
of	O
nights	O
.	O
My	O
apprentice	O
after	O
this	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
things	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
[	O
producing	O
six	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
pewter	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
plate	O
block	O
]	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
turnings	O
of	O
pewter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
I	O
am	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
apprentice	O
,	O
knowing	O
myself	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
been	O
suspected	O
of	O
robbing	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
I	O
concealed	O
myself	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
in	O
order	O
if	O
possible	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
who	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
begged	O
forgiveness	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
some	O
witnesses	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
James	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Saunders	O
Davenport	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Fleming	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walpool	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Ironmonger	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Anderside	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Case	I-pers
,	O
and	O
his	O
own	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
170	O
,	O
171	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Stapeler	I-pers
and	O
Esther	B-pers
Shelson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
child	O
's	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
one	O
child	O
's	O
linen	O
jacket	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
two	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pots	O
,	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Torrent	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
February	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Torrent	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Samuel	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
in	O
Gravel	B-place
lane	I-place
,	I-place
Houndsditch	I-place
,	O
and	O
having	O
lost	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
suspected	O
John	B-pers
Stapeler	I-pers
.	O
There	O
I	O
found	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
and	O
two	O
childrens	O
bed-gowns	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
a	O
coarse	O
apron	O
at	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Stapeler	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
bonnet	O
,	O
an	O
India	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
quart	O
pots	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
taken	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
[	O
The	O
goods	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
George	B-pers
Wardley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Stapeler	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
other	O
boys	O
sell	O
things	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
encouraged	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
what	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
three	O
quart	O
pots	O
and	O
stamped	O
them	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
These	O
goods	O
here	O
produced	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
stole	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tvrrent	O
took	O
Esther	B-pers
Shelson	I-pers
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Ellice	B-pers
Elerton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
and	O
two	O
child	O
's	O
bed-gowns	O
;	O
he	O
pawned	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
his	O
mother	O
Beersheba	O
Stapeler	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
prisoner	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Stapeler	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
people	O
used	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
victuals	O
,	O
and	O
Esther	B-pers
Shelson	I-pers
advised	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
something	O
that	O
lay	O
about	O
in	O
Torrent	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
bring	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
hurt	O
.	O
Stapeler	O
guilty	O
.	O
Shelson	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
171	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
++	O
Daniel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	B-place
Poultry	I-place
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
coming	O
out	O
I	O
felt	O
an	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Turning	O
round	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cross	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
so	O
suspected	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
slip	O
something	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
still	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
stopped	O
in	O
Grocer	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
trust	O
him	O
behind	O
me	O
but	O
he	O
refused	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
;	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
Mr.	O
Barrot	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Old	O
Jury	O
on	O
Friday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
assistants	O
that	O
followed	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
observed	O
something	O
like	O
one	O
fly	O
and	O
drop	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
has	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
dropped	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Barrot	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
thinking	O
no	O
harm	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
Old	O
Jury	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
into	O
a	O
lane	O
going	O
my	O
direct	O
way	O
home	O
;	O
this	O
gentleman	O
came	O
quick	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
room	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
for	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
presently	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
for	O
some	O
body	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
stunned	O
by	O
the	O
blow	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
way	O
I	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
and	O
dragged	O
me	O
about	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Archer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Blacklidge	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Lydia	B-pers
Leversage	I-pers
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acq	O
.	O
172	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Weatley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
February	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
Charles	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
Ludgate-Hill	B-place
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
glimpse	O
of	O
something	O
fly	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
pleased	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Fountain	O
Tavern	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
do	O
you	O
remember	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Appleby	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
it	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
examine	O
Mr.	O
Lilley	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lilley	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
boy	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
a	O
drawer	O
at	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
here	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
as	O
bad	O
a	O
boy	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
.	O
See	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Fairbrother	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Degon	O
,	O
No	O
467	O
,	O
in	O
Alderman	O
Gascoigne	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
173	O
,	O
174	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Strong	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
bushels	O
of	O
malt	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
hempen	O
sack	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Barney	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Foulback	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Feb.	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
warehouse	O
at	O
Bull	B-place
Wharf	I-place
near	I-place
Queenhithe	I-place
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Horton	O
near	O
Windsor	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
missed	O
two	O
sacks	O
of	O
malt	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
wharfinger	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
refer	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
evidences	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
Bing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
warehouse-keeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pearson	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
ten	O
quarters	O
of	O
malt	O
in	O
twenty	O
sacks	O
came	O
in	O
on	O
Saturday	O
se'nnight	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
sacks	O
of	O
it	O
about	O
six	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
did	O
they	O
contain	O
?	O
Bing	O
.	O
Eight	O
bushels	O
.	O
There	O
being	O
an	O
alarm	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
counted	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
up	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Foulback	O
for	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Foulback	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
;	O
Strong	O
asked	O
Foulback	O
for	O
the	O
sack	O
,	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
;	O
it	O
belongs	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Barney	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
Strong	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
sack	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
malt	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
partner	O
(	O
not	O
taken	O
)	O
carried	O
the	O
other	O
sack	O
and	O
shot	O
the	O
malt	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
sack	O
away	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Strong	O
say	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
us	O
to	O
one	O
Foulback	O
's	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
us	O
the	O
binn	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
shot	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
ask	O
Foulback	O
for	O
the	O
sacks	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
blown	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
nothing	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
have	O
the	O
sacks	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
first	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
and	O
took	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
on	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Strong	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Pearson	O
's	O
warehouse	O
with	O
a	O
sack	O
on	O
his	O
Back	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
malt	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
Queenhithe	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
mentioned	O
before	O
him	O
at	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lullock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
doors	O
open	O
about	O
six	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Strong	O
with	O
a	O
sack	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
sack	O
?	O
Lullock	O
.	O
A	O
large	O
sack	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
sweepings	O
of	O
malt	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
beef	O
the	O
bargeman	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
pushed	O
it	O
off	O
his	O
shoulders	O
;	O
it	O
burst	O
in	O
the	O
fall	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
malt	O
.	O
Strong	O
.	O
He	O
say	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
'till	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
candle	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Barney	I-pers
.	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
malt	O
down	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Pearson	O
's	O
warehouse	O
,	O
ten	O
quarters	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
twenty	O
sacks	O
,	O
four	O
bushels	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
sack	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
Barney	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
sack	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
Strong	O
;	O
in	O
going	O
up	O
Bow-Lane	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
information	O
of	O
those	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
Cheapside	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
Magpye	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
accused	O
of	O
having	O
taken	O
two	O
sacks	O
of	O
malt	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Harry	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
other	O
name	O
,	O
that	O
worked	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Whitfield	O
's	O
wharf	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
gaol	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
it	O
avail	O
to	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
gaol	O
?	O
I	O
can	O
shew	O
you	O
the	O
binn	O
where	O
the	O
malt	O
was	O
shot	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
will	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Foulback	O
's	O
in	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
nor	O
saw	O
them	O
bring	O
a	O
sack	O
out	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Nash	O
.	O
What	O
conversation	O
had	O
you	O
with	O
Foulback	O
?	O
Nash	O
.	O
In	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
malt	O
of	O
Strong	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
buy	O
malt	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
ten	O
shillings	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
but	O
Strong	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
but	O
eight	O
shillings	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
a	O
quarter	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Rutt	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Foulback	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
Monday	O
se'nnight	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
after	O
Strong	O
had	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
sack	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
place	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
hole	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
This	O
produced	O
is	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Strong	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
Saturday	O
as	O
they	O
talk	O
of	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Strong	O
,	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
Foulback	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
175	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Edward	I-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ann	I-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Ann	O
Allen	O
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
stars	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Margaret	O
.	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Marybone	B-place
parish	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
chairwoman	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
stars	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
only	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
she	O
come	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
apartment	O
for	O
ten	O
days	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
:	O
I	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
none	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
shilling	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
work	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Cherry	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
business	O
?	O
Cherry	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
clean	O
out	O
the	O
closet	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Bullion	I-pers
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
three	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
coach	O
and	O
horses	O
,	O
in	O
Great	O
Marlborough-street	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
;	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
chair	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
made	O
her	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
wicked	O
action	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
accused	O
with	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
fetch	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
daughter	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
:	O
I	O
fetched	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
work	O
for	O
her	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
'till	O
she	O
had	O
worked	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
together	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
two	O
stars	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
produce	O
the	O
stars	O
?	O
Bullion	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
or	O
heard	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Knowles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
's	O
daughter	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
money	O
mentioned	O
,	O
being	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
:	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
work	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
could	O
earn	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
.	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
dwelling-house	O
you	O
live	O
in	O
?	O
Cherry	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
keep	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
176	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
sconce	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
set	O
of	O
curtains	O
,	O
one	O
callico	O
quilt	O
,	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
two	O
pillow-cases	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
tongs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
fire	O
shovel	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Dews	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
February	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
177	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Hawley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barwell	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
holland	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sam	B-pers
Tavan	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
Samuel	B-pers
Tavan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
holland	O
shirts	O
within	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
Upon	O
suspecting	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
servant	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Grant	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
his	O
box	O
was	O
searched	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Eager	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Ridge	O
.	O
One	O
shirt	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
:	O
which	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
they	O
brought	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
asked	O
him	O
after	O
these	O
shirts	O
?	O
Tavan	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
produced	O
the	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
box	O
;	O
he	O
persisted	O
upon	O
having	O
no	O
knowledge	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
brought	O
it	O
among	O
his	O
linnen	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Westminster-school	O
,	O
and	O
board	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Grant	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
shirt	O
,	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
clean	O
,	O
and	O
folded	O
up	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
proper	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
put	O
his	O
linnen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
box	O
locked	O
?	O
Ridge	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
another	O
box	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
?	O
Ridge	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Eager	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Ridge	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ridge	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Gyles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
washed	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tavan	O
.	O
I	O
washed	O
this	O
shirt	O
here	O
produced	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
ironed	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
brought	O
Mr.	O
Tavan	O
's	O
linnen	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
deliver	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
leave	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
laundry	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
