TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
JULY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
27th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1754	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1754	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Kings	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RAWLINSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	B-pers
PARKER	I-pers
*	O
,	O
Sir	O
MICHAEL	O
FOSTER	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
,	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BIRCH	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
||	O
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hemans	I-pers
,	O
Jos	B-pers
Warr	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wilkes	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Peach	I-pers
,	O
Mandevile	O
Somersall	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Druit	I-pers
*	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wellings	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Norris	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Furman	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Huddle	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
Thomas	O
Druit	O
and	O
William	O
Wilton	O
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
were	O
sworn	O
in	O
their	O
room	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Boozshire	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Nicolson	I-pers
.	O
347	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Lovegrove	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
pottage	O
pot	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
one	O
wooden	O
pail	O
,	O
one	O
iron	O
shovel	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
May	O
2	O
++	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Hill	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
ready	O
furnish	O
'd	O
lodging	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
lett	O
with	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
evidence	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Hill	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
They	O
lent	O
me	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
348	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cradock	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Aspinner	I-pers
,	O
one	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
everlasting	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Careless	I-pers
May	O
16	O
*	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
349	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
David	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
lawn	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
June	O
25	O
||	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Exchange	I-place
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
shewn	O
him	O
there	O
two	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
pick-pocket	O
.	O
I	O
watch	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
down	O
Cornhill	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
wiped	O
his	O
face	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
another	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
;	O
presently	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
that	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
likewise	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
porters	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
pickpocket	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pick	O
a	O
person	O
's	O
pocket	O
once	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
some	O
from	O
his	O
pockets	O
and	O
some	O
from	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
mine	O
was	O
one	O
[	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
or	O
2	O
s.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Trottman	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
'd	O
assist	O
in	O
securing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Having	O
seen	O
him	O
pick	O
a	O
pocket	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
common	O
pickpocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
more	O
from	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
owned	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Taking	O
him	O
along	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
5	O
s.	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
release	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blaks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
he	O
offer	O
'd	O
us	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
evidence	O
to	O
prove	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
city	O
towards	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
think	O
I	O
would	O
know	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
if	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
More	O
.	O
(	O
She	O
points	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
small	O
bundle	O
,	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
halves	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
none	O
.	O
Then	O
there	O
came	O
up	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
halves	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
them	O
none	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
either	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Trottman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
Change	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
of	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
it	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
secure	O
him	O
?	O
Trottman	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
gentleman	O
going	O
on	O
business	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
350	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
perriwig	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
breeches	O
,	O
two	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
flannel	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
cap	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ingraham	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ingraham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
goods	O
in	O
Essex	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Rosemary-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
deliver	O
'd	O
into	O
my	O
hands	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
)	O
The	O
Prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
351	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Knapton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Phillibrown	I-pers
,	O
one	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jasper	B-pers
Morley	I-pers
,	O
June	O
the	O
4th	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Phillibrown	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
uncle	O
's	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
spoons	O
were	O
missing	O
on	O
Whitson	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
hat-box	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
broke	O
each	O
in	O
two	O
pieces	O
.	O
We	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
brought	O
from	O
our	O
house	O
at	O
Ponder	O
's	O
End	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phillibrown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Morley	O
's	O
my	O
uncle	O
on	O
the	O
Whitson	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
stay	O
till	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
man	O
's	O
boxes	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
the	O
spoons	O
were	O
found	O
broke	O
in	O
a	O
hat-box	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
my	O
uncle	O
upon	O
his	O
mentioning	O
the	O
spoons	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
nothing	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sorry	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
what	O
view	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
they	O
came	O
broke	O
,	O
he	O
pretended	O
the	O
table	O
spoon	O
was	O
bent	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
tea-spoon	O
he	O
broke	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
in	O
bringing	O
it	O
from	O
Ponder's-End	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
table	O
spoon	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
before	O
Whitson	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
teaspoon	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
mention	O
breaking	O
these	O
in	O
the	O
cleaning	O
them	O
?	O
Phillibrown	O
.	O
Not	O
one	O
word	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
that	O
hat-box	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
Phillibrown	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
table	O
spoon	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
flung	O
it	O
in	O
that	O
box	O
,	O
fearing	O
to	O
lose	O
my	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
broke	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
bringing	O
it	O
from	O
Ponder's-End	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Caygill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bean	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
both	O
born	O
in	O
a	O
town	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
character	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
wrong	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
352	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Fare	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Crasteyn	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
June	O
3	O
++	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Piper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Crasteyn	O
;	O
the	O
coat	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
care	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
coat	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
coach-box	O
on	O
Whitson	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
buying	O
some	O
cherries	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
for	O
seven	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lacy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
taking	O
the	O
coat	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
sober	O
when	O
he	O
confessed	O
it	O
?	O
Lacy	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
yard	O
several	O
times	O
when	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
eating	O
house	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Royal	O
Exchange	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
from	O
Alehouse	O
to	O
Alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
own	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
coat	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
clear	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
bought	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Regan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
transaction	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Gready	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
353	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Macdonald	I-pers
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hanshaw	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1	O
++	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Hanshaw	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
spoon	O
lost	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
(	O
a	O
spoon	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Threlkill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
This	O
spoon	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
Margaret	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
She	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
crest	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
gentleman	O
being	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
flew	O
at	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
two	O
pieces	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
leave	O
it	O
I	O
would	O
advertise	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
insulting	O
language	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
stopp	O
'd	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
concealed	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
search	O
'd	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
over-against	O
the	O
Mansion-House	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
spoon	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
found	O
.	O
They	O
differ	O
'd	O
greatly	O
in	O
their	O
accounts	O
;	O
they	O
first	O
said	O
they	O
bought	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
Wapping	O
,	O
then	O
of	O
a	O
beggar	O
woman	O
,	O
then	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Theophilus	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
Perkins	O
denied	O
delivering	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Wapping	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
beggar	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
then	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
agreed	O
in	O
their	O
accounts	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
Perkins	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
handle	O
in	O
Macdonald	O
's	O
shoe	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
toe	O
of	O
her	O
shoe	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
her	O
right	O
foot	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Threlkill	O
deliver	O
'd	O
the	O
bowl	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Martingale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Mansion-House	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
in	O
the	O
right	O
foot	O
shoe	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Macdonald	O
,	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Macdonald	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
buy	O
old	O
clothes	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Wapping	O
with	O
a	O
broken	O
spoon	O
,	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
12	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
for	O
9	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
stopp	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
was	O
named	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wallice	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
nine	O
days	O
in	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Martingale	O
.	O
They	O
never	O
told	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
nor	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Jones	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
The	O
room	O
door	O
was	O
wrench	O
'd	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
spoon	O
lay	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Ann	O
Corner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Margaret	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
fifteen	O
years	O
;	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
to	O
my	O
hearing	O
is	O
very	O
good	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
fault	O
,	O
make	O
her	O
flesh	O
suffer	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
354	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Cobley	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Barrington	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Lintott	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
140	O
volumes	O
in	O
folio	O
of	O
the	O
manuscript	O
journals	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Lords	O
and	O
Rolls	O
in	O
Parliament	O
,	O
value	O
100	O
l.	O
and	O
11	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
a	O
stove	O
grate	O
,	O
a	O
warming	O
pan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
harpsichord	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
laid	O
over	O
again	O
for	O
stealing	O
these	O
goods	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Lintott	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
++	O
Henry	B-pers
Lintott	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
chambers	O
in	O
the	O
inner	O
Temple	O
,	O
the	O
garrets	O
whereof	O
were	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
were	O
taken	O
142	O
volumes	O
of	O
the	O
Rolls	O
in	O
Parliament	O
,	O
and	O
Journals	O
of	O
the	O
House	O
of	O
Lords	O
in	O
manuscript	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
which	O
are	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Lintott	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
them	O
?	O
Lintott	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
Thursday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
told	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
(	O
Those	O
were	O
warehouses	O
that	O
I	O
seldom	O
went	O
into	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
to	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-Market	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-Market	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
papers	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
of	O
several	O
sorts	O
,	O
some	O
printed	O
and	O
some	O
written	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
waste	O
paper	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
books	O
that	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
York	O
river	O
company	O
;	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
dated	O
1720	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Barrington	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
those	O
sort	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
understood	O
by	O
his	O
answer	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
broker	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
hop	O
'd	O
he	O
came	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Cold	O
Bath	O
Fields	O
with	O
his	O
father-in-law	O
.	O
That	O
parcel	O
came	O
to	O
3	O
l.	O
odd	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
he	O
wou	O
'd	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
receipt	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
one	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
it	O
and	O
he	O
sign	O
'd	O
his	O
name	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
June	O
10	O
,	O
1754	O
.	O
Received	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Calvert	I-pers
3	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
waste	O
paper	O
,	O
in	O
full	O
of	O
all	O
demands	O
,	O
J.	O
Barrington	O
.	O
Whiston	O
Bristow	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Calvert	O
's	O
shop	O
(	O
with	O
whom	O
I	O
deal	O
)	O
and	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
surprize	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shelves	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
these	O
volumes	O
,	O
stripp	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
they	O
now	O
appear	O
(	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
volumes	O
brought	O
into	O
court	O
,	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
covers	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
)	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
gone	O
thro	O
'	O
my	O
hands	O
some	O
years	O
ago	O
(	O
I	O
have	O
acted	O
as	O
agent	O
for	O
booksellers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mr.	O
Calvert	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
several	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
two	O
considerable	O
piles	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
60	O
or	O
70	O
volumes	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
immediately	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
books	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
who	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
first	O
step	O
proper	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
of	O
safety	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
owner	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
customary	O
way	O
among	O
their	O
trade	O
when	O
one	O
lights	O
of	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
waste	O
paper	O
,	O
to	O
assist	O
each	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
two	O
parcels	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
two	O
different	O
cheesemongers	O
.	O
I	O
advised	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
immediately	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
advance	O
the	O
price	O
rather	O
than	O
not	O
get	O
them	O
back	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
volumes	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sandby	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
an	O
intimate	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
his	O
advice	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
advertising	O
them	O
we	O
should	O
soon	O
hear	O
of	O
the	O
owner	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
are	O
but	O
very	O
few	O
copies	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
kingdom	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Calvert	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
joy	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
back	O
both	O
the	O
parcels	O
untouch	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
often	O
saw	O
the	O
person	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
pass	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hoped	O
he	O
should	O
soon	O
come	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
)	O
Mr.	O
Calvert	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
books	O
:	O
he	O
there	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
several	O
parcels	O
of	O
such	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
sold	O
Mr.	O
Calvert	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
,	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
We	O
none	O
of	O
us	O
knew	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
volumes	O
then	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
set	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
set	O
any	O
where	O
else	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
two	O
volumes	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
,	O
a	O
bookseller	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
his	O
place	O
of	O
abode	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Cold-Bath-Fields	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
lodging	O
in	O
Salisbury-Court	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
stockingshop	O
.	O
(	O
having	O
been	O
inform	O
'd	O
so	O
by	O
some	O
porters	O
)	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
His	O
Lordship	O
granted	O
us	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
woman	O
if	O
one	O
Barrington	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lodging	O
taken	O
there	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
laid	O
there	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
nights	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
had	O
entertained	O
an	O
indifferent	O
person	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
well	O
recommended	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
room	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
harpsichord	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
found	O
out	O
Mr.	O
Lintot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
harpsichord	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
some	O
loose	O
prints	O
and	O
papers	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
were	O
his	O
;	O
some	O
printed	O
books	O
and	O
waste	O
of	O
books	O
,	O
and	O
odd	O
sheets	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
we	O
divided	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Cold-Bath-Fields	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Horshoe	O
and	O
Magpye	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
if	O
one	O
Barrington	O
lodged	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lodged	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
out	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
had	O
discharg	O
'd	O
him	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
right	O
name	O
was	O
James	B-pers
Cobley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
father	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
that	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
books	O
,	O
or	O
parchments	O
,	O
or	O
papers	O
of	O
any	O
kind	O
,	O
that	O
might	O
be	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
welcome	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
find	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
pamphlets	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
read	O
to	O
divert	O
himself	O
with	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lintott	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Lintott	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
Bristow	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
's	O
a	O
bookseller	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
volumes	O
of	O
the	O
Lords	O
Journals	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
out	O
those	O
two	O
very	O
books	O
from	O
his	O
back	O
shop	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
He	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
name	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
at	O
a	O
second	O
examination	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Bristow	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
related	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Lintott	O
was	O
very	O
desirous	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
this	O
thing	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
thought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
accomplice	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
on	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
concerning	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
taking	O
140	O
volumes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
was	O
named	O
Welch	O
,	O
he	O
described	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Lord	O
granted	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
apprehending	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lintott	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
examined	O
these	O
books	O
that	O
are	O
brought	O
into	O
court	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Lintott	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
volumes	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
?	O
Lintott	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
140	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
exclusive	O
of	O
those	O
two	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
's	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
chambers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
them	O
in	O
your	O
rooms	O
?	O
Lintott	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
and	O
have	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
now	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Calvert	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
examined	O
all	O
these	O
books	O
?	O
Calvert	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
them	O
of	O
?	O
Calvert	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
at	O
several	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
140	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
bought	O
some	O
other	O
papers	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lintott	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
value	O
them	O
as	O
a	O
curiosity	O
,	O
but	O
tell	O
us	O
what	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
?	O
Lintott	O
.	O
The	O
sett	O
have	O
been	O
advertised	O
some	O
years	O
ago	O
for	O
500	O
l.	O
Q	O
.	O
Would	O
you	O
take	O
an	O
100	O
l.	O
for	O
them	O
now	O
?	O
Lintott	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
nor	O
200	O
l.	O
neither	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Calvert	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Calvert	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
rate	O
of	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
a	O
hundred	O
weight	O
,	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
than	O
appears	O
on	O
that	O
receipt	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
of	O
paper	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
besides	O
these	O
books	O
?	O
Calvert	O
.	O
Really	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
700	O
weight	O
to	O
one	O
man	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Potten	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
waste	O
paper	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
in	O
all	O
there	O
were	O
307	O
pounds	O
weight	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
asked	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
nor	O
took	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
14	O
s.	O
a	O
hundred	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
42	O
s.	O
in	O
all	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Irons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
ply	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Market	O
The	O
prisoner	O
once	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
waste	O
paper	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
books	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
)	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
,	O
to	O
Mr	O
Potten	O
's	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Market	O
.	O
I	O
also	O
brought	O
several	O
parcels	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
to	O
Mr	O
Calvert	O
's	O
;	O
what	O
quantity	O
in	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
believe	O
were	O
books	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
paper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
bring	O
them	O
from	O
?	O
Moses	B-pers
Irons	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
from	O
up	O
stairs	O
in	O
a	O
chamber	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
in	O
the	O
Temple	O
?	O
Moses	B-pers
Irons	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
stair-case	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
Temple	O
Gate	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
fetch	O
any	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
?	O
Moses	B-pers
Irons	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
sometimes	O
day	O
light	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
sometimes	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
betwixt	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
latest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
ever	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
books	O
were	O
?	O
Moses	B-pers
Irons	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
always	O
put	O
the	O
parcels	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
deliver	O
any	O
parcels	O
to	O
you	O
there	O
?	O
Moses	B-pers
Irons	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
One	O
night	O
a	O
gentleman	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
I.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lintott	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
staircase	O
situate	O
as	O
the	O
evidence	O
describes	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Lintott	O
.	O
The	O
staircase	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
going	O
down	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Larnell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
employed	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
loads	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
justly	O
say	O
how	O
many	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
several	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
books	O
;	O
some	O
I	O
brought	O
openly	O
;	O
some	O
were	O
bound	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
unbound	O
,	O
like	O
these	O
produced	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Larnell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
a	O
stair-head	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
the	O
temple	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
going	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
from	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
delivered	O
them	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
on	O
the	O
resting	O
place	O
at	O
the	O
stair-head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
them	O
to	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Larnell	I-pers
.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Calvert	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet	O
Market	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
carried	O
any	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
Newgate-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
carry	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Larnell	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
some	O
betwixt	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
at	O
Noon	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Calvert	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
these	O
two	O
porters	O
bringing	O
the	O
books	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Calvert	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
this	O
last	O
evidence	O
shewed	O
me	O
Mr.	O
Lintott	O
's	O
chambers	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Potten	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
these	O
porters	O
brought	O
parcels	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Potten	O
.	O
Irons	O
brought	O
all	O
to	O
me	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
mine	O
was	O
all	O
waste	O
paper	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
bound	O
books	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Calvert	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
how	O
much	O
you	O
paid	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Calvert	O
produced	O
a	O
book	O
.	O
l.	O
s.	O
d.	O
The	O
first	O
article	O
was	O
1	O
14	O
9	O
The	O
second	O
1	O
19	O
6	O
The	O
next	O
1	O
3	O
6	O
1	O
9	O
6	O
2	O
6	O
4	O
0	O
18	O
0	O
1	O
4	O
0	O
1	O
2	O
6	O
1	O
13	O
0	O
1	O
18	O
0	O
0	O
17	O
6	O
0	O
15	O
2	O
These	O
sums	O
sometimes	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
I	O
myself	O
set	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
paid	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
books	O
and	O
paper	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
Monday	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
about	O
a	O
little	O
business	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
gentleman	O
and	O
Porter	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
where	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
well	O
dressed	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
from	O
6	O
o'clock	O
to	O
about	O
7	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
talking	O
how	O
paper	O
sold	O
a	O
pound	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
unfortunate	O
as	O
to	O
fall	O
into	O
discourse	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
paper	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
tell	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
might	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
meet	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
chamber	O
where	O
these	O
books	O
were	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
chambers	O
;	O
so	O
accordingly	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
papers	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
,	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
355	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Mooney	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
smith	O
's	O
vice	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Redbourn	I-pers
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Redbourn	I-pers
,	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
stock-vice	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
in	O
Codpiss-Row	B-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
crown	O
reward	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Mooney	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
he	O
confessed	O
taking	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
I.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Redbourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
value	O
it	O
at	O
7	O
s.	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
with	O
the	O
vice	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bembrick	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
this	O
woman	O
to	O
pawn	O
this	O
vice	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
knowing	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
notice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
my	O
fellow	O
servants	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
walk	O
to	O
Islington	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
back	O
place	O
to	O
case	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
vice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
with	O
that	O
woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
356	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Tracy	B-pers
Tutt	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Vain	I-pers
did	O
break	O
,	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
out	O
thence	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
one	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
gown	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
,	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
++	O
Sarah	B-pers
Vain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
chandler	B-place
's	I-place
Rents	I-place
,	I-place
Black-friers	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
who	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
nights	O
before	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Vain	O
's	O
shop	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
break	O
her	O
shop	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
watchman	O
coming	O
it	O
hindred	O
us	O
then	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
after	O
I	O
parted	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
sell	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
shoes	O
a	O
box-iron	O
and	O
heaters	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
child	O
's	O
stockings	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
only	O
the	O
pumps	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
pawned	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
man	O
has	O
been	O
tried	O
here	O
before	O
now	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
once	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
evidence	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
things	O
:	O
He	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
work	O
on	O
Saturday	O
Night	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
forewarned	O
him	O
coming	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
this	O
out	O
of	O
spight	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
357	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Paul	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
did	O
break	O
,	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
out	O
thence	O
one	O
shag	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shag	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
everlasting	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
whole	O
valued	O
at	O
upwards	O
of	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Somerset-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
in	O
Aldgate	O
Parish	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
lodger	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
something	O
for	O
supper	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
a-jar	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
scarlet	O
shag	O
waistcoat	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
finished	O
,	O
two	O
old	O
coats	O
,	O
one	O
old	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Taylor	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
after	O
this	O
before	O
Justice	O
Withers	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
evidence	O
here	O
.	O
They	O
confessed	O
nothing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
the	O
goods	O
again	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
persons	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
before	O
Justice	O
,	O
Withers	O
.	O
We	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
left	O
a	O
jar	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
locks	O
broken	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
about	O
15	O
Years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
sent	O
me	O
to	O
this	O
taylor	O
's	O
door	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
push	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
pushed	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Jos	O
.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
betwixt	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Then	O
Hamilton	O
pulled	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
open	O
it	O
better	O
than	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
with	O
a	O
hook	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
immediately	O
put	O
back	O
the	O
bolt	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
entry	O
.	O
Wood	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Make	O
haste	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
growing	O
late	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
went	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
of	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
open	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
a	O
red	O
plush	O
waistcoat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buck-skin	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
with	O
leather	O
linings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
duffil	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
coat	O
with	O
one	O
sleeve	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
fustian	O
sleeves	O
with	O
blue	O
ribbons	O
and	O
brass	O
buttons	O
.	O
We	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Sadler	I-pers
to	O
sell	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
for	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
wife	O
;	O
we	O
all	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
we	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
selling	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
each	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
your	O
goods	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
coat	O
as	O
he	O
mentioned	O
with	O
one	O
sleeve	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
coats	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
.	O
About	O
10	O
s.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
shag	O
waistcoat	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
shag	O
cost	O
30	O
s.	O
besides	O
the	O
making	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
old	O
waistcoat	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
.	O
That	O
is	O
but	O
a	O
trifle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
the	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
shag	O
breeches	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Adcock	I-pers
.	O
Four	O
shillings	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
bought	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
cap	O
I	O
have	O
on	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
is	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
then	O
Hamilton	O
began	O
to	O
tell	O
all	O
he	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Withers	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
youngest	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
make	O
me	O
evidence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lodge	O
?	O
Jos	O
.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
On	O
Saltpetre-Bank	O
,	O
a	O
private	O
house	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Withers	O
Hamilton	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
confess	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Withers	O
knowing	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
evidence	O
here	O
in	O
January	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
five	O
persons	O
for	O
transportation	O
*	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
admit	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
admitted	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
96	O
,	O
97	O
,	O
98	O
,	O
99	O
,	O
100	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
Wood	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
thief-catchers	O
desired	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
prosecute	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
him	O
a	O
reward	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
offer	O
you	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
mentioned	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
runners	O
or	O
turnkeys	O
of	O
New-prison	O
and	O
Bridewell	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
my	O
chance	O
.	O
Hamilton	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
That	O
evidence	O
is	O
egg	O
'd	O
on	O
by	O
the	O
thief-catchers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
will	O
swear	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
says	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Dubois	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Paul	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
always	O
in	O
my	O
care	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
he	O
your	O
brother	O
?	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Wood	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Dubois	I-pers
.	O
Mine	O
is	O
the	O
French	O
name	O
for	O
Wood	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
draw-boy	O
to	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
draft-weaver	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
he	O
worked	O
with	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Dubois	I-pers
.	O
He	O
is	O
my	O
brother	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
worked	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
any	O
body	O
where	O
he	O
did	O
work	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Liaver	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
such	O
an	O
affair	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
prison	O
offer	O
him	O
10	O
l.	O
if	O
the	O
boys	O
were	O
hanged	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
358	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Stoner	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
sack	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
camblet	O
skirt	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
8	O
.	O
||	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Joseph	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
for	O
striping	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
Bartholomew	O
close	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
having	O
had	O
one	O
stript	O
,	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
out	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
it	O
was	O
she	O
that	O
stripp	O
'd	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
there	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stripped	O
two	O
others	O
:	O
And	O
since	O
she	O
has	O
owned	O
that	O
my	O
child	O
's	O
stays	O
and	O
stockings	O
were	O
stopped	O
on	O
Clerkenwell-green	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
person	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
his	O
evidence	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
eleven	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
next	O
monday	O
Q.	O
to	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
E.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
we	O
live	O
all	O
in	O
one	O
street	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
her	O
aunt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
child	O
stripped	O
?	O
E.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
My	O
child	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
with	O
only	O
two	O
green	O
petticoats	O
and	O
her	O
cap	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
telling	O
her	O
name	O
and	O
place	O
of	O
abode	O
was	O
brought	O
home	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
from	O
off	O
her	O
?	O
E.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
A	O
Linen	O
sack	O
,	O
her	O
stays	O
,	O
skirt	O
,	O
shift	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
shoes	O
,	O
a	O
pin	O
cloth	O
from	O
before	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
topknot	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Beesley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
comrade	O
;	O
coming	O
by	O
Frog-lane	O
the	O
turnpike	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
have	O
mercy	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
like	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
there	O
sits	O
a	O
child	O
that	O
is	O
stripped	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
a	O
ditch	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
meddle	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
with	O
only	O
one	O
petticoat	O
on	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
its	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
that	O
and	O
pinned	O
it	O
over	O
her	O
shoulders	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
who	O
she	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
name	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Peggy	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
her	O
mother	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
its	O
mother	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
,	O
(	O
produces	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
sack	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
into	O
the	O
court	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Look	O
on	O
that	O
sack	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
My	O
child	O
had	O
this	O
on	O
that	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
she	O
was	O
stripped	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
,	O
produces	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
skirt	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
half	O
pence	O
for	O
this	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
skirt	O
?	O
E.	O
Jackson	O
:	O
This	O
my	O
child	O
had	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
beforementioned	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Linch	I-pers
,	O
produces	O
an	O
under	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
knot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
check	O
cloth	O
.	O
These	O
things	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Are	O
these	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
E.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
The	O
pin	O
cloth	O
and	O
topknot	O
are	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
on	O
my	O
child	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
the	O
petticoat	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
.	O
I	O
buy	O
old	O
clothes	O
.	O
He	O
produces	O
a	O
stay	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
on	O
Clerkenwell	O
green	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
offered	O
me	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
where	O
her	O
mother	O
lived	O
,	O
she	O
mentioned	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
another	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
stopped	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
E.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
child	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
fields	O
to	O
get	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
butterflowers	O
with	O
some	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Nicks	I-pers
,	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
Character	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
this	O
girl	O
about	O
7	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
she	O
did	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
kind	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
is	O
about	O
eleven	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Letgold	I-pers
.	O
We	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
month	O
old	O
,	O
she	O
,	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
July	O
1743	O
,	O
O.	O
S.	O
We	O
had	O
her	O
bound	O
apprentice	O
to	O
us	O
by	O
Lambeth	O
parish	O
in	O
August	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
her	O
uncle	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
wronged	O
us	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
shirt	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Rich	B-pers
Tustin	I-pers
,	O
June	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
Ann	B-pers
Tustin	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Richard	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
this	O
child	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
stripped	O
in	O
Bartholomew	B-place
close	I-place
;	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
particular	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
is	O
about	O
22	O
months	O
old	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
where	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
mother	O
lives	O
,	O
in	O
Black-horse	O
yard	O
,	O
Pick-ax	O
street	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
news	O
that	O
a	O
child	O
was	O
stripped	O
near	O
Bartholomew-close	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
child	O
it	O
was	O
then	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
she	O
stripped	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
proffered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
sale	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
off	O
the	O
child	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
Dawson	O
.	O
A	O
coat	O
and	O
skirt	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Then	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
father	O
of	O
that	O
child	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
father	O
.	O
A	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-mayor	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Dawson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Dicks	I-pers
,	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
swore	O
she	O
would	O
stab	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
the	O
petticoat	O
off	O
;	O
but	O
while	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
licking	O
me	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
359	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
-	I-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
yards	O
and	O
1/2	O
of	O
sattin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Lomax	B-pers
Ryder	I-pers
,	O
&	O
c.	O
May	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Lomax	O
Ryder	O
.	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
daughter	O
in	O
making	O
hoop	O
petticoats	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
for	O
work	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
her	O
daughter	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
shop	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
About	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
in	O
her	O
daughter	O
's	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
more	O
.	O
She	O
stayed	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
her	O
daughter	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
and	O
reached	O
something	O
from	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
was	O
suspicious	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
she	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
conceal	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
:	O
this	O
encreased	O
my	O
suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
she	O
stopped	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
more	O
about	O
her	O
than	O
belonged	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
her	O
apron	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
sattin	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
she	O
could	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
her	O
daughter	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
possible	O
she	O
could	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
mistake	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
six	O
people	O
to	O
her	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
360	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
June	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Newmarket	B-place
in	O
my	O
way	O
home	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
talking	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
home	O
:	O
she	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
refused	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
over	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
penny	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
behaved	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
indecent	O
manner	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
pulling	O
up	O
her	O
coats	O
,	O
and	O
telling	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
feel	O
of	O
her	O
-	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
deny	O
such	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Then	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
my	O
fob	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
dragged	O
me	O
to	O
where	O
her	O
companion	O
was	O
standing	O
.	O
Presently	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
went	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
your	O
watch	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
Groves	O
.	O
Just	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
lamp	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
fob	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Groves	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
perceive	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Groves	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
close	O
together	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
went	O
off	O
?	O
Groves	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
them	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
?	O
Groves	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
near	O
enough	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Groves	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
fob	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
first	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
till	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
Groves	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
she	O
was	O
near	O
enough	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Groves	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
just	O
at	O
her	O
going	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
reach	O
her	O
hand	O
?	O
Groves	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
were	O
they	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
?	O
Groves	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
but	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
touch	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Groves	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Groves	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
June	O
at	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
watch	O
night	O
.	O
There	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
in	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
told	O
this	O
?	O
Downs	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
:	O
and	O
that	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
penny	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
here	O
?	O
Downs	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
afterwards	O
committed	O
by	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
farther	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
than	O
desiring	O
he	O
should	O
bring	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
searched	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
nobody	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
pulling	O
and	O
haleing	O
one	O
another	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
with	O
my	O
back	O
against	O
post	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
button	O
up	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
me	O
searched	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
indecent	O
manner	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
,	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
For	O
my	O
part	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
with	O
my	O
eyes	O
before	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
carried	O
me	O
down	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
were	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
this	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
constable	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
sober	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
value	O
your	O
watch	O
at	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
At	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
361	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hickson	I-pers
,	O
June	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Hickson	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
John	O
,	O
we	O
keep	O
the	O
Golden	B-place
Lion	I-place
at	I-place
Hide-park	I-place
corner	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
cyder	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
tap-house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
complained	O
he	O
was	O
cold	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
another	O
customer	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
bear	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
drew	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
my	O
candlesticks	O
were	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
mantlepiece	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
candlesticks	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
a	O
market	O
woman	O
who	O
uses	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
telling	O
me	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Clare	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
road	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
upon	O
being	O
searched	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
directed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
both	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
knew	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
candlesticks	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
belonging	O
to	O
St.	O
Margaret	O
's	O
parish	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
stealing	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
apron	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
told	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
me	O
in	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
woman	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
clothes	O
man	O
for	O
24	O
d.	O
over	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
near	O
Hide-park	O
corner	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
362	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Duboice	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
4	O
silver	O
seals	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
gold	O
seal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
12	O
silver	O
sizes	O
for	O
rings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hollier	I-pers
,	O
June	O
6	O
,	O
+	O
Acq	O
.	O
363	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Logey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
copper	O
pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
brass	O
stew	O
pan	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
pillow	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
1	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
June	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
these	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodgings	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
directed	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
364	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass	O
arm	O
and	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
,	O
July	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
backwards	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
washing	O
my	O
hands	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
7	O
d.	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
some	O
brass	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
7	O
d.	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
some	O
old	O
brass	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
went	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
came	O
a	O
neighbour	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
offered	O
this	O
brass	O
arm	O
to	O
sell	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
first	O
one	O
place	O
then	O
another	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Brinn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
betwixt	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Thursday	O
last	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
old	O
brass	O
.	O
the	O
brass	O
weighed	O
4	O
ounces	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
this	O
brass	O
arm	O
of	O
a	O
candlestick	O
to	O
sale	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
(	O
he	O
lives	O
over	O
against	O
me	O
)	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
sent	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
brass	O
I	O
went	O
backward	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bassit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Child	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Brinn	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
Golden-Lane	O
end	O
;	O
the	O
branch	O
hung	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
branch	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
proposed	O
to	O
sell	O
that	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
365	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Taunton	I-pers
,	O
February	O
28	O
++	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
named	O
James	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shift	O
sleeves	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
h	O
andkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
sister	O
Mary	O
Taunton	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
charity	O
till	O
she	O
could	O
hear	O
of	O
a	O
service	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
taking	O
these	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Lucas	O
gave	O
me	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
setch	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
366	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
7	O
*	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
yearly	O
servant	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
I	O
missed	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
desk	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
mistake	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
wrote	O
upon	O
the	O
papers	O
how	O
much	O
each	O
parcel	O
contained	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
them	O
by	O
finding	O
them	O
often	O
short	O
when	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
longer	O
a	O
mistake	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
desirous	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
thief	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
missed	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
15	O
or	O
20	O
l.	O
On	O
Whitson	O
Eve	O
I	O
put	O
ten	O
guineas	O
into	O
my	O
desk	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
)	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
ten	O
guineas	O
more	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
scratched	O
out	O
the	O
ten	O
guineas	O
on	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
down	O
five	O
;	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
but	O
fourteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
upon	O
this	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
no	O
more	O
gold	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
19	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
it	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
church	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
church	O
I	O
told	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
only	O
17	O
s.	O
I	O
asked	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
none	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
this	O
confirmed	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
suspicion	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
sunday	O
following	O
,	O
the	O
seventh	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
to	O
watch	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
hole	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
put	O
in	O
11	O
half	O
crowns	O
and	O
17	O
shillings	O
,	O
he	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
telling	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
money	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
fix	O
'd	O
me	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
to	O
watch	O
last	O
sunday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
10	O
o'clock	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
alone	O
below	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
walk	O
'd	O
softly	O
across	O
the	O
parlour	O
to	O
the	O
stair	O
foot	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
to	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
and	O
opening	O
it	O
drew	O
out	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
desk	O
.	O
On	O
seeing	O
this	O
I	O
stepped	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
on	O
seeing	O
me	O
seemed	O
pretty	O
much	O
fluttered	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
meddled	O
with	O
the	O
desk	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Wilkinson	O
had	O
told	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
6	O
s.	O
In	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
observed	O
his	O
hand	O
clinched	O
close	O
,	O
we	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
2	O
half	O
crowns	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
that	O
Mr	O
Wilkinson	O
had	O
put	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
utterly	O
ruined	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
mark	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
by	O
running	O
an	O
engraver	O
along	O
the	O
Letters	O
V	O
and	O
W	O
in	O
Carolus	O
and	O
William	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
?	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
money	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
)	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
afterward	O
with	O
which	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
desk	O
;	O
this	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
of	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
that	O
has	O
had	O
my	O
first	O
floor	O
ever	O
since	O
last	O
September	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Scofield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
took	O
out	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
half	O
pence	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
but	O
seeing	O
his	O
hand	O
clos	O
'd	O
,	O
we	O
would	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
2	O
half	O
crowns	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
marked	O
as	O
before	O
mentioned	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
mercy	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
goes	O
to	O
church	O
very	O
frequently	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
clean	O
my	O
buckles	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
kitchen	O
and	O
cut	O
myself	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
butter	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
parlour	O
again	O
forgot	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
search	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
I	O
believe	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
shillings	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Would	O
that	O
key	O
open	O
your	O
desk	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
lock	O
and	O
unlock	O
it	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
367	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Collis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
sacrilegiously	O
stealing	O
a	O
linnen	O
surplice	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
church-wardens	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
parish	O
,	O
June	O
28	O
+	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
surplice	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
church	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Catharine	O
Cree	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
clark	O
's	O
care	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
hung	O
the	O
key	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
vestry	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
hood	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
that	O
the	O
minister	O
wears	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
follow	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
doors	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
surplice	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
among	O
the	O
Jews	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
go	O
so	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
gone	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
,	O
to	O
stop	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Thackery	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Rachel	B-pers
Israel	I-pers
with	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
church	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
place	O
on	O
it	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
mended	O
.	O
(	O
Produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
)	O
She	O
had	O
cut	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
collar	O
off	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
stockings	O
being	O
splashed	O
with	O
dirt	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
a	O
slit	O
on	O
his	O
elbow	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Friday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
his	O
face	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
had	O
he	O
changed	O
his	O
dress	O
you	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
sworn	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
church	O
did	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
vestry	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
thence	O
?	O
Rachel	B-pers
Israel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
went	O
past	O
my	O
window	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
he	O
looked	O
in	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
good	O
hat	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
old	O
clothes	O
,	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
surplice	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
five	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
After	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
properly	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
sold	O
me	O
the	O
thing	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
church	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
woman	O
6	O
s.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
Felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
368	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simms	I-pers
,	I-pers
spinster	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Elizabeth	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Terrey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
cambrick	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
June	O
7	O
||	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledg	O
'd	O
2	O
handkerchiefs	O
with	O
me	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Mure	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledg	O
'd	O
4	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
with	O
me	O
(	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
as	O
her	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
.	O
These	O
6	O
handkerchiefs	O
produced	O
here	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Major	O
Johnson	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
2	O
other	O
women	O
besides	O
me	O
used	O
to	O
wash	O
at	O
Major	O
Johnson	O
's	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
in	O
my	O
name	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
help	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
369	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
with	O
2	O
seals	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
20	O
guineas	O
and	O
2	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Willis	B-pers
Farrows	I-pers
.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Michael	O
Carrey	O
,	O
June	O
6	O
||	O
.	O
Willis	B-pers
Farrows	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
with	O
some	O
friends	O
drinking	O
plentifully	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
safe	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
me	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Bread-Street	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
more	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Michael	B-pers
Cartey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Parker's-Lane	B-place
,	O
there	O
I	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
my	O
breeches	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
awak	O
'd	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
she	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
this	O
house	O
in	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
?	O
Farrows	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
private	O
lodging	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Farrows	O
.	O
Because	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
Farrows	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
under	O
no	O
pretence	O
whatsoever	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
James	I-pers
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
June	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
casually	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
sad	O
deplorable	O
dress	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
believed	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
returned	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
her	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
change	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
enquired	O
where	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
some	O
new	O
clothes	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
guinea	O
or	O
two	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
clothes	O
enough	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
by	O
my	O
direction	O
brought	O
some	O
clothes	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
several	O
things	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
enquired	O
where	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
a	O
lodging	O
to	O
lodge	O
safe	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
full	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
have	O
committed	O
something	O
bad	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
De'el	O
took	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
mons	O
moony	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
husbands	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
business	O
in	O
Cavendish-Square	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
was	O
her	O
business	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
muckle	O
mon	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
heard	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
saucy	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
about	O
her	O
business	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'd	O
turn	O
her	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
gang	O
no	O
farther	O
till	O
I	O
treate	O
you	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
2	O
seals	O
hang	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
have	O
done	O
some	O
bad	O
action	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
see	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
there	O
,	O
pray	O
what	O
o'clock	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
I	O
courted	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
must	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
farther	O
account	O
before	O
you	O
go	O
any	O
farther	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
perriwig-maker	O
in	O
Brewer-Street	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
my	O
apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
enquire	O
whether	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
did	O
live	O
there	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
sister	O
lived	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Bedwell	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
38	O
shillings	O
and	O
6	O
l.	O
in	O
silver	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
guineas	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
n	O
gold	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
bosom	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
watch	O
and	O
seals	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
.	O
James	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
going	O
along	O
that	O
she	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
by	O
Carnaby-Market	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Parker	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
there	O
they	O
drank	O
together	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
helped	O
him	O
off	O
with	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
together	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
them	O
20	O
golden	O
guineas	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
quantity	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Topham	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
present	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
rash	O
action	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
to	O
keep	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
no	O
more	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
Parker's-Lane	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
James	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
went	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Bedwell	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
talks	O
of	O
being	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bedwell	O
was	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
mention	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
money	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Cartey	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Parker's-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
since	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
more	O
money	O
that	O
she	O
says	O
she	O
hid	O
there	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
in	O
Cartey	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Parker's-Lane	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
forwards	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
that	O
lower	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
she	O
did	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
My	O
child	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
cill	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
the	O
gentleman	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
child	O
get	O
up	O
and	O
let	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
sleep	O
without	O
it	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
gentleman	O
)	O
and	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
entry	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
six-pence	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
change	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
A.	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
receiving	O
some	O
money	O
from	O
Edinburgh	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
Broad-street	O
by	O
Golden-Square	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
worried	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
another	O
house	O
and	O
chang	O
'd	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
salmon	O
and	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
we	O
came	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Parker's-Lane	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
have	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
this	O
woman	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
;	O
he	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
'd	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
clothes	O
and	O
watch	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
down	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
pull	O
them	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
my	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
door	O
padlock	O
'd	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
I	O
wanted	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
wife	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
smock	O
,	O
2	O
petticoats	O
and	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
because	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
padlock	O
'd	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
take	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
lodging	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
all	O
night	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
spent	O
a	O
farthing	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
again	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
washing	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
thief	O
catchers	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
kept	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
bought	O
.	O
James	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
money	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
detain	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
says	O
you	O
gave	O
her	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
order	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
keep	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
sure	O
I	O
never	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
believe	O
she	O
did	O
assist	O
me	O
in	O
pulling	O
my	O
breeches	O
off	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
370	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Oats	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
36	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
and	O
3	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	O
Knight	O
,	O
privately	O
and	O
secretly	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
July	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
name	O
is	O
Ann	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
pleaded	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
?	O
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Mitchel	I-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
July	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
toss	O
'd	O
up	O
their	O
hoops	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
pass	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
!	O
every	O
body	O
is	O
admiring	O
my	O
breast	O
as	O
they	O
go	O
along	O
.	O
Lord	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
perhaps	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
admiring	O
,	O
she	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
said	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
brought	O
us	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
Rummer	O
by	O
Charing-Cross	B-place
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
in	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
port	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
below	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
bottle	O
?	O
Knight	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
flung	O
down	O
2	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
before	O
we	O
tasted	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
all	O
her	O
clothes	O
to	O
her	O
navel	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
knee	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
my	O
dear	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
she	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
my	O
breeches	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
all	O
out	O
shirt	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
and	O
button	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
st	O
-	O
d	O
by	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
unbutton	O
'd	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
James's-street	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
companion	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
Moll	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
haul	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
all	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
Edwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
other	O
come	O
near	O
you	O
?	O
Knight	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
Edwards	O
to	O
come	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
going	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
slip	O
'd	O
away	O
in	O
an	O
instant	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
ten	O
36	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
and	O
3	O
guineas	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
quantity	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
found	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
at	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
lay	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
were	O
advis	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
;	O
accordingly	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
my	O
face	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
were	O
here	O
together	O
last	O
night	O
with	O
two	O
young	O
ladies	O
,	O
(	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
pleased	O
to	O
call	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
two	O
young	O
devils	O
to	O
me	O
)	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
they	O
liv	O
'd	O
and	O
their	O
names	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
either	O
.	O
That	O
did	O
not	O
satisfy	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
conceal	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
gave	O
us	O
directions	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
affair	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
drawer	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
porter	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
again	O
whether	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
My	O
friend	O
called	O
for	O
