TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
27th	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
Year	O
1754	O
.	O
BEING	O
THE	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1754	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
Kings	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
THOMAS	B-pers
RAWLINSON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
PARKER	O
*	O
,	O
Sir	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
FOSTER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	O
BIRCH	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
||	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
M.	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barwick	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
,	O
Anthony	B-pers
Stayner	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hurt	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Westgarth	I-pers
,	O
Frederick	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Toms	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Knowlys	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chapel	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Heritage	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Colins	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Doyley	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Stother	I-pers
,	O
Griffith	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Pemberton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
.	O
80.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Beach	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
5	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
81	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Foreman	I-pers
and	I-pers
Mary	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
and	O
Mary	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
copper	O
sauce-pan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sheers	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
Dec.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
lodgings	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
accordingly	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
82	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass	O
kettle	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Ann	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Round	B-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
broker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
large	O
pot	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
woman	O
into	O
Chandos-street	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
running	O
along	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
seeing	O
me	O
come	O
after	O
her	O
dropped	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Hawkins	O
took	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
pot	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
home	O
,	O
having	O
left	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Busbey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
take	O
a	O
pot	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Ann	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
,	O
she	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Burley	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
informed	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
pot	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Smithson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
pot	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smithson	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Smithson	O
took	O
the	O
pot	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
near	O
Round-Court	O
these	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
pot	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bell	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
nine	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
all	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
83	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Kempster	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
one	O
bolster	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pillow	O
,	O
one	O
flaxen	O
sheet	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
December	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Kennedy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Scotland-Yard	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
weeks	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
room	O
was	O
let	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
she	O
said	O
was	O
in	O
Jamaica	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
fortnight	O
;	O
when	O
taken	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
pawned	O
and	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
as	O
she	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
]	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Perry	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
,	O
Leicester	O
Fields	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
these	O
two	O
pillows	O
and	O
tea-kettle	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
84	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fazakerley	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
85	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Derter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
70	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
rags	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wetworth	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
86	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
mare	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
black	O
colour	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Healing	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Healing	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Hounslow	B-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
black	O
mare	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
two	O
other	O
horses	O
and	O
a	O
mare	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
ground	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
safe	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
black	O
mare	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
again	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
9th	O
at	O
Spinham-land	O
in	O
Berkshire	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Sandey	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
subpena	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
there	O
?	O
Healing	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
Matthew	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
my	O
loss	O
,	O
who	O
knew	O
my	O
mare	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Wayhill	O
Fair	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
enquire	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
me	O
word	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
at	O
Sceal	O
beyond	O
Reading	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
enquiry	O
found	O
her	O
out	O
.	O
Launcelot	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Twickenham	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
Reading	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
mare	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
.	O
Coming	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
saw	O
Sandey	O
the	O
younger	O
come	O
gallopping	O
hard	O
up	O
the	O
town	O
on	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
mare	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Sandey	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
there	O
they	O
both	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
mare	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
he	O
sold	O
her	O
to	O
Sandey	O
;	O
and	O
Sandey	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
six	O
guineas	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
who	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
?	O
Hide	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
George	O
at	O
Old	O
Brentford	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
knew	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
such	O
sign	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
mare	O
there	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
again	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ascue	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
Arms	O
at	O
Reading	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
mare	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
after	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
too	O
heavy	O
for	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
therefore	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
3rd	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
mare	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
ground	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
rails	O
were	O
broke	O
down	O
and	O
the	O
mare	O
gone	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
in	O
Reading	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
mare	O
into	O
my	O
stable	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
white	O
face	O
and	O
a	O
rat	O
tail	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
her	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
her	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
and	O
staid	O
all	O
night	O
:	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
Wayhill	O
Fair	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
mare	O
.	O
I	O
knowing	O
her	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
and	O
enquire	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
hear	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
word	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
at	O
Sceal	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
riding	O
on	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
mare	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
enough	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
the	O
mare	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
was	O
he	O
going	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
He	O
rode	O
out	O
of	O
an	O
inn	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
towards	O
Reading	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
hostler	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
who	O
had	O
just	O
rode	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
got	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
mare	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
mares	O
both	O
together	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
,	O
being	O
then	O
confined	O
at	O
Reading	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
they	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
Launcelot	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
's	O
mare	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
cast	O
on	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
that	O
.	O
87	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Beezley	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
set	O
of	O
green	O
bed	O
curtains	O
and	O
vallens	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
teakettle	O
,	O
two	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
three	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
one	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jervas	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Dec.	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Jervas	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
a	O
ready-furnish	O
'd	O
lodging	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
13th	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
not	O
returning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
[	O
naming	O
them	O
all	O
over	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
curtains	O
,	O
blankets	O
,	O
vallens	O
,	O
saucepan	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Shilingworth	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Water-lane	O
,	O
Black-friars	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
sheets	O
,	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
flat	O
irons	O
and	O
teakettle	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
and	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
also	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
myself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
88.	O
Robert	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
forty	O
guineas	O
,	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
five	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
four	O
moidores	O
,	O
one	O
two	O
moidore	O
and	O
half	O
piece	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Julian	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
16	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
certain	O
acquittance	O
for	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
13	O
s.	O
11	O
d.	O
1/2	O
,	O
and	O
uttering	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
true	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
forged	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
,	O
Dec.	O
4	O
.	O
As	O
no	O
evidence	O
appeared	O
to	O
prove	O
the	O
forgery	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
89	O
,	O
90	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
and	O
Catherine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
steel	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mark	B-pers
Verit	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Dec.	O
24	O
.	O
||	O
Mark	B-pers
Verit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Bow-street	B-place
,	I-place
Covent-garden	I-place
,	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
betwixt	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
round	O
the	O
waist	O
,	O
and	O
Catharine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
coming	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
they	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
tobacco	O
box	O
;	O
they	O
then	O
crossed	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
friend	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
he	O
to	O
you	O
when	O
they	O
stopped	O
you	O
?	O
Verit	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
when	O
they	O
first	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
gone	O
forwards	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
rescue	O
them	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
medling	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
called	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harrison	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
There	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
danger	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
go	O
and	O
bring	O
the	O
tobacco	O
box	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
bringing	O
it	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
picked	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Verit	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
.	O
One	O
says	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
says	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Middleton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
lay	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
round	O
the	O
waist	O
.	O
I	O
walked	O
forward	O
to	O
a	O
cellar	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
rum	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
women	O
into	O
Charles-street	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Eaton	O
.	O
Several	O
people	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
assistance	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
whom	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
?	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
into	O
Russel-street	O
,	O
where	O
,	O
with	O
other	O
assistance	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
Eaton	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
Covent-garden	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
watch	O
house-keeper	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
picking	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
tobacco	O
box	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
would	O
make	O
matters	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
bring	O
the	O
box	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
incouraging	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
it	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
detained	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
who	O
he	O
charged	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
nobody	O
but	O
Eaton	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
Turn	O
every	O
body	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
Catharine	O
Davis	O
desired	O
to	O
stay	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
matters	O
could	O
be	O
accommodated	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
bring	O
the	O
box	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
long	O
will	O
you	O
be	O
gone	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
She	O
then	O
w	O
ent	O
and	O
fetched	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
detained	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
the	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
said	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
spent	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
hoped	O
she	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
no	O
harm	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
only	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
goal	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
but	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
went	O
and	O
surrendered	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
admitted	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
the	O
two	O
Prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
in	O
Russel-street	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
his	O
tobacco	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
Catharine	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
's	O
man	O
,	O
or	O
bully	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
on	O
her	O
gettings	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
opened	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
but	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Davis	O
's	O
bully	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Round-house	O
to	O
Eaton	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
against	O
any	O
body	O
but	O
Eaton	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Eaton	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
to	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
running	O
after	O
the	O
evidence	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
where	O
being	O
searched	O
,	O
nothing	O
was	O
found	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
Davis	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
91	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Portman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
George	I-pers
Norman	I-pers
.	O
He	O
also	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
with	O
manslaughter	O
,	O
Nov.	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
Charles	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
fourteen	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
my	O
mother	O
was	O
ironing	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
with	O
me	O
standing	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
live	O
in	O
Gloucester-court	B-place
,	I-place
White-cross	I-place
street	I-place
.	O
This	O
was	O
betwixt	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
mother	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stand	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
brick	O
bat	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
near	O
Mrs.	O
Norman	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
he	O
from	O
his	O
wife	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
About	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
yards	O
,	O
the	O
alley	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
is	O
about	O
two	O
yards	O
broad	O
.	O
His	O
wife	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Norman	O
put	O
her	O
head	O
out	O
at	O
her	O
door	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
take	O
care	O
.	O
But	O
before	O
these	O
words	O
were	O
well	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
mouth	O
the	O
brick	O
bat	O
hit	O
Mrs.	O
Norman	O
on	O
the	O
forehead	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
bounded	O
into	O
the	O
kennel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
words	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
before	O
this	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
heard	O
his	O
wife	O
say	O
,	O
You	O
Dog	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
noise	O
you	O
before	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
quarreling	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
the	O
kennel	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
above	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
large	O
was	O
the	O
brick	O
bat	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
brick	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Norman	O
clapped	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
her	O
forehead	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
send	O
for	O
Mrs.	O
Willis	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
killed	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
husband	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Norman	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
throw	O
that	O
stone	O
?	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
several	O
times	O
that	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
hurt	O
that	O
poor	O
woman	O
;	O
meaning	O
Mrs.	O
Norman	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
poor	O
woman	O
bleeding	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Norman	O
and	O
his	O
son	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
They	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
apothecary	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
place	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
he	O
had	O
hurt	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
this	O
he	O
said	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
much	O
talk	O
between	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
rogue	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
I	O
keep	O
you	O
?	O
and	O
such	O
aggravating	O
words	O
.	O
The	O
witness	O
Charles	O
Lane	O
is	O
my	O
son	O
by	O
my	O
first	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
die	O
?	O
Willis	O
.	O
She	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
her	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
illness	O
;	O
she	O
found	O
herself	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
could	O
be	O
expected	O
the	O
first	O
fortnight	O
,	O
afterwards	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
pain	O
shooting	O
thro	O
'	O
her	O
head	O
;	O
then	O
her	O
stomach	O
fell	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
wound	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
?	O
Willis	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
it	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
perfect	O
health	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
her	O
door	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
husband	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fireside	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
being	O
washing	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
not	O
opened	O
it	O
above	O
a	O
minute	O
and	O
half	O
before	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
almost	O
killed	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Charles	O
Lane	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Who	O
threw	O
this	O
?	O
and	O
he	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
but	O
him	O
near	O
.	O
My	O
son	O
and	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
throw	O
it	O
at	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
wife	O
.	O
His	O
wife	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
comes	O
by	O
your	O
tongue	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
along	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
beat	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
make	O
no	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Withers	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
surgeon	O
giving	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
the	O
wound	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
die	O
?	O
Willis	B-pers
On	I-pers
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
She	O
kept	O
her	O
bed	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
hopes	O
,	O
for	O
near	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
recovered	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
she	O
bent	O
her	O
head	O
forward	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
violent	O
weight	O
upon	O
the	O
forepart	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
judge	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
;	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
good	O
health	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
then	O
a	O
washing	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
her	O
opinion	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Willis	O
.	O
She	O
often	O
said	O
this	O
wound	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
of	O
opinion	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
words	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
throw	O
it	O
at	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
daughter	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
my	O
mother	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
washing	O
.	O
Hearing	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
she	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
looked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
the	O
brick	O
bat	O
cut	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
brick	O
bat	O
fly	O
from	O
her	O
face	O
to	O
the	O
kennel	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
She	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
hands	O
to	O
her	O
forehead	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
covered	O
with	O
blood	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
flung	O
it	O
at	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Charles	O
Lane	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
from	O
Mrs.	O
Norman	O
's	O
door	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
your	O
mother	O
say	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
would	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
accident	O
?	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
she	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Norman	O
.	O
Who	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
brickbat	O
?	O
Norman	O
.	O
Charles	O
Lane	O
and	O
my	O
son	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
attended	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
that	O
day	O
to	O
dress	O
the	O
wound	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pretty	O
large	O
one	O
across	O
the	O
right	O
eye-brow	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
skull	O
was	O
quite	O
bare	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
no	O
fissure	O
nor	O
fracture	O
.	O
A	O
fissure	O
is	O
a	O
crack	O
like	O
a	O
hair	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
try	O
it	O
with	O
ink	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
effusion	O
of	O
blood	O
from	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
complained	O
of	O
being	O
very	O
faint	O
and	O
weak	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
no	O
fever	O
or	O
bad	O
symptoms	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
My	O
man	O
attended	O
her	O
two	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
complained	O
of	O
a	O
pain	O
in	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
neck	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
fever	O
coming	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
pulse	O
was	O
quick	O
.	O
She	O
continued	O
growing	O
worse	O
and	O
worse	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
died	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
After	O
her	O
death	O
,	O
I	O
opened	O
her	O
head	O
before	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
jury	O
.	O
Upon	O
taking	O
off	O
her	O
scalp	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
member	O
that	O
closes	O
the	O
brain	O
quite	O
free	O
from	O
any	O
coagulated	O
blood	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
divide	O
the	O
dura	O
mater	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
collection	O
of	O
matter	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
the	O
wound	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
left	O
globe	O
of	O
the	O
brain	O
was	O
in	O
its	O
natural	O
state	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
what	O
in	O
your	O
opinion	O
was	O
the	O
cause	O
of	O
her	O
death	O
?	O
Riley	O
.	O
In	O
all	O
probability	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
from	O
a	O
rupture	O
of	O
a	O
small	O
vessel	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
be	O
occasioned	O
by	O
the	O
blow	O
given	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
concussion	O
of	O
the	O
brain	O
.	O
Such	O
a	O
concussion	O
of	O
the	O
brain	O
is	O
much	O
more	O
dangerous	O
,	O
than	O
if	O
the	O
skull	O
had	O
only	O
been	O
broke	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
mentioned	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Norman	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
certify	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
danger	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
Jail	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
said	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
accidental	O
thing	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
unfortunately	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
threw	O
the	O
stone	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
occasioned	O
that	O
fever	O
?	O
Riley	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
opinion	O
it	O
was	O
from	O
that	O
eruption	O
of	O
the	O
brain	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
o'clock	O
Mr.	O
Norman	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
thrown	O
a	O
stone	O
at	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hit	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
affright	O
his	O
own	O
wife	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
opening	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
it	O
happened	O
to	O
hit	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
happening	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
names	O
she	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
stone	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
desired	O
she	O
'd	O
desist	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
paid	O
for	O
my	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
stone	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
jerk	O
'd	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
happened	O
to	O
hit	O
this	O
poor	O
woman	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
About	O
eight	O
days	O
after	O
this	O
accident	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
surgeon	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fair	O
way	O
of	O
recovery	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
better	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
pain	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
willing	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
man	O
out	O
of	O
jail	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
five	O
shillings	O
per	O
week	O
till	O
she	O
could	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
pay	O
all	O
charges	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
by	O
all	O
means	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
accident	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
flung	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
hurt	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
abiding	O
in	O
jail	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
satisfaction	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Norman	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
your	O
wife	O
saying	O
these	O
words	O
?	O
Norman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
no	O
such	O
words	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
behave	O
amiss	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
nor	O
ever	O
heard	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burnham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
manslaughter	O
.	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
92	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Ashley	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Bishop	B-place
's	I-place
Court	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
Old-Bailey	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
printer	O
.	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
at	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
when	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
(	O
being	O
sent	O
for	O
about	O
eleven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
her	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
excuse	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
remember	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
John-Matthews	O
Graydon	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Ratcliff-Highway	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Eliot	O
,	O
that	O
lives	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
above	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
woman	O
with	O
her	O
lap	O
full	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
no	O
such	O
person	O
lived	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Eliot	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
answered	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
neighbour	O
lived	O
the	O
stairs	O
below	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
replied	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
church	O
porch	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eliot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
over	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
evidence	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
met	O
a	O
woman	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
which	O
he	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
sheets	O
were	O
gone	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
we	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
St.	O
Sepulchre	O
's	O
church	O
porch	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
93	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Griffice	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
one	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
two	O
linnen	O
pillow	O
cases	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
stewpan	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
December	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
George	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
and	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Horse	B-place
and	I-place
Groom	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
John	I-place
's	I-place
Street	I-place
.	O
I	O
let	O
a	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
herself	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
again	O
by	O
her	O
directions	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jewel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
the	O
taking	O
these	O
goods	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
bad	O
husband	O
,	O
who	O
does	O
not	O
bring	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
so	O
it	O
was	O
necessity	O
that	O
obliged	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
ordered	O
me	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
91	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pettit	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
stock	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
one	O
boulster	O
,	O
one	O
pillow	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
chairs	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
October	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
taken	O
very	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Infirmary	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
there	O
.	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
what	O
conditions	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
in	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Infirmary	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
seven	O
weeks	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sold	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hartley	O
in	O
Tothill-Street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
since	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
she	O
sold	O
them	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Strughton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Infirmary	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
wine	O
to	O
comfort	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
broker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
one	O
and	O
twenty	O
pence	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
her	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
brought	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
she	O
made	O
of	O
her	O
goods	O
,	O
she	O
replied	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
no	O
such	O
order	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
goods	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
95	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barefoot	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Tomley	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
December	O
10	O
.	O
||	O
Richard	B-pers
Tomley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
,	O
and	O
waiting	O
for	O
a	O
lady	O
in	O
Welbank	B-place
Street	I-place
by	I-place
Oxford	I-place
Market	I-place
,	O
I	O
lighted	O
of	O
this	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
snowy	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
watchman	O
's	O
apartment	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
being	O
tired	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
awaked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
right	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
both	O
ran	O
down	O
Oxford-Road	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
house	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
was	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
near	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Church	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
soldier	O
to	O
assist	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
owned	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
nothing	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
coming	O
down	O
Oxford-Road	O
,	O
inquiring	O
after	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
assistance	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
soldier	O
deliver	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
Bess	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
that	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
at	O
Oxford	O
Market	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
fire	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
sit	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
or	O
hot	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
I	O
awaked	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
were	O
gone	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Hampshire	O
Hog	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
the	O
soldier	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
soldier	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
a	O
spout	O
under	O
some	O
snow	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
testimony	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
]	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Going	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
talking	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
crown	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
hot	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
Price	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
Perry	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
she	O
were	O
together	O
at	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
fuddled	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
Perry	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Two	O
Brewers	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
where	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
,	O
had	O
us	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Flanerkin	O
's	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
searched	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Perry	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
give	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
replied	O
,	O
you	O
fool	O
,	O
the	O
soldier	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
whic	O
h	O
he	O
delivered	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
bill	O
was	O
found	O
ignoramus	O
at	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
against	O
Perry	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
intended	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
mistook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
96	O
,	O
97	O
,	O
98	O
,	O
99	O
,	O
100	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Radborn	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Ambrass	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Radborn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Eler	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
Holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
hooping	O
cloth	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jeffery	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
January	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Jeffery	O
Burton	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
in	I-place
the	I-place
East	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
slop	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Mr	O
Gardner	O
called	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
replied	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
of	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
Holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
thirteen	O
yards	O
of	O
hooping	O
cloth	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
thieves	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
.	O
Pugh	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
where	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
thieves	O
lodg	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
gang	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
of	O
their	O
company	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
soon	O
let	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watchman	O
went	O
in	O
likewise	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
evidence	O
telling	O
us	O
where	O
they	O
resorted	O
to	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Anne	O
Brown	O
,	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Radborn	I-pers
.	O
We	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Rickards	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
evidence	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
one	O
upon	O
Thomas	B-pers
Radborn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
goods	O
on	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
hooping	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Spittle-fields	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
pawned	O
by	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hambleton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
turned	O
of	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Radborn	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
Daniel	O
Pugh	O
,	O
Jack	B-pers
Radborn	I-pers
,	O
Anne	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Radborn	I-pers
took	O
them	O
from	O
near	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
shelf	O
:	O
this	O
was	O
I	O
believe	O
on	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
staid	O
under	O
an	O
arch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
Thomas	B-pers
Radborn	I-pers
.	O
We	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
where	O
John	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
and	O
I	O
lived	O
.	O
Bell	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Radborn	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
shirt	O
each	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
pay	O
Pugh	O
when	O
the	O
cloth	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
three	O
shillings	O
for	O
his	O
share	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
had	O
seven	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
cloth	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
afterwards	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
six	O
shillings	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
piece	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Pugh	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
that	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
three	O
shirts	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
us	O
three	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Radborn	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Bell	O
's	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Pugh	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
happened	O
accidentally	O
to	O
be	O
coming	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Radborn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
Anne	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
the	O
boy	O
is	O
speaking	O
of	O
To	O
Bell	O
Samuel	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Bell	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
weaver	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
.	O
All	O
five	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
101	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
Ounces	O
of	O
brass	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeffery	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeffery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brass	O
turner	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
brass	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
two	O
evidences	O
now	O
here	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
parcels	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
The	O
whole	O
is	O
17	O
Ounces	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
the	O
Friday	O
before	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Lusham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
founder	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
parcel	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
[	O
taking	O
up	O
a	O
parcel	O
.	O
]	O
Dec.	O
31	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
it	O
weighed	O
11	O
ounces	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
fivepence	O
halfpenny	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
As	O
it	O
was	O
patterns	O
and	O
suspicious	O
brass	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
blamed	O
me	O
for	O
buying	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Jeffery	O
.	O
As	O
old	O
brass	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
worth	O
5	O
d.	O
a	O
pound	O
Charles	B-pers
Trinkwate	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Gyles	O
,	O
a	O
founder	O
,	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
takes	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
parcel	O
.	O
]	O
This	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
it	O
weighed	O
six	O
ounces	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
in	O
this	O
world	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
102	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Christmas	O
Friday	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
chain	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wished	O
the	O
right	O
owner	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
no	O
heed	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
just	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
said	O
somebody	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
turning	O
about	O
,	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
assistance	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
dropped	O
something	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
dropped	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
walked	O
side	O
by	O
side	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
seeing	O
him	O
drop	O
something	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
a	O
dozen	O
times	O
,	O
Why	O
do	O
not	O
you	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
a	O
black	O
bonnet	O
and	O
scarlet	O
cloak	O
came	O
by	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
flung	O
his	O
basket	O
from	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
all	O
false	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
chain	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Elener	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
side	O
by	O
side	O
all	O
alone	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
sober	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
wrong	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Bridget	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
six	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Scandon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
103	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
black	O
weather	O
sheep	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rant	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Dec.	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Banes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Shepherd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rant	I-pers
.	O
We	O
lost	O
57	O
sheep	O
5	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Monday	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
turnips	O
at	O
Northall	B-place
in	I-place
Hertfordshire	I-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
at	O
the	O
Ram	O
at	O
Islington	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
after	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
another	O
parcel	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
black	O
weather	O
sheep	O
,	O
on	O
Christmas-day	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
parcel	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
nineteen	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
black	O
one	O
,	O
of	O
one	O
Story	O
,	O
a	O
Butcher	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
branded	O
with	O
R.	O
L.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
was	O
the	O
black	O
sheep	O
?	O
Banes	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Rant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
?	O
Banes	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
brand	O
,	O
by	O
its	O
countenance	O
,	O
and	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Story	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
twenty	O
sheep	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
We	O
bargained	O
for	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
ground	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	O
,	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
ground	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
who	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
his	O
father	O
in	O
law	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
John	O
Plastow	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
'Squire	O
Rant	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
very	O
ill.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
ever	O
a	O
black	O
weather	O
sheep	O
among	O
them	O
?	O
Story	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
.	O
Banes	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pay	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Story	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
paid	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
or	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
being	O
owned	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
earnest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Story	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Beecher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
town	O
mill	O
at	O
Hertford	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
mill	O
door	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
standing	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
sheep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Beecher	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
sheep	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
from	O
Cattery	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
the	O
sheep	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Boreham	O
's	O
at	O
Hodsdon	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sheep	O
by	O
the	O
horns	O
,	O
and	O
dragged	O
her	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
.	O
Finding	O
the	O
other	O
would	O
not	O
follow	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
two	O
dogs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
set	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
parted	O
into	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
parts	O
,	O
the	O
biggest	O
whereof	O
went	O
thro	O
'	O
Hertford	O
for	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
master	O
went	O
away	O
to	O
Hitchen	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
two	O
men	O
enquired	O
after	O
such	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
sheep	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
stole	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Rant	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
Herbert	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
12th	O
or	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
inquired	O
whether	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
leave	O
some	O
sheep	O
in	O
my	O
ground	O
,	O
in	O
ordea	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
market	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Thursday	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Story	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
my	O
tenant	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
him	O
make	O
a	O
bargain	O
for	O
some	O
sheep	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
agreed	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
a	O
score	O
of	O
sheep	O
for	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
property	O
these	O
sheep	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
drew	O
the	O
agreement	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
in	O
his	O
name	O
Allen	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
married	O
Robert	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
's	O
daughter	O
.	O
The	O
sheep	O
were	O
branded	O
with	O
R.	O
L.	O
Mr.	O
Story	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
agreement	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
presence	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
this	O
ground	O
of	O
yours	O
?	O
Thomas	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
county	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
Mr.	O
Story	O
came	O
and	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
sheep	O
were	O
stolen	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
men	O
and	O
claimed	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rant	I-pers
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
What	O
defence	O
can	O
I	O
make	O
?	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rant	O
to	O
do	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
pleases	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
104	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Skelt	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
raisins	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
observed	O
by	O
the	O
watchman	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
raisins	O
from	O
amongst	O
divers	O
others	O
at	O
Fresh	B-place
Wharf	I-place
,	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
about	O
five	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
rest	O
them	O
on	O
an	O
oil	O
barrel	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
raisins	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
105	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
M'Cormeck	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bulkley	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Bulkley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Fleet-street	B-place
about	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
asking	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
He	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
found	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
footman	O
said	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
any	O
body	O
pick	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Bulkley	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
any	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
print	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
footman	O
declared	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
pick	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
that	O
he	O
need	O
not	O
appear	O
here	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
106	O
,	O
107	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
and	O
Catharine	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
with	O
a	O
stone	O
fixed	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
January	O
15.	O
*	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Grove	I-pers
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
Russel-Street	O
,	O
near	O
a	O
night	O
cellar	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
Moreover	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
.	O
Moreover	O
,	O
the	O
girls	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
welcome	O
.	O
Moreover	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
hot	O
on	O
the	O
steps	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
people	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
Brown	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tooley	O
's	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	B-place
,	O
where	O
the	O
three	O
persons	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
more	O
hot	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
three	O
pots	O
.	O
Moreover	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
left	O
their	O
company	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
we	O
had	O
eighteen	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
punch	O
.	O
Moreover	O
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
sat	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
hot	O
pot	O
made	O
of	O
?	O
Grove	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
They	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
my	O
ring	O
on	O
my	O
finger	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
returned	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Moreover	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
length	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
drawed	O
it	O
off	O
my	O
finger	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
immediately	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
likewise	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
liquor	O
was	O
drank	O
up	O
.	O
Moreover	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Jackson	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
snatched	O
my	O
watch	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
whereupon	O
I	O
immediately	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
took	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
into	O
Russel-Street	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
watch-house	O
;	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
not	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Grove	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Briant	O
Tooley	O
.	O
Last	O
monday	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
their	O
business	O
,	O
they	O
paid	O
their	O
reckoning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
Elizabeth	O
Humphrys	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Round-House	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
searched	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
Brown	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
herself	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
watch	O
,	O
she	O
replied	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
,	O
there	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
rolled	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
hair	O
behind	O
,	O
under	O
her	O
cap	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Humphrys	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
ring	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carrey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
brought	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
to	O
the	O
Round-House	O
;	O
he	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
asking	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
ring	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
Was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
sober	O
?	O
Carrey	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
fuddled	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
Catharine	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
desired	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
backwards	O
and	O
search	O
her	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Brown	O
,	O
went	O
backwards	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
ring	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
[	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
]	O
My	O
wife	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
watch	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
clapt	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
watch	O
on	O
a	O
lump	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
ring	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
but	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tooley	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
young	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
hot	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
eighteen	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
punch	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
Catharine	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
the	O
ring	O
off	O
of	O
his	O
finger	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Brown	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
reckoning	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Tooley	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
very	O
rude	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
conveniency	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Greyhound	O
;	O
I	O
replied	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
some	O
alley	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
down	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
crystal	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
deliver	O
up	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
but	O
having	O
been	O
knocked	O
down	O
,	O
resolved	O
not	O
to	O
deliver	O
up	O
the	O
watch	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
farther	O
.	O
To	O
their	O
Characters	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Mooney	I-pers
I	O
have	O
known	O
Humphrys	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Brown	O
from	O
her	O
birth	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
character	O
was	O
good	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Brown	O
above	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
have	O
employ	O
'd	O
her	O
in	O
doing	O
plain	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
husband	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
Brown	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
worked	O
and	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
108	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Champness	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
two	O
brass	O
pots	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
tablecloth	O
,	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
one	O
iron	O
poker	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
iron	O
shovel	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tempest	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
109	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
144	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Godard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
December	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Godard	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
goods	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
five	O
o'clock	O
,	O
but	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
tied	O
up	O
between	O
two	O
boards	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
.	O
A	O
much	O
larger	O
quantity	O
than	O
is	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
parcel	O
above	O
sixteen	O
dozen	O
.	O
[	O
Some	O
handkerchiefs	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
cut	O
in	O
single	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
marks	O
taken	O
off	O
.	O
]	O
What	O
convinces	O
me	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
some	O
are	O
a	O
pattern	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
drawing	O
.	O
and	O
some	O
spoiled	O
in	O
the	O
printing	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
Nay	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
they	O
are	O
all	O
mine	O
.	O
One	O
has	O
the	O
printer	O
's	O
name	O
on	O
the	O
selvage	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
whom	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
name	O
is	O
Robert	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
Cross-Examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
that	O
pattern	O
been	O
made	O
of	O
your	O
drawing	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
About	O
eighteen	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
May	O
not	O
other	O
tradesmen	O
have	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
They	O
may	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
you	O
say	O
is	O
spoiled	O
in	O
the	O
printing	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
May	O
not	O
there	O
be	O
others	O
spoiled	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
this	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
There	O
may	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Bevil	O
Bird	O
.	O
As	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
Strand	O
together	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
this	O
window	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
;	O
I	O
lifted	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
shut	O
it	O
down	O
again	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
shop	O
shutting	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
Cooke	O
lifted	O
the	O
window	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
goods	O
out	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
these	O
are	O
a	O
part	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
packed	O
up	O
between	O
two	O
boards	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
parted	O
them	O
betwixt	O
us	O
.	O
Cooke	O
pawned	O
one	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Keys	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
a	O
parcel	O
more	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
either	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-Street	O
,	O
or	O
Aldersgate-Street	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
one	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
sold	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
not	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
sold	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
the	O
cloaths	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
Cross-Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
kept	O
shop	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
this	O
ago	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
been	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Anchor	O
in	O
Little	O
New-Street	O
,	O
near	O
Shoe-Lane	O
,	O
that	O
night	O
the	O
thing	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
propose	O
there	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
into	O
business	O
?	O
Bird	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
business	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
work	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mensils	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
parliament	O
duty	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
constable	O
for	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
After	O
it	O
was	O
out	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
being	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Hemans	O
's	O
Row	O
,	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
were	O
Bevil	O
Bird	O
and	O
Cooke	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
alehouse	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Church-Lane	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
help	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Bird	O
drinking	O
with	O
some	O
women	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
bundle	O
dropt	O
under	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
six	O
new	O
ones	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
this	O
old	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
;	O
I	O
replied	O
,	O
then	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
must	O
belong	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
he	O
confessed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
took	O
these	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
and	O
six	O
of	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Cox	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
part	O
of	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
concealed	O
in	O
one	O
Harrison	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
father	O
in	O
law	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
Street	O
.	O
There	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
more	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
bed	O
.	O
Cooke	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
another	O
constable	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Bevil	O
Bird	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
five	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
spent	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
debtor	O
to	O
Bird	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Purcel	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
December	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
apprehended	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-Market	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Williams	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
picked	O
up	O
off	O
the	O
floor	O
that	O
lay	O
near	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
]	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
he	O
dropt	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
bounds	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
to	O
deliver	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Cox	O
's	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
there	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
these	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Williams	O
.	O
Look	O
upon	O
these	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
they	O
are	O
yours	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
by	O
having	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brittin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
Cooke	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye	O
by	O
Holborn-Bridge	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
Cross-Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Brittin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye	O
by	O
Holborn-Bridge	O
.	O
He	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
never	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
eleven	O
months	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
for	O
whatever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
scowrer	O
and	O
dyer	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
got	O
an	O
income	O
of	O
about	O
thirteen	O
pounds	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
necessitous	O
circumstances	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
many	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
informed	O
he	O
has	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Sydney	O
Cross	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
or	O
heard	O
any	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
a	O
year	O
to	O
live	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Gillet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
reputable	O
tradesmen	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
110	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hore	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
clogs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
scissors	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
,	O
January	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hampstead	B-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
losing	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
[	O
A	O
pair	O
of	O
clogs	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scissors	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
scissors	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
an	O
iron	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deposed	O
was	O
taken	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
before	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
111	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Martha	B-pers
Mingest	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ninety	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cellea	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
fixed	O
to	O
a	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
Dec.	O
29	O
.	O
||	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cellea	O
,	O
cutting	O
off	O
lead	O
,	O
who	O
flung	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
below	O
picking	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
dropt	O
some	O
pieces	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
lead	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
said	O
I	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
stealing	O
lead	O
on	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
112	O
,	O
113	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Purvise	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Hayes	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Carlow	I-pers
,	O
January	O
3	O
.	O
||	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Carlow	I-pers
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
I	O
employed	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
knowing	O
her	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Hays	O
told	O
me	O
one	O
was	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
pawned	O
The	O
other	O
owned	O
to	O
nothing	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Tomison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sheets	O
of	O
Purvise	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Hayes	O
brought	O
the	O
other	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
twenty	O
pence	O
.	O
[	O
Both	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
]	O
Purvise	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
of	O
taking	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Hayes	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
114	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
China	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
.	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Chilwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
through	O
the	O
glass	O
door	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
pursued	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
glass	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
it	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
glass	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
witness	O
brought	O
the	O
glass	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Thief	O
,	O
Thief	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
found	O
the	O
china	O
mug	O
.	O
Both	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Chilwell	O
,	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Chilwell	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
115	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
James	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
dozen	O
of	O
worsted	O
hose	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
hempen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Dec.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Kings	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
writing	O
in	O
my	O
compting	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
even	O
with	O
the	O
front	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Fidge	I-pers
called	O
me	O
out	O
to	O
look	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
haste	O
to	O
pursue	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
my	O
other	O
servant	O
Harrison	O
returned	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
into	O
my	O
compting	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
The	O
stockings	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
the	O
stockings	O
worth	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
They	O
cost	O
me	O
11	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
they	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
From	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
withinside	O
,	O
or	O
out	O
?	O
Roberts	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
within	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
is	O
all	O
inclosed	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
hands	O
take	O
a	O
truss	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
stood	O
on	O
the	O
bulk	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
,	O
but	O
ran	O
out	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
outside	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
bulk	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
shut	O
up	O
our	O
windows	O
that	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
truss	O
stood	O
is	O
shut	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
reckon	O
it	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
We	O
do	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
walking	O
softly	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
truss	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
He	O
turned	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
stole	O
these	O
stockings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
threw	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
nothing	O
of	O
yours	O
,	O
stop	O
me	O
at	O
your	O
peril	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
struggle	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
on	O
his	O
collar	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
tore	O
his	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
away	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
yards	O
farther	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
again	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
had	O
assistance	O
.	O
We	O
then	O
brought	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stockings	O
also	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
compting	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
so	O
much	O
sight	O
of	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
.	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Fidge	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
over	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pack	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
All	O
on	O
a	O
sudden	O
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
sprung	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
struggling	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
truss	O
of	O
stockings	O
within	O
about	O
four	O
yards	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Harrison	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
did	O
you	O
first	O
seize	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
four	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Evidence	O
continues	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
truss	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
to	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
immediately	O
went	O
to	O
assist	O
Harrison	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
several	O
people	O
come	O
to	O
our	O
assistance	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
compting	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fenchurch-street	O
,	O
near	O
an	O
open	O
bulk	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
seemingly	O
piled	O
one	O
upon	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
grating	O
.	O
A	O
porter	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
hamper	O
,	O
which	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
this	O
truss	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
almost	O
stunn	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
after	O
the	O
porter	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
dropt	O
something	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
kept	O
going	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
They	O
are	O
none	O
of	O
yours	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cleared	O
myself	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
They	O
then	O
called	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
twenty	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wine-cooper	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
vintner	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
brandy	O
,	O
rum	O
,	O
and	O
wine	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
carried	O
them	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
cash	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
within	O
these	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Priod	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
betwixt	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
abroad	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
Indies	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
is	O
good	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twenty	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
character	O
;	O
he	O
portered	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
nine	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
.	O
116	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Osbourne	I-pers
and	I-pers
company	I-pers
and	O
company	O
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
tobacco	O
was	O
in	O
hogsheads	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
lighter	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
custom-house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
observed	O
by	O
the	O
merchants	O
watchman	O
to	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
lighter	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
tobacco	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
deposed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
company	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
lighter	O
's	O
bow	O
,	O
but	O
kicking	O
against	O
that	O
tobacco	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Thomas	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Mansell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
117	O
,	O
118	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Grace	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
Catharine	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Bunn	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Barnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
packer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Aldermanbury	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Snaps	O
,	O
a	O
packer	O
in	O
Fenchurch-street	O
,	O
for	O
fourteen	O
pieces	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
returning	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
goods	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Barnet	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Howel	I-pers
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cotton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Snaps	O
for	O
fourteen	O
pieces	O
of	O
cloth	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
other	O
nine	O
there	O
then	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
for	O
them	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
piece	O
missing	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
pile	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Readway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Winter	O
,	O
a	O
clothworker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Magpye	O
,	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
in	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
A	O
piece	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Barnet	O
deposed	O
to	O
as	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Howel	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
on	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
asking	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
Grace	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
said	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
by	O
the	O
price	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
so	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
bind	O
the	O
bargain	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
constable	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
justice	O
of	O
peace	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
clerk	O
telling	O
me	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
myself	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
make	O
a	O
proper	O
title	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Catharine	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
bargaining	O
for	O
the	O
cloth	O
?	O
Readway	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
did	O
about	O
offering	O
it	O
to	O
sale	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Catharine	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
.	O
Did	O
I	O
not	O
desire	O
you	O
'd	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
it	O
to	O
advertise	O
it	O
?	O
Readway	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
talk	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
advertising	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rimall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
journeyman	O
Clothworker	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Winter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Magpye	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
and	O
exposed	O
to	O
sale	O
by	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Catharine	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
pawned	O
at	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
yard	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
While	O
my	O
partner	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
mark	O
and	O
Number	O
,	O
to	O
inquire	O
who	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
directed	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
business	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Howel	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
both	O
concerned	O
in	O
offering	O
the	O
cloth	O
to	O
sale	O
?	O
Rimall	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
cloth	O
and	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
charge	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Grace	B-pers
Bunn	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
Coming	O
back	O
,	O
in	O
Mark-lane	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
a	O
step	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
there	O
lay	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dirty	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
lift	O
it	O
.	O
but	O
brought	O
my	O
