TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
DECEMBER	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Twenty-ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1756	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
SLINGSBY	O
BETHELL	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
J.ROBINSON	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Lion	O
,	O
in	O
Ludgate-Street	O
.	O
1755	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SLINGSBY	O
BETHELL	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
FOSTER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
*	O
Sir	O
SYDNEY	O
STAFFORD	O
SMYTH	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
the	O
honourable	O
Mr.	O
BATHURST	O
||	O
;	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
John	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Hurt	I-pers
William	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
Joshua	B-pers
Hassel	I-pers
Laurance	B-pers
Giles	I-pers
William	B-pers
Stokes	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Brookes	I-pers
William	B-pers
Payton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Pickersgill	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Medstone	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Barwick	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Banister	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
William	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
George	B-pers
Stamford	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
Joshua	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
William	B-pers
Spinage	I-pers
Timothy	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Huntley	I-pers
1	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cooley	I-pers
,	I-pers
widow	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Margaret	I-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
-	I-pers
Cooley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pint	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
pewter	O
chamber	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
half	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
brass	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
Nov.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Eliz	O
.	O
More	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Cratched	B-place
Friars	I-place
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
wash	O
the	O
kitchen	O
window	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
;	O
that	O
night	O
we	O
missed	O
a	O
pewter	O
chamber	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
we	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
missed	O
,	O
also	O
some	O
brasses	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
used	O
the	O
mug	O
to	O
throw	O
water	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
We	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
nobody	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
knowing	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
her	O
mother	O
lived	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Harding	O
,	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
advertising	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
the	O
mug	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
chamber	O
pot	O
and	O
brasses	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
th	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
offer	O
this	O
mug	O
to	O
late	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Westminster-Infirmary	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Broadway	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
mug	O
about	O
half	O
full	O
of	O
pease	O
porridge	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
advertise	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
right	O
owner	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
taken	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
More	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
as	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Harding	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
about	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
of	O
ribbon	O
.	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
Oct.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Samuel	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
sessions	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
ribbon	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
some	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
others	O
;	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
my	O
back	O
to	O
deliver	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
to	O
another	O
customer	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
round	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
ribbon	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
piece	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
pull	O
off	O
her	O
says	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
her	O
left	O
breast	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
'd	O
it	O
towards	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
buying	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
ribbon	O
out	O
and	O
throw	O
'd	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
little	O
room	O
near	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
colour	O
was	O
the	O
ribbon	O
?	O
Cowley	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
black	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
September	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	O
West	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
some	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
some	O
others	O
;	O
he	O
snatch	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
stop	O
thief	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
some	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
some	O
more	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
have	O
them	O
for	O
nothing	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mob	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
dog	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
lad	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Reddey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
privately	O
and	O
secretly	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brinsden	I-pers
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Nov.	O
25	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Brinsden	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
seven	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
I	O
felt	O
somebody	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
by	O
a	O
companion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
at	O
a	O
lottery	O
ticket	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
Seeing	O
him	O
join	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
it	O
my	O
business	O
to	O
observe	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
their	O
company	O
(	O
named	O
Curd	O
)	O
,	O
point	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
man	O
may	O
do	O
to	O
a	O
dog	O
,	O
crying	O
hi	O
ver	O
.	O
Immediately	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
closed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
He	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
sware	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
confessed	O
that	O
Curd	O
and	O
Williams	O
;	O
were	O
the	O
names	O
of	O
two	O
who	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
fourth	O
handkerchief	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
before	O
,	O
No	O
302	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Little	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smither	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Nov.	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Smither	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Castle	O
in	O
Portugal-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Lincoln's-Inn	I-place
Fields	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
whom	O
he	O
calls	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
other	O
company	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
company	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
three	O
halfpence	O
to	O
pay	O
.	O
Some	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
also	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
my	O
servant	O
if	O
Little	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
three	O
half-pence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
see	O
you	O
tell	O
his	O
wife	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
comes	O
at	O
night	O
with	O
her	O
oisters	O
.	O
(	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
miss	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
most	O
evenings	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
William	B-pers
Hodgen	I-pers
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
in	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
either	O
buying	O
or	O
selling	O
something	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
daughters	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Briscoe	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Friday	O
Street	O
)	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
second	O
hand	O
tankard	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
shewn	O
several	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
mine	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Briscoe	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
there	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
passed	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
a	O
mug	O
or	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
No	O
2	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
his	O
wife	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
four	O
tankards	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
all	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
cypher	O
and	O
number	O
'd	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
No	O
.	O
1	O
,	O
2	O
,	O
3	O
,	O
4	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
that	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Little	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
brother	O
's	O
son	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
at	O
night	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Molly	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
room	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
this	O
body	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
let	O
me	O
leave	O
this	O
in	O
your	O
room	O
till	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
Hannah	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
(	O
meaning	O
his	O
wife	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
go	O
upon	O
guard	O
to-morrow	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
)	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
come	O
off	O
I	O
will	O
come	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Daniel	O
,	O
take	O
care	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
detriment	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
Mary	B-pers
Little	I-pers
lived	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
that	O
which	O
Hannah	O
Little	O
left	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
yesterday	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Friend	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
mistaken	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
since	O
Monday	O
night	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
Good	O
woman	O
make	O
no	O
words	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
want	O
;	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
mean	O
.	O
Friend	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
,	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
thin	O
piece	O
of	O
silver	O
that	O
goes	O
round	O
the	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
spoke	O
just	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
body	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
mentioned	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
cypher	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
weight	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rutter	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Smither	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
assistance	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
beadle	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
returned	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
delivered	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hodgen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Briscoe	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
silversmith	O
there	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smither	O
telling	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
tankard	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
only	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Hodgen	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Briscoe	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
with	O
this	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
handle	O
to	O
a	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
or	O
not	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
touched	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Briscoe	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
or	O
not	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
:	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
appear	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
concern	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
selling	O
it	O
?	O
Briscoe	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
paid	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
her	O
basket	O
to	O
sell	O
oisters	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
something	O
passed	O
between	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
spoke	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
thing	O
was	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
a	O
just	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
The	O
day	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
more	O
in	O
company	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
after	O
dinner	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Hannah	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
and	O
buy	O
some	O
oisters	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
fetch	O
my	O
knot	O
and	O
hat	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
returned	O
again	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
got	O
her	O
sieve	O
upon	O
her	O
head	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
borrow	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
her	O
landlady	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Chancery-lane	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
staid	O
for	O
her	O
pretty	O
near	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
walked	O
down	O
Fleet-street	O
into	O
White-Friars	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
we	O
were	O
just	O
removed	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
borrowed	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
that	O
would	O
fetch	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
by	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
church	O
among	O
some	O
rubbish	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
silversmiths	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
she	O
shewed	O
me	O
four	O
shillings	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
church-yard	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
more	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Briscoe	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
sold	O
another	O
bit	O
;	O
what	O
she	O
got	O
for	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
purpose	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
's	O
in	O
Beach-lane	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
into	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
into	O
White-friars	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
my	O
uncle	O
's	O
in	O
Norton-falgate	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
got	O
cross	O
Moorfields	O
she	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
something	O
that	O
will	O
fetch	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
still	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
It	O
where	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
wanted	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
,	O
until	O
I	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
scoundrel	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
thing	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
it	O
among	O
the	O
Jews	O
I	O
might	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
leave	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
cousin	O
until	O
I	O
come	O
from	O
off	O
guard	O
at	O
Kensington	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
time	O
to	O
enquire	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
cousin	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
there	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
off	O
guard	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
At	O
what	O
time	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
go	O
away	O
from	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
staid	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
H.	I-pers
I	I-pers
am	O
a	O
serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
guards	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
twelve	O
or	O
thirteen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
regiment	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
him	O
I	O
believe	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
unhappy	O
accident	O
happened	O
his	O
discharge	O
was	O
wrote	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
postponed	O
giving	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
hoping	O
that	O
as	O
he	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
character	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
lent	O
him	O
money	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
paid	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mord	B-pers
Cohen	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
23	O
++	O
Mord	O
Cohen	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
Nov.	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
crowd	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
too	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
dirt	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7	O
,	O
8	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hipworth	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
sheepskins	O
,	O
3-qrs	O
.	O
of	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
thread	O
,	O
3	O
ounces	O
of	O
sewing	O
silk	O
3-qrs	O
.	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fennimore	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
October.++	O
J.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Fennimore	O
my	O
journeyman	O
;	O
Hipworth	O
was	O
my	O
apprentice	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
Fennimore	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
keep	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
green	O
ag	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
their	O
indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
goods	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
James	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
linen	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
forced	O
the	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
blamed	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
Fennimore	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Jansen	O
:	O
the	O
any	O
thing	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
did	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
there	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
C.	I-pers
I	I-pers
am	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
owned	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
goods	O
into	O
Fennimore	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Fennimore	O
by	O
then	O
?	O
Edward	B-pers
Craine	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Fennimore	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
boy	O
would	O
force	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
said	O
Fennimore	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
cut	O
it	O
to	O
as	O
I	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Fennimore	O
cut	O
it	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
said	O
Fennimore	O
gave	O
him	O
sometimes	O
2	O
d.	O
and	O
sometimes	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
sometimes	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
goods	O
he	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Waistworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Fennimore	O
confess	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
goods	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Tompkins	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
him	O
a	O
cloth	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bn	I-pers
.	O
Fennimore	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
received	O
these	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
Hipworth	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Fennimore	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
to	O
make	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
some	O
buttons	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
mine	O
to	O
give	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
give	O
him	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
:	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
persuasions	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
several	O
things	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
master	O
would	O
find	O
me	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
money	O
,	O
a	O
penny	O
or	O
two	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
learn	O
me	O
my	O
trade	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
my	O
master	O
had	O
missed	O
a	O
few	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
pretended	O
his	O
conscience	O
pricked	O
him	O
.	O
Fennimore	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
asked	O
the	O
boy	O
for	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
What	O
the	O
boy	O
says	O
is	O
very	O
false	O
.	O
To	O
Fennimore	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Tompkins	O
said	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
Fennimore	O
was	O
bailed	O
out	O
he	O
would	O
employ	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Tompkins	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
such	O
a	O
word	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sherrard	O
.	O
Fennimore	O
served	O
seven	O
years	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
boarded	O
three	O
years	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
since	O
.	O
He	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
honestly	O
and	O
justly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
of	O
late	O
?	O
Sherrard	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
much	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
these	O
last	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
a	O
slender	O
capacity	O
,	O
but	O
will	O
not	O
hurt	O
a	O
worm	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
His	O
general	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
was	O
he	O
acquitted	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
effects	O
I	O
have	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Yates	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Salisbury-court	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sharp	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
or	O
upwards	O
.	O
His	O
general	O
character	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honestman	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
poor	O
weak	O
sort	O
of	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
honestest	O
men	O
that	O
can	O
be	O
this	O
day	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
better	O
than	O
twenty	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Cox	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Clarkson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
as	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
ever	O
broke	O
bread	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
weak	O
in	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
9	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gretton	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Gretton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Fleet-Street	B-place
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
and	O
a	O
tall	O
fellow	O
pass	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
looked	O
very	O
hard	O
at	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
some	O
design	O
upon	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
spit	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
quick	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
while	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
only	O
two	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
this	O
or	O
the	O
other	O
at	O
home	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
upon	O
it	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
positive	O
it	O
was	O
yours	O
?	O
Gretton	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
by	O
the	O
tall	O
fellow	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
10	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Andrew	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
shillings	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sterrop	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Sterrop	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
almost	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
strong	O
reason	O
towards	O
the	O
latter	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
of	O
robbing	O
me	O
(	O
his	O
having	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
money	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
carried	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
to	O
an	O
engraver	O
in	O
Gutter-Lane	O
,	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
a	O
private	O
mark	O
on	O
each	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
gave	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
one	O
Wilson	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Rayner	O
,	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
lay	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
money-drawer	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
persons	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
made	O
15	O
s.	O
Then	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
Mrs.	O
Rayner	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
said	O
has	O
she	O
not	O
laid	O
out	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
recollect	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
out	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
'd	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
readily	O
pulled	O
out	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
l.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
from	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
:	O
Then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
engraver	O
who	O
mark	O
'd	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pick	O
'd	O
out	O
that	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
All	O
mark	O
'd	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
now	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
and	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
?	O
Sterrop	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
keeps	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
?	O
Sterrop	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
key	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
use	O
to	O
trust	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
money	O
for	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Sterrop	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
frequently	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
laid	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
?	O
Sterrop	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbing	O
me	O
for	O
3	O
months	O
past	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
11	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Rachael	B-pers
Marshal	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
coral	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Godard	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Christopher	O
Godard	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
in	O
Little-Britain	B-place
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
glass	O
case	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
with	O
silver	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
my	O
glass	O
case	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Having	O
lost	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
boy	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
watch	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
fingers	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
glass	O
case	O
;	O
she	O
lifted	O
the	O
case	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
silver	O
chain	O
drawn	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
grabble	O
it	O
with	O
her	O
fingers	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
constable	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
got	O
into	O
Bartholomew-Close	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
maid	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
there	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
girls	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
delivered	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
four	O
silver	O
chains	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
case	O
not	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
seals	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
last	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
glass	O
case	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
lift	O
up	O
the	O
glass	O
case	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
back	O
was	O
towards	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
searched	O
twice	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hughs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Susannah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worstead	O
hose	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Coomes	I-pers
,	O
Oct	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
Rhodes	O
Hayes	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Coomes	I-pers
,	O
a	O
hosier	O
at	O
Holborn-Bridge	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
down	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
over	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
up	O
3	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
let	O
me	O
feel	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
these	O
;	O
she	O
weighted	O
them	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
a	O
toss	O
down	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
saw	O
but	O
two	O
pair	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
parcel	O
over	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
wanted	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
number	O
.	O
She	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
her	O
leg	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
large	O
stocking	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
large	O
leg	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
by	O
her	O
feet	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
took	O
off	O
her	O
garter	O
and	O
measured	O
the	O
calf	O
of	O
her	O
leg	O
,	O
then	O
measured	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
these	O
are	O
not	O
big	O
enough	O
.	O
Then	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
tie	O
her	O
stocking	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
stoop	O
very	O
low	O
with	O
her	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
pair	O
or	O
stockings	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
under	O
her	O
petticoats	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
but	O
21	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
stockings	O
she	O
had	O
measured	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
throw	O
'd	O
myself	O
over	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
get	O
none	O
cheaper	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
pair	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
feel	O
about	O
her	O
coats	O
,	O
there	O
lay	O
the	O
stockings	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
by	O
her	O
feet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
the	O
stockings	O
did	O
not	O
lay	O
there	O
before	O
?	O
Hayes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
upon	O
the	O
floor	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
husband	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
call	O
her	O
names	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
bad	O
company	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13	O
,	O
14	O
,	O
15	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burkhamshire	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Burkhamshire	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
.	O
Coming	O
home	O
,	O
my	O
maid	O
Mary	B-pers
Seward	I-pers
had	O
got	O
Ann	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
St.	O
Lawrance	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
Stafford	O
's	O
ing	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
denied	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
saw	O
Ann	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
go	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
,	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
distance	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
naming	O
a	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
had	O
no	O
such	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
property	O
she	O
owned	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Stafford	O
was	O
called	O
upon	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Stafford	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Buckley	O
and	O
Ward	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silk	O
capuchin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Ready	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Dec.	O
3	O
,	O
1754	O
.	O
*	O
Hannah	O
Ready	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
yesterday	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silk	O
capuchin	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
Ann	O
Stafford	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
stole	O
them	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
knew	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
stoln	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
she	O
came	O
round	O
by	O
a	O
stable	O
yard	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
Stafford	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Stafford	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Buckley	O
and	O
Ward	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haskins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
7	O
linen	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
2	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
1	O
damask	O
napkin	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
1	O
shag	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
1	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
1	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
East	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
Oct.	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
Jane	O
Baterson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
William	B-pers
East	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
married	O
a	O
fellow	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
permitted	O
to	O
live	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
They	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Name	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
saucepan	O
,	O
7	O
linen	O
tablecloths	O
,	O
2	O
shirts	O
,	O
1	O
damask	O
napkin	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
;	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
:	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
crimson	O
velvet	O
shag	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
these	O
were	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
son	O
's	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
said	O
nobody	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
him	O
and	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
finding	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Snowball	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
East	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
in	O
July	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
till	O
we	O
returned	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
October	O
;	O
then	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
granted	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
are	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
?	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
here	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Alixander	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
them	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
?	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
young	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Snowball	O
.	O
What	O
say	O
you	O
?	O
Snowball	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
young	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
Alixander	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
month	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
tablecloth	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
tablecloth	O
.	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Alixander	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
he	O
brought	O
another	O
table	O
cloth	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
.	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
That	O
also	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
Alixander	O
.	O
September	O
the	O
6th	O
he	O
brought	O
another	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
.	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
That	O
also	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
Alixander	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
he	O
brought	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
shirts	O
.	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Alixander	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
pledge	O
these	O
things	O
with	O
you	O
as	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
?	O
Alixander	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
lately	O
married	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
many	O
good	O
things	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
family	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Munk	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
silver	O
saucepan	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
this	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
two	O
tablecloths	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
these	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
those	O
tablecloths	O
.	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
damask	O
napkin	O
also	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
napkin	O
.	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
tablecloth	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
J	O
Baterson	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wakefield	I-pers
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
tablecloth	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
tablecloth	O
.	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
from	O
a	O
Juryman	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
marks	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
J.	O
Baterson	O
.	O
The	O
linen	O
is	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
mark	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
also	O
the	O
washerwoman	O
's	O
mark	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
Albert	B-pers
Hortsel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
me	O
this	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
September	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Snowball	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
?	O
Snowball	O
.	O
I	O
brush	O
'd	O
them	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
young	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
)	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
these	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Snowball	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
are	O
these	O
?	O
Snowball	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
do	O
it	O
with	O
any	O
other	O
intent	O
but	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Woodman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
me	O
7	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
leave	O
your	O
service	O
?	O
Woodman	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Hawks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kent	I-pers
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
alter	O
some	O
locks	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
with	O
things	O
of	O
considerable	O
value	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Hawks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
stain	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
accident	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
cork-serews	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
recognizance	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
18	O
,	O
19	O
,	O
20	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Blunt	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Pottle	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Appleby	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Randolph	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pocketbook	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
20	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-lane	B-place
.	O
The	O
coat	O
and	O
pocket	O
book	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
[	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
lay	O
before	O
him	O
]	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
that	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
coat	O
?	O
Blunt	O
own	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
kitchen	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Cole	O
the	O
evidence	O
said	O
Blunt	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
5	O
s.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
after	O
this	O
.	O
-	O
Cole	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
Randolph	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
,	O
and	O
I	O
going	O
along	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
;	O
Pottle	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
Blunt	O
put	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
pawn	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
Then	O
Pottle	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Blunt	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
Pottle	O
hid	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
all	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
which	O
this	O
coat	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
5	O
s.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Pottle	O
.	O
Whether	O
Blunt	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
me	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
Blunt	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
Appleby	O
and	O
Pottle	O
were	O
cast	O
at	O
Hick	O
's	O
Hall	O
this	O
sessions	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
want	O
to	O
get	O
Blunt	O
off	O
.	O
Pottle	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
pocket	O
was	O
that	O
book	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Banks	O
.	O
Blunt	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Cole	O
has	O
done	O
this	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
spite	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Blunt	O
and	O
Pottle	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Appleby	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
.	O
+	O
Martha	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Great	B-place
Wild-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
chairwoman	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
to	O
lace	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
stays	O
on	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Patrick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
candlesticks	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kingsmill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
her	O
character	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
good	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
She	O
chaired	O
for	O
my	O
wife	O
;	O
we	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
22	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Souther	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
house	O
of	O
office	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
Oct.	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
begging	O
about	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
at	O
times	O
,	O
for	O
about	O
3-qrs	O
.	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
sit	O
near	O
an	O
empty	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
my	O
children	O
used	O
to	O
pass	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
school	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
children	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
school	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
their	O
stays	O
and	O
things	O
on	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
late	O
without	O
their	O
stays	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
your	O
children	O
's	O
names	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
The	O
eldest	O
her	O
name	O
is	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Sarah	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
but	O
what	O
the	O
children	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
stuck	O
up	O
bills	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
cloaths	O
off	O
the	O
children	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
other	O
stays	O
for	O
21	O
d.	O
My	O
wife	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
she	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
from	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
his	O
book	O
;	O
in	O
looking	O
it	O
over	O
I	O
found	O
,	O
Old	O
stays	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
stays	O
;	O
here	O
are	O
other	O
witnesses	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
words	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
in	O
her	O
confession	O
?	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
cruel	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
cloaths	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
children	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
children	O
to	O
school	O
,	O
dressed	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
with	O
their	O
stays	O
on	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
home	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
without	O
their	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
of	O
their	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
sit	O
begging	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
had	O
taken	O
their	O
cloaths	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Elizabeth	O
lose	O
?	O
E.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
lost	O
her	O
stays	O
,	O
her	O
under	O
petticoat	O
,	O
her	O
cap	O
,	O
ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
E.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
seven	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
last	O
Midsummer	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
five	O
in	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Horse	O
in	O
Mill	O
yard	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
they	O
put	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
with	O
a	O
dozen	O
women	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
my	O
children	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
my	O
youngest	O
child	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
took	O
her	O
stays	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
clap	O
'd	O
her	O
hand	O
on	O
her	O
knee	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
mistaken	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
your	O
child	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
child	O
the	O
prisoner	O
held	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
.	O
)	O
After	O
that	O
my	O
eldest	O
child	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
it	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
still	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
she	O
owned	O
every	O
thing	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
children	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
E.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
this	O
difference	O
between	O
the	O
children	O
's	O
account	O
and	O
hers	O
;	O
the	O
children	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
off	O
their	O
stays	O
in	O
a	O
necessary	O
house	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
branch	O
alley	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
that	O
alley	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
another	O
alley	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
grandmother	O
to	O
the	O
children	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
's	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
stays	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
usually	O
dressed	O
and	O
undressed	O
the	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
Elizabeth	O
's	O
stays	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Thwate	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
with	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
pair	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
E.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
stays	O
.	O
E.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
lace	O
them	O
on	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
believe	O
they	O
are	O
what	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Christian	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
Look	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
?	O
Christian	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
stays	O
that	O
the	O
child	O
Elizabeth	O
wore	O
.	O
Thwate	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
18	O
d.	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Hazard	O
Austin	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
made	O
these	O
stays	O
for	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
we	O
have	O
new	O
covered	O
them	O
since	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeffs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Bailey	O
and	O
the	O
children	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
youngest	O
in	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
directly	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
mamma	O
,	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
stays	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
Jeffs	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
two	O
children	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
children	O
's	O
names	O
mentioned	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Jeffs	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
stupified	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
really	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Thwate	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
stays	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
at	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
swore	O
she	O
lost	O
them	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Christian	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
the	O
stays	O
on	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
C.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
school	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
remember	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Thwate	O
.	O
Name	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
.	O
Thwate	O
.	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
exceed	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
your	O
children	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
school	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
T.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
The	O
children	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
school	O
till	O
near	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Thwate	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
when	O
the	O
stays	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
T.	O
Bailey	O
.	O
Thwate	O
's	O
servant	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
,	O
about	O
dinner	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
master	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
in	O
recognizance	O
to	O
appear	O
here	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
has	O
here	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Thwate	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
maid	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Thwate	O
.	O
Her	O
name	O
is	O
Hannah	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
.	O
Court	O
to	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
.	O
See	O
if	O
she	O
is	O
bound	O
over	O
.	O
Clerk	O
of	O
the	O
Arraigns	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
bound	O
over	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
called	O
upon	O
her	O
recognizance	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Thwate	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
that	O
is	O
necessary	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
.	O
Thwate	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Virginia-street	O
,	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Armstrong	I-pers
's	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
23	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
2	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
1	O
coverlid	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
2	O
flat	O
irons	O
,	O
1	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
1	O
copper	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
1	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
pictures	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Weston	O
,	O
Nov.	O
11	O
.	O
||	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
24	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Clayton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
25	O
pound	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Coats	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
last	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Michael	O
Paterson	O
contesting	O
at	O
a	O
warehouse	O
door	O
on	O
Ralph	B-place
's	I-place
key	I-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ticket	O
porter	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
stroked	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
large	O
pockets	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
geat	O
bulk	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
cooper	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
some	O
sugar	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
Paterson	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
returned	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
cooper	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
trowsers	O
had	O
a	O
large	O
pocket	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
full	O
of	O
sugar	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
him	O
pull	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
trowsers	O
,	O
sugar	O
and	O
all	O
,	O
weighed	O
30	O
pounds	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
sugar	O
in	O
that	O
warehouse	O
where	O
you	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Coats	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
then	O
6	O
or	O
700	O
hogsheads	O
in	O
the	O
building	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
work	O
in	O
that	O
warehouse	O
?	O
Coats	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Paterson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
warehouses	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
from	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Coats	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
a	O
cooper	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
the	O
sugar	O
,	O
Then	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
others	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
cooper	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
usual	O
for	O
coopers	O
to	O
give	O
away	O
sugar	O
in	O
these	O
warehouses	O
.	O
Paterson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
full	O
of	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
keys	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
that	O
sugar	O
to	O
the	O
Red	O
house	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
carry	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Bridget	B-pers
Dailey	I-pers
,	O
Julian	B-pers
Morison	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Margaret	B-pers
Lines	I-pers
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
25	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Rutherford	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Wherren	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
uttering	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
forged	O
,	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
warrant	O
,	O
or	O
order	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
21	O
l.	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
,	O
Nov.	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
order	O
to	O
me	O
(	O
holding	O
a	O
paper	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
name	O
is	O
signed	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
signed	O
William	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
William	B-pers
Wilmot	I-pers
?	O
Wallis	B-pers
No	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
much	O
surprised	O
at	O
having	O
such	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
having	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
dealings	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
I	O
now	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
paper-maker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wholesale	O
stationer	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
(	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
order	O
)	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
,	O
and	O
expected	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
again	O
in	O
town	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Wherren	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
that	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
The	O
bill	O
being	O
made	O
payable	O
to	O
one	O
of	O
that	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
forgery	O
.	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
my	O
servant	O
aside	O
(	O
named	O
John	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
)	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
on	O
London-Bridge	O
.	O
My	O
man	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
shopkeeper	O
at	O
Shoreham	O
.	O
My	O
man	O
seemed	O
to	O
flatter	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
hopes	O
of	O
letting	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
how	O
the	O
account	O
stood	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
that	O
money	O
due	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
offer	O
that	O
as	O
a	O
good	O
note	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
;	O
drawn	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
alteration	O
;	O
except	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
wrote	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
my	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
order	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
,	O
but	O
very	O
badly	O
spelt.	O
``	O
SIR	O
,	O
``	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
in	O
London	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
this	O
Instant	O
,	O
``	O
and	O
shall	O
bring	O
with	O
me	O
100	O
reams	O
of	O
fine	O
``	O
srcap	O
nett	O
,	O
100	O
ditto	O
fine	O
pot	O
,	O
150	O
ditto	O
small	O
coarse	O
,	O
``	O
120	O
ditto	O
large	O
reams	O
writing	O
demy	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
``	O
hope	O
will	O
please	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
good	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
have	O
``	O
laid	O
my	O
mill	O
still	O
for	O
these	O
two	O
months	O
;	O
it	O
has	O
``	O
cost	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
``	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
pay	O
Mr.	O
Wherren	O
20	O
guineas	O
upon	O
``	O
sight	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
You	O
will	O
oblige	O
your	O
's	O
to	O
serve.	O
``	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILMOT	I-pers
``	O
Shoreham	O
,	O
Nov.	O
4	O
,	O
1755.	O
``	O
SIR	O
,	O
``	O
Please	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Wherren	I-pers
the	O
sum	O
of	O
``	O
21	O
l.	O
for	O
use	O
received	O
.	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILMOT	I-pers
.	O
``	O
Place	O
it	O
to	O
account	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
oblige	O
your	O
's	O
,	O
``	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
WILMOT	I-pers
.	O
''	O
Directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Willis	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Scepter	O
,	O
stationer	O
,	O
in	O
Gracechurch-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sum	O
did	O
he	O
demand	O
of	O
you	O
on	O
producing	O
the	O
bill	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
The	O
sum	O
of	O
21	O
l.	O
John	B-pers
Merry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
letter	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
master	O
has	O
given	O
an	O
account	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
spelt	O
his	O
name	O
(	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
his	O
writing	O
and	O
the	O
order	O
were	O
alike	O
.	O
)	O
So	O
he	O
wrote	O
this	O
name	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wherren	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
ask	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
that	O
order	O
,	O
of	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
Merry	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
tell	O
my	O
master	O
he	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
write	O
the	O
order	O
;	O
or	O
he	O
wrote	O
it	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Shoreliam	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
called	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
;	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
occasion	O
for	O
present	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
be	O
glad	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
draught	O
to	O
town	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
a	O
letter	O
would	O
be	O
safer	O
carriage	O
than	O
cash	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
draught	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
And	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
shop-keeper	O
at	O
Shoreham	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
he	O
spoke	O
of	O
the	O
hardship	O
of	O
staying	O
for	O
money	O
when	O
they	O
come	O
with	O
a	O
draught	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
I	O
might	O
know	O
farther	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
compting-house	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
my	O
master	O
traded	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
,	O
who	O
traded	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believed	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
mistake	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
money	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
So	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
the	O
writing	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
like	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
contrived	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
compting	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
hand-writing	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
extremely	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
many	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
upon	O
this	O
order	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
this	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
writing	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
verily	O
believe	O
it	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
writing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilmott	O
spells	O
his	O
name	O
with	O
a	O
double	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
has	O
but	O
one	O
t	O
;	O
and	O
here	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
mistakes	O
in	O
the	O
spelling	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Wilmott	O
understands	O
accounts	O
,	O
and	O
spells	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
writing	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
like	O
his	O
writing	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Wilmott	O
,	O
the	O
paper	O
maker	O
;	O
and	O
am	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
;	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
order	O
.	O
Allen	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
;	O
here	O
Wilmot	O
is	O
spelt	O
with	O
a	O
single	O
t	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
spells	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
double	O
tt	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
tweanty	O
for	O
twenty	O
;	O
gewenet	O
for	O
guinea	O
.	O
This	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Wilmott	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Roger	B-pers
Orford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mardstone	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
and	O
have	O
for	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Orford	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
journeyman	O
paper-maker	O
;	O
and	O
did	O
work	O
at	O
Sittingbourn-Mill	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Mathewson	O
.	O
He	O
usual	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rutherford	I-pers
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
other	O
name	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
from	O
that	O
mill	O
?	O
Orford	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
away	O
some	O
time	O
this	O
summer	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
there	O
at	O
work	O
last	O
March	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
letter	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
Ship	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
man	O
an	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
money	O
til	O
the	O
letter	O
was	O
opened	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
reward	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
26.	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
to	I-pers
John	I-pers
Townsley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
sattin	O
bonnet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
1	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
2	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
4	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
stuff	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
gloves	O
,	O
1	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
1	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
1	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
1	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
1	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Macarty	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
18	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
recognizances	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Townley	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass	O
fire	O
shovel	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
brass	O
tongs	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
sender	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
tea	O
kettle	O
,	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
one	O
box-iron	O
,	O
one	O
iron	O
heater	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Nibbs	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
left	O
by	O
contact	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
May	O
.	O
12	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
28	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
.	O
He	O
likewise	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
for	O
manslaughter	O
,	O
Nov.	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
Civil	O
Tompson	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	B-place
Hat	I-place
and	I-place
Ton	I-place
at	I-place
Hatton	I-place
wall	I-place
;	O
the	O
thing	O
happened	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
Deceased	O
?	O
Tompson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
temper	O
'd	O
,	O
drunken	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Tompson	O
.	O
A	O
good	O
temper	O
'd	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
will	O
drink	O
sometimes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
when	O
the	O
accident	O
happened	O
?	O
Tompson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
sober	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
deceased	O
before	O
.	O
That	O
night	O
I	O
and	O
Yarbury	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Tun	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
yesterday	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
people	O
dancing	O
and	O
merry	O
.	O
Presently	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
sidler	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
play	O
me	O
a	O
tune	O
;	O
he	O
play	O
'd	O
,	O
she	O
danced	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
more	O
women	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
each	O
at	O
last	O
.	O
The	O
Fidler	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
husband	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
(	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
angry	O
with	O
)	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
more	O
need	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
supper	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
many	O
ill	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
do	O
what	O
she	O
pleased	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
more	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
a	O
beating	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
with	O
her	O
double	O
fist	O
about	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
resist	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
his	O
hand	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
once	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
here	O
I	O
kept	O
that	O
blow	O
off	O
.	O
She	O
very	O
much	O
abused	O
him	O
with	O
her	O
tongue	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
gin	O
and	O
beer	O
.	O
She	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
ill	O
words	O
,	O
especially	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
aggravate	O
him	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
you	O
dog	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
have	O
it	O
yet	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
some	O
more	O
beer	O
before	O
I	O
go	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
blow	O
fall	O
?	O
Tompson	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
under	O
the	O
jaw	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
severe	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
pretty	O
sharpish	O
blow	O
.	O
She	O
sat	O
on	O
her	O
seat	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
or	O
hardly	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
drop	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
face	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
rowl	O
'd	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
little	O
noise	O
in	O
her	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
drunk	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Tompson	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
pretty	O
full	O
of	O
liquor	O
whilst	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
She	O
drank	O
gin	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
seem	O
'd	O
pretty	O
full	O
of	O
liquor	O
when	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
some	O
time-her	O
husband	O
came	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
subject	O
to	O
his	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
struck	O
her	O
dead	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
is	O
a	O
blow	O
with	O
to	O
much	O
violence	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
sober	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
killed	O
her	O
?	O
Tompson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
it	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
kill	O
her	O
,	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
not	O
made	O
any	O
mistake	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Yarbury	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
at	O
the	O
Hat	O
and	O
Tun	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
deceased	O
merry	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
sidler	O
;	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
giving	O
him	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
'd	O
have	O
a	O
dance	O
;	O
the	O
sidler	O
play	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
other	O
women	O
joined	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
dance	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
her	O
husband	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
keep	O
her	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
you	O
dog	O
I	O
'd	O
do	O
as	O
I	O
lease	O
;	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
cagmag	O
dog	O
,	O
and	O
Welch	O
dog	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
.	O
Her	O
husband	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
drinking	O
gin	O
now	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
have	O
some	O
more	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
rose	O
up	O
and	O
struck	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
rose	O
up	O
and	O
pitch	O
'd	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
face	O
;	O
he	O
lifted	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
is	O
apt	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
fits	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
water	O
on	O
her	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
wiped	O
her	O
face	O
;	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
we	O
perceived	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
parish-officer	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
coroner	O
to	O
inspect	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bruise	O
upon	O
her	O
forehead	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
I	O
cut	O
through	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
bone	O
was	O
fractured	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
injury	O
done	O
to	O
the	O
bone	O
.	O
I	O
likewise	O
examined	O
her	O
jaw	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
injury	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
her	O
death	O
?	O
Chapman	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
seem	O
'd	O
not	O
quite	O
certain	O
where	O
the	O
blow	O
was	O
given	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
greatly	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
The	O
fall	O
might	O
contribute	O
to	O
her	O
death	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
fall	O
itself	O
might	O
occasion	O
her	O
death	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
troubled	O
with	O
fits	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
fell	O
in	O
the	O
streets	O
,	O
and	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
dead	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
call	O
Mrs.	O
Tompson	O
again	O
.	O
C.	O
Tompson	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
had	O
several	O
sits	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
in	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
passion	O
threw	O
her	O
into	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
a	O
lab	O
orious	O
hard	O
working	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
29	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
watch	O
made	O
of	O
lane	O
metal	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Caple	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Daniel	B-pers
Caple	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
a	O
sister	O
of	O
mine	O
through	O
Cheapside	B-place
;	O
near	O
Sadlers	O
hall	O
there	O
were	O
workmen	O
erecting	O
a	O
stand	O
for	O
some	O
company	O
against	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
being	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
behind	O
the	O
stand	O
there	O
lay	O
boards	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
the	O
path	O
very	O
narrow	O
;	O
here	O
stood	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
perceived	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
directed	O
behind	O
him	O
towards	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
near	O
me	O
but	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pickpocket	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
watch	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sob	O
;	O
immediately	O
I	O
siezed	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
or	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
workmen	O
for	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
their	O
candles	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
his	O
right	O
and	O
left	O
pockets	O
but	O
stood	O
nothing	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
workmen	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
workmen	O
called	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
he	O
Compter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
's	O
day	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Worsley	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Caple	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
the	O
workmen	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
this	O
man	O
has	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
his	O
pockets	O
and	O
about	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Caple	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Compter	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stood	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
presecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Whether	O
if	O
this	O
watch	O
should	O
lie	O
in	O
that	O
narrow	O
path	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
trampled	O
to	O
pieces	O
;	O
only	O
think	O
of	O
that	O
my	O
good	O
lord	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
had	O
thrown	O
me	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
house	O
side	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
tumbled	O
me	O
about	O
the	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
my	O
good	O
lord	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
signal	O
came	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
Bow	O
church	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
stood	O
still	O
my	O
good	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
head	O
under	O
a	O
plank	O
,	O
there	O
this	O
man	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
have	O
any	O
I	O
have	O
yours	O
;	O
for	O
,	O
my	O
good	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
watch	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
year	O
:	O
I	O
wash	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
gets	O
buying	O
and	O
meading	O
of	O
stays	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Simmond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sober	O
man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
30	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
and	I-pers
James	I-pers
Mezarue	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
19	O
.	O
||	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
31	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Merron	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Haxley	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
9	O
.	O
||	O
James	B-pers
Haxley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
he	O
draw	O
'd	O
beer	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
gold	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
l.	O
He	O
left	O
me	O
in	O
August	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
my	O
maid	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
bedchamber	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
thought	O
she	O
had	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
at	O
the	O
chest	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
somebody	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
strove	O
to	O
break	O
my	O
buroe	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
my	O
neighbours	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
somebody	O
upon	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
mistrusting	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
his	O
father	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
boy	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
)	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
boy	O
denied	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
so	O
much	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
7	O
guineas	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
time	O
my	O
mind	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
time	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
my	O
buroe	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
halfpence	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
bag	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
and	O
hid	O
them	O
among	O
some	O
bricks	O
in	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
Inn	O
Fields	O
;	O
where	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
about	O
20	O
d.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
them	O
now	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Haxley	O
.	O
I	O
understand	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
13	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cuningham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
boy	O
confess	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
closet	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
mentioned	O
and	O
stole	O
the	O
halfpence	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
halfpence	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
32	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
1	O
pewter	O
plate	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Alsop	I-pers
,	O
Nov	O
||	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
33	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Isabella	B-pers
Buckham	I-pers
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
her	O
male	O
bastard	O
child	O
.	O
She	O
like	O
wise	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
for	O
the	O
midmurder	O
.	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
nurse	O
in	O
Faith	B-place
's	I-place
ward	I-place
,	I-place
Bartholomew	I-place
's	I-place
hospital	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
patient	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
burg	O
her	O
the	O
bed	O
pan	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
child	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
loose	O
stool	O
in	O
the	O
pan	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
emptied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
fire	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
puking	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
held	O
the	O
bed	O
pan	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
pulled	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
emptied	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
by	O
her	O
bedside	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
fire	O
side	O
again	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
warm	O
her	O
a	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
to	O
put	O
round	O
her	O
waist	O
,	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pin	O
it	O
round	O
her	O
waist	O
;	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
pricking	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
on	O
herself	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
again	O
;	O
Molly	B-pers
Elger	I-pers
called	O
to	O
Peggy	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
not	O
hear	O
a	O
child	O
cry	O
?	O
Peggy	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
hear	O
one	O
cry	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
A.	O
Smith	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
betwixt	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
this	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
nurse	O
,	O
my	O
sheets	O
are	O
all	O
wet	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
the	O
cloaths	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
sheets	O
all	O
as	O
they	O
are	O
when	O
a	O
woman	O
has	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
here	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
nurse	O
do	O
not	O
say	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
She	O
bid	O
me	O
put	O
the	O
sheets	O
out	O
and	O
have	O
them	O
wash	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
M.	O
Elger	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
look	O
here	O
,	O
she	O
says	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
child	O
is	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Then	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
pray	O
where	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
midwife	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
cleared	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
after	O
burthen	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
bason	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
her	O
white	O
flannel	O
petticoat	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
print	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
it	O
where	O
it	O
had	O
laid	O
.	O
After	O
sometime	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
drove	O
the	O
stage	O
coach	O
to	O
Bethnal-green	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
(	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
father	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
none	O
but	O
you	O
(	O
to	O
me	O
)	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
ward	O
can	O
save	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
child	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
child	O
afterwards	O
in	O
the	O
dead	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
coffin	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
swear	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
been	O
mother	O
of	O
children	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
people	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
condition	O
in	O
miscarriages	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
was	O
her	O
child	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
childbed	O
linen	O
among	O
her	O
things	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
looked	O
among	O
her	O
things	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Elger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
patient	O
in	O
the	O
ward	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
child	O
cry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
whence	O
did	O
it	O
come	O
?	O
Elger	O
.	O
From	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
ward	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
come	O
from	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
?	O
Elger	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
right	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Peggy	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
hear	O
a	O
child	O
cry	O
?	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
!	O
Polly	O
,	O
so	O
do	O
I	O
hear	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
this	O
child	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Elger	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
taking	O
in	O
room	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
coroner	O
sat	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
first	O
in	O
the	O
dead	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
you	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Elger	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
distance	O
of	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
yards	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
child	O
?	O
Elger	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
so	O
for	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
say	O
they	O
heard	O
some	O
young	O
kittens	O
cry	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
?	O
Elger	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour-after	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
upon	O
my	O
bed	O
a	O
coughing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Elger	I-pers
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Peggy	B-pers
Bland	I-pers
,	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
hear	O
a	O
child	O
cry	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Elger	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
,	O
Polly	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
hear	O
a	O
child	O
cry	O
too	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
myself	O
down	O
and	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
midwife	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
after	O
burthen	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
tracks	O
,	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
bed	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
child	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
dead	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
blood	O
and	O
matter	O
on	O
the	O
sheets	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
her	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
round	O
mark	O
in	O
the	O
petticoat	O
as	O
if	O
a	O
child	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
sheets	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
petticoat	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
blood	O
on	O
the	O
sheets	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
About	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
talk	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Lewis	O
