TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Twenty-ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1755	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
THEODORE	I-pers
JANSSEN	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1755	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
THEODORE	I-pers
JANSSEN	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
WILLES	O
*	O
,	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DENNISON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
,	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
||	O
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Delander	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Box	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
West	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Healey	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Covey	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
,	O
Adrean	B-pers
Marsh	I-pers
,	O
Jervice	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
,	O
Silver	B-pers
Crispin	I-pers
*	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Bosworth	I-pers
*	O
,	O
*	O
Crispin	O
and	O
Bosworth	O
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Bonham	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
served	O
part	O
in	O
their	O
stead	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlings	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Powels	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Flower	I-pers
.	O
299	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Lyger	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
peruke	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Nathanael	B-pers
Hatwell	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Nathanael	O
Hatwell	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
August	O
this	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
Lothbury	B-place
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Hatwell	O
.	O
At	O
a	O
dyer	O
's	O
shop	O
opposite	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
dyer	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Lothbury	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
from	O
thence	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
out	O
this	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
.	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
home	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
lying	O
at	O
the	O
carpenter	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
Seeing	O
nobody	O
nigh	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
a	O
person	O
if	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
about	O
mine	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Bentley	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
within	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Bentley	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
hat	O
out	O
under	O
one	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wig	O
in	O
his	O
right-hand	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
300	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Edward	I-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass	O
fender	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
one	O
iron	O
trever	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
drinking-pot	O
,	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
napkin	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
June	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
301	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Wigmore	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
a	O
certain	O
pistol	O
loaded	O
with	O
gunpowder	O
and	O
a	O
leaden	O
bullet	O
,	O
did	O
wilfully	O
and	O
maliciously	O
shoot	O
off	O
at	O
Duncan	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
Duncan	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
from	O
London	O
with	O
the	O
York	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
box	O
with	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
going	O
over	O
Finchly-Common	B-place
.	O
There	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
a	O
bright	O
bay	O
horse	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
small	O
swish	O
tail	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
fustian	O
frock	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
greasy	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
face	O
covered	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
mask	O
,	O
a	O
slouch	O
'd	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
peruke	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
overtake	O
or	O
meet	O
you	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
He	O
overtook	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
on	O
the	O
off-side	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
oath	O
,	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
'd	O
blow	O
his	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
The	O
ladies	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
seeing	O
him	O
pass	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
mask	O
on	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
said	O
one	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
there	O
comes	O
a	O
collector	O
,	O
get	O
your	O
money	O
ready	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
passengers	O
were	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
gentlewomen	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
of	O
about	O
50	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
The	O
coach	O
stopped	O
.	O
He	O
immediately	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
ladies	O
to	O
pull	O
down	O
the	O
coach	O
windows	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
'd	O
blow	O
their	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
gentlewomen	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
patience	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
our	O
money	O
directly	O
.	O
He	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
oath	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
business	O
is	O
haste	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
belonging	O
to	O
capt	O
.	O
Paterson	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
.	O
The	O
robber	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
fire-arms	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
come	O
out	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
being	O
quite	O
new	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
perceive	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
fire	O
it	O
off	O
;	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
near	O
my	O
eye	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
finger	O
on	O
the	O
guard	O
or	O
the	O
trigger	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
perceived	O
me	O
.	O
Upon	O
seeing	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
rascal	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
your	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
rode	O
round	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
fearing	O
he	O
should	O
shoot	O
the	O
coachman	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
coachman	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
get	O
down	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
robber	O
rode	O
round	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
'd	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
robber	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
round	O
,	O
to	O
fire	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
order	O
him	O
to	O
fire	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
better	O
chance	O
to	O
fire	O
last	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
fire	O
.	O
Immediately	O
I	O
fired	O
at	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
directly	O
fired	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
say	O
I	O
hit	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
certain	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
His	O
ball	O
went	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
right	O
shoulder	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
graz	O
'd	O
,	O
my	O
shoulder	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
hole	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
having	O
it	O
on	O
.	O
)	O
Immediately	O
I	O
jump	O
'd	O
from	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
near	O
side	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
his	O
horse	O
over	O
the	O
ditch	O
by	O
the	O
road-side	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
his	O
horse	O
's	O
head	O
about	O
towards	O
the	O
coach	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
round	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
attack	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
my	O
other	O
pistol	O
;	O
I	O
talk	O
'd	O
much	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
shot	O
at	O
me	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
his	O
ball	O
went	O
just	O
by	O
my	O
body	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
rob	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
That	O
ball	O
graz	O
'd	O
under	O
the	O
coach	O
wheel	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
your	O
master	O
now	O
;	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
no	O
more	O
powder	O
and	O
ball	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
he	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
between	O
that	O
and	O
him	O
.	O
Immediately	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
third	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
shot	O
at	O
me	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
.	O
That	O
ball	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
puddle	O
of	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
thanks	O
to	O
God	O
,	O
did	O
not	O
hit	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
immediately	O
he	O
rode	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
many	O
names	O
as	O
he	O
rode	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
coach-box	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
fired	O
at	O
you	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cogdel	I-pers
.	O
There	O
came	O
a	O
gentleman	O
riding	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
highwayman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Cogdel	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
East-Barnet	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Enfield-Chase	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
throw	O
his	O
pistols	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
throw	O
them	O
away	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
young	O
man	O
stop	O
before	O
you	O
come	O
any	O
further	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
stop	O
before	O
you	O
come	O
any	O
further	O
;	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
not	O
let	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
hurt	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
help	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
three	O
horse	O
pistols	O
.	O
)	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Barnet	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Swan	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
lay	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
me	O
?	O
Cogdel	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
justly	O
tell	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lockey	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
among	O
others	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
,	O
East-Barnet	O
to	O
Enfield-Chase	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
About	O
what	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
?	O
Lockey	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
High-Barnet	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
examined	O
there	O
,	O
being	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
my	O
cloaths	O
I	O
had	O
pulled	O
off	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
thigh	O
cut	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
ball	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
ball	O
?	O
Lockey	O
.	O
I	O
shot	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
taken	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Robertson	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
shew	O
the	O
hole	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
highwayman	O
shot	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Swale	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
the	O
York	O
coach	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
on	O
Finchley-Common	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
gun	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
somewhat	O
of	O
a	O
noise	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
stepped	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
over	O
some	O
pales	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
attacking	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Roberson	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
sirrah	O
,	O
you	O
rogue	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
not	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
highwayman	O
,	O
a	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Robertson	O
fire	O
once	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Swale	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
upon	O
the	O
pursuit	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
whether	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
was	O
cover	O
'd	O
?	O
Swale	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
200	O
yards	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
did	O
he	O
make	O
off	O
?	O
Swale	O
.	O
He	O
rode	O
towards	O
Brown's-Wells-Hill	O
,	O
coming	O
towards	O
London	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Describe	O
the	O
horse	O
he	O
rode	O
upon	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Swale	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
bright	O
bay	O
lame	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
darkish	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
frock	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
hat	O
not	O
cock	O
'd	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
wig	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
will	O
rob	O
,	O
or	O
has	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
Swale	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
upon	O
Finchley-Common	O
,	O
making	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
wood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
Swale	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
wood	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
did	O
I	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
forsake	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
wood	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
horse	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
made	O
away	O
for	O
East-Barnet	O
and	O
Enfield-Chase	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
run	O
so	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
rode	O
.	O
Two	O
men	O
on	O
horseback	O
began	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
hanging	O
in	O
chains	O
on	O
Finchley-Common	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
witnesses	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
examined	O
followed	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
Coney-hatch	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
round	O
the	O
wood	O
?	O
Swale	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
200	O
yards	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
once	O
was	O
within	O
50	O
yards	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
followed	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Swale	O
.	O
One	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
the	O
other	O
John	B-pers
Newil	I-pers
;	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
kept	O
galloping	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
facing	O
the	O
man	O
hanging	O
in	O
chains	O
on	O
Finchley-Common	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
round	O
the	O
wood	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
described	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
had	O
stopped	O
the	O
coach	O
in	O
another	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
dress	O
than	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
on	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
on	O
a	O
loose	O
brown	O
great-coat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
whitish	O
wig	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
bayish	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
horse	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Swale	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
man	O
you	O
saw	O
a	O
great-coat	O
on	O
?	O
Swale	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
coach	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wood	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
loose	O
great-coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
light	O
wig	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
you	O
saw	O
before	O
?	O
Swale	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
size	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
as	O
nigh	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
guess	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
face	O
?	O
Swale	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
from	O
the	O
wood	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
mask	O
on	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Swale	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Swale	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
74th	O
year	O
of	O
my	O
age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
Swale	O
.	O
The	O
horse	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
swish	O
or	O
wisk	O
tail	O
;	O
a	O
bay	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
lame	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
rode	O
who	O
attacked	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Taylor	O
continues	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
that	O
place	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
His	O
horse	O
broke	O
his	O
leg	O
at	O
East-Barnet	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
Enfield-Chase	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
at	O
Barnet	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
Swan	O
at	O
Barnet	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
his	O
wound	O
dressed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
part	O
was	O
he	O
wounded	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
wounded	O
through	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
the	O
thigh	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Newil	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
highwayman	O
in	O
the	O
wood	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
described	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
my	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
described	O
?	O
Newil	O
.	O
To	O
have	O
a	O
lightish	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
horse	O
with	O
a	O
swish	O
tail	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
wood	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
see	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
out	O
came	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
sixty	O
yards	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
loose	O
horseman	O
's	O
coat	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
frock	O
underneath	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
was	O
described	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
imagined	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
grey	O
wig	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
that	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
we	O
will	O
follow	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
pistol	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
we	O
followed	O
him	O
he	O
'd	O
blow	O
our	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
turned	O
back	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Coney-hatch	O
,	O
then	O
through	O
a	O
large	O
wood	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
riding	O
up	O
a	O
hill	O
at	O
East-Barnet	O
,	O
his	O
horse	O
broke	O
his	O
leg	O
short	O
in	O
two	O
.	O
I	O
rode	O
and	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
a	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
rode	O
down	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
whole	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
miles	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
sometimes	O
within	O
an	O
hundred	O
yards	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
less	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
upon	O
the	O
Common	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
firing	O
at	O
a	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
hewing	O
of	O
timber	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
horse	O
went	O
lame	O
.	O
We	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
track	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
bar-shoe	O
.	O
I	O
also	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
horse	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bar-shoe	O
on	O
.	O
Kinga	O
Brebrook	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
attack	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
fire	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
wood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
when	O
he	O
attacked	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
Brebrook	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
bright	O
bay	O
horse	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
swish	O
tail	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
him	O
I	O
track	O
'd	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
bar-shoe	O
the	O
horse	O
had	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wood	O
again	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
wood	O
?	O
Brebrook	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
out	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
path-way	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
He	O
drew	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
pistols	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
left-hand	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
path	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
by	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
seen	O
before	O
?	O
Brebrook	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
horse	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
wood	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Coney-hatch	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
got	O
another	O
witness	O
to	O
call	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
coachman	O
that	O
drove	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
may	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Call	O
John	B-pers
Pooley	I-pers
;	O
he	O
will	O
tell	O
the	O
court	O
the	O
horse	O
the	O
man	O
rode	O
had	O
a	O
cut	O
tail	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pooley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
drove	O
the	O
York	O
stage	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
stopp	O
'd	O
,	O
as	O
has	O
been	O
mentioned	O
.	O
C.	O
Describe	O
the	O
horse	O
the	O
man	O
rode	O
on	O
.	O
Pooley	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
brown	O
bay	O
horse	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
swish	O
tail	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Doubleday	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
we	O
had	O
an	O
affair	O
to	O
settle	O
with	O
the	O
overseers	O
of	O
Enfield	O
parish	O
.	O
As	O
my	O
brother	O
constable	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
we	O
will	O
call	O
and	O
see	O
Jonathan	O
's	O
horse	O
.	O
We	O
call	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Cat	O
;	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
bayish	O
gelding	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
mane	O
and	O
tail	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
a	O
cut	O
tail	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
at	O
his	O
shoes	O
?	O
Doubleday	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
long	O
the	O
tail	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
?	O
Doubleday	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
circumstance	O
of	O
the	O
bar-shoe	O
then	O
?	O
Doubleday	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Humphry	O
Buckle	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
constable	O
and	O
I	O
going	O
towards	O
Enfield	O
,	O
we	O
called	O
at	O
East-Barnet	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
marks	O
and	O
colour	O
of	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Buckle	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
seven	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
?	O
Buckle	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bay	O
horse	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
cut	O
black	O
tail	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
?	O
Buckle	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
or	O
was	O
it	O
not	O
cut	O
?	O
Buckle	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Buckle	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
cut	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
?	O
Buckle	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
it	O
been	O
cut	O
a	O
week	O
?	O
Buckle	O
.	O
Above	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
either	O
.	O
Here	O
has	O
been	O
many	O
people	O
examined	O
here	O
that	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
a	O
horse	O
from	O
a	O
cow	O
,	O
except	O
by	O
the	O
horns	O
.	O
I	O
get	O
my	O
bread	O
by	O
buying	O
and	O
selling	O
horses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Buckle	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
;	O
my	O
character	O
is	O
fairish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
about	O
the	O
bar	O
shoe	O
?	O
Buckle	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lockey	I-pers
.	O
This	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
We	O
killed	O
the	O
horse	O
in	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
That	O
man	O
shot	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
thigh	O
,	O
both	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
three	O
pistols	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
swear	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
three	O
pistols	O
that	O
were	O
shot	O
off	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
once	O
kept	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Palmer	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
character	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
he	O
out	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
thought	O
him	O
capable	O
of	O
doing	O
such	O
an	O
act	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Megers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
man	O
have	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
anything	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
many	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
in	O
Fleet-lane	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
substance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Megers	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Porter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
neighbour	O
,	O
and	O
bore	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
shooting	O
at	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
neither	O
will	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
neighbours	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
substance	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
earned	O
many	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
fact	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
?	O
Holding	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
kept	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
this	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
has	O
he	O
followed	O
within	O
these	O
five	O
years	O
?	O
Holding	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
this	O
last	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Palmer	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
alehouse	O
?	O
Palmer	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
alehouse	O
he	O
married	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
mother	O
lived	O
together	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
an	O
estate	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
on	O
their	O
substance	O
.	O
Since	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
used	O
the	O
Bull-and-Gatter	O
in	O
Fleet-market	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
that	O
estate	O
per	O
year	O
?	O
Palmer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
40	O
l.	O
per	O
year	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
way	O
?	O
Palmer	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
what	O
else	O
he	O
was	O
employed	O
in	O
?	O
Q.	O
to	O
Holding	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
business	O
have	O
you	O
earn	O
'd	O
many	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Holding	O
.	O
I	O
earned	O
20	O
l.	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
?	O
Holding	O
.	O
In	O
scouring	O
cloaths	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Molear	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
last	O
past	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Bell-savage-yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
a	O
house	O
there	O
?	O
Molear	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
frequently	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
302	O
,	O
303	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Reddy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Zebulon	B-pers
Thrift	I-pers
Blackston	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Geo	B-pers
.	I-pers
Bellas	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
||	O
Giles	B-pers
Nightengale	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
thro	O
'	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
church-yard	O
some	O
time	O
last	O
month	O
;	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
gentleman	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
standing	O
near	O
the	O
toyshop	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
Mr.	O
Bellas	O
close	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
those	O
boys	O
look	O
like	O
pick-pockets	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
can	O
detect	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
followed	O
them	O
through	O
Ludgate	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
turned	O
up	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bellas	O
proceeded	O
forward	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bellas	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoners	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Nightengale	O
.	O
The	O
crowd	O
was	O
so	O
great	O
at	O
Ludgate	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
them	O
there	O
?	O
Nightengale	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
within	O
about	O
15	O
yards	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
close	O
behind	O
Mr.	O
Bellas	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bellas	O
immediately	O
reply	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
suspected	O
two	O
lads	O
that	O
had	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
turn	O
back	O
we	O
might	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
boys	O
saw	O
that	O
,	O
they	O
run	O
;	O
we	O
pursued	O
them	O
through	O
several	O
alleys	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
cross	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
run	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
my	O
lord-mayor	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
handkerchief	O
found	O
,	O
neither	O
would	O
they	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
search	O
where	O
the	O
boys	O
had	O
run	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
down	O
an	O
alley	O
a	O
man	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Bellas	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
girl	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
drop	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Nightengale	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
so	O
fast	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
that	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Bellas	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
This	O
gentleman	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
giving	O
his	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Ludgate	O
hill	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
would	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
last	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
remember	O
?	O
Bellas	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
coat	O
open	O
?	O
Bellas	O
.	O
My	O
coat	O
generally	O
is	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
might	O
be	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
shewn	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
a	O
pretty	O
way	O
up	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
together	O
;	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
were	O
both	O
strangers	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
lent	O
me	O
a	O
stick	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
;	O
the	O
boys	O
seeing	O
me	O
run	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
ran	O
down	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
called	O
Black-and-white-court	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
down	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gateway	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
slung	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
away	O
;	O
they	O
ran	O
cross	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
up	O
a	O
hill	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
among	O
the	O
narrow	O
places	O
,	O
we	O
stopp	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
my	O
lord-mayor	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
both	O
were	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
handkerchief	O
found	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
convinced	O
that	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
either	O
lost	O
,	O
or	O
slung	O
away	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
pursuit	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Fleet-lane	O
,	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Evans	O
told	O
us	O
his	O
servant	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
Black-and-white-court	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
here	O
?	O
Bellas	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
child	O
of	O
about	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
of	O
years	O
sufficient	O
to	O
give	O
testimony	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
my	O
lord-mayor	O
.	O
The	O
boys	O
were	O
separately	O
examined	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
hopes	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
would	O
have	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
evidence	O
against	O
the	O
great	O
one	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
great	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
Blackstone	O
,	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
both	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
picking	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
did	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Blackstone	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
;	O
I	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
Reddy	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Blackstone	O
,	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
304.	O
William	B-pers
Levit	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
.	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Hassel	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
10	O
.	O
No	O
prosecutor	O
appeared	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
305	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Henry	I-pers
Besley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
July	O
30	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
306.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fagan	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
three-pence	O
,	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
and	O
secretly	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
recognizance	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
307.	O
Lydia	B-pers
Franklin	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
china	O
cups	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
,	O
July	O
17	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
appeared	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
308	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
glove-tops	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
6	O
yards	O
and	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Catts	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
4	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
309	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Christopher	B-pers
Dorman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
iron	O
ax	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
;	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
compasses	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jerem	B-pers
Adkerson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
It	O
appearing	O
by	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
since	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
no	O
evidence	O
could	O
prove	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
310	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
one	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
,	O
July	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Judith	B-pers
Brook	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Hospital-gate	B-place
,	I-place
Smithfield	I-place
;	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
coffee-house	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
or	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
away	O
the	O
day	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
?	O
Brook	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
John	O
Brook	O
.	O
A	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine-informed	O
me	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
silver	O
spoon	O
to	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
buying	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Greenaway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
took	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
a	O
table-spoon	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
pawned	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
Bride-lane	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
silver-smith	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
spoon	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
Cross-keys	O
tavern	O
,	O
Holborn	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
remembered	O
she	O
bought	O
such	O
.	O
a	O
spoon	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
tea-spoons	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buttons	O
in	O
exchange	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
was	O
truth	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
311	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Fagan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
My	O
wife	O
keeps	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
shop	O
,	O
in	O
Middle-row	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
backwards	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
my	O
servant	O
was	O
gone	O
after	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
picked	O
up	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
having	O
seen	O
the	O
gown	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
;	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
stock	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
for	O
change	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
change	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
tremble	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
gown	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
calling	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
a	O
wheeler	O
's	O
yard	O
,	O
Newtoner's-lane	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
gown	O
?	O
Ash	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
gown	O
was	O
found	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
it	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hallowday	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coach-wheeler	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
in	O
Newtoner's-lane	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
gown	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ash	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
gown	O
?	O
Ash	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
just	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
.	O
Hallowday	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
out-cry	O
of	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
run	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
:	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
throw	O
something	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
where	O
he	O
flung	O
it	O
,	O
saw	O
it	O
taken	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
this	O
gown	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
maid	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
gown	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
-	O
Plunket	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Cater	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
an	O
ill	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
service	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cater	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
true	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
312	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Folks	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pieces	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
containing	O
52	O
yards	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
July	O
11	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pedlar	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
linen	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
me	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
at	O
Old-Brentford	B-place
to	O
buy	O
some	O
cloth	O
.	O
She	O
bought	O
three	O
yards	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
in	O
seven	O
pieces	O
of	O
clear	O
lawn	O
,	O
52	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
pack	O
up	O
my	O
linen	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
her	O
neighbours	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
other	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
saw	O
the	O
lawn	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
fix	O
it	O
upon	O
this	O
woman	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
rest	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
had	O
no	O
hand	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
so	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
she	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Grimsdel	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
neighbours	O
of	O
us	O
together	O
at	O
a	O
dinner	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
told	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
house	O
consisted	O
of	O
two	O
rooms	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
lawn	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
vault	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tongs	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
roll	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
paper	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
jump	O
through	O
the	O
ceiling	O
when	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
brought	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
my	O
womb	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Porter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
above	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
she	O
once	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
business	O
?	O
Porter	O
.	O
She	O
makes	O
and	O
mends	O
for	O
people	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
313	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Swift	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
no	O
person	O
being	O
therein	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
iron	O
tobacco-box	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
||	O
James	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
upon	O
Ricelup-Common	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
seven	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
fore-door	O
open	O
;	O
a	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
drawn	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bolt	O
but	O
just	O
shot	O
into	O
the	O
hole	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
ring	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
One	O
John	B-pers
Field	I-pers
went	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
tobacco	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
box	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
'd	O
had	O
the	O
box	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
up-stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
Not	O
for	O
six	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
again	O
of	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Stonely	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
gold	O
ring	O
and	O
iron	O
tobacco-box	O
,	O
some	O
bread	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
pork	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
ring	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
that	O
Saturday	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
father	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
threaten	O
or	O
coax	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
confess	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
either	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
stole	O
my	O
gold	O
ring	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
of	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Stonely	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
M.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
They	O
say	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
his	O
14th	O
year	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Scarsbrook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
up	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	B-pers
The	I-pers
boy	O
owned	O
he	O
did	O
steal	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
George	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
one	O
Stonely	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
our	O
Common	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
ring	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
boy	O
threatened	O
?	O
Scarsbrook	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Stonley	O
's	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
Clark	O
?	O
Scarsbrook	O
.	O
Because	O
Clark	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
314	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Povey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
seventeen	O
linen	O
bags	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
23	O
.	O
||	O
Peter	B-pers
Colver	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Golding	O
's	O
bowling-green	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Old-street	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bowl-room	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
his	O
occasions	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
towards	O
Old-street	O
workhouse	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
his	O
bosom	O
found	O
three	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
bags	O
to	O
use	O
for	O
bowling	O
;	O
I	O
value	O
them	O
all	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
When	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
another	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
take	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
before	O
the	O
boy	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dracope	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
of	O
Colver	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
one	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
take	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
boys	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
put	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
my	O
bosom	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
looking	O
at	O
the	O
people	O
at	O
bowls	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
boy	O
from	O
an	O
infant	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
wrong	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
are	O
dead	O
.	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Holder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
boys	O
with	O
him	O
were	O
very	O
wicked	O
children	O
.	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Wilsher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
almost	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
315	O
,	O
316	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Benson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Richard	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
three-pence	O
,	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
number	O
'd	O
;	O
one	O
iron	O
key	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
money	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
July	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	O
Stevens	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
Somerset-street	B-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
ward	I-place
of	I-place
Portsoken	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Aldgate	I-place
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
going	O
through	O
Harrow-alley	O
,	O
that	O
leads	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
under	O
a	O
gate-way	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
;	O
I	O
pass	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
twenty	O
yards	O
off	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
coming	O
after	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
being	O
lame	O
,	O
step	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
come	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
short	O
again	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
another	O
word	O
he	O
'd	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
e'er	O
a	O
pistol	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
right-hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
thence	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
six-pence	O
,	O
three	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
bureau	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
other	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
queen	O
Anne	O
's	O
half-crown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
live	O
a	O
stone	O
's	O
cast	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
going	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
rob	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
;	O
but	O
fearing	O
he	O
should	O
prejudice	O
me	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
wife	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
what	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
whom	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
coming	O
the	O
rounds	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
hour	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
case	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
son	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
several	O
women	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
About	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
the	O
same	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
assistance	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Benson	O
hanging	O
over	O
a	O
post	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
son	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
Oliver-and-porter	O
,	O
in	O
Harrow-alley	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Benson	O
being	O
a	O
desperate	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
place	O
,	O
my	O
son	O
took	O
a	O
cutteau	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
all	O
three	O
together	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
just	O
under	O
the	O
gateway	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
talking	O
to	O
each	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Benson	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Jack	O
I	O
charge	O
you	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
Parrot	O
sneak	O
'd	O
off	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
but	O
about	O
three-pence	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
how	O
dare	O
you	O
do	O
a	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
?	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
bureau	O
?	O
that	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
the	O
bureau	O
is	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
do	O
it	O
hurt	O
to	O
break	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
also	O
said	O
I	O
valu	O
'd	O
the	O
half-crown	O
(	O
having	O
it	O
a	O
pledge	O
from	O
my	O
wife	O
before	O
I	O
married	O
,	O
about	O
twenty-one	O
years	O
ago	O
)	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
guinea	O
.	O
He	O
wrung	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
you	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
immediately	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
half-crown	O
to	O
Parrot	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
key	O
is	O
of	O
no	O
use	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
fit	O
my	O
lock	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
half-crown	O
from	O
the	O
officer	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
,	O
or	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
which	O
.	O
She	O
cry	O
'd	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
;	O
Benson	O
accused	O
her	O
of	O
putting	O
him	O
upon	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
'd	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
if	O
he	O
died	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
said	O
)	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
gentleman	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
say	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
chance	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
suckey	O
,	O
(	O
supposing	O
me	O
drunk	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
am	O
lame	O
,	O
and	O
walk	O
hobbling	O
)	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
do	O
it	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
answer	O
she	O
made	O
was	O
,	O
suppose	O
I	O
bid	O
you	O
kill	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
your	O
inclination	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
She	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
hang	O
me	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
only	O
transport	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
a	O
bright	O
woman	O
when	O
you	O
are	O
dead	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
but	O
a	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
much	O
ado	O
to	O
get	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
again	O
.	O
You	O
villain	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
guinea	O
had	O
I	O
?	O
You	O
only	O
fetch	O
'd	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
me	O
a	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
the	O
guinea	O
was	O
changed	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
striped	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
leather	O
apron	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
spent	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
half-crown	O
and	O
two-pence	O
half-penny	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
we	O
met	O
Parrot	O
very	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
?	O
I	O
never	O
answer	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
seemed	O
then	O
to	O
be	O
upon	O
the	O
look-out	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
person	O
made	O
any	O
outcry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
for	O
years	O
.	O
When	O
Benson	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
pawn	O
my	O
stays	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
ring	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
make	O
it	O
easy	O
upon	O
those	O
circumstances	O
.	O
We	O
thought	O
it	O
necessary	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Collet	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Benson	O
.	O
Whether	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
passage	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
a	O
man	O
ca	O
n't	O
see	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
moon-light	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Jefford	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
when	O
Benson	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
that	O
he	O
rob	O
'd	O
my	O
father	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
what	O
?	O
J.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
the	O
particulars	O
;	O
only	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
guinea	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
half-crown	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
son	O
to	O
the	O
Oliver-and-porter	O
;	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
Benson	O
;	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
was	O
mistaken	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
pistols	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
two	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
fell	O
in	O
a	O
passion	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
how	O
can	O
you	O
deny	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
so	O
well	O
?	O
Parrot	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matters	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
company	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Benson	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
of	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
half-a-crown	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
six-pence	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
three-pence	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
key	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
of	O
no	O
service	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
and	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
my	O
half-crown	O
is	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
value	O
it	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
guinea	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
called	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
,	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
key	O
and	O
half-crown	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
brought	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
them	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
satisfied	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
key	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
seeing	O
it	O
,	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
our	O
key	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
unlock	O
'd	O
and	O
lock	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
key	O
and	O
half-crown	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
the	O
half-crown	O
twenty-one	O
years	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
scratch	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
named	O
the	O
letter	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
shewn	O
to	O
the	O
jury	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
To	O
Benson	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hiliar	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Benson	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Benson	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
20	O
l.	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pay	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
embezzled	O
a	O
farthing	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Parrot	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
as	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
much	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cherry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Benson	O
six	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
honest	O
man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
eleven	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Benson	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Parrot	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
317	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Catharine	B-pers
Curtice	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
harrateen	O
bed-curtains	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Loach	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
August	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Anne	B-pers
Loach	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
several	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
away	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
these	O
two	O
harrateen	O
curtains	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Clements	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
servant	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
lent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
curtains	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
318	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
three	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
one	O
pewter	O
spoon	O
,	O
two	O
knives	O
,	O
two	O
forks	O
,	O
two	O
flatts	O
,	O
an	O
iron	O
frying-pan	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
tongs	O
,	O
one	O
napkin	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bolt	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
319	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Williamson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Phipps	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	B-place
.	O
All	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
tea-chest	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Owen	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Phipps	O
;	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Linsey	I-pers
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
just	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropt	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
secured	O
.	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Linsey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
informed	O
Owen	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
there	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
,	O
some	O
was	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
was	O
behind	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
stealing	O
a	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
two	O
years	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
320	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Amelia	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
.	O
The	O
pumps	O
were	O
at	O
his	O
window	O
hanging	O
upon	O
two	O
pins	O
at	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
missed	O
about	O
two	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
by	O
a	O
neighbour	O
,	O
who	O
informed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
321	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Callard	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Paul	B-pers
Callard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
King-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
bought	O
goods	O
of	O
me	O
between	O
the	O
10th	O
and	O
18th	O
of	O
August	O
last	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
I	O
missed	O
twelve	O
gold	O
rings	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shew-glass	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
suspecting	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
eight	O
rings	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
sorry	O
I	O
have	O
taken	O
eight	O
gold	O
rings	O
from	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
worse	O
man	O
for	O
me	O
by	O
more	O
than	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
by	O
paying	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
week	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
six	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
at	O
five	O
different	O
places	O
;	O
one	O
in	O
Newport-street	O
,	O
two	O
in	O
Sidner	O
's	O
alley	O
,	O
one	O
in	O
St.	O
James's-street	O
,	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
Some	O
we	O
found	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Callard	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
40	O
s.	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Innocent	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
George	O
Kennady	O
,	O
Murry	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
between	O
the	O
20th	O
and	O
23d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
(	O
he	O
produces	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
:	O
)	O
this	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
]	O
Abraham	B-pers
Barrear	I-pers
,	O
the	O
journeyman	O
,	O
deposed	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
three	O
times	O
to	O
buy	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
trusted	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
drawer	O
in	O
which	O
the	O
rings	O
were	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
them	O
at	O
his	O
pleasure	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
has	O
trusted	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
the	O
drawer	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
extraordinary	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
those	O
rings	O
and	O
they	O
not	O
be	O
missed	O
sooner	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
jury	O
whether	O
it	O
is	O
probable	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
silver	O
thimbles	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
nail	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
ring	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
hung	O
up	O
a	O
thimble	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
so	O
easily	O
missed	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
332	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Sears	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Humphry	O
Trott	O
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Aug.	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Humphry	O
Trott	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
the	O
Peacock	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
lane	O
,	O
Rag-fair	B-place
,	O
to	O
treat	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
was	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
skirt	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
into	O
Sears	O
's	O
company	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Trott	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
before	O
.	O
Sears	O
insisted	O
of	O
my	O
going	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
another	O
house	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
stole	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
?	O
Trott	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
my	O
breeches	O
being	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
Trott	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
had	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Trott	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Why	O
,	O
you	O
was	O
fuddled	O
.	O
Trott	O
.	O
Not	O
so	O
fuddled	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
what	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
and	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
possession	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gore	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
had	O
pledged	O
it	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
from	O
Carey	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
girl	O
?	O
Trott	O
.	O
I	O
treated	O
them	O
with	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
left	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Carey	O
.	O
Ask	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
any	O
present	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Trott	O
.	O
No	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Goadby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale-shop	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
;	O
that	O
day	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
girl	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
madam	O
there	O
is	O
some	O
whores	O
in	O
your	O
alley	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
which	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
They	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
as	O
Carey	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
produced	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
afterwards	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
:	O
Sears	O
was	O
blind	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
easily	O
secured	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Carey	O
.	O
Did	O
I	O
not	O
tell	O
you	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
Goadby	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
watch	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
here	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Rothery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
door	O
this	O
day	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
alley	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Carey	O
hold	O
the	O
watch	O
up	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blind	O
prisoner	O
Sears	O
was	O
groping	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Goadby	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
Mrs.	O
Goadby	O
deposed	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
addition	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Carey	O
's	O
pocket	O
apron	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
from	O
Carey	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
borrow	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Cosgrave	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
Anne	B-pers
Rothery	I-pers
at	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
rest	O
as	O
Rothery	O
had	O
deposed	O
.	O
)	O
Carey	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
left	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
publick	O
house	O
while	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
houses	O
distance	O
with	O
Sears	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
deliver	O
him	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
he	O
wanted	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
half	O
crown	O
which	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
that	O
money	O
.	O
Sears	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
along	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
:	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
room	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
his	O
watch	O
with	O
Carey	O
till	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
insisted	O
upon	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
,	O
without	O
giving	O
me	O
the	O
half	O
crown	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
324	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Colley	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Frances	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Robert	I-pers
Cockerill	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
sauce-pan	O
,	O
a	O
pewter	O
sauce-pan	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
stew-pan	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
August	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
325	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Cook	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
two	O
lawn	O
caps	O
,	O
one	O
lawn	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
lawn	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
one	O
candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
child	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
linen	O
caps	O
on	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
cloak	O
and	O
cap	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
326	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Sands	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edgar	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edgar	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
and	O
hosier	O
in	O
East	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
check	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
check	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
at	O
some	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
shuffled	O
about	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
goods	O
that	O
lay	O
tumbled	O
about	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
shewing	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
away	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
stept	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
doors	O
from	O
mine	O
she	O
droped	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
eight	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
She	O
strove	O
to	O
conceal	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
dropt	O
two	O
more	O
parcels	O
of	O
two	O
different	O
sorts	O
of	O
pieces	O
of	O
16	O
handkerchiefs	O
more	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
327	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
one	O
counterpane	O
,	O
two	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
iron	O
fender	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Inwood	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Aug.	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
328	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
22	O
s.	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
shalloon	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
quarter	O
of	O
worsted	O
stuff	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
hempen	O
cloth	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
unknown	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
thimble	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Jecocks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Horne	O
in	O
Well-close-square	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
goods	O
come	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
Birmingham	O
stage	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
advice	O
of	O
their	O
coming	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
stage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
book-keeper	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
delivered	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
porter	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
inquired	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
the	O
porter	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parcel	O
directed	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bramwish	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
ticket-porter	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Bull-and-mouth	O
in	O
Bull-and-mouth-street	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
parcel	O
of	O
goods	O
delivered	O
in	O
my	O
care	O
,	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
consigned	O
to	O
Richard	B-pers
Jecocks	I-pers
:	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Warwickshire	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
that	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
eight	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
all	O
but	O
two	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
White-hart	O
in	O
Grace-church-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
occasions	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
came	O
there	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
parcels	O
:	O
that	O
directed	O
to	O
Jecocks	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
another	O
woman	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
their	O
beer	O
behind	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
that	O
draw	O
'd	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
pursued	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
parcel	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	O
Cutter	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Harrow-alley	O
,	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
at	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
our	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
unlocked	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
leave	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
drag	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
She	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
ruffled	O
shirt	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Septimius	O
Moseen	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
watchman	O
and	O
warder	O
,	O
in	O
Aldgate-ward	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
or	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
choose	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
might	O
sit	O
on	O
the	O
stone	O
steps	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
should	O
hurt	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
thimble	O
for	O
my	O
daughter	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
I	O
produced	O
the	O
thimble	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Jecocks	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
thimble	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
there	O
that	O
claimed	O
the	O
thimble	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
bruise	O
in	O
it	O
before	O
she	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Orchard	I-pers
.	O
That	O
thimble	O
that	O
the	O
watchman	O
has	O
got	O
was	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
She	O
takes	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
by	O
several	O
marks	O
.	O
Miss	O
Heath	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
come	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
relation	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Jecocks	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
but	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
thimble	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
329	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Barron	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pike	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
warringer	O
at	O
Sisner's-key	B-place
;	O
he	O
is	O
accountable	O
for	O
what	O
is	O
deficient	O
when	O
it	O
goes	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouses	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
coming	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
sugar	O
loose	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
330	O
,	O
331	O
,	O
332	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Hines	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
;	O
the	O
two	O
others	O
for	O
being	O
accessary	O
thereunto	O
,	O
by	O
aiding	O
,	O
abetting	O
,	O
and	O
assisting	O
the	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
June	O
19	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
for	O
man-slaughter	O
.	O
||	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
widow	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
beaten	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
neither	O
speak	O
,	O
sit	O
,	O
or	O
stand	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
sense	O
than	O
the	O
sole	O
of	O
my	O
shoe	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
blooded	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
for	O
health	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
?	O
Crane	O
.	O
I	O
dined	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
hearty	O
and	O
well	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
workhouse	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
Friday	O
;	O
he	O
remained	O
there	O
till	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
carried	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
to	O
Westminster-infirmary	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
but	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
carried	O
him	O
home	O
by	O
his	O
desire	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
after	O
the	O
beating	O
five	O
weeks	O
and	O
one	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Crane	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
sell	O
milk	O
one	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
eight	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
took	O
to	O
his	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
marks	O
did	O
you	O
perceive	O
on	O
him	O
?	O
Crane	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
cut	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
his	O
hip	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
his	O
groin	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
complained	O
of	O
mortal	O
bruises	O
inwardly	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
my	O
work	O
just	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Owen	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
walking	O
up	O
King-street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
,	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
large	O
stick	O
,	O
something	O
like	O
a	O
broom-stick	O
;	O
somebody	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
mob	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
Crane	O
pass	O
'd	O
through	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
chairman	O
,	O
drew	O
out	O
his	O
chair-pole	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
it	O
hit	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
them	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
thirty	O
yards	O
off	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
made	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
coloured	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
up	O
with	O
red	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
silver-laced	O
hat	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
up	O
his	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
chairman	O
took	O
up	O
Owen	O
Crane	O
's	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
more	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
company	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
part	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
assign	O
any	O
reason	O
why	O
the	O
chairman	O
drew	O
out	O
the	O
chair-pole	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
at	O
the	O
deceased	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
no	O
other	O
reason	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
their	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
workhouse	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
after	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
excessive	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
reach	O
'd	O
very	O
much	O
with	O
blood	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
several	O
marks	O
about	O
his	O
body	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
black	O
mark	O
under	O
his	O
rib	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
pain	O
lay	O
on	O
his	O
left-side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
do	O
anything	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
against	O
them	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
that	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
were	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
groun	O
d	O
together	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
struggle	O
between	O
them	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
possible	O
the	O
fall	O
might	O
disorder	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
fell	O
uppermost	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
blows	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
fall	O
hard	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
He	O
fell	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
thinking	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
chairman	O
strike	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
deceased	O
struck	O
him	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
strike	O
at	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
pole	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
or	O
not	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
deceased	O
abroad	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
down	O
King-street	O
once	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
how	O
long	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
abroad	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
appear	O
then	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
He	O
appeared	O
excessive	O
bad	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
led	O
home	O
,	O
or	O
partly	O
carry	O
'd	O
between	O
two	O
men	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hamilton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
Crane	O
on	O
his	O
death-bed	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
22d	O
,	O
or	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
bruises	O
he	O
received	O
at	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
bruises	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
two	O
chairmen	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
beat	O
him	O
till	O
his	O
sight	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
mes	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
named	O
Salter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
lay	O
your	O
death	O
to	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
lay	O
my	O
death	O
to	O
Salter	O
in	O
particular	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
Crane	O
died	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
esquire	O
Manby	O
;	O
Esquire	O
Manby	O
said	O
,	O
Salter	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
for	O
this	O
;	O
so	O
am	O
I	O
,	O
said	O
Salter	O
;	O
for	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
others	O
should	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
a	O
justice	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Salter	O
(	O
he	O
having	O
a	O
broom-stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
I	O
suppose	O
that	O
is	O
what	O
you	O
hurt	O
the	O
man	O
with	O
yesterday	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
by	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
I	O
would	O
serve	O
you	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
an	O
authority	O
to	O
serve	O
any	O
body	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
hear	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
deceased	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
?	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
authority	O
to	O
serve	O
any	O
man	O
so	O
?	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
orders	O
to	O
aid	O
and	O
assist	O
.	O
Cicilia	O
Read	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
blows	O
happened	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
King-street	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
Owen	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
before	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
your	O
comrades	O
are	O
taken	O
prisoners	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
comrades	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
his	O
fellow-labourers	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Salter	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
murder	O
'd	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
why	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Owen	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
had	O
a	O
broom-stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
held	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
to	O
strike	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
defend	O
himself	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
which	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
point	O
it	O
towards	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
he	O
hold	O
it	O
cross-ways	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
it	O
cross-ways	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Salter	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
down	O
with	O
a	O
chair-pole	O
;	O
I	O
clap	O
'd	O
my	O
hands	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
murder	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
footman	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
going	O
to	O
murder	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
Owen	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
;	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
stop	O
when	O
Salter	O
bid	O
him	O
stand	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
did	O
the	O
chair-pole	O
come	O
on	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
came	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
shoulder	O
or	O
side	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
struck	O
him	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
it	O
did	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
did	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
lay	O
down	O
,	O
Salter	O
had	O
his	O
left	O
knee	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
there	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
footman	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
silver-laced	O
hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
deceased	O
and	O
the	O
footman	O
struggle	O
together	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
thing	O
said	O
when	O
they	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
,	O
upon	O
your	O
oath	O
,	O
say	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
falling	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
blow	O
or	O
the	O
struggling	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
oath	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
chair-pole	O
knocking	O
him	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
them	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
was	O
within	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Palmer	O
or	O
Hines	O
then	O
?	O
Read	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
off	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
knock	O
'd	O
down	O
.	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Bowen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
Coach-and-horses	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
mob	O
gather	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
deceased	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Salter	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
and	O
Salter	O
struck	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
with	O
a	O
broom-stick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
chair-pole	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
chair-pole	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
Salter	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
broom-stick	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
broom-stick	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Salter	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
when	O
he	O
struck	O
him	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
stick	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
hit	O
the	O
deceased	O
a	O
blow	O
cross	O
the	O
stomach	O
;	O
and	O
immediately	O
the	O
blood	O
gushed	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
mouth	O
and	O
nose	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
workhouse	O
;	O
he	O
complain	O
'd	O
of	O
pain	O
in	O
the	O
pit	O
of	O
his	O
stomach	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
body	O
say	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
murder	O
'd	O
a	O
woman	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
deceased	O
out	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
Bowen	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
apothecary	O
's	O
for	O
something	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
betwixt	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
going	O
along	O
King-street	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
James	B-pers
Hines	I-pers
take	O
the	O
deceased	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
him	O
