TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
26th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
27th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
;	O
Saturday	O
the	O
1st	O
;	O
Monday	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
MARCH	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Twenty-eighth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1755	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
THEODORE	I-pers
JANSSEN	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1755	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDING	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
STEPHEN	B-pers
THEODORE	I-pers
JANSSEN	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILMOTT	O
+	O
;	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Recorder	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Heavysides	I-pers
,	O
Gamaliel	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Nesbit	I-pers
,	O
Ebenezar	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Poperton	I-pers
,	O
Randalph	B-pers
Baileys	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Keen	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Basson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Brewin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pricklow	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lowry	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hand	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carruthers	I-pers
,	O
Christopher	B-pers
Blenkarn	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lecister	I-pers
,	O
*	O
*	O
Lecister	O
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Moncure	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goldsmith	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
,	O
Humphrey	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
,	O
92	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
china	O
tea-cups	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
a	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
,	O
china	O
bason	O
,	O
one	O
chinasugar-dish	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Filks	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Filks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Long-acre	B-place
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
wine-merchant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
my	O
door	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
hair-cloth	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
through	O
a	O
little	O
parlour	O
into	O
the	O
dining-room	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
stairs	O
I	O
stopt	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
seven	O
cups	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
saucers	O
,	O
a	O
tea-pot	O
,	O
a	O
bason	O
,	O
and	O
sugar-dish	O
,	O
all	O
china	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
a	O
cup	O
and	O
saucer	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
all	O
the	O
china	O
you	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
lap	O
your	O
china	O
?	O
Filks	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Filks	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Filks	O
were	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
beyond	O
the	O
dining-room	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
some	O
china	O
rattle	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
china	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
lap	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cup	O
and	O
saucer	O
broke	O
in	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
93	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
George	I-pers
Shader	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
one	O
lawn	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Luker	I-pers
;	O
two	O
ells	O
of	O
dowlas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Burtor	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
let	O
to	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
lodging	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
from	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
at	O
their	O
return	O
they	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gone	O
;	O
they	O
at	O
last	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
full	O
of	O
smoak	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
opening	O
a	O
drawer	O
found	O
divers	O
linen	O
things	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
at	O
two	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
No	O
punishment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
94	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Decemb	O
.	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
95	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Fleck	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Clemoutson	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
Edward	O
Clemoutson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Russel-court	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
;	O
just	O
coming	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
with	O
this	O
bundle	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
ten	O
pair	O
)	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
with	O
that	O
bundle	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
a	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
him	O
three-pence	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
:	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Abchurch-lane	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
work	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
stood	O
near	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
lad	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
earn	O
threepence	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
doing	O
what	O
?	O
He	O
pointed	O
to	O
that	O
bundle	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
that	O
bundle	O
and	O
follow	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
96	O
,	O
97	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Hales	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
shalloon	O
,	O
containing	O
two	O
hundred	O
and	O
twenty-four	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
l.	O
two-pieces	O
of	O
bays	O
,	O
containing	O
seventy-four	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
thirty	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
called	O
everlasting	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Royds	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
in	O
their	O
warehouse	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cowley	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Royds	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Haines	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
Mr.	O
Sky	O
in	O
Bucklersbury	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Gee	O
at	O
the	O
Lock-and-key	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
servant	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
parcel	O
left	O
at	O
his	O
(	O
Mr.	O
Sky	O
's	O
house	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
two	O
shalloons	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Sky	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Lock-and-key	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
Cowley	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
receiving	O
shalloons	O
from	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
my	O
porter	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
liberty	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
allowed	O
him	O
two-pence	O
a	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
by	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
down	O
some	O
bays	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
because	O
the	O
marks	O
were	O
taken	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
two	O
shalloons	O
,	O
and	O
twenty	O
yards	O
of	O
bays	O
to	O
one	O
Abraham	B-pers
Port	I-pers
in	O
Cloth-fair	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
four	O
shalloons	O
,	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
each	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
the	O
selling	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
everlasting	O
,	O
containing	O
thirty	O
yards	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
for	O
27	O
s.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
sometimes	O
for	O
one	O
price	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
for	O
another	O
.	O
He	O
also	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
sold	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Black	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Black-friars	O
seventeen	O
yards	O
of	O
Bays	O
;	O
and	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Carshaw	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Drury-lane	O
twenty	O
yards	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
could	O
easily	O
get	O
at	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
mention	O
Haines	O
's	O
name	O
to	O
Cowley	O
?	O
Royds	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
(	O
Four	O
pieces	O
of	O
shalloon	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Sky	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Bucklersbury	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
four	O
pieces	O
that	O
Pierce	O
bought	O
by	O
Cowley	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
produce	O
,	O
nor	O
tell	O
whould	O
he	O
has	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sky	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
Haines	O
brought	O
these	O
two	O
piece	O
of	O
bay	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
here	O
?	O
Sky	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
is	O
near	O
her	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
capacity	O
to	O
attend	O
here	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
servant	O
is	O
gone	O
away	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
country	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Haines	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
there	O
these	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
from	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
warehouse	O
mentioned	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
him	O
any	O
favour	O
previous	O
to	O
this	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
every	O
thing	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
means	O
of	O
making	O
his	O
case	O
more	O
favourable	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
obstinate	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
he	O
first	O
confessed	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
four	O
.	O
I	O
mentioned	O
the	O
bays	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
produced	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
piece	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
this	O
he	O
owned	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
these	O
four	O
pieces	O
of	O
shalloon	O
and	O
this	O
bays	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
shalloons	O
are	O
worth	O
about	O
six	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bays	O
about	O
eighteen	O
or	O
nineteen	O
shillings	O
;	O
these	O
are	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
I	O
could	O
fix	O
upon	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
piece	O
of	O
everlasting	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Haines	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
this	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cross-rib	O
,	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
mark	O
being	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
thirty	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Cowley	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Cowley	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
Cowley	O
with	O
receiving	O
these	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Cowley	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
some	O
at	O
little	O
more	O
than	O
half	O
the	O
value	O
;	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
everlasting	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Fort	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cloth-fair	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
looks	O
at	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
shalloon	O
,	O
and	O
takes	O
out	O
two	O
pieces	O
)	O
these	O
were	O
once	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
,	O
Cowley	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
received	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
bays	O
before	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
shalloon	O
of	O
a	O
customer	O
,	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deal	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
then	O
how	O
his	O
friend	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
brother	O
in	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
but	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
now	O
and	O
then	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
a-piece	O
for	O
these	O
two	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
twenty-six	O
shillings	O
a-piece	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
goods	O
now	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
I	O
bought	O
from	O
Yorkshire	O
at	O
twenty-four	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
at	O
twenty-eight	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
these	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
shalloon	O
of	O
Cowley	O
for	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
for	O
twenty-nine	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
pieces	O
for	O
two	O
pounds	O
fifteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
Pierce	O
refused	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
pieces	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
Cowley	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
some	O
much	O
dearer	O
than	O
these	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
from	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
to	O
four	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Pierce	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
bays	O
;	O
was	O
what	O
you	O
bought	O
of	O
Cowley	O
like	O
these	O
?	O
Pierce	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
as	O
near	O
the	O
quality	O
to	O
these	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
.	O
I	O
inquired	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
are	O
the	O
shalloons	O
you	O
bought	O
of	O
Cowley	O
?	O
Pierce	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
?	O
Pierce	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
certain	O
how	O
long	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
them	O
now	O
in	O
your	O
custody	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Pierce	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
produce	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Pierce	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
can	O
?	O
Pierce	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
person	O
you	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
?	O
Pierce	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
some	O
to	O
one	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
cut	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Ca	O
n't	O
you	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
any	O
particular	O
person	O
?	O
Pierce	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
whether	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
white	O
or	O
dy	O
'd	O
?	O
Pierce	O
to	O
the	O
Question	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
sold	O
in	O
the	O
white	O
cut	O
to	O
pieces	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
cutting	O
,	O
and	O
wearing	O
this	O
white	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
book	O
to	O
produce	O
to	O
shew	O
who	O
you	O
sold	O
these	O
goods	O
to	O
?	O
Pierce	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
what	O
you	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
?	O
Pierce	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
per	O
yard	O
?	O
Pierce	O
.	O
Fourteen-pence	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
this	O
man	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
give	O
his	O
evidence	O
here	O
,	O
he	O
refused	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
shew	O
me	O
black	O
and	O
white	O
I	O
will	O
come	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
before	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
.	O
Cowley	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
one	O
evening	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
shalloon	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
one	O
Haines	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
tell	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
per	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
justly	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
slight	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
be	O
worth	O
about	O
a	O
shilling	O
per	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Haines	O
twice	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
Haines	O
came	O
by	O
such	O
goods	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Haines	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
in	O
exchange	O
for	O
some	O
old	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
Cowley	O
had	O
some	O
bays	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
understood	O
that	O
the	O
bays	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
or	O
fourteen-pence	O
per	O
yard	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
Haines	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
inquire	O
into	O
the	O
thing	O
,	O
fearing	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
bad	O
affair	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
Haines	O
's	O
master	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sky	O
at	O
the	O
Green-man	O
in	O
Bucklersbury	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Haines	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
bays-factor	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Royds	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Sky	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
they	O
found	O
Cowley	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
Cowley	O
told	O
me	O
one	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bays	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
Haines	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
Haines	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
brought	O
his	O
master	O
and	O
brother	O
to	O
have	O
released	O
him	O
.	O
Haines	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
goods	O
I	O
had	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
cellar	O
amongst	O
the	O
straw	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
Cowley	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
one	O
Jennings	O
from	O
Yorkshire	O
,	O
Cowley	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
.	O
To	O
their	O
characters	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Vest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
both	O
my	O
countrymen	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stockall	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Cowley	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
and	O
honestly	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rooker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Cowley	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Cowley	O
has	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
character	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
him	O
justice	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Jarret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Cowley	O
upwards	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
he	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
bore	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Haines	O
guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Cowley	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
98	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gayler	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
one	O
brass	O
copper	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
bell-metal	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Owen	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
9	O
++	O
Elisabeth	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Owen	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
Limehouse	O
;	O
between	O
the	O
8th	O
and	O
9th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
know	O
not	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Davis	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
cast	O
last	O
sessions	O
for	O
receiving	O
other	O
stolen	O
goods	O
.	O
(	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
86	O
,	O
87	O
)	O
There	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
took	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Christopher	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
copper	O
by	O
the	O
confession	O
of	O
Davis	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Poplewell	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Christopher	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
cast	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
all	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
break	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
warehouse	O
open	O
.	O
Christopher	O
knowing	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
afterwards	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
copper	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
the	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Davis	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
amongst	O
us	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
nor	O
called	O
any	O
witness	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
99	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
Cheshire	O
cheeses	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
one	O
wooden	O
firkin	O
filled	O
with	O
butter	O
,	O
containing	O
56	O
lb	O
.	O
value	O
26	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Goswel-street	B-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
advertisement	O
of	O
such	O
goods	O
in	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
paper	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
was	O
turned	O
evidence	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
West	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
one	O
that	O
stole	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
the	O
justice	O
to	O
admit	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
witness	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
having	O
any	O
hand	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
owned	O
to	O
other	O
robberies	O
.	O
West	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
where	O
they	O
disposed	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
lodged	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
who	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
.	O
John	O
West	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
on	O
New-year's-day	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
rob	O
,	O
we	O
having	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
were	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
one	O
Cheshire	O
cheese	O
and	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Pottle	I-pers
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
another	O
Cheshire	O
cheese	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
my	O
cheese	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
for	O
twenty-eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
amongst	O
us	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knew	O
the	O
woman	O
before	O
;	O
Pottle	O
is	O
gone	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
has	O
often	O
told	O
me	O
when	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
together	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
lick	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
coming	O
from	O
Bedlam	O
;	O
and	O
turned	O
upon	O
the	O
right	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
where	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
yarn	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Tooten	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Abraham	O
,	O
Dec.	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Abraham	B-pers
Tooten	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tyburn-road	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
day	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
lost	O
twenty	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
yarn-stockings	O
,	O
value	O
twenty-five	O
shillings	O
and	O
upwards	O
,	O
but	O
know	O
nothing	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
an	O
advertisement	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
West	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
or	O
own	O
it	O
.	O
West	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
eight	O
shillings	O
and	O
two-pence	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
granted	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
and	O
I	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
John	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
I	O
,	O
William	O
Banks	O
,	O
and	O
Pottle	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Tyburn-road	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
our	O
agreement	O
was	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
walk	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
to	O
get	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
To	O
rob	O
,	O
A	O
little	O
boy	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
Banks	O
and	O
Pottle	O
proposed	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
and	O
buy	O
a	O
halfpeny-worth	O
of	O
worsted-Pottle	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Banks	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
Pottle	O
stood	O
before	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
stockings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
two	O
bundles	O
to	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
other	O
myself	O
,	O
then	O
Pott	O
)	O
came	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
Banks	O
delivered	O
one	O
bundle	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
Parker's-lane	O
for	O
eight	O
shillings	O
and	O
four-pence	O
,	O
and	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
amongst	O
us	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
at	O
the	O
Royal-oak	O
in	O
High-street	O
drinking	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Pottle	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
stay	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
aprons	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
back	O
they	O
had	O
bundles	O
in	O
their	O
aprons	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
not	O
where	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
100	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
James	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
box-iron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
iron	O
heater	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
bed-quilt	O
,	O
two	O
rugs	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
fender	O
,	O
one	O
iron	O
shovel	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
tongs	O
,	O
two	O
pillows	O
,	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
napkin	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
curtain	O
,	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Lenard	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
June	O
25	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
101	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bed-quilt	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
one	O
box-iron	O
,	O
one	O
pewter	O
bason	O
,	O
one	O
pewter	O
plate	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Churne	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Dec.	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
102	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Buckley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
bacon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawrance	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lawrance	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hand-court	O
,	O
Holborn	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
fire	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
we	O
moved	O
our	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
we	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bacon	O
about	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
,	O
worth	O
about	O
ten	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
bacon	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
groat	O
to	O
carry	O
the	O
bacon	O
to	O
the	O
Three-tuns	O
,	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
bacon	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
string	O
it	O
hung	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hole	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
cut	O
to	O
the	O
gammon	O
end	O
)	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
a	O
gentleman	O
offered	O
him	O
two-pence	O
or	O
a	O
grant	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
named	O
Field	O
,	O
in	O
Whetstone's-park	O
by	O
Lincoln	O
's	O
inn-fields	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Holborn	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Law	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
neighbours	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
fire	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
day	O
of	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Whetstone's-park	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bacon	O
at	O
his	O
back	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
brother	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
fry	O
'd	O
with	O
some	O
eggs	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
know	O
how	O
you	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
just	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Whetstone's-park	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
there	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Field	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
who	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
bacon	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
New-prison	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Shoe-lane	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
above	O
Chancery-lane	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
tumbled	O
over	O
the	O
bacon	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Field	O
's	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bacon	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
watchman	O
with	O
the	O
bacon	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
103	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Bruff	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Arlington	I-pers
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
one	O
brass	O
warming-pan	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
pot	O
and	O
cover	O
,	O
four	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
one	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
one	O
metal	O
bell	O
,	O
two	O
weights	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
clock	O
,	O
two	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
two	O
pewter	O
dishes	O
,	O
one	O
five-pint	O
pewter	O
tankard	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Arlington	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Swan-yard	O
,	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Ponder's-end	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
side	O
in	O
summer-time	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
or	O
11th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
door	O
being	O
taken	O
off	O
the	O
hinges	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
more	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
leave	O
my	O
key	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
that	O
lives	O
just	O
by	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
some	O
lead	O
,	O
and	O
committed	O
by	O
Justice	O
Tashmaker	O
,	O
he	O
impeached	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
New-prison	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
breaking	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Vass	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
his	O
words	O
?	O
Arlington	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
indeed	O
Sir	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
break	O
into	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
undid	O
the	O
lower	O
hinge	O
of	O
your	O
back-door	O
,	O
and	O
Vass	O
the	O
upper	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
without	O
my	O
naming	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
cut	O
the	O
pots	O
and	O
saucepans	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
candlesticks	O
to	O
a	O
brasier	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
got	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
again	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vass	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
the	O
Two	O
Bridges	O
near	O
Ponder's-end	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
in	O
Enfield	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
September	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Ponder's-end	O
,	O
knowing	O
nobody	O
lived	O
in	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
;	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
lower	O
hinge	O
of	O
the	O
back-door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
warming-pan	O
,	O
a	O
five-pint	O
pewter	O
tankard	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
pot	O
with	O
a	O
lid	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
with	O
a	O
lid	O
,	O
two	O
brass	O
clock-weights	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Norton-falgate	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
brasier	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
half	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
came	O
one	O
morning	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
some	O
dirt	O
into	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
garden	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
a	O
prize	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
copper	O
and	O
brass	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
?	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
coaksed	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
garden	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
hanged	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
brass	O
and	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
felony	O
,	O
acquitted	O
of	O
the	O
burglary	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Henry	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
10	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
Nov.	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
home	O
at	O
Edmonton	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
November	O
from	O
Enfield	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Houndsfields	B-place
,	O
two	O
men	O
started	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
hedge	O
and	O
pulled	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
ten	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
penyworth	O
of	O
half-pence	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
dark	O
and	O
he	O
affrighted	O
,	O
could	O
not	O
charge	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
evidence	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vass	I-pers
deposed	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
committed	O
this	O
robbery	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cantril	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linen	O
bags	O
,	O
with	O
money	O
in	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
16	O
shillings	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
losing	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
two	O
bags	O
with	O
halfpence	O
and	O
farthings	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
handle	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
spoon	O
in	O
a	O
deep	O
ditch	O
,	O
where	O
Vass	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
they	O
had	O
flung	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to.	O
)	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vass	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
broke	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
farthings	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shears	O
,	O
cut	O
out	O
a	O
piece	O
in	O
the	O
bowl	O
of	O
the	O
spoon	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
tried	O
to	O
eraze	O
the	O
name	O
from	O
the	O
handle	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
deep	O
ditch	O
full	O
of	O
water	O
and	O
mud	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
buried	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
plowed	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
it	O
as	O
they	O
wanted	O
it	O
to	O
spend	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
evidence	O
being	O
unsupported	O
by	O
any	O
witness	O
of	O
credit	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
never	O
confessing	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
104	O
,	O
105	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jaques	B-pers
De	I-pers
Blancourt	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Lashershang	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
George	O
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Martha	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan's-court	I-place
,	I-place
Fleet-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
for	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
George	B-pers
Baily	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
wanted	O
?	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
stept	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
?	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
were	O
reading	O
the	O
bill	O
upon	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
lodgings	O
to	O
let	O
.	O
Lashershang	O
asked	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
room	O
to	O
let	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
language	O
did	O
he	O
speak	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
(	O
He	O
having	O
an	O
interpreter	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
M.	O
Baily	O
.	O
In	O
English	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
can	O
we	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
shut	O
my	O
parlour-door	O
with	O
my	O
left-hand	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
near	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
both	O
followed	O
me	O
:	O
Lashershang	O
followed	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
up	O
,	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
stairs	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
called	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
hearing	O
him	O
below	O
,	O
ran	O
down	O
by	O
Lashershang	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
room-door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
gone	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
Lashershang	O
,	O
and	O
Lashershang	O
shewed	O
us	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
When	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
to	O
Lashershang	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
;	O
where	O
is	O
your	O
friend	O
?	O
he	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
neighbour	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
ran	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
looked	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
nobody	O
running	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
Lashershang	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
public-house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
that	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
talk	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
speak	O
English	O
:	O
he	O
threw	O
his	O
cloaths	O
about	O
,	O
to	O
show	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
companion	O
had	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Guild-hall	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
the	O
little	O
man	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
taken	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
taken	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
De	O
Blancourt	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
three-quarter	O
:	O
they	O
found	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
My	O
Lord-Mayor	O
talked	O
French	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
explained	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
.	O
Cross-examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
parlour-door	O
locked	O
?	O
M.	O
Baily	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Lashershang	O
speak	O
English	O
?	O
M.	O
Baily	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
Hole-in-the-wall	O
alehouse	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
not	O
you	O
command	O
the	O
prospect	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
?	O
M.	O
Baily	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
possible	O
for	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
be	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
fight	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
M.	O
Baily	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
for	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
Lashershang	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
second	O
stair	O
,	O
or	O
there-abouts	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
your	O
friend	O
?	O
he	O
has	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
stairs	O
for	O
some	O
minutes	O
before	O
?	O
M.	O
Baily	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Acton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Flower-de-luce-court	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
the	O
day	O
this	O
watch	O
was	O
lost	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Baily	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
Hole-in-the-wall	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Lashershang	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
;	O
going	O
by	O
the	O
Poultry-compter	O
,	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
on	O
foot	O
then	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
from	O
Guild-hall	O
.	O
Lashershang	O
clapt	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
's	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
French	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
little	O
man	O
pushed	O
off	O
directly	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
certainly	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
pushed	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
catched	O
him	O
near	O
the	O
Royal-Exchange	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
Lashershang	O
speak	O
English	O
at	O
the	O
Hole-in-the-wall	O
?	O
Acton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
your	O
friend	O
wants	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
me	O
go	O
.	O
They	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
heard	O
in	O
French	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Lord	O
spoke	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
French	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
both	O
spoke	O
French	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
understand	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
committed	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
twice	O
after	O
that	O
;	O
they	O
spoke	O
French	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
that	O
passed	O
there	O
but	O
what	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
Cross-examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
make	O
any	O
resistance	O
?	O
Acton	O
.	O
When	O
a	O
prisoner	O
is	O
in	O
safe	O
hands	O
,	O
he	O
may	O
very	O
well	O
go	O
easy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
pushing	O
away	O
?	O
Acton	O
.	O
When	O
a	O
man	O
runs	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
pushing	O
hard	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
.	O
Lashershang	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
my	O
companion	O
in	O
Hays	O
's	O
court	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
new	O
lodging	O
to	O
lodge	O
together	O
;	O
as	O
one	O
did	O
understand	O
the	O
language	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
make	O
shift	O
to	O
get	O
one	O
.	O
In	O
our	O
walk	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
chymist	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bill	O
put	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
lodging	O
did	O
not	O
suit	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
proceeded	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
lives	O
;	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
called	O
to	O
us	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
us	O
what	O
we	O
wanted	O
?	O
She	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
about	O
four	O
steps	O
from	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
being	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
after	O
her	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
up	O
the	O
second	O
story	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
more	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
.	O
Then	O
my	O
companion	O
called	O
me	O
down	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
my	O
companion	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
had	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
parlour	O
she	O
seized	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
She	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
last	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
go	O
that	O
way	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
remained	O
with	O
my	O
arms	O
across	O
till	O
her	O
return	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
there	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
without	O
knowing	O
what	O
she	O
wanted	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
might	O
search	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
At	O
my	O
coming	O
from	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
my	O
companion	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
?	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
looking	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
seek	O
for	O
help	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
apply	O
for	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
made	O
motion	O
to	O
let	O
the	O
people	O
know	O
that	O
was	O
my	O
companion	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nothing	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
upon	O
us	O
.	O
After	O
having	O
been	O
in	O
prison	O
seven	O
days	O
,	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
let	O
me	O
out	O
to	O
come	O
upon	O
my	O
own	O
recognizance	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
I	O
appear	O
.	O
De	O
Blancourt	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
reason	O
why	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
first	O
was	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
staid	O
without	O
;	O
being	O
got	O
into	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
several	O
ways	O
for	O
my	O
companion	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
rebuked	O
him	O
for	O
having	O
hid	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
pursued	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
master	O
!	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
they	O
wanted	O
?	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
,	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
wanted	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
examined	O
apart	O
in	O
French	O
and	O
English	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
we	O
said	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
was	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
them	O
in	O
English	O
.	O
De	O
Blancourt	O
called	O
Peter	B-pers
Cacoe	I-pers
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
Joseph	O
Nichiloe	O
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Delsonce	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Becket	I-pers
,	O
all	O
which	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
106	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Talbot	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
made	O
of	O
stuff	O
called	O
thickset	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Worth	I-pers
,	O
Novemb	O
.	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
107	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Ruggles	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
drawer	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
till	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Josiah	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
11	O
.	O
++	O
Josiah	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tallow	O
chandler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bear-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Tower-street	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
backwards	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
rusling	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
till	O
was	O
gone	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
boy	O
jump	O
off	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
!	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
saw	O
a	O
boy	O
run	O
up	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
till	O
fall	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Haystings	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
till	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Haystings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Tower-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
Bear-lane	O
,	O
and	O
dropt	O
the	O
till	O
close	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
stopt	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
stopt	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
108	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Pointer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
copper	O
nails	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
copper	O
key-bolts	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Gilbert	B-pers
Ford	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
coppersmith	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
worked	O
journeywork	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
months	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
to	O
another	O
journeyman	O
,	O
to	O
beg	O
some	O
small	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
observed	O
with	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
where	O
the	O
copper	O
nails	O
lay	O
.	O
At	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
journeyman	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
seeing	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
it	O
appearing	O
more	O
bulky	O
than	O
at	O
coming	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
out	O
eight	O
copper	O
nails	O
;	O
one	O
forged	O
nail	O
was	O
Posed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Williams	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
key-bolt	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
109	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tomson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
butter-firkin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
fifty-six	O
pounds	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Carter	B-pers
Deacon	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
Feb.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
110	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Middleman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
November	O
30	O
.	O
+	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hogg	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
November	O
about	O
eleven	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
eight	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
thirty-six-shilling	O
pieces	O
in	O
my	O
bureau	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
sat	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
locked	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
about	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
alone	O
for	O
about	O
fifteen	O
minutes	O
.	O
My	O
keys	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
bunch	O
together	O
,	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
book-case	O
lock	O
which	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
bureau	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
sitting	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
keys	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
.	O
And	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
four	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lodgers	O
above	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
suspect	O
nobody	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
having	O
left	O
nobody	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
him	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
C.	O
Hogg	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
three	O
half-crowns	O
out	O
that	O
morning	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
safe	O
then	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Hood	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Anne	B-pers
Bourne	I-pers
,	O
all	O
lodgers	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
ago	O
lodged	O
there	O
.	O
On	O
their	O
cross-examination	O
they	O
all	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
111	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
saddle	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
31	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Forster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
George-inn	O
,	O
Snow-hill	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
my	O
ostler	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
and	O
my	O
saddle	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
been	O
lying	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Lying-in-hospital	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
something	O
to	O
support	O
her	O
.	O
Justinian	B-pers
Londy	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
the	O
Monmouth	O
waggon	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
horse	O
returned	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
tied	O
to	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
waggon	O
stopped	O
to	O
tie	O
a	O
wheel	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
down-hill	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
saddle	O
off	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
four	O
lamps	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
saddle	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Smithfield-market	O
and	O
sold	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
the	O
saddle	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
necessity	O
that	O
drove	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
saddle	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
get	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
saddle	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
there	O
a	O
minute	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
only	O
by	O
the	O
saddle-cloth	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Hayter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
112	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cart	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
a	O
cart-harness	O
for	O
two	O
horses	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
black	O
geldings	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
chattels	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carman	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
fourteen	O
or	O
fifteen	O
days	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Drury-lane	O
with	O
my	O
cart	O
and	O
two	O
horses	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
tallow	O
to	O
St.	O
Giles's-pound	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
till	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
advertised	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
's	O
at	O
Windmill-hill	O
near	O
Bunhill-fields	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
home	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
the	O
jobb	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
Gilbert	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
cart	O
marked	O
?	O
Pickering	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
name	O
was	O
upon	O
three	O
places	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
number	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
?	O
Pickering	O
.	O
He	O
knew	O
me	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
cart	O
and	O
horses	O
at	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
's	O
,	O
the	O
cart	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
horses	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
rogue	O
,	O
but	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
was	O
a	O
bigger	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
know	O
the	O
horses	O
and	O
cart	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Pickering	O
's	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Biggs	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Pickering	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
go	O
to	O
Drury-lane	O
and	O
fetch	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
tallow	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
through	O
Bow-yard	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Pickering	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
wrong	O
way	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
right	O
way	O
to	O
where	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Ludgate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
go	O
to	O
sell	O
Mr.	O
Pickering	O
's	O
cart	O
and	O
horses	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
rogue	O
,	O
but	O
Gilbert	O
is	O
a	O
bigger	O
,	O
for	O
once	O
before	O
I	O
sold	O
him	O
a	O
cart	O
and	O
two	O
horses	O
for	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sold	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
for	O
six	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
with	O
the	O
cart	O
and	O
other	O
horse	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
then	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
these	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
guineas	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
more	O
;	O
Watson	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Watson	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
any	O
thing	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
said	O
before	O
;	O
Biggs	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
of	O
Gilbert	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
two	O
guineas	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
part	O
for	O
the	O
cart	O
and	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
the	O
jobb	O
was	O
not	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
arrested	O
and	O
carried	O
away	O
to	O
Ludgate	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
guineas	O
of	O
Godfrey	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
's	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
the	O
cart	O
and	O
harness	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
113	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Sims	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Star	O
,	O
Leaden-hall-street	O
;	O
my	O
brother	O
is	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
under	O
a	O
pretence	O
of	O
buying	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
some	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
more	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
more	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
some	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
tur	O
ned	O
about	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dropped	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
shew	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
check	O
for	O
an	O
apron	O
for	O
his	O
mother	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
down	O
some	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
amongst	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
piece	O
,	O
containing	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
waistcoat-flap	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
check	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
them	O
.	O
Upon	O
lifting	O
up	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
brother	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
114	O
,	O
115	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Humphrys	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Wilbourn	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
gallons	O
of	O
white-wine	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Newel	I-pers
and	O
Bridget	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Newel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Jerusalem-tavern	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Bridget	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
is	O
my	O
partner	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
day	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harlow	O
's	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Humphrys	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
tap-house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
and	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
accomplice	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
John	B-pers
Wilbourn	I-pers
and	O
Francis	B-pers
Pattern	I-pers
,	O
the	O
last	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
wine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
confess	O
it	O
?	O
Newel	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
wine	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
wine	O
might	O
you	O
miss	O
?	O
Newel	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Harlow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualer	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Clerkenwell-green	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
called	O
up	O
by	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
two	O
men	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Newel	O
's	O
vaults	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Humphrys	O
with	O
a	O
cask	O
full	O
of	O
something	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
vault	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
justice	O
Withers	O
,	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
cask	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
cask	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
white-wine	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wine	O
in	O
that	O
cellar	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
belongs	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Horton	O
and	O
me	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
West	I-pers
Apletree	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Newel	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
these	O
wine-vaults	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
about	O
twenty	O
gallons	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
half	O
hogshead	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
twelfth	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
in	O
that	O
vault	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
cellar	O
and	O
examined	O
the	O
vessels	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
tight	O
and	O
full	O
,	O
all	O
was	O
right	O
then	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
five	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
outward	O
door	O
pushed	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
blood	O
on	O
the	O
lock	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
broke	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
inward	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
casks	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
twenty	O
gallons	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
half-hogshead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
that	O
been	O
tapped	O
?	O
Apletree	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
wine	O
taken	O
out	O
?	O
Apletree	O
.	O
The	O
bung	O
had	O
been	O
knocked	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wine	O
craned	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Apletree	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bung	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
tight	O
in	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
the	O
vessel	O
was	O
full	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
?	O
Apletree	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
known	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
?	O
Apletree	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
Humphrys	O
before	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
repairing	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
cask	O
?	O
Apletree	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
they	O
brought	O
it	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
going	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Harlow	O
's	O
to	O
call	O
the	O
hour	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
;	O
they	O
crossed	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Newel	O
's	O
vault	O
.	O
Humphrys	O
was	O
first	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
cask	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
lesser	O
cask	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pewter	O
cratie	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
stand	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
what	O
business	O
they	O
had	O
there	O
?	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
coming	O
again	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
behind	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
understand	O
by	O
that	O
answer	O
?	O
Isaac	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
meant	O
more	O
wine	O
or	O
more	O
men	O
behind	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
vault-door	O
and	O
halloold	O
;	O
but	O
none	O
answered	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
directly	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Harlow	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
down	O
Mutton-lane	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
overtook	O
Humphry	O
about	O
Ward's-rents	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
biggest	O
cask	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
thi	O
bottle	O
of	O
wine	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
fain	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
us	O
take	O
the	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Harlow	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
compound	O
felony	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Newel	O
.	O
Milbourn	O
was	O
taken	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
six	O
and	O
ten	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
bottle	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
marked	O
as	O
I	O
mark	O
all	O
my	O
full	O
quarts	O
with	O
a	O
long	O
J	O
upon	O
the	O
neck	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
casks	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
Mountain	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
both	O
filled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
hogshead	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Isaac	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
when	O
Wilbourn	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
a	O
dozen	O
I	O
pitched	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
crane	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
then	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
threatened	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
crane	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Humphrys	O
ordered	O
her	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Newel	O
asked	O
him	O
whose	O
crane	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Humphrys	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
he	O
also	O
owned	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
carried	O
to	O
Wilbourn	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
into	O
Sharp's-alley	O
.	O
Humphrys	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Wilbourn	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Frank	B-pers
Pattern	I-pers
called	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
earn	O
a	O
trifle	O
?	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Humphrys	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
draw	O
off	O
some	O
wine	O
for	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
directly	O
.	O
To	O
Humphrys	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Humphrys	O
above	O
twenty	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
to	O
a	O
cooper	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
settled	O
in	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
work	O
for	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
honestly	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
his	O
trade	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
lately	O
worked	O
journey-work	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
fifteen	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Brian	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
upwards	O
of	O
fifteen	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
that	O
his	O
character	O
was	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
's	O
in	O
England	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
of	O
reason	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
married	O
a	O
clever	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
value	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Basset	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
him	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
116	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Dorothy	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Walter	I-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gown	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
stuff	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
calimanco	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Shootes	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Farr	I-pers
,	O
February	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Shootes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
journey-woman	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
a	O
mantua-maker	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
alone	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
and	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
hung	O
the	O
key	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
then	O
at	O
dinner	O
in	O
another	O
room	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
about	O
three	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
came	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
gown	O
tried	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
rang	O
the	O
bell	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
above	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Shootes	O
.	O
We	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Westminster	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
gowns	O
and	O
black	O
calimanco	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
how	O
much	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
drawers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
?	O
Shootes	O
.	O
She	O
passes	O
for	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shootes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
alone	O
not	O
quite	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
stay	O
long	O
at	O
dinner	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
missed	O
the	O
two	O
gowns	O
and	O
piece	O
of	O
calimanco	O
about	O
three	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
things	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
as	O
her	O
's	O
and	O
Farr's-property	O
)	O
.	O
Milbrow	O
Jones	O
,	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
confirmed	O
her	O
account	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
finish	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Merridy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
gowns	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
must	O
part	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
chose	O
rather	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
out	O
and	O
out	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
three	O
guineas	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Shootes	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
with	O
two	O
women	O
;	O
they	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
;	O
we	O
shewed	O
them	O
these	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
fetched	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
claimed	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
again	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
hurry	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
work	O
done	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
home	O
to	O
finish	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
a	O
dram	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
head	O
was	O
very	O
light	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
drank	O
two	O
more	O
drams	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
doing	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sensible	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
made	O
money	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
agreed	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
it	O
a	O
debt	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
things	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
payment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Tinsley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
master	O
horner	O
in	O
Petticoat-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Baptist-head	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Baily	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
things	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
this	O
extremity	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
a	O
debt	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
agreed	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
delivered	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
a	O
capuchin	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
valued	O
the	O
stays	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
at	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Fisher	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
fully	O
satisfied	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
by	O
the	O
advice	O
of	O
some	O
other	O
person	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
.	O
A	O
paper	O
produced	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
.	O
This	O
note	O
I	O
gave	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
remainder	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
note	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
Feb.	O
20	O
,	O
1755	O
.	O
We	O
jointly	O
and	O
separately	O
promise	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Merridy	I-pers
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
two	O
pounds	O
,	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
delivery	O
of	O
a	O
striped	O
lutestring	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
figured	O
alapine-gown	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
yards	O
of	O
calimanco	O
,	O
without	O
further	O
trouble	O
.	O
Witness	O
our	O
hands	O
,	O
Geo	B-pers
Shootes	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Sherif	I-pers
.	O
I	O
being	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Merridy	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
this	O
affair	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
also	O
Mrs.	O
Fisher	O
promise	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Besson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Tinsley	I-pers
;	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
frequently	O
trusted	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
again	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
seven	O
months	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
hope	O
this	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
punishment	O
to	O
her	O
for	O
this	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
borrowed	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tinsley	I-pers
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
Tinsley	O
's	O
brother	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
her	O
Uncle	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
paid	O
again	O
,	O
at	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
stays	O
and	O
piece	O
of	O
stuff	O
were	O
left	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
security	O
for	O
that	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
and	O
sold	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
the	O
day	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
deposed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
The	O
note	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
Dec.	O
31	O
,	O
1754	O
.	O
We	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tinsley	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
one	O
pound	O
,	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
six-pence	O
,	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
,	O
By	O
us	O
,	O
Mary	O
Shootes	O
,	O
Dorothy	O
Taylor	O
.	O
To	O
be	O
paid	O
at	O
two	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
per	O
week	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
117	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk-gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
lawn	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
fustian	O
frock	O
,	O
two	O
quilted	O
petticoats	O
,	O
two	O
damask	O
napkins	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
one	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
two	O
petticoats	O
,	O
one	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
three	O
napkins	O
,	O
two	O
check	O
'd	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
pillowbear	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Anne	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hounsditch	B-place
,	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Stephen	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
;	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
23d	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
my	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
surprise	O
,	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
my	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
mentioning	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
gown	O
and	O
quilted	O
coat	O
;	O
she	O
begged	O
forgiveness	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
pawn	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
get	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
lie	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
'd	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
back	O
again	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
;	O
I	O
finding	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
at	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
in	O
Barbican	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
pawned	O
by	O
Mary	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	O
to	O
one	O
Dickenson	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
about	O
nine	O
or	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
her	O
servant	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Barbican	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
robbed	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
where	O
she	O
used	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Armsted	O
's	O
in	O
Redcross-street	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
five	O
napkins	O
,	O
a	O
neckcloth	O
and	O
a	O
pillowbear	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
was	O
set	O
out	O
for	O
Shrewsbury	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
book-keeper	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
him	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
name	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
house	O
and	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Upper-holloway	O
overtook	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
Mrs.	O
Coleman	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
Mrs.	O
Coleman	O
of	O
two	O
petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
the	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
quilted	O
petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
fustian	O
frock	O
and	O
a	O
white	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dickenson	O
in	O
Hounsditch	O
.	O
(	O
She	O
looks	O
them	O
out	O
from	O
all	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thorp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Black-dog	O
at	O
Highgate	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Holloway	O
,	O
there	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
justice	O
Cross	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
from	O
her	O
mistress	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
lawn	O
gown	O
,	O
some	O
petticoats	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
whom	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
them	O
,	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
their	O
names	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
was	O
not	O
with	O
me	O
there	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
packed	O
up	O
my	O
things	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
shew	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bid	O
a	O
shop-girl	O
who	O
lives	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
only	O
to	O
Barnet	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
118	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Philip	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
thirteen	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
one	O
woman	O
's	O
gown	O
,	O
eight	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
garden-seeds	O
,	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pounds	O
of	O
snuff	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Welling	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
Williams	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
as	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
119	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Insel	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shuttleworth	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shuttleworth	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
own	O
door	O
opposite	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
press-gang	O
hawling	O
a	O
man	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
two	O
minutes	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
next	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
betwixt	O
her	O
arm	O
and	O
her	O
gown	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
not	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
up	O
at	O
a	O
door	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
120	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Maddin	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
laced	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Lowther	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Purple-lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
from	O
that	O
service	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Green-dragon	O
,	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
;	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
,	O
searched	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
the	O
sheet	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Purple-lane	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Semour	I-pers
.	O
About	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
Mr.	O
Lowther	O
's	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
inquired	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
's	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
Mr.	O
Lowther	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
his	O
cousin	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
once	O
asked	O
his	O
wife	O
for	O
an	O
old	O
gown	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
made	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
gown	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
sheet	O
also	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
some	O
aprons	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
my	O
wife	O
never	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
made	O
up	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
121	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Malbourn	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Catherine	B-pers
Malbourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
Martha	B-pers
Scofield	I-pers
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
gown	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Scofield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
gown	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
last	O
Thursday	O
was	O
week	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
well	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
secured	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
hanging	O
upon	O
a	O
line	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
.	O
Another	O
woman	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
confessing	O
she	O
took	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
gown	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
this	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
my	O
confession	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
likely	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
said	O
,	O
be	O
it	O
what	O
they	O
pleased	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
122	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Gilman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Rogerson	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
shop	O
,	O
Feb.	O
17	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
coat	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Norman	O
,	O
her	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
123	O
,	O
124	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Marchant	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
out	O
thence	O
three	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
fustian	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
fustian	O
frock	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
my	O
maid	O
going	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
child	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
betwixt	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
heard	O
a	O
rumbling	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
higher	O
and	O
saw	O
somebody	O
under	O
a	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
where	O
my	O
men	O
laid	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
man	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nobody	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
looking	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
trap-door	O
that	O
goes	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
cloaths	O
upon	O
the	O
mens	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
houses	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
trap-door	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
some	O
distance	O
about	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
houses	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
somebody	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
:	O
the	O
houses	O
join	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
over	O
the	O
houses	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
got	O
within	O
one	O
house	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
heard	O
murder	O
cried	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
seemed	O
to	O
come	O
from	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
dry	O
cloaths	O
upon	O
some	O
leads	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
over	O
the	O
other	O
house	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
women	O
in	O
their	O
shifts	O
on	O
the	O
leads	O
,	O
screaming	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
thieves	O
broke	O
into	O
their	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
stand	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
jumped	O
down	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
them	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
search	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
had	O
robbed	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
doors	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
apprehended	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
thro	O
'	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
morrow	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
an	O
evidence	O
here	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
three	O
houses	O
from	O
that	O
house	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
to	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
garret	O
or	O
cock-loft	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
round-house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
as	O
to	O
break	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
rob	O
me	O
?	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
,	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
I	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
betwixt	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
broke	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
entered	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
Marchant	O
drew	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
stab	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
met	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
three	O
sheets	O
in	O
the	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garrets	O
,	O
there	O
they	O
thought	O
to	O
begin	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
,	O
and	O
strip	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
bottom	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
lie-in	O
in	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
for	O
strangling	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
they	O
to	O
know	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
there	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
They	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
labour	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
women	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
evidence	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
good	O
mistress	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
going	O
up	O
disturbed	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
trap-door	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
sheets	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
one	O
way	O
and	O
he	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lay	O
betwixt	O
some	O
chimnies	O
all	O
night	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
before	O
justice	O
Bedwell	O
.	O
Myers	O
owned	O
there	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
Drury-lane	O
he	O
tried	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
some	O
houses	O
,	O
but	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
Marchant	O
said	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
Evans	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
also	O
said	O
they	O
took	O
nothing	O
away	O
,	O
upon	O
their	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
three	O
sheets	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sixteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
their	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Preston	O
in	O
Brown's-gardens	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
is	O
a	O
dust-man	O
,	O
and	O
hires	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
about	O
to	O
take	O
other	O
peoples	O
properties	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
head	O
at	O
the	O
Seven-dials	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
hot	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
sitting	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
thieving	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
by	O
yourselves	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
by	O
ourselves	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
privately	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
other	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
rob	O
the	O
first	O
house	O
we	O
could	O
,	O
by	O
breaking	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
no	O
house	O
convenient	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
there	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
there	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Myers	O
lifted	O
up	O
the	O
latch	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
fast	O
,	O
it	O
has	O
a	O
spring-lock	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
put	O
their	O
backs	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
flew	O
open	O
.	O
We	O
heard	O
a	O
rumbling	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
then	O
Myers	O
drew	O
his	O
knife	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
that	O
offered	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
resistance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
Myers	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
