TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Twenty-ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1756	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
SLINGSBY	O
BETHELL	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
ROBINSON	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Lion	O
,	O
in	O
Ludgate-Street	O
,	O
1756	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SLINGSBY	O
BETHELL	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
PARKER	O
,	O
*	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
BIRCH	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILMOT	O
,	O
||	O
Sir	O
,	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
++	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
Martin	B-pers
Capel	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Strahan	I-pers
John	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
David	B-pers
Mowden	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Barrif	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gar	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Bradgate	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Heritage	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Slaid	I-pers
William	B-pers
Collings	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Doyley	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
John	B-pers
Girdler	I-pers
John	B-pers
Carpenter	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
Griffith	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
William	B-pers
Staples	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Firts	I-pers
John	B-pers
Skirman	I-pers
60	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Millner	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
11	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
61.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Dec	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
some	O
goods	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
's	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	B-place
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
near	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
missing	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
missed	O
mine	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
behind	O
me	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
turn	O
'd	O
himself	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
in	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Axe	O
.	O
(	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
do	O
so	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
last	O
?	O
Abraham	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
's	O
apprentice	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
walking	O
down	O
Leadenhall-street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
taking	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
threw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
pick	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
62	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Dodd	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Sise	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Hayman	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Woodard	I-pers
,	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Sise	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
and	O
secretly	O
,	O
Dec.	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
James	O
Sise	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hayman	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
comeing	O
through	O
St.	B-place
James's-park	I-place
,	O
when	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hayman	I-pers
gave	O
her	O
money	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Sise	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
1	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
1	O
l.	O
19	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
it	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
Sise	O
.	O
It	O
belonged	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Hayman	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Woodard	I-pers
,	O
and	O
myself	O
,	O
we	O
being	O
fellow	O
servants	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Christmas	O
box	O
money	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
4	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
told	O
it	O
over	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
2	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
?	O
Sise	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
park	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
forth	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
the	O
centinel	O
,	O
as	O
though	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
money	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
spoke	O
with	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
at	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
something	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
how	O
much	O
.	O
Joyce	B-pers
Carrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
watch-house	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
her	O
being	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
money	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
produced	O
some	O
more	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
bosom	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
1	O
pound	O
8	O
shillings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
St.	O
James's-park	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
this	O
man	O
and	O
another	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
:	O
I	O
answered	O
,	O
Home	O
.	O
They	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
take	O
them	O
some	O
where	O
else	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
some	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
grass	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
lie	O
down	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
more	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
lay	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
He	O
came	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
pulled	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
down	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
his	O
6	O
d.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
63.	O
William	B-pers
Myers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
30	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
64	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
1	O
pint	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
3	O
and	O
6	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
draw	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
that	O
were	O
missing	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
found	O
it	O
since	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
Christmas	O
evening	O
,	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
mug	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
lend	O
her	O
15	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
how	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
A	O
great	O
while	O
.	O
Who	O
bought	O
it	O
?	O
My	O
husband	O
.	O
What	O
might	O
he	O
give	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
old	O
silver	O
in	O
exchange	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
price	O
it	O
cost	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
but	O
15	O
s.	O
to	O
make	O
up	O
some	O
rent	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
fetch	O
it	O
again	O
next	O
week	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
,	O
say	O
'd	O
she	O
,	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
brought	O
a	O
tea-spoon	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
I	O
read	O
in	O
the	O
Advertiser	O
,	O
``	O
A	O
silver	O
pint	O
``	O
mug	O
,	O
marked	O
E.	O
M.	O
M.	O
stole	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Two	O
``	O
Chairmen	O
,	O
in	O
Warder-street	O
,	O
Soho	O
.	O
''	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
daughter	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
desire	O
Samuel	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
to	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
advertised	O
a	O
mug	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
remarkable	O
?	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
this	O
because	O
the	O
mug	O
had	O
a	O
wooden	O
bottom	O
,	O
not	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
advertisement	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
E.	O
M.	O
M.	O
on	O
the	O
handle	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
bruised	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
there	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
:	O
A	O
wooden	O
bottom	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
your	O
mug	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
whom	O
he	O
suspected	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
nam	O
'd	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Davis	O
(	O
a	O
name	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
by	O
)	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
another	O
tea-spoon	O
when	O
she	O
brought	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
neither	O
knew	O
me	O
nor	O
the	O
mug	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
altered	O
her	O
dress	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
swear	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
mug	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
this	O
evidence	O
mention	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
related	O
here	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Ursula	B-pers
Hornise	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
12	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
3	O
years	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
above	O
twenty	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
or	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
all	O
over	O
my	O
house	O
divers	O
times	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
husband	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
above	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
65	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
widow	O
,	O
Dec.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Sarah	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
money	O
several	O
times	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawer	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
S.	O
Pool	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
an	O
oil	O
and	O
colour	O
shop	O
.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
porter	O
.	O
I	O
consulted	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
my	O
next	O
witness	O
,	O
about	O
finding	O
the	O
thief	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Give	O
me	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
mark	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
shall	O
see	O
me	O
lock	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
done	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Dec	O
,	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
10	O
d	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
mark	O
?	O
S.	O
Pool	O
.	O
Four	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
farthings	O
.	O
The	O
drawer	O
was	O
always	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
access	O
to	O
the	O
drawer	O
?	O
S.	O
Pool	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
but	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
I	O
concluded	O
,	O
to	O
trust	O
him	O
another	O
day	O
so	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
we	O
put	O
in	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
mark	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kendal	O
to	O
count	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
1	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
missed	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kendal	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
all	O
my	O
servants	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
robbing	O
his	O
mistress	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kendal	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
swear	O
this	O
I	O
marked	O
.	O
In	O
all	O
they	O
found	O
21	O
halfpence	O
,	O
all	O
marked	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
said	O
,	O
Young	O
man	O
how	O
much	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
have	O
rob	O
'd	O
your	O
mistress	O
of	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
in	O
half	O
pence	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
rob	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
says	O
her	O
drawer	O
is	O
always	O
lock	O
'd	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
I	O
will	O
show	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
then	O
put	O
the	O
bolt	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
draw	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
before	O
found	O
the	O
drawer	O
up	O
by	O
so	O
doing	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
and	O
shewed	O
us	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
table	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
lifted	O
the	O
counter	O
up	O
.	O
Cross	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
Justice	O
was	O
you	O
before	O
?	O
S.	O
Pool	O
.	O
Before	O
justice	O
Trent	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
wages	O
did	O
you	O
owe	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
S.	O
Pool	O
.	O
A	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
's	O
wages	O
were	O
in	O
day	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
and	O
odd	O
shillings	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
him	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
him	O
his	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
occasion	O
had	O
he	O
to	O
rob	O
his	O
mistress	O
of	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
owed	O
him	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
?	O
S.	O
Pool	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
rob	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
S.	O
Pool	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
to	O
receive	O
money	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
S.	O
Pool	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
bill	O
he	O
has	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
give	O
change	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
in	O
a	O
morning	O
?	O
S.	O
Pool	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
swear	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
S.	O
Pool	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
was	O
trusted	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
confined	O
that	O
to	O
my	O
daughter	O
;	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
that	O
drawer	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
I.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Kendal	O
?	O
S.	O
Pool	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
S.	O
Pool	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
master	O
painter	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
as	O
brothers	O
.	O
John	O
Kendal	O
.	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pool	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
suspected	O
her	O
servant	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
in	O
money	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
suspect	O
him	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
by	O
his	O
dress	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
spent	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
no	O
wages	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
will	O
be	O
to	O
mark	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
marked	O
some	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
key	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
counted	O
them	O
over	O
.	O
We	O
missed	O
nine	O
pence	O
and	O
two	O
farthings	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
some	O
errand	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
night	O
I	O
marked	O
six	O
shillings	O
worth	O
of	O
half	O
pence	O
and	O
farthings	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
missed	O
fourteen	O
pence	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Laybourne	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
him	O
backwards	O
,	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
pull	O
out	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
from	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
amongst	O
which	O
were	O
twenty-one	O
halfpence	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
marked	O
the	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
Then	O
Mrs	O
.	O
Pool	O
said	O
,	O
Joseph	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
rob	O
me	O
who	O
have	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
mistress	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Then	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
cry	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
said	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
confess	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
wonder	O
'd	O
he	O
never	O
took	O
silver	O
or	O
gold	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
shew	O
us	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
the	O
till	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
by	O
lifting	O
the	O
counter	O
up	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
hands	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
bolt	O
clear	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
drew	O
out	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
how	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
halfpence	O
promiscuously	O
as	O
they	O
lay	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
halfpence	O
being	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
?	O
Kendal	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
There	O
could	O
be	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
the	O
money	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
coat	O
pocket	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
?	O
Kendal	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
his	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
then	O
above	O
stairs	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Laybourne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
served	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
with	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
wanted	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Kendal	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
his	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
backwards	O
to	O
search	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
some	O
halfpence	O
from	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
mark	O
'd	O
(	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
halfpence	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
halfpence	O
which	O
were	O
marked	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
amongst	O
those	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
there	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
his	O
mistress	O
of	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Douglas	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
Mr.	O
Kendal	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
evidence	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
two	O
warrants	O
,	O
one	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
for	O
robbing	O
her	O
till	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Kendal	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
your	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
strong	O
suspicion	O
of	O
his	O
robbing	O
his	O
mistress	O
's	O
till	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
God	O
forbid	O
he	O
should	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
confess	O
anything	O
?	O
Douglas	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
lift	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
draw	O
'd	O
the	O
nails	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
the	O
till	O
could	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
ease	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
just	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
left	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
much	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
rob	O
his	O
mistress	O
of	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
ask	O
her	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
return	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
her	O
of	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
s.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
mistress	O
owed	O
him	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
that	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
.	O
These	O
halfpence	O
here	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
These	O
halfpence	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
of	O
mine	O
(	O
put	O
in	O
by	O
somebody	O
)	O
that	O
had	O
hung	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
take	O
them	O
out	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
another	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
that	O
on	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
deal	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
for	O
goods	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
them	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
civility	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Bready	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
goods	O
from	O
his	O
mistress	O
's	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
civil	O
and	O
honest	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mosley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
often	O
brought	O
things	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
from	O
his	O
mistress	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Preston	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Cordoroy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
fellow-servant	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
66	O
,	O
67	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lamprey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
James	I-pers
Childerey	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
cloth	O
made	O
of	O
linen	O
and	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Law	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Law	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Whitechapel	B-place
,	O
am	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
abroad	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cheque	O
)	O
Here	O
is	O
my	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
information	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
of	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cheque	O
being	O
taken	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
following	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
piece	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lamprey	I-pers
acknowledg	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Law	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Law	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
his	O
apprentice	O
.	O
This	O
piece	O
of	O
cheque	O
produced	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
Law	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
together	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
shirt	O
;	O
they	O
bought	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
both	O
concerned	O
in	O
buying	O
it	O
?	O
Law	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
Sarah	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
2	O
such	O
women	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
.	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
Have	O
they	O
bought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cheque	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
one	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
drop	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
dirt	O
,	O
the	O
end	O
having	O
got	O
loose	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
could	O
shew	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cheque	O
:	O
They	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mary	B-pers
Childerey	I-pers
said	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
fetch	O
the	O
cheque	O
;	O
do	O
n't	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
noise	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Lamprey	O
pretended	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
Lamprey	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
from	O
our	O
shop	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
where	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lamprey	I-pers
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
my	O
barrow	O
I	O
saw	O
Lamprey	O
drop	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cheque	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
catch	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
seeming	O
to	O
be	O
affrighted	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
bought	O
some	O
cheque	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
a	O
child	O
where	O
the	O
women	O
lived	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
own	O
they	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
S.	O
Warner	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lamprey	I-pers
owned	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
also	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
Lamprey	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
;	O
this	O
other	O
woman	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
Mary	B-pers
Childerey	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mary	B-pers
Childerey	I-pers
7	O
or	O
8	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
constantly	O
imployed	O
her	O
twice	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Childerey	I-pers
has	O
work	O
'd	O
often	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Lamprey	O
guilty	O
,	O
Childerey	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
68	O
,	O
69	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Gold	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Shervil	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Tom	I-pers
Thumb	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Halsey	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
her	O
shop	O
,	O
Nov.	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Poynting	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Halsey	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
one	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Poynting	O
.	O
In	O
Gracechurch-street	B-place
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Poynting	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
the	O
evidence	O
Holmes	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
him	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Rickards	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Plump	O
,	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
neither	O
have	O
I	O
seen	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
justice	O
Rickards	O
,	O
who	O
committed	O
them	O
to	O
Newgate	O
,	O
and	O
Holmes	O
to	O
Clerkenwell	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoners	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Poynting	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
were	O
lost	O
?	O
Poynting	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
from	O
the	O
outside	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thumb	I-pers
and	O
William	O
Gold	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
Angel-alley	O
,	O
Whitechapel	O
;	O
Shervil	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
where	O
you	O
may	O
get	O
a	O
crown	O
presently	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
Gracechurch-street	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
paper	O
before	O
Mrs.	O
Halsey	O
's	O
window	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
the	O
wind	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
glass	O
being	O
broke	O
.	O
Shervil	O
ran	O
his	O
hand	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
whistle	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
many	O
handkerchiefs	O
are	O
there	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
About	O
seven	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
into	O
Plump	O
's	O
shop	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
in	O
:	O
so	O
I	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
Shervil	O
told	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
kept	O
the	O
other	O
eleven	O
themselves	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
nights	O
after	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Tower-Hill	O
with	O
one	O
Barnes	O
,	O
he	O
snatched	O
a	O
sixpenny	O
pye	O
;	O
the	O
pastry-cook	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
in	O
a	O
gang	O
of	O
thieves	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
justice	O
Rickards	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
Plump	O
live	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
,	O
facing	O
Well-close	O
square	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sold	O
many	O
handkerchiefs	O
and	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
and	O
others	O
have	O
stolen	O
,	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
tell	O
you	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Halsey	O
's	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
observed	O
the	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
being	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
.	O
Gold	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
fast	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
glass-house	O
.	O
Shervil	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
70	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Campion	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Judith	B-pers
M'Carty	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Jan.	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Stephen	B-pers
Pett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
beadle	O
of	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
,	O
Wapping	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
through	O
East-Smithfield	B-place
,	O
where	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
murder	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
dray	O
standing	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
where	O
the	O
drayman	O
was	O
(	O
I	O
understood	O
she	O
was	O
kill	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
dray	O
)	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
he	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Pell	O
,	O
who	O
boucd	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
coming	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
workhouse	O
.	O
[	O
she	O
belongs	O
there	O
]	O
as	O
the	O
dray	O
was	O
turning	O
at	O
a	O
corner	O
;	O
the	O
drayman	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
turn	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
foot	O
before	O
the	O
fore-horse	O
.	O
She	O
kept	O
forward	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stop	O
his	O
horses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
she	O
have	O
avoided	O
the	O
dray	O
in	O
the	O
condition	O
she	O
was	O
?	O
Wells	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Pett	O
.	O
Could	O
she	O
hear	O
well	O
?	O
Pett	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
her	O
hearing	O
well	O
.	O
Wells	O
.	O
The	O
dray	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
hill	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cattle	O
were	O
strong	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
horses	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
to	O
stop	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
the	O
horse	O
he	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
;	O
the	O
place	O
being	O
so	O
very	O
narrow	O
,	O
people	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
a	O
dray	O
as	O
it	O
comes	O
down	O
without	O
running	O
a	O
hazard	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
dray-man	O
;	O
he	O
clap	O
'd	O
his	O
hands	O
on	O
her	O
shoulder	O
to	O
get	O
her	O
clear	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
the	O
dray	O
took	O
her	O
against	O
her	O
stomach	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
the	O
horses	O
had	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
dray	O
stop	O
'd	O
against	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
back	O
drove	O
in	O
a	O
plank	O
of	O
the	O
boards	O
she	O
was	O
drove	O
up	O
against	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
dray	O
was	O
drawn	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
drop	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
carried	O
away	O
for	O
dead	O
.	O
Pett	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Littleby	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
came	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
driving	O
his	O
horses	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shove	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
woman	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
But	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
forward	O
,	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
did	O
he	O
shove	O
her	O
?	O
A.	O
Littleby	O
.	O
To	O
go	O
from	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
halter	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
wo	O
!	O
but	O
the	O
horses	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
hill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
stop	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
jamb	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
tin	O
pot	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
dray	O
was	O
drawn	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
with	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
she	O
never	O
stir	O
'd	O
afterwards	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
dray	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
breast	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
turn	O
down	O
the	O
gateway	O
;	O
the	O
horses	O
turn	O
'd	O
in	O
very	O
short	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
very	O
narrow	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
hollow	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
shove	O
her	O
to	O
clear	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
there	O
is	O
room	O
for	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
pass	O
a	O
dray	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
does	O
that	O
dray	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
To	O
Duffill	O
and	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
they	O
furnish	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
or	O
does	O
the	O
dray	O
man	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
They	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
dray	O
take	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
jamb	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
We	O
drew	O
the	O
dray	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
down	O
dead	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
some	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
temper	O
'd	O
,	O
careful	O
,	O
steady	O
,	O
sober	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
71	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Rees	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Ascue	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
19	O
++	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Ascue	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
4	O
days	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
early	O
one	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
cut	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
put	O
money	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
mother	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
prevented	O
his	O
taking	O
any	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
hat	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Whitacker	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
at	O
Westminster	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
72	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Jolley	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Jolley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
was	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
his	O
forehead	O
full	O
of	O
blood	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
easy	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
hurt	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
Dec.	O
7	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
complained	O
his	O
head	O
was	O
very	O
bad	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
to	O
drink	O
much	O
?	O
S.	O
Jolley	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
should	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
regular	O
man	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
I	O
found	O
his	O
head	O
was	O
sadly	O
swell	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
cut	O
over	O
his	O
eye	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
eyes	O
were	O
black	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
his	O
death	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Mathews	O
at	O
the	O
alehouse	O
;	O
tha	O
t	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
struck	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
said	O
,	O
She	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
seen	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
His	O
head	O
swell	O
'd	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
at	O
all	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mathews	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
Mrs.	O
Mathews	O
was	O
sitting	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
side	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
here	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
have	O
used	O
him	O
very	O
ill	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
is	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
dies	O
he	O
will	O
lay	O
his	O
death	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
She	O
fainted	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
herself	O
,	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
any	O
advice	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
her	O
surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
surgeon	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Hewit	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
him	O
to	O
Hyde-park	O
infirmary	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Mathews	O
paid	O
2	O
chairmen	O
for	O
carrying	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
died	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Crambourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
opposite	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Mathews	O
push	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
such	O
a	O
push	O
that	O
would	O
have	O
thrown	O
a	O
sober	O
man	O
down	O
?	O
Crambourn	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
steps	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
before	O
he	O
fell	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
with	O
his	O
head	O
near	O
the	O
channel	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
face	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
:	O
when	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
his	O
face	O
was	O
all	O
over	O
dirt	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Kren	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Hop-Yard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Jolley	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
way	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
push	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
would	O
have	O
attended	O
that	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
she	O
wash	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
fainted	O
away	O
:	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
herself	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
died	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
desire	O
but	O
to	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
should	O
never	O
enjoy	O
a	O
happy	O
hour	O
.	O
She	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
surgeon	O
Hewit	O
to	O
attend	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
note	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
deceased	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mathews	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ordered	O
a	O
chair	O
for	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Onyon	I-pers
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
this	O
accident	O
happened	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
hit	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
hit	O
him	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
with	O
the	O
pot	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
work	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
:	O
he	O
then	O
could	O
not	O
hold	O
up	O
his	O
head	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
quite	O
innocent	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Mathews	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
then	O
dying	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
Mr.	O
Jolley	O
do	O
n't	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
dying	O
.	O
Jolley	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Whenever	O
the	O
constable	O
dies	O
his	O
soul	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
hell	O
.	O
My	O
Master	O
was	O
constable	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
bear	O
those	O
words	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
are	O
a	O
Welch	O
woman	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
worth	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
said	O
,	O
Pray	O
go	O
out	O
:	O
He	O
refused	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
my	O
mistress	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
shoved	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
fall	O
down	O
;	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
sober	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
fallen	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
in	O
your	O
mistress	O
's	O
hands	O
?	O
S.	O
Collet	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
hospital	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
the	O
deceased	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
small	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
fore	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
sticking	O
plaister	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
matter	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
swelling	O
and	O
inflammation	O
all	O
over	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fore	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
wound	O
:	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
skull	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
head	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
fracture	O
on	O
the	O
skull	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
kind	O
of	O
contusion	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
durn	O
&	O
c	O
pie	O
meter	O
of	O
the	O
brains	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
affected	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
look	O
'd	O
a	O
little	O
red	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
inflam	O
'd	O
:	O
upon	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
the	O
blow	O
he	O
receiv	O
'd	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
died	O
so	O
soon	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
received	O
that	O
wound	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
properly	O
taken	O
care	O
of	O
by	O
a	O
surgeon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
understood	O
he	O
drank	O
hard	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
the	O
wound	O
worse	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
sticking	O
plaister	O
did	O
him	O
harm	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
deceased	O
came	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
afternoon	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
making	O
a	O
noise	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Dear	O
man	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
dying	O
:	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
She	O
held	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
shoved	O
him	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
,	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
liquor	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
fell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
?	O
Russel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
all	O
that	O
passed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
hardly	O
stand	O
on	O
his	O
legs	O
.	O
Accidental	O
death	O
.	O
73	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
2	O
other	O
persons	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
jury	O
unknown	O
,	O
on	O
Frederick	B-pers
Lenard	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
33	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
Jan.	O
9	O
.	O
||	O
Frederick	B-pers
Lenard	I-pers
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
and	O
speaking	O
but	O
very	O
bad	O
English	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
all	O
int	O
.	O
Fredrick	O
Lenard	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Angel-al-house	O
that	O
leads	O
up	O
to	O
Devonshire-square	B-place
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
sennight	O
at	O
night	O
going	O
from	O
thence	O
wards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Rose	O
's	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
persons	O
standing	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
blow	O
from	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
passing	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
forehead	O
,	O
which	O
stunned	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
persons	O
gave	O
you	O
that	O
blow	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
stab	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
cut	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
blood	O
ran	O
prodigiously	O
.	O
He	O
thought	O
to	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
put	O
down	O
my	O
chin	O
,	O
and	O
received	O
the	O
cut	O
thereon	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
hold	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cut	O
my	O
finger	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
two	O
large	O
long	O
wounds	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
his	O
chin	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
cheek	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
on	O
his	O
finger	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
let	O
go	O
my	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
assistance	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
part	O
did	O
you	O
hold	O
him	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
collar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
understand	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
not	O
knowing	O
English	O
:	O
he	O
stabb	O
'd	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
reach	O
my	O
is	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
hold	O
him	O
fast	O
.	O
We	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
33	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
pocket	O
was	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
purse	O
or	O
loose	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
loose	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
on	O
it	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
3	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
disturbed	O
in	O
my	O
brains	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
came	O
to	O
your	O
assistance	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
That	O
night	O
at	O
12	O
o'clock	O
I	O
was	O
carried	O
with	O
my	O
wounds	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
light	O
,	O
nor	O
yet	O
quite	O
dark	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
I	O
were	O
to	O
see	O
I	O
should	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
if	O
you	O
first	O
laid	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
blow	O
I	O
received	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
escape	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stab	O
'd	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
seeing	O
myself	O
in	O
danger	O
turn	O
'd	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
let	O
go	O
till	O
assistance	O
came	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
or	O
street	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
street	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
persons	O
men	O
or	O
women	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
men	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
attack	O
you	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
capable	O
of	O
giving	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
being	O
so	O
full	O
of	O
blood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
constable	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
a	O
constable	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Woolpack-alley	O
by	O
Houndsditch	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
enough	O
in	O
London	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
places	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
any	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
with	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
being	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
came	O
to	O
your	O
assistance	O
?	O
Lenard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
till	O
he	O
discover	O
'd	O
himself	O
.	O
Barnard	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
in	O
Woolpack	O
Alley	O
,	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
pulling	O
off	O
my	O
shoes	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
in	O
the	O
German	O
language	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
,	O
shall	O
I	O
die	O
such	O
a	O
miserable	O
death	O
?	O
Q.	O
Repeat	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
language	O
he	O
spoke	O
it	O
.	O
Moses	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
language	O
,	O
O	O
Lord	O
,	O
Almighty	O
God	O
,	O
must	O
I	O
die	O
such	O
a	O
miserable	O
death	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
will	O
come	O
and	O
help	O
me	O
!	O
Then	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
men	O
standing	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
were	O
beating	O
him	O
with	O
sticks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
sticks	O
?	O
Moses	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
to	O
murder	O
the	O
poor	O
soul	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
was	O
uppermost	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
or	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
?	O
Moses	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
uppermost	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
said	O
blast	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
bare	O
him	O
through	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
peep	O
'd	O
thro	O
'	O
a	O
place	O
that	O
is	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
pull	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
my	O
door	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
alley	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
again	O
in	O
his	O
language	O
Is	O
there	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
can	O
help	O
me	O
?	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
my	O
opportunity	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
fire	O
and	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
this	O
great	O
cry	O
of	O
mine	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
men	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Dutchman	O
were	O
still	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
continuing	O
to	O
be	O
uppermost	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
The	O
Dutchman	O
said	O
dem	O
people	O
rob	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
meony	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
lose	O
my	O
moony	O
,	O
I	O
lose	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
off	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
's	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
in	O
Dutch	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
you	O
must	O
help	O
me	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
Dutchman	O
said	O
in	O
his	O
language	O
I	O
am	O
so	O
barbarously	O
used	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
able	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
help	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
very	O
bloody	O
?	O
Moses	O
.	O
All	O
his	O
face	O
and	O
every	O
part	O
of	O
him	O
were	O
all	O
over	O
blood	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
me	O
for	O
blood	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
pistol	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
deliver	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Moses	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Woolpack-Alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Jane	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
there	O
?	O
Moses	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
one	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
?	O
Moses	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
heard	O
the	O
words	O
bore	O
him	O
through	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
you	O
think	O
they	O
were	O
applicable	O
to	O
,	O
you	O
or	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
?	O
Moses	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
saw	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
Moses	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
it	O
a	O
lock	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Moses	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
charged	O
?	O
Moses	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
ever	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
?	O
Moses	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
knife	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
struggling	O
with	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
?	O
Moses	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
place	O
a	O
thorough-fare	O
?	O
Moses	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Terry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
Aldgate	O
high	O
street	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
of	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
coming	O
from	O
towards	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
It	O
being	O
my	O
watch	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
arm	O
in	O
arm	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
exceeding	O
bloody	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
so	O
bloody	O
to	O
be	O
alive	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
cloaths	O
all	O
over	O
dirt	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
how	O
this	O
came	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
in	O
English	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
Presently	O
after	O
came	O
a	O
Jew	O
or	O
two	O
that	O
understood	O
his	O
language	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
interpreted	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
twenty	O
times	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sure	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
never	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
together	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
came	O
in	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
here	O
Tom	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
know	O
your	O
lad	O
?	O
Terry	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
He	O
lived	O
but	O
a	O
few	O
doors	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
your	O
lad	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Terry	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
fumble	O
with	O
their	O
coats	O
close	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
no	O
jealousy	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
then	O
,	O
so	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Terry	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Butcher-row	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
minute	O
after	O
my	O
lad	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
in	O
frighted	O
almost	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
wits	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
is	O
not	O
this	O
a	O
pretty	O
fellow	O
to	O
give	O
your	O
servant	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
my	O
pistol	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Cockayne	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
?	O
Terry	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
?	O
Terry	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
on	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
watch	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
pistol	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
walk	O
out	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
producing	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Arnold	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
our	O
house	O
sometimes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
your	O
master	O
?	O
Arnold	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
is	O
a	O
publican	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
flint	O
in	O
the	O
pistol	O
,	O
neither	O
was	O
it	O
loaded	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
condition	O
it	O
is	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
pistol	O
?	O
Arnold	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
that	O
John	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
had	O
given	O
me	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
Angel	O
alehouse	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
whether	O
that	O
money	O
you	O
mention	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
alehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
drank	O
any	O
quantity	O
of	O
liquor	O
there	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
had	O
only	O
three	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
usually	O
carry	O
your	O
money	O
in	O
your	O
coat	O
pocket	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
seldom	O
carry	O
any	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
carry	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
together	O
usually	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
3	O
l	O
,	O
a	O
quarter	O
paid	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
generally	O
put	O
it	O
all	O
together	O
when	O
I	O
receive	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
were	O
fighting	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
designed	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
or	O
accidental	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
fighting	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
lain	O
with	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
their	O
own	O
room	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
here	O
now	O
to	O
prove	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
making	O
such	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
defence	O
,	O
his	O
witnesses	O
were	O
all	O
sworn	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
taken	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
and	O
examined	O
separate	O
,	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Spurr	I-pers
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
said	O
in	O
my	O
iing	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
and	O
her	O
together	O
?	O
E.	O
Spurr	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Jane	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
never	O
rob	O
'd	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Tindal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gravel-Lane	O
,	O
Houndsditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
employment	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
fruit	O
and	O
fish	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
,	O
my	O
child	O
,	O
my	O
grand-child	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Devonshire-square	O
shops	O
,	O
at	O
pretty	O
near	O
9	O
o'clock	O
yesterday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
:	O
We	O
had	O
3	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
an	O
ill	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
ill.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
telling	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
money	O
on	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
money	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
was	O
most	O
of	O
it	O
silver	O
;	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
more	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
pipe	O
in	O
his	O
mouth	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Jew	O
selling	O
money	O
on	O
his	O
sabbath	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
something	O
like	O
forty	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
40	O
.	O
He	O
swept	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
with	O
both	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
pocket	O
did	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
which	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
might	O
there	O
be	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
bulk	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
above	O
20	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
made	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
Coming	O
through	O
the	O
polls	O
I	O
met	O
Jenny	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
with	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
holding	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
left	O
arm	O
.	O
just	O
beyond	O
the	O
pump	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
him	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
alehouse	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
him	O
in	O
liquor	O
by	O
her	O
holding	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
true	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
thick	O
mud	O
like	O
hasty	O
padding	O
through	O
all	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
narrow	O
passage	O
coming	O
under	O
an	O
arch	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
door	O
came	O
to	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
they	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
not	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
more	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
In	O
came	O
John	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
old	O
one	O
?	O
How	O
does	O
your	O
husband	O
do	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Is	O
he	O
so	O
little	O
that	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
head	O
was	O
leaning	O
against	O
my	O
shoulder	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
pot	O
and	O
drank	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
shilling	O
and	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
change	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
one	O
pint	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
after	O
came	O
word	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
battle	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Jack	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
not	O
that	O
Jew	O
that	O
stood	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
fighting	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
I	O
sup	O
there	O
every	O
night	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
sup	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
or	O
after	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
I	O
sup	O
'd	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
home	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
Between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
your	O
house	O
from	O
the	O
Angel	O
alehouse	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
10	O
yards	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
home	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
no	O
longer	O
than	O
while	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
alehouse	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
alehouse	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
man	O
up	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
Better	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
say	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
shall	O
not	O
tell	O
a	O
lye	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
Boswell	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
did	O
he	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
He	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
two	O
pints	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
many	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
then	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
people	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
all	O
their	O
names	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
a	O
weaver	O
.	O
Q	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
H.	O
Tindal	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Woolf	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Devonshire-Square	O
steps	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
betwixt	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
,	O
or	O
near	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
up	O
from	O
Deptford	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
enter	O
'd	O
on	O
board	O
an	O
Indiaman	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
four	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
Jane	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
call	O
'd	O
me	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
like	O
a	O
Jew	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
near	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
before	O
her	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
Jane	O
Trueman	O
's	O
,	O
she	O
desires	O
the	O
door	O
may	O
be	O
open	O
'd	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
you	O
may	O
go	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
door	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
a	O
back	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Jane	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
before	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
over	O
her	O
head	O
five	O
weeks	O
before	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
home	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
alehouse	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
return	O
'd	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Harrow-Alley	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Petticoat-Lane	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
alehouse	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
quarter	O
before	O
nine	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
and	O
I	O
drank	O
2	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
for	O
Jane	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
near	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
evidence	O
Tindal	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
drinking	O
there	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
there	O
first	O
,	O
they	O
or	O
you	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
there	O
first	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
in	O
the	O
alehouse	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
home	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
her	O
talk	O
of	O
making	O
her	O
bed	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
before	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
home	O
and	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
her	O
husband	O
in	O
the	O
alehouse	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
:	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
in	O
the	O
Angel	O
alehouse	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
there	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
gone	O
from	O
that	O
alehouse	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
above	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Tindal	O
the	O
evidence	O
there	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
back	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
alehouse	O
from	O
first	O
to	O
last	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
how	O
long	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
four	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
the	O
last	O
when	O
Jenny	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
came	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
Tindal	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
stay	O
there	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
how	O
long	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
that	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
lean	O
'd	O
upon	O
her	O
shoulder	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
you	O
first	O
went	O
in	O
?	O
A.	O
Woolf	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
indeed	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
as	O
I	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
but	O
Tindal	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
by	O
name	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
my	O
dear	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
speak	O
that	O
in	O
English	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
answer	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
pray	O
let	O
me	O
alone	O
[	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
come	O
out	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
the	O
folks	O
said	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
a	O
full-pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
watch	O
'd	O
me	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
go	O
along	O
,	O
for	O
you	O
are	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
fuddled	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
Nan	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
for	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
because	O
a	O
man	O
follows	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lock	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
Pretyman	O
said	O
stay	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
perhaps	O
we	O
may	O
get	O
something	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
She	O
unlock	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
which	O
door	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
fore	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
continue	O
there	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
sell	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
We	O
sell	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
3	O
d.	O
change	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
fetch	O
it	O
from	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Angel	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
-	O
Council	O
for	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
body	O
asks	O
you	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
.	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
fire-side	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
seven	O
shillings	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
pick	O
'd	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
more	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
the	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
money	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
speak	O
in	O
English	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
as	O
plain	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
could	O
speak	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
immediately	O
.	O
Boswell	O
and	O
Will	O
.	O
Watts	O
happening	O
to	O
come	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Boswell	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
here	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
.	O
Boswell	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
none	O
of	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
said	O
I	O
want	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
and	O
lifted	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
Boswell	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
stooping	O
down	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
let	O
him	O
beat	O
on	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
beat	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
Dutchman	O
struck	O
Boswell	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
leg	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
beat	O
till	O
the	O
stick	O
broke	O
.	O
Boswell	O
was	O
still	O
stooping	O
,	O
I	O
wonder	O
'd	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
assure	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
was	O
a	O
cutlass	O
or	O
a	O
hanger	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
glisten	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
woman	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
.	O
Nanny	O
Pretyman	O
came	O
over	O
soon	O
after	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
19	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
blood	O
on	O
the	O
threshold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
fight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Barnaby	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
betwixt	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
Nancy	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
Pretyman	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
that	O
person	O
's	O
other	O
name	O
whom	O
you	O
call	O
Nancy	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
her	O
other	O
name	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
people	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
abouts	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
saw	O
her	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
She	O
stood	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
inside	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Hannah	B-pers
Tindal	I-pers
and	O
her	O
husband	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
there	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
I	O
stay	O
'd	O
no	O
longer	O
than	O
while	O
they	O
draw	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
Nancy	O
being	O
there	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
in	O
company	O
or	O
alone	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
that	O
young	O
man	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
Nancy	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
she	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
indeed	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
did	O
ask	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
both	O
together	O
?	O
J.	O
Trueman	O
.	O
We	O
came	O
there	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
either	O
the	O
man	O
or	O
Boswell	O
again	O
,	O
though	O
I	O
were	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Trueman	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
first	O
into	O
ill	O
ways	O
:	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
thieving	O
for	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
fellows	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
used	O
to	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
ca	O
n't	O
you	O
do	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
;	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
not	O
fit	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
whore	O
!	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
understand	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
happen	O
'd	O
yesterday	O
was	O
sennight	O
at	O
her	O
house	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
That	O
very	O
day	O
I	O
had	O
boil	O
'd	O
mutton	O
for	O
dinner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
her	O
house	O
between	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
for	O
dinner	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
mutton	O
and	O
broth	O
.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
some	O
broth	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
carry	O
them	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
About	O
6	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
playing	O
at	O
cards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
there	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
is	O
here	O
nam	O
'd	O
Nanny	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fellow	O
that	O
lives	O
with	O
her	O
nam	O
'd	O
Jack	O
Hall	O
,	O
his	O
brother	O
was	O
hang	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
fellow	O
that	O
she	O
lives	O
with	O
,	O
nam	O
'd	O
Daniel	B-pers
Post-Chaise	I-pers
,	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
help	O
'd	O
to	O
beat	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
and	O
goes	O
out	O
a	O
thieving	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
not	O
.	O
She	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
eat	O
the	O
broth	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
have	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
however	O
,	O
accordingly	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
This	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
8	O
,	O
or	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
beer	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Angel	O
alehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
she	O
stay	O
before	O
she	O
returned	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
She	O
staid	O
out	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Nanny	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
Nanney	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
before	O
they	O
talked	O
about	O
the	O
beer	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
somebody	O
coming	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
This	O
was	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
8	O
;	O
then	O
a	O
Dutchman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
Nanny	O
and	O
Trueman	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
the	O
court	O
which	O
came	O
in	O
first	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
Nanny	O
came	O
in	O
first	O
,	O
Trueman	O
next	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
after	O
;	O
then	O
Nanny	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back-door	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
what	O
she	O
would	O
drink	O
:	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
or	O
shut	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
door	O
was	O
left	O
open	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
lower	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
doors	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
said	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
neither	O
will	O
I	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
be	O
obliged	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
understand	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
know	O
vat	O
you	O
mean	O
.	O
Says	O
she	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
do	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
,	O
continued	O
he	O
,	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
pull	O
off	O
your	O
cloaths	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
but	O
me	O
nothing	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
more	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
Trueman	O
's	O
man	O
,	O
Daniel	B-pers
Post-Chaise	I-pers
,	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
six-pence	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
me	O
three	O
pence	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
Hall	O
and	O
Post-Chaise	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
Hall	O
and	O
Post-Chaise	O
ran	O
both	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
back-door	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
either	O
of	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
fetched	O
before	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
or	O
after	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
fetch	O
'd	O
before	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
Boswell	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
's	O
money	O
than	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
mother	O
alive	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
said	O
after	O
Boswell	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
what	O
I	O
want	O
:	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
with	O
sticks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
began	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
Boswell	O
began	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
there	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
said	O
,	O
Go	O
it	O
,	O
go	O
it	O
,	O
cut	O
his	O
eye-strings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
it	O
said	O
to	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
That	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
Boswell	O
:	O
then	O
Boswell	O
stooped	O
down	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
knife	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
pull	O
his	O
stockings	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Boswell	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
fighting	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
or	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
It	O
happen	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
after	O
Boswell	O
had	O
shov	O
'd	O
the	O
man	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
call	O
'd	O
Woolpack-alley	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
there	O
besides	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
Will	O
.	O
Watts	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
cap	O
brought	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-mayor	O
afterterwards	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
Post-Chaise	O
's	O
cap	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Post-Chaise	O
do	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Boswell	O
was	O
cutting	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
after	O
the	O
knife	O
was	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Watts	O
and	O
Post-Chaise	O
there	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Boswell	O
had	O
his	O
knife	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
yards	O
were	O
they	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
when	O
Boswell	O
drew	O
his	O
knife	O
out	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
alley	O
is	O
not	O
above	O
a	O
yard	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Boswell	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
or	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
his	O
knife	O
out	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
withinside	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
on	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
as	O
far	O
from	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
is	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
Pointing	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
in	O
court	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
yards	O
distance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
first	O
words	O
that	O
passed	O
between	O
Boswell	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
Boswell	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Trueman	I-pers
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
here	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
here	O
:	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Said	O
Boswell	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
and	O
they	O
fell	O
to	O
fighting	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Dutchman	O
's	O
coming	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
whether	O
Trueman	O
ever	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
No	O
.	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
,	O
dureing	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
battle	O
was	O
over	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
out	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
give	O
Post-Chaise	O
the	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Pretyman	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Wooton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upwards	O
of	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
M.	O
Wooton	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Water-lane	O
,	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
M.	O
Wooton	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
M.	O
Wooton	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
of	O
very	O
honest	O
parents	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
deal	O
very	O
largely	O
in	O
trade	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
character	O
?	O
M.	O
Wooton	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
,	O
of	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
bacon-shop	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
for	O
butchers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
22	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
served	O
my	O
time	O
in	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
wrong	O
or	O
defraud	O
any	O
man	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
honest	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
untold	O
gold	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
books	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
could	O
lay	O
my	O
life	O
for	O
his	O
honestly	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Aldgate	O
high	O
street	O
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
20	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
him	O
but	O
honesty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
had	O
any	O
dealings	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Painter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washerwoman	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
lived	O
in	O
Aldgate	O
high	O
street	O
40	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
E.	O
Painter	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Owen	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Harrow-Alley	O
,	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
on	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
sign	O
you	O
keep	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Still	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
The	O
jury	O
declared	O
they	O
believed	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
what	O
Tindal	O
had	O
sworn	O
;	O
and	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
that	O
Woolf-Trueman	O
,	O
and	O
Pretyman	O
had	O
sworn	O
:	O
And	O
desiring	O
that	O
the	O
three	O
last	O
might	O
be	O
committed	O
for	O
perjury	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
committed	O
accordingly	O
.	O
74	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Bills	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
17	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
and	O
Vincent	B-pers
Briscoe	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
3	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
75	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Randolph	B-pers
Douse	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
damask	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
six	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
pillowbiers	O
,	O
six	O
tablecloths	O
,	O
and	O
nine	O
towels	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Jan.	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
had	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
She	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coach	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
by	O
mistake	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
got	O
home	O
she	O
declared	O
she	O
believed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
;	O
only	O
kept	O
them	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
a	O
reward	O
would	O
be	O
offered	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
them	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
76	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Martha	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
-	I-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
copper	O
coffee	O
pot	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shervey	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Shervey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Field-Lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
shirts	O
were	O
missing	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
coffee-pot	O
was	O
pawned	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
Snow-Hill	O
,	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
blankets	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hosier-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-mayor	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
it	O
