TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
18th	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Thirtieth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1756	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
SLINGSBY	O
BETHELL	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
ROBINSON	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Lion	O
,	O
in	O
Ludgate-Street	O
.	O
1756	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SLINGSBY	O
BETHELL	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
My	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Willes	O
,	O
*	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
+	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
||	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
++	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
,	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
James	B-pers
Meuer	I-pers
James	B-pers
Nivon	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bardwell	I-pers
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Sabe	I-pers
James	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hollingsworth	I-pers
Smith	B-pers
Woolnoth	I-pers
William	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Henshaw	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
William	B-pers
Lambert	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Milward	I-pers
John	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Dickson	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Ridge	I-pers
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
Christopher	B-pers
Kempster	I-pers
Christopher	O
Kempster	O
being	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Randal	I-pers
serv	O
'd	O
in	O
his	O
stead	O
.	O
319	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
holland	O
stock	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
1	O
brass	O
stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
August	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
John	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
through	O
Drury-Lane	B-place
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
.	O
She	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
She	O
dragged	O
me	O
up	O
a	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
another	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fob	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
company	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
There	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
take	O
you	O
there	O
against	O
your	O
will	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
unbuttoned	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
fuddled	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
my	O
shopmates	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
betwixt	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
there	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
She	O
sat	O
there	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
sleep	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
staid	O
till	O
I	O
delivered	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spensley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
man	O
say	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
bitch	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
a	O
watchman	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
,	O
namely	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
stock	O
and	O
stock-buckle	O
;	O
them	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
.	O
Then	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
watchman	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
pulling	O
her	O
hand	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
described	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
maker	O
's	O
name	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
number	O
.	O
]	O
John	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Spensley	O
charged	O
me	O
to	O
aid	O
and	O
assist	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
hand	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
it	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
likewise	O
the	O
stock	O
and	O
buckle	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
that	O
morning	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Covent-Garden	O
market	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
uproar	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
women	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
to	O
the	O
King's-Head	O
door	O
.	O
To	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bewers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
washing	O
and	O
scowering	O
,	O
particularly	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
320	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
Vigonia	O
wool	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
and	I-pers
James	I-pers
Rossiter	I-pers
,	O
August	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Rossiter	I-pers
.	O
My	O
father	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
hatters	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
whose	O
mother	O
works	O
for	O
me	O
)	O
brought	O
her	O
work	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
servant	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
wool	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
call	O
Vigonia	O
or	O
reed	O
wool	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
fetch	O
'd	O
her	O
back	O
and	O
ordered	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
to	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
who	O
took	O
a	O
pound	O
and	O
two	O
ounces	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Rossiter	O
.	O
It	O
cost	O
me	O
nine	O
shillings	O
per	O
pound	O
.	O
The	O
wool	O
her	O
mother	O
work	O
'd	O
was	O
worth	O
only	O
about	O
nine	O
pence	O
per	O
pound	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
some	O
reed	O
wool	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
bag	O
in	O
master	O
's	O
warehouse	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Rossiter	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
work	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
delivered	O
her	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
presently	O
master	O
and	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
together	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
search	O
that	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
her	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
quantity	O
of	O
reed	O
wool	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rossiter	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
wool	O
?	O
Rossiter	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
the	O
woman	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
under	O
lock	O
and	O
key	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
produced	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
321	O
,	O
322	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jefferys	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Finley	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worstead	O
stockings	O
,	O
eleven	O
linen	O
clouts	O
,	O
and	O
27	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
17	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
them	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
||	O
Ann	B-pers
Noble	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	O
.	O
We	O
lodged	O
in	O
Queen	B-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Seven-Dials	I-place
,	O
where	O
we	O
had	O
one	O
room	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
I	O
missed	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
under	O
no	O
lock	O
and	O
key	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
lock	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
since	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
twenty-seven	O
shillings	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
bandbox	O
,	O
wrap	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
brown	O
paper	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Jefferys	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Finley	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
she	O
having	O
gone	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
at	O
Hungerford	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
her	O
aunt	O
lives	O
,	O
with	O
quite	O
new	O
cloaths	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
27	O
s	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
aunt	O
asking	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
mistress	O
sent	O
her	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
opened	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
mistress	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
in	O
Monmouth-Street	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
box	O
(	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
who	O
she	O
said	O
took	O
them	O
)	O
and	O
her	O
mistress	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
pair	O
afterwards	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
take	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
some	O
sattin	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
mistress	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
mistress	O
took	O
two	O
more	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bandbox	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
laid	O
out	O
the	O
27	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
cloaths	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
20	O
d.	O
I	O
took	O
Finley	O
up	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
(	O
tho	O
'	O
the	O
girl	O
confess	O
'd	O
this	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
)	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Rickets	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
whom	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
27	O
s.	O
The	O
girl	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
trunk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Finley	O
sent	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
stockings	O
,	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
clouts	O
and	O
ribbon	O
.	O
Jefferys	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
and	O
I	O
having	O
some	O
words	O
one	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Halfmoon-Street	O
,	O
treated	O
me	O
with	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
cloath	O
myself	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Noble	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
say	O
my	O
mistress	O
sent	O
me	O
up	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
.	O
Finley	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Noble	O
took	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
used	O
us	O
all	O
very	O
ill.	O
She	O
spit	O
in	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
whores	O
,	O
rogues	O
and	O
thieves	O
.	O
We	O
bid	O
her	O
quit	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
snap	O
her	O
fingers	O
at	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
us	O
kiss	O
her	O
backside	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
a	O
warrant	O
out	O
against	O
her	O
from	O
justice	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
New-prison	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
her	O
promising	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
rent	O
due	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
beg	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
gaol	O
:	O
After	O
which	O
she	O
began	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
this	O
girl	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
Hungerford	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
round	O
by	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
me	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Noble	O
had	O
offer	O
'd	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
double	O
apparel	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
say	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
.	O
Jefferys	O
guilty	O
.	O
Finley	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
323	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
loaf	O
of	O
bread	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Weeden	I-pers
,	O
August	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
324	O
,	O
325	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Frances	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
necklace	O
and	O
locket	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Adkins	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Sept.	O
2	O
.8	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Adkins	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Chappel-Street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
a	O
gold	O
bead	O
necklace	O
and	O
locket	O
on	O
my	O
table	O
,	O
which	O
cost	O
me	O
4	O
l	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
almost	O
40	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
both	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
liver	O
and	O
bacon	O
to	O
dress	O
for	O
their	O
dinners	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
E.	O
Adkins	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
live	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
necklace	O
and	O
locket	O
,	O
and	O
making	O
inquiry	O
I	O
understood	O
the	O
mother	O
had	O
been	O
shewing	O
a	O
necklace	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
mother	O
had	O
got	O
new	O
cloaths	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
girl	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
necklace	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
under	O
the	O
table	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
;	O
the	O
mother	O
also	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
26	O
s.	O
to	O
Paul	B-pers
Callerd	I-pers
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
directly	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Callerd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
women	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
gold	O
necklace	O
.	O
I	O
weigh	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
weigh	O
'd	O
12	O
pennyweights	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
26	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
advertised	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
reward	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
,	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
guilty	O
31	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Frances	O
guilty	O
of	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
326	O
,	O
327	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lins	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Esther	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
ounces	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiveing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
July	O
.	O
23	O
*	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
328	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Martha	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Edward	I-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
one	O
copper	O
stewpan	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Marmaduke	B-pers
Grange	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Sept.	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
329	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Maccalpin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Saffery	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Chaplin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Saffery	I-pers
,	O
who	O
provides	O
me	O
with	O
hats	O
,	O
cloaths	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
pew	O
at	O
church	O
where	O
I	O
sat	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
my	O
hat	O
off	O
a	O
pin	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
church	O
.	O
He	O
perceived	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
Stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
own	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
putting	O
one	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
He	O
beg	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
He	O
'll	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
and't	O
please	O
your	O
lordship	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
service	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
whom	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
instead	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
I	O
took	O
another	O
hat	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
330	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Beal	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
over	O
again	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Sept.	O
8	O
.	O
||	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
331	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Day	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
June	O
the	O
10th	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	O
Day	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
last	O
June	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Billingsgate	B-place
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breast	O
pocket	O
to	O
wipe	O
my	O
fingers	O
,	O
having	O
handled	O
some	O
mackerel	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
minute	O
's	O
time	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
lost	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
'd	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
Darkhouse-lane	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
pointed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
into	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
observing	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
drop	O
it	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
332	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
14	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
333	O
,	O
334	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Street	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
sacks	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Wilks	I-pers
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Street	O
guilty	O
.	O
Wade	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
335	O
,	O
336	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ridout	I-pers
and	O
James	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Macdaniel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Alexander	O
,	O
Aug.	O
15	O
.	O
*	O
Alexander	O
Macdaniel	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
in	O
the	O
Fields	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
which	O
cost	O
me	O
7	O
l.	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
had	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Macdaniel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Macdaniel	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
them	O
both	O
own	O
,	O
that	O
Ridout	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Prosser	O
,	O
who	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
Prosser	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
cobler	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
one	O
Woodhouse	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
since	O
bail	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
cobler	O
and	O
Prosser	O
had	O
each	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
they	O
confess	O
this	O
?	O
Macdaniel	O
.	O
Before	O
justice	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
,	O
had	O
Ridout	O
no	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Macdaniel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
stop	O
'd	O
immediately	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
tankard	O
being	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
prison	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Macdaniel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
the	O
tankard	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
Ridout	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
believe	O
two	O
hours	O
.	O
Prosser	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
two	O
pints	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
pursuing	O
them	O
Ridout	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
Southampton-Street	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
overtake	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Ridout	O
confess	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
from	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Prosser	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
Prosser	O
said	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
cobler	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Woodhouse	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cobler	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Ridout	O
confess	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
from	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
our	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Prosser	O
;	O
and	O
Prosser	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
cobler	O
at	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
Pound	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Woodhouse	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
two	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
Ridout	O
had	O
nothing	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Todd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fellow	O
soldier	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Prosser	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
barrack	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
;	O
(	O
Prosser	O
's	O
barrack	O
was	O
over	O
mine	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
fall	O
.	O
I	O
step	O
'd	O
out	O
and	O
saw	O
something	O
shine	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
held	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
lamp	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
cover	O
to	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
.	O
Prosser	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
intend	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
good	O
hand	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
yourself	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Park	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
one	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
comrades	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
others	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
barrack	O
,	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
;	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
.	O
It	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
sergeant	O
major	O
's	O
car	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
colonel	O
next	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
related	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
.	O
He	O
ordered	O
the	O
corporal	O
and	O
I	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
confine	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
;	O
which	O
we	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
justice	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
cover	O
was	O
tin	O
.	O
Ridout	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
was	O
asked	O
whether	O
Prosser	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Then	O
Prosser	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
a	O
cobler	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
cobler	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Woodhouse	O
in	O
Oxford-Road	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
;	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
other	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
337.	O
Richard	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
tankard	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
Ridout	O
and	O
Prosser	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
338.	O
William	B-pers
Cannyent	I-pers
was	I-pers
indicted	I-pers
for	I-pers
the	I-pers
wilful	I-pers
murder	I-pers
of	I-pers
Dorothy	I-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Dorothy	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
feloniously	O
,	O
wickedly	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
malice	O
afore	O
thought	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
pair	O
of	O
scissars	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
iron	O
and	O
steel	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
and	O
held	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
said	O
Dorothy	O
,	O
did	O
assault	O
,	O
stick	O
and	O
stab	O
,	O
giving	O
her	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
on	O
her	O
neck	O
,	O
near	O
her	O
left	O
ear	O
,	O
breadth	O
one	O
inch	O
,	O
and	O
depth	O
three	O
inches	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
wound	O
she	O
did	O
instantly	O
die	O
.	O
He	O
stood	O
charged	O
likewise	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
murder	O
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
received	O
sentence	O
of	O
death	O
,	O
being	O
overwhelmed	O
with	O
grief	O
and	O
tears	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
speak	O
much	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
into	O
court	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
``	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
unhappy	O
perpetrator	O
of	O
that	O
``	O
most	O
horrid	O
and	O
unparallel	O
'd	O
crime	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
``	O
stand	O
charged	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
sue	O
for	O
``	O
but	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
God	O
to	O
my	O
poor	O
soul	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
give	O
``	O
this	O
honourable	O
court	O
no	O
farther	O
trouble	O
:	O
But	O
as	O
``	O
a	O
penitent	O
,	O
sensible	O
of	O
my	O
horrid	O
guilt	O
,	O
I	O
earnestly	O
``	O
beg	O
the	O
prayers	O
of	O
all	O
good	O
christians	O
;	O
that	O
God	O
``	O
through	O
his	O
infinite	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
through	O
the	O
intercession	O
``	O
of	O
our	O
blessed	O
Saviour	O
and	O
Redeemer	O
Jesus	O
``	O
Christ	O
,	O
may	O
blot	O
out	O
this	O
stain	O
of	O
shedding	O
innocent	O
``	O
blood	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
the	O
motives	O
which	O
induced	O
``	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
wicked	O
act	O
will	O
not	O
appear	O
here	O
,	O
``	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
acknowledge	O
my	O
guilt	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
that	O
``	O
the	O
publick	O
may	O
be	O
fully	O
satisfied	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
I	O
``	O
have	O
delivered	O
under	O
my	O
own	O
hand	O
writing	O
,	O
a	O
``	O
just	O
and	O
full	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
progress	O
of	O
that	O
``	O
sad	O
and	O
fatal	O
transaction	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
to	O
``	O
its	O
final	O
and	O
fatal	O
end	O
:	O
To	O
be	O
published	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
``	O
Walker	O
the	O
publisher	O
,	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
``	O
more	O
in	O
this	O
transitory	O
world	O
:	O
In	O
hopes	O
the	O
same	O
``	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
warning	O
to	O
all	O
others	O
,	O
to	O
avoid	O
the	O
steps	O
``	O
that	O
led	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
God	O
of	O
his	O
infinite	O
mercy	O
``	O
I	O
hope	O
will	O
have	O
mercy	O
on	O
me	O
.	O
''	O
339	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susannah	B-pers
Winch	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
September	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Susannah	B-pers
Burchet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Little	O
Chelsea	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
gardener	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
Susannah	B-pers
Winch	I-pers
lives	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
.	O
She	O
had	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
bolster	O
of	O
her	O
bed	O
,	O
a	O
box	O
full	O
of	O
silver	O
and	O
fifteen	O
or	O
sixteen	O
shillings	O
in	O
halfpence	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
by	O
whom	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
very	O
infirm	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
attend	O
her	O
at	O
times	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Newbolt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
in	O
Kensington	O
parish	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
five	O
pence	O
in	O
halfpence	O
and	O
farthings	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
five	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
in	O
a	O
housewife	O
,	O
put	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
pit	O
.	O
This	O
box	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
bosom	O
.	O
S.	O
Burchet	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
the	O
box	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
.	O
Newbolt	O
.	O
She	O
pretended	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
working	O
girl	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
box	O
given	O
me	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
snuff	O
in	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
340	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Jameson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
five	O
ells	O
of	O
holland	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lucy	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
cloth	O
cloak	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abigail	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
August	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
Hannah	B-pers
Boroughs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
family	O
got	O
up	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
away	O
till	O
about	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
following	O
.	O
In	O
his	O
absence	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
hat	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
four	O
shillings	O
on	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
by	O
some	O
method	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
in	O
another	O
house	O
backwards	O
.	O
He	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
two	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Gosling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
got	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
hat	O
and	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
two	O
,	O
cloaks	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
and	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
holland	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	B-pers
On	I-pers
the	O
thirteenth	O
when	O
my	O
family	O
arose	O
,	O
the	O
doors	O
were	O
open	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
this	O
key	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
and	O
by	O
looking	O
about	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
behind	O
my	O
garret	O
door	O
concealed	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
servant	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
,	O
and	O
there	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
true	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
he	O
got	O
down	O
the	O
cellar	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
turned	O
him	O
away	O
immediately	O
,	O
upon	O
finding	O
him	O
out	O
about	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Powis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
servant	O
.	O
She	O
turned	O
him	O
away	O
about	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
missed	O
a	O
hat	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
absent	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
returned	O
,	O
mistress	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
also	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
cloaks	O
and	O
five	O
elis	O
of	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
an	O
old	O
Jew	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
the	O
cloaks	O
belong	O
to	O
?	O
E.	O
Powis	O
.	O
They	O
belong	O
to	O
Lucy	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
and	O
Abigail	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
341	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Knott	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
tap	O
at	O
New-prison	B-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
hanging	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
all	O
the	O
gates	O
to	O
be	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
proper	O
watches	O
over	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
all	O
search	O
'd	O
.	O
The	O
turnkey	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
book	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
watch	O
put	O
in	O
your	O
bar	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
hanging	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
wall	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
from	O
your	O
missing	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
your	O
searching	O
him	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
than	O
the	O
man	O
unborn	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
very	O
drunk	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
watches	O
hung	O
side	O
by	O
side	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
hanging	O
afterwards	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
fob	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Lashbrook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
a	O
boy	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
mathematical-instrument	O
maker	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
journeyman	O
where	O
he	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
342	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Cartwright	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
hat	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Maring	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
September	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Cavendish-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Cavendish-Square	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
who	O
married	O
my	O
own	O
sister	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
children	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
gin	O
.	O
We	O
parted	O
in	O
Berwick-Street	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Appletree	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
.	O
He	O
proposed	O
to	O
come	O
again	O
on	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
purposed	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
dinner	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
fair	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
looked	O
about	O
some	O
time	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
rod	O
and	O
struck	O
my	O
child	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
thinking	O
she	O
had	O
let	O
somebody	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
said	O
,	O
nobody	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
but	O
her	O
uncle	O
.	O
Then	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
Esther	B-pers
Maring	I-pers
,	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
a	O
milking	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
pocket-handkerchief	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
that	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
trunk	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
money	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
buckles	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
.	O
I	O
got	O
only	O
the	O
buckles	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Harrow	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Panton-Street	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
own	O
brother	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
talked	O
of	O
lending	O
his	O
brother	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
paying	O
the	O
landlord	O
there	O
an	O
old	O
score	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
landlord	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
him	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
landlord	O
would	O
assist	O
in	O
securing	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
neither	O
would	O
he	O
let	O
the	O
watchman	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
assist	O
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
away	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
Round-house	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
broke	O
open	O
my	O
box	O
with	O
the	O
poker	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
trunk	O
out	O
and	O
wrapped	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
in	O
a	O
passion	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
three-pence	O
halfpenny	O
,	O
my	O
silver	O
buttons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
(	O
not	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
Presently	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
lost	O
three	O
pounds	O
seven	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
in	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
.	O
He	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
opened	O
my	O
trunk	O
,	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
at	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
him	O
?	O
Tame	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
afterwards	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
guinea	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
afterwards	O
changed	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Maring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
.	O
I	O
remember	O
his	O
coming	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
a	O
milking	O
,	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
examined	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Timothy	B-pers
More	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
charging	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
paying	O
his	O
debts	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
what	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
shew	O
us	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
he	O
produced	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
three	O
pounds	O
seven-shillings	O
.	O
He	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
one	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
343	O
,	O
344	O
,	O
345	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Eve	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Tippet	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Riley	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hundred	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
July	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
Eve	O
guilty	O
,	O
Tippet	O
and	O
Riley	O
acquitted	O
.	O
346	O
,	O
347	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Kelsey	I-pers
and	O
George	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
10	O
yards	O
of	O
callico	O
wrapper	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Waradle	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Daniel	O
,	O
July	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Waradle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Daniel	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Chandlers	B-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
Grosvenor-Square	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Wright	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
coarse	O
handkerchiefs	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
while	O
Kelsey	O
turned	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
the	O
very	O
instant	O
.	O
I	O
pushed	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
goods	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
followed	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
man	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
and	O
pointed	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
left	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
all	O
3	O
ran	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
callico	O
wrapper	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
.	O
He	O
followed	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
are	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Waradle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
parlour	O
when	O
these	O
people	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
us	O
of	O
some	O
callico-wrapper	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
North-Audley-Street	O
I	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
three	O
men	O
;	O
two	O
in	O
red	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
light	O
colour	O
cloaths	O
.	O
They	O
ran	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ran	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
They	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
in	O
the	O
light	O
colour	O
'd	O
cloaths	O
turn	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
Kelsey	O
's	O
collar	O
(	O
He	O
had	O
this	O
hanger	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
producing	O
one	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
other	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
Kelsey	O
drew	O
the	O
hanger	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
on	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
hilt	O
,	O
secured	O
it	O
and	O
them	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Red-Lion	O
.	O
There	O
went	O
the	O
landlord	O
and	O
others	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
as	O
I	O
directed	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
this	O
wrapper	O
(	O
here	O
produced	O
)	O
which	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
ditch	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
goods	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Or	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
soldiers	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
light	O
colour	O
'd	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Waradle	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
There	O
they	O
were	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
them	O
.	O
Going	O
to	O
gaol	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
was	O
a	O
recruit	O
which	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
run	O
all	O
together	O
far	O
?	O
Waradle	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
ran	O
better	O
than	O
half	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
together	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sat	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
in	O
little	O
Queen-Street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
two	O
in	O
soldiers	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
colour	O
'd	O
coat	O
,	O
run	O
by	O
my	O
window	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
soldier	O
drop	O
'd	O
something	O
white	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stoop	O
'd	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
paper	O
or	O
linen	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
people	O
came	O
after	O
in	O
a	O
hue	O
and	O
cry	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
which	O
way	O
they	O
went	O
.	O
Kelsey	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
serve	O
his	O
majesty	O
king	O
George	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
directly	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
came	O
making	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
of	O
her	O
things	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
hang	O
us	O
right	O
or	O
wrong	O
.	O
Wright	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
recruit	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
knock	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
foot	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
and	O
ran	O
against	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
.	O
She	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
shop	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
has	O
got	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
man	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
;	O
because	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
occasion	O
of	O
our	O
running	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
was	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
running	O
a	O
race	O
for	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
recruit	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
us	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
348	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pint	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grice	I-pers
,	O
August	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Grice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Four	O
Swans	O
Inn	O
,	O
Bishopsgate-Street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
a	O
private	O
room	O
,	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
something	O
for	O
supper	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
and	O
I	O
in	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
come	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
wine	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
join	O
company	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
spent	O
three	O
pence	O
each	O
.	O
The	O
others	O
went	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
I	O
alone	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
servant	O
so	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
keep	O
an	O
eye	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
towards	O
the	O
door	O
twice	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
he	O
was	O
laying	O
as	O
though	O
asleep	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
customary	O
for	O
people	O
that	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
horse	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
their	O
liquor	O
before	O
they	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
my	O
man	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
mug	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
tapster	O
at	O
this	O
inn	O
.	O
Master	O
bid	O
me	O
watch	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
fearing	O
he	O
should	O
carry	O
away	O
the	O
mug	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
the	O
hostler	O
to	O
stand	O
at	O
the	O
wicket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
watched	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
peep	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Seeing	O
nobody	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
mug	O
between	O
his	O
thighs	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
conceal	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
walked	O
down	O
the	O
yard	O
beyond	O
all	O
our	O
doors	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
his	O
collar	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mug	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
this	O
house	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
sleep	O
all	O
night	O
(	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Bristol	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
landlord	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
bed	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
another	O
half	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
supper	O
and	O
beer	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
I	O
tap	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
foot	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
came	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
pot	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
and	O
going	O
for	O
them	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
my	O
bed	O
they	O
stop	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
349	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Young	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
two	O
moidores	O
,	O
sixteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
,	O
August	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Samuel	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Kentish-Town	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
farmer	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
both	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
my	O
servant	O
was	O
left	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
and	O
ordered	O
Rogers	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
to	O
supper	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
out	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
seven	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
treat	O
this	O
body	O
and	O
that	O
body	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
it	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
bricks	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
just	O
under	O
the	O
kitchen	O
floor	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
there	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
eleven	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
two	O
moidores	O
,	O
sixteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
usually	O
put	O
your	O
money	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
my	O
landlord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
small	O
beer	O
tub	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
.	O
About	O
three	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lay	O
it	O
there	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
small	O
beer	O
could	O
perceive	O
it	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
They	O
might	O
go	O
twenty	O
times	O
and	O
never	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
lay	O
so	O
close	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
but	O
just	O
room	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
dark	O
brown	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
high	O
is	O
the	O
cellar	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
The	O
cellar	O
is	O
just	O
high	O
enough	O
for	O
a	O
but	O
to	O
stand	O
in	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
your	O
money	O
lay	O
just	O
about	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
eye	O
when	O
he	O
stands	O
up	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
money	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
produced	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
hands	O
.	O
I	O
accused	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
surrender	O
'd	O
eleven	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
sixteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
twenty-seven	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
a	O
trifle	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
Master	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
your	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
broke	O
no	O
lock	O
nor	O
drawer	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
number	O
and	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
before	O
he	O
produced	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
About	O
twenty-four	O
hours	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
had	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
have	O
gone	O
off	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
a	O
yearly	O
servant	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
year	O
next	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
has	O
he	O
behaved	O
while	O
in	O
your	O
service	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
cleared	O
I	O
'll	O
let	O
him	O
to	O
work	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
this	O
money	O
had	O
been	O
laid	O
in	O
a	O
proper	O
drawer	O
,	O
or	O
place	O
where	O
money	O
is	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
,	O
whether	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
'd	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Edge	I-pers
(	O
the	O
constable	O
)	O
produced	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Tell	O
it	O
over	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
(	O
tells	O
it	O
over	O
.	O
)	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
right	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Take	O
care	O
where	O
you	O
put	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
not	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
350	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Scot	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
flannel	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
shag	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
dimity	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
seven	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Racket	I-pers
,	O
then	O
a	O
widow	O
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
drawer	O
at	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
Porter	O
in	O
Leicester	O
Fields	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
my	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mary	O
Racket	O
,	O
then	O
a	O
widow	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
the	O
shirts	O
were'in	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cloaths	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
the	O
exact	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
all	O
my	O
cloaths	O
again	O
,	O
except	O
two	O
shirts	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
justice	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
denied	O
having	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
by	O
his	O
directions	O
;	O
that	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
carry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
come	O
into	O
Mary	O
Racket	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
for	O
a	O
penny	O
worth	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
inform	O
'd	O
my	O
uncle	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Plough	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
of	O
my	O
loss	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
let	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
such	O
cloaths	O
on	O
a	O
horse	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
near	O
Edgware	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
cloaths	O
found	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
value	O
them	O
at	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
At	O
ten	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
when	O
taken	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
this	O
man	O
.	O
My	O
brother-in-law	O
living	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
porter	O
at	O
the	O
Gentleman	O
and	O
Porter	O
in	O
Leicester	O
Fields	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
a	O
box	O
the	O
last	O
night	O
from	O
Rupert-street	O
to	O
somewhere	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Justice	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
granted	O
me	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
after	O
looking	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
divers	O
places	O
to	O
no	O
purpose	O
;	O
but	O
having	O
had	O
further	O
intelligence	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Kingsbury	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
farmer	O
's	O
house	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
gone	O
towards	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
an	O
alehouse	O
door	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
dress	O
and	O
the	O
horse	O
he	O
rode	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
once	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
in	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
coat	O
.	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
shirt	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
.	O
On	O
searching	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Newgate	O
on	O
his	O
second	O
examination	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
and	O
Still	O
in	O
Tyburn-road	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
opened	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
shirts	O
and	O
a	O
coat	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
things	O
there	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
shirts	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
four	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
big	O
was	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
in	O
length	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
kept	O
lock	O
'd	O
or	O
unlock	O
'd	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
bean	O
feast	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
people	O
going	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
stairs	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
not	O
lock	O
'd	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Sunday	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
believed	O
we	O
might	O
find	O
the	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
Hog	O
in	O
the	O
Pound	O
in	O
Tyburn-road	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
that	O
from	O
the	O
Green	O
Man	O
and	O
Still	O
?	O
Thornton	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
only	O
it	O
has	O
a	O
double	O
sign	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
box	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
shirts	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
one	O
farmer	O
Finch	O
at	O
Kingsbury-Green	O
.	O
On	O
a	O
wet	O
day	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
one	O
Stapleton	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
that	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
going	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Antigallican	O
privateer	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
me	O
the	O
cloaths	O
very	O
cheap	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
agreed	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
30	O
s.	O
for	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
shirts	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
Lambeth	O
Marsh	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
King's-Arm	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
attend	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
bringing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
he	O
sham	O
'd	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
from	O
his	O
horse	O
twice	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
wanted	O
to	O
call	O
at	O
an	O
alehouse	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
chare	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
flung	O
this	O
Common-Prayer	O
book	O
down	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlord	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
,	O
That	O
is	O
my	O
prayer-book	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fryer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
but	O
once	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Compasses	O
in	O
Silver	O
Street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
stay	O
'd	O
from	O
five	O
o'clock	O
till	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
.	O
Brown	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
distant	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
at	O
eight	O
overnight	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
351	O
,	O
352	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
&	O
Richard	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
100	O
lb	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Longstaff	I-pers
,	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
Aug.	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
353	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Knott	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
worstead	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
and	O
woollen	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
16	O
.	O
||	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
at	O
haymaking	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Page	O
,	O
on	O
Finchley-Common	B-place
,	O
so	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
cloaths	O
and	O
money	O
,	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
loft	O
,	O
hanging	O
upon	O
a	O
peg	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
we	O
went	O
all	O
together	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
field	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
quitted	O
the	O
field	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
son	O
happening	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
lost	O
,	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
pursued	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
her	O
at	O
Mims	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
the	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
(	O
the	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
gown	O
(	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
)	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
under	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
for	O
herself	O
?	O
S.	O
Thomas	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
money	O
or	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
rag	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
bag	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Page	I-pers
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Page	I-pers
his	O
son	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
account	O
as	O
above	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
the	O
constable	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
set	O
on	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
354	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Canney	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Benney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Hannah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Smart	I-pers
,	O
and	O
her	O
the	O
said	O
Hannah	O
did	O
ravish	O
and	O
carnally	O
know	O
,	O
against	O
her	O
will	O
,	O
Sept.	O
10	O
.	O
++	O
Hannah	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
subject	O
to	O
fits	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
was	O
seven-night	O
being	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
myself	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
H.	O
Smart	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Explain	O
what	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
being	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
H.	O
Smart	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
body	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
very	O
act	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
power	O
to	O
speak	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
spoke	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
my	O
body	O
very	O
sore	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sensible	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
H.	O
Smart	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
there	O
did	O
.	O
My	O
two	O
children	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
girl	O
five	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
three	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
H.	O
Smart	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
come	O
from	O
work	O
.	O
A	O
girl	O
that	O
sells	O
oisters	O
at	O
our	O
door	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
up	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
sit	O
in	O
my	O
chair	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
thing	O
was	O
transacted	O
in	O
an	O
elbow	O
chair	O
.	O
]	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
live	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
nor	O
he	O
in	O
mine	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
drink	O
together	O
?	O
H.	O
Smart	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
manner	O
of	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
good	O
night	O
or	O
good	O
morrow	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
very	O
subject	O
to	O
fits	O
?	O
H.	O
Smart	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
for	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
an	O
out-pensioner	O
at	O
Bartholomew	O
's	O
hospital	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
after	O
the	O
affair	O
happened	O
before	O
you	O
took	O
this	O
man	O
up	O
?	O
H.	O
Smart	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
made	O
my	O
complaint	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
any	O
body	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
?	O
H.	O
Smart	O
.	O
Nobody	O
but	O
the	O
woman	O
who	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
(	O
whom	O
I	O
told	O
of	O
it	O
aswsoon	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
)	O
and	O
one	O
Hannah	B-pers
Godier	I-pers
,	O
who	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
have	O
told	O
my	O
husband	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
mob	O
was	O
so	O
violent	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
torn	O
me	O
to	O
pieces	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
had	O
a	O
hard	O
piece	O
of	O
work	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
My	O
neighbours	O
are	O
all	O
Irish	O
people	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
country	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
so	O
violent	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
endeavour	O
'd	O
to	O
keep	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
fits	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
your	O
own	O
room	O
before	O
you	O
fell	O
into	O
your	O
fits	O
?	O
H.	O
Smart	O
.	O
I	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
fit	O
assoon	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
finding	O
myself	O
very	O
sick	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
this	O
man	O
ever	O
before	O
come	O
into	O
your	O
room	O
,	O
to	O
assist	O
you	O
when	O
in	O
fits	O
?	O
H.	O
Smart	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
name	O
that	O
sells	O
oisters	O
?	O
H.	O
Smart	O
.	O
Betty	B-pers
Billington	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
offer	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
you	O
some	O
money	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
him	O
?	O
H.	O
Smart	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
offer	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
him	O
about	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
,	O
nor	O
he	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
H.	O
Smart	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
he	O
is	O
65	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
these	O
fits	O
occasioned	O
by	O
drinking	O
strong	O
liquors	O
?	O
H.	O
Smart	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
nothing	O
but	O
small	O
beer	O
and	O
ale	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
husband	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
seven-night	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
the	O
usual	O
time	O
.	O
We	O
lay	O
by	O
at	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
wife	O
in	O
a	O
single	O
chair	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
dear	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
treated	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
the	O
rabbit	O
merchant	O
has	O
used	O
me	O
so	O
and	O
so	O
;	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
my	O
landlady	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
when	O
she	O
saw	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
from	O
above	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
below	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
help	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
stone	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
very	O
unwilling	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
he	O
went	O
willingly	O
enough	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
an	O
opportunity	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
after	O
your	O
landlady	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Smart	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
directly	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
child	O
of	O
five	O
years	O
old	O
tell	O
you	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Smart	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
she	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Smart	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
does	O
not	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Winington	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Smart	O
's	O
little	O
girl	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
her	O
mamma	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fit	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
girl	O
that	O
lives	O
backwards	O
,	O
of	O
eight	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
fit	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
two	O
arm	O
chair	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Canney	I-pers
also	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
help	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
desired	O
you	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
?	O
E.	O
Winington	O
.	O
My	O
landlady	O
.	O
She	O
struggled	O
and	O
he	O
held	O
her	O
arms	O
in	O
the	O
arm	O
chair	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
which	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
about	O
four	O
minutes	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
hold	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
too	O
strong	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
come	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
?	O
E.	O
Winington	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
complain	O
he	O
had	O
used	O
her	O
ill	O
?	O
E.	O
Winington	O
.	O
Yes	O
she	O
did	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
the	O
two	O
children	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
E.	O
Winington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
E.	O
Winington	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
torn	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
where	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
character	O
?	O
E.	O
Winington	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
esteem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
quiet	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
this	O
woman	O
use	O
to	O
drink	O
gin	O
?	O
E.	O
Winington	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
her	O
fuddled	O
?	O
E.	O
Winington	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
sometimes	O
pretty	O
near	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
she	O
was	O
so	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
E.	O
Winington	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
A	O
neighbour	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
herself	O
into	O
that	O
fit	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
fuddled	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
E.	O
Winington	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
duskish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
known	O
this	O
woman	O
have	O
fits	O
before	O
?	O
E.	O
Winington	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
them	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
man	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
?	O
E.	O
Winington	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Hannah	B-pers
Godier	I-pers
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Go	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
subject	O
to	O
fits	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
myself	O
,	O
left	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
flung	O
into	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
355	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Taber	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Taber	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
the	B-place
Fox	I-place
and	I-place
Anchor	I-place
in	I-place
Charterhouse-Lane	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
parlour	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
that	O
I	O
draw	O
'd	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
for	O
?	O
My	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
'd	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
if	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
not	O
stoln	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
maid	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
draw	O
in	O
a	O
tankard	O
to	O
two	O
strangers	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
one	O
(	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
)	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
believed	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Missing	O
my	O
tankard	O
,	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
Publick-Advertiser	O
,	O
two	O
guineas	O
reward	O
;	O
but	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
About	O
seven	O
weeks	O
ago	O
there	O
came	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
tankard	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
found	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
They	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
describe	O
the	O
men	O
I	O
suspected	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
described	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
held	O
down	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
committed	O
by	O
my	O
Lord-mayor	O
for	O
picking	O
a	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
girl	O
going	O
along	O
to	O
be	O
exceeding	O
careful	O
who	O
she	O
pitch	O
'd	O
upon	O
.	O
Going	O
in	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
twopenny	O
to	O
put	O
into	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
and	O
the	O
tankard	O
were	O
gone	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
desired	O
he	O
'd	O
put	O
his	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
occasion	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
positive	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
she	O
swore	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
All	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
time	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
their	O
reckoning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
not	O
there	O
other	O
people	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Taber	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
five	O
people	O
from	O
Buckinghamshire	O
that	O
deal	O
in	O
lace	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
Kelsey	O
,	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
tried	O
here	O
yesterday	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Bagley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
several	O
times	O
come	O
into	O
master	O
Taber	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
always	O
draw	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
draw	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
at	O
past	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
over	O
against	O
each	O
other	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
lace	O
men	O
at	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
soldier	O
sat	O
opposite	O
to	O
them	O
(	O
they	O
were	O
sitting	O
near	O
the	O
street	O
window	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
sent	O
me	O
down	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
twopenny	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
gone	O
,	O
tankard	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Kelsey	O
?	O
A.	O
Bagley	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
his	O
place	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
this	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
beating	O
hemp	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
as	O
well	O
in	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
as	O
in	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
did	O
you	O
pitch	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
A.	O
Bagley	O
.	O
I	O
pitch	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
immediately	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
coat	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
A.	O
Bagley	O
.	O
The	O
very	O
same	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
The	O
coat	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
since	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
say	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
stoln	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
girl	O
pitch	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
and	O
taylor	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
coat	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
,	O
I	O
sold	O
him	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
A.	O
Bagley	O
.	O
Of	O
what	O
colour	O
was	O
the	O
coat	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
?	O
A.	O
Bagley	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
white	O
.	O
Such	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
Buckland	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
coat	O
of	O
the	O
colour	O
of	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
fellow	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Trusty	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
needle	O
maker	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Trusty	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
twenty	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
fellow	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
fellow	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Macklin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
fourteen	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
sober	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
serv	O
'd	O
my	O
time	O
to	O
his	O
father	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
356	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Cofield	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Colfield	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Scotfield	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
tallow	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
September	O
9	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
357	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Gibons	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
garters	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Griffice	I-pers
,	O
September	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
358	O
,	O
359	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Reader	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Port	I-pers
;	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
;	O
&	O
c.	O
August	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Briggs	O
guilty	O
,	O
Reader	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
360	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Conway	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
stuff	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worstead	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
holland	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
August	O
9	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
both	O
lodged	O
in	O
one	O
room	O
,	O
in	O
two	O
separate	O
beds	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
August	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
and	O
my	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
my	O
gown	O
on	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
now	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Peate	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
'd	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
'd	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
(	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
cloaths	O
shop	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
five	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
for	O
twenty-two	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
holland	O
apron	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
have	O
since	O
sold	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
white	O
holland	O
apron	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
two	O
seams	O
that	O
are	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
361	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wilkerson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Freemantle	I-pers
,	O
September	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Freemantle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
a	O
place	O
call	O
'd	O
Hardly-Row	O
,	O
in	O
Hampshire	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
at	O
Chessey	O
in	O
Surry	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Field	O
's	O
warehouse	O
there	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dowling	I-pers
.	O
A	O
coachman	O
came	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
stoln	O
some	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
Twickenham	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
two	O
great	O
coats	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
upon	O
him	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
boots	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
put	O
.	O
Dowling	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
The	O
boots	O
and	O
one	O
coat	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Freemantle	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
great	O
coat	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
warehouse	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
362	O
,	O
363	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
brass	O
housings	O
,	O
with	O
leather	O
pads	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Slingsby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Daniel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Slingsly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hackney	O
coachman	O
.	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
or	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
my	O
stable	O
door	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
Leather-Lane	B-place
;	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
six	O
harnesses	O
five	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
cut	O
and	O
mangled	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
brass	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
desired	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
send	O
my	O
man	O
about	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
harness	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
find	O
them	O
that	O
were	O
lost	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
brass	O
found	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
brass	O
founder	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
she	O
carried	O
brass	O
to	O
sell	O
for	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
divers	O
times	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
Keeling	O
,	O
and	O
Davis	O
was	O
fetch	O
'd	O
thither	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
brass	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
brass	O
founder	O
.	O
Between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
last	O
Davis	O
's	O
apprentice	O
came	O
with	O
some	O
brass	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Wright	O
.	O
He	O
keeps	O
an	O
old	O
iron	O
shop	O
within	O
three	O
doors	O
of	O
Mutton-Lane	O
.	O
It	O
weigh	O
'd	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
nine	O
shillings	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
nine	O
pence	O
per	O
pound	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
observed	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
it	O
look	O
uncommonly	O
black	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
burn	O
off	O
the	O
leather	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
continue	O
in	O
the	O
scale	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
would	O
come	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
such	O
brass	O
brought	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
enquire	O
.	O
Wright	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
a	O
housing	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
judged	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
they	O
inquired	O
about	O
.	O
Upon	O
comparing	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
their	O
master	O
.	O
I	O
readily	O
granted	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
at	O
justice	O
Keeling	O
's	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
could	O
lend	O
her	O
[	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
his	O
deferioing	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
.	O
]	O
There	O
she	O
correcyed	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
and	O
a	O
dram	O
for	O
selling	O
it	O
to	O
Davis	O
.	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
nine	O
shillings	O
;	O
but	O
then	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
eight	O
pounds	O
of	O
that	O
brass	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
parcel	O
being	O
old	O
because	O
and	O
other	O
sort	O
of	O
stuff	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clerk	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
beltman	O
and	O
serve	O
as	O
constable	O
at	O
Clerkenwell	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
the	O
brass	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
housing	O
and	O
leather	O
pad	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
compared	O
and	O
agreed	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
not	O
half	O
the	O
brass	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Jones	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
one	O
Higgs	O
a	O
carpenter	O
that	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Mosses	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
after	O
that	O
Higgs	O
a	O
carpenter	O
(	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
)	O
into	O
Black-Boy	O
Alley	O
.	O
We	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Davis	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
brass	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
boy	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
four-shillings	O
and	O
six-pence	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
boy	O
buy	O
some	O
brass	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
It	O
weigh	O
'd	O
eight	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
her	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Davis	O
call	O
'd	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mangleman	I-pers
and	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Croaker	I-pers
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
364.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mainstone	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
goods	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
value	O
above	O
40	O
s.	O
No	O
prosecutor	O
appearing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
365	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hole	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
rev	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heming	I-pers
,	O
clerk	O
,	O
one	O
cambrick	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shudal	I-pers
,	O
July	O
18	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Shudal	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holloway-Street	O
,	O
St.	O
Clement-Danes	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
robe	O
maker	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
under	O
a	O
general	O
repair	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
removed	O
our	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
the	O
workman	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
we	O
could	O
.	O
The	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
,	O
the	O
breeches	O
lay	O
open	O
in	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Shudal	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
them	O
all	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
hired	O
herself	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
as	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
our	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
immediately	O
convinced	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
base	O
woman	O
.	O
At	O
her	O
first	O
coming	O
she	O
would	O
stay	O
a	O
great	O
length	O
of	O
time	O
in	O
going	O
of	O
errands	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
other	O
ill	O
behaviour	O
I	O
turned	O
her	O
away	O
at	O
three	O
weeks	O
end	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
inquired	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
person	O
told	O
me	O
who	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Bowen	O
.	O
Upon	O
which	O
Bowen	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
breeches	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
which	O
she	O
,	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
owned	O
also	O
.	O
She	O
also	O
confessed	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
her	O
key	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Jenkins	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
)	O
who	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
box	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
her	O
box	O
?	O
Shudal	O
.	O
In	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
(	O
the	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Fleetditch	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
on	O
and	O
off	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
stole	O
the	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Bowen	O
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
her	O
keys	O
to	O
look	O
over	O
er	O
things	O
,	O
imagining	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
something	O
of	O
mine	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
searching	O
her	O
box	O
these	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
her	O
behaviour	O
while	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Jenkins	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
her	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
things	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
surprised	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
turn	O
out	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Manchester	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
)	O
these	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
Bowen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
They	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
reverend	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Heming	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
366	O
,	O
367	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
King	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Collings	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Haste	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Aug.	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Haste	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Bethnal-Green	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
their	O
company	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
hat	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
)	O
and	O
a	O
plain	O
gold	O
ring	O
from	O
off	O
my	O
finger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
your	O
hat	O
or	O
ring	O
since	O
?	O
Hasle	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
hands	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
parish	O
There	O
being	O
a	O
great	O
outcry	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
August	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Collings	O
for	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
King	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
some	O
other	O
person	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
persons	O
that	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
they	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
hat	O
and	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
both	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
more	O
than	O
once	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
the	O
persons	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoners	O
say	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
Collings	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
King	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
hat	O
found	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
ring	O
neither	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
King	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
hat	O
and	O
ring	O
were	O
then	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whose	O
property	O
these	O
are	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
under	O
or	O
over	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
August	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
Collings	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
