TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
8th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
DECEMBER	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Thirtieth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
I.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1757	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
First	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
MARSHE	O
DICKINSON	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
J.ROBINSON	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Lion	O
,	O
in	O
Ludgate-Street	O
,	O
1756	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
,	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
MARSHE	O
DICKINSON	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Michael	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
++	O
and	O
other	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Characters	O
*	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
,	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bradury	I-pers
William	B-pers
Yersley	I-pers
James	B-pers
Tame	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Torrent	I-pers
John	B-pers
Yenn	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Howes	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Collet	I-pers
James	B-pers
Sangster	I-pers
Moses	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Green	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Graves	I-pers
James	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
John	B-pers
Wesley	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Wilbraham	I-pers
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
John	B-pers
Griffue	I-pers
George	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
James	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
John	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
1	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hempen	O
sack	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
and	O
four	O
bushels	O
of	O
salt	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
November	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Queen-Hith	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
November	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
bushels	O
of	O
salt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
partner	O
?	O
Ward	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Matthew	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
employed	O
this	O
man	O
to	O
carry	O
five	O
,	O
sacks	O
up	O
from	O
my	O
lighter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ward	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
He	O
carried	O
four	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
took	O
money	O
for	O
five	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Bear	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Garlick-Hill	O
.	O
This	O
sack	O
being	O
missing	O
I	O
by	O
inquiring	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
salt	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
bushels	O
were	O
in	O
that	O
sack	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
Four	O
bushels	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
trust	O
him	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
five	O
sacks	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Bulls	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Brown-Bear	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Garlick-Hill	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
sack	O
of	O
salt	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
set	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
room	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
might	O
carry	O
it	O
backwards	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
I	O
'd	O
let	O
it	O
be	O
there	O
till	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
again	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
empty	O
sack	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
sack	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
subject	O
to	O
have	O
falling	O
fits	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
carried	O
up	O
this	O
salt	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
2.	O
John	B-pers
Phelps	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Griffin	I-pers
,	O
one	O
horse-whip	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
laced	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
honourable	O
Henry	B-pers
Temple	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
November	O
14	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
3	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Alexander	B-pers
Connell	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pints	O
of	O
porter	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
d.	O
and	O
12	O
wooden	O
pipe	O
staves	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Valentine	B-pers
Grimstead	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
Nov.	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
James	O
Bickley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
store	O
cellars	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
man	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
of	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
near	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
head	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
out	O
a	O
glass	O
bottle	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
again	O
with	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
some	O
pipe	O
staves	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
acquaint	O
the	O
next	O
witness	O
Francis	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
brewhouse	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
Bickley	O
.	O
Their	O
names	O
are	O
Coaker	O
and	O
Grimstead	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
partners	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
other	O
evidence	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
store	O
cellar	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Coaker	O
and	O
Grimstead	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
with	O
some	O
beer	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
drinking	O
.	O
I	O
talked	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
believ	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
beer	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
also	O
some	O
pipe	O
staves	O
,	O
my	O
masters	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Coaker	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
this	O
cellar	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
beer	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
4	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Franklin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
Common-prayer-book	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burgess	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	O
Burgess	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Kensington	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
She	O
asked	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
dish	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
tea	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
and	O
my	O
Common-prayer-book	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
E.	O
Burgess	O
.	O
By	O
inquiring	O
about	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
ring	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
The	O
book	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
vault	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
at	O
Knightsbridge	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
ring	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
?	O
E.	O
Burgess	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
ring	O
before	O
you	O
lost	O
it	O
?	O
E.	O
Burgess	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Leen	I-pers
.	O
(	O
He	O
looks	O
on	O
the	O
ring	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledg	O
'd	O
this	O
ring	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
her	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Leen	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
8	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Leen	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hide-Park	O
Corner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nevel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
woman	O
that	O
found	O
the	O
prayer	O
book	O
in	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
being	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
threw	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
upon	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tea	O
chest	O
;	O
this	O
she	O
also	O
confessed	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
farther	O
;	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
'd	O
call	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
she	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
'd	O
sit	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
near	O
noon	O
,	O
drinking	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
'd	O
have	O
a	O
dish	O
of	O
tea	O
;	O
she	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
staying	O
till	O
her	O
husband	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
jealous	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
things	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
spent	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
a	O
crown	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
this	O
ring	O
to	O
pawn	O
:	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
that	O
;	O
since	O
this	O
she	O
has	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
revenged	O
of	O
me	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
eleven	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
neglected	O
letting	O
her	O
friends	O
know	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
or	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
had	O
many	O
friends	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
5	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Jolley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
Charles	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
and	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
and	O
20	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Oct.	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
Charles	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Godde	O
,	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
sadler	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
on	O
horseback	O
over	O
Hounslow-Heath	B-place
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
between	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Between	O
the	O
powder	O
mills	O
and	O
the	O
eleven	O
mile	O
stone	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
coming	O
towards	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
north	O
side	O
the	O
road	O
coming	O
towards	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
south	O
going	O
from	O
London	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
tied	O
about	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
which	O
hung	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
his	O
cheek	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
cover	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
a	O
perfect	O
view	O
of	O
his	O
face	O
?	O
Dyer	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
clear	O
afternoon	O
,	O
as	O
bright	O
as	O
most	O
days	O
in	O
that	O
season	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
almost	O
opposite	O
me	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
that	O
almost	O
cover	O
'd	O
all	O
his	O
other	O
apparel	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
it	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
what	O
little	O
matter	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
twenty	O
pence	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
under	O
two	O
shillings	O
.	O
He	O
palm	O
'd	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
all	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
little	O
;	O
Then	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
inclined	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
After	O
some	O
time	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
your	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
called	O
his	O
maker	O
to	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
it	O
he	O
'd	O
blow	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
then	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
parted	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
towards	O
Belsont	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
towards	O
Hounslow	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
rode	O
along	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
Dyer	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
after	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
New-gaol	O
,	O
Surry	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
immediately	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
Dyer	O
.	O
Justice	O
Clark	O
had	O
advertised	O
a	O
person	O
taken	O
with	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
hint	O
given	O
you	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
when	O
you	O
came	O
there	O
?	O
Dyer	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
charge	O
him	O
there	O
?	O
Dyer	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
upon	O
him	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Wimbleton	O
with	O
a	O
periwig	O
.	O
Coming	O
home	O
,	O
about	O
forty	O
yards	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
Wandsworth	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
gentleman	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
myself	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
footpad	O
on	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
now	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
another	O
robbery	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
secured	O
?	O
Ware	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
one	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Look	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
watch	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
on	O
Hounslow	O
Heath	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Groom	I-pers
.	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
one	O
looking	O
glass	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
sheet	O
and	O
two	O
curtains	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Matth.ew	B-pers
Frankland	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
October	O
10	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
7	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Rickins	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Mastern	I-pers
,	O
November	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
Joseph	O
Mastern	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
but	O
remember	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
before	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
man	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
mug	O
.	O
I	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
convinced	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Mastern	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
November	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
justly	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Mastern	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
an	O
intire-stranger	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
any	O
time	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Mastern	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
much	O
like	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Spires	I-pers
.	O
This	O
pint	O
mug	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pledge	O
,	O
on	O
or	O
about	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
?	O
Spires	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
that	O
woman	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
this	O
is	O
she	O
.	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
with	O
that	O
woman	O
?	O
Spires	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
constable	O
?	O
Spires	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
[	O
As	O
neither	O
of	O
the	O
evidences	O
could	O
identify	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
]	O
8	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mungo	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
22	O
.	O
*	O
Mungo	O
Barnes	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Great	O
Peter-Street	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
hat	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
he	O
left	O
his	O
own	O
hat	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
mine	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
hat	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Since	O
that	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
for	O
desertion	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
some	O
goods	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
.	O
They	O
mentioned	O
two	O
shirts	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
shirt	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
Mungo	O
Barnes	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
son	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
her	O
son	O
;	O
but	O
never	O
said	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
these	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
out	O
Ruth	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
demand	O
the	O
hat	O
.	O
He	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
'd	O
come	O
again	O
for	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
hat	O
?	O
R.	O
Barnes	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
hat	O
my	O
husband	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
shew	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
hat	O
you	O
shew	O
'd	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Wilkins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
confined	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Savoy	O
as	O
a	O
deserter	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
this	O
Wilkin	O
s.	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Barnes	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
some	O
difficulty	O
Wilkins	O
's	O
wife	O
did	O
shew	O
it	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
gave	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
particular	O
orders	O
not	O
to	O
deliver	O
the	O
hat	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
without	O
paying	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
.	O
Said	O
Wilkins	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
brought	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Said	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
something	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
warrant	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
the	O
constable	O
a	O
punch	O
on	O
the	O
breast	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
him	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
while	O
he	O
ran	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
concealed	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
although	O
he	O
had	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
just	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mungo	O
Barnes	O
's	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
measure	O
of	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
help	O
them	O
to	O
remove	O
some	O
goods	O
;	O
they	O
got	O
fuddled	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
the	O
hat	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
desertion	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
sent	O
any	O
person	O
for	O
the	O
hat	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
9	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Pallister	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
quart	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
September	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
George	O
Pratt	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
quart	O
mug	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
so	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Pratt	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
White-Hart	B-place
Yard	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Pratt	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
worth	O
about	O
six	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
since	O
?	O
Pratt	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
when	O
one	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
two	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
man	O
staying	O
backwards	O
so	O
long	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
looking	O
into	O
my	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
seemingly	O
doing	O
up	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
every	O
thing	O
safe	O
in	O
my	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
either	O
of	O
these	O
three	O
men	O
?	O
M.	O
Pratt	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
two	O
that	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
had	O
drawn	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
quart	O
mug	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
they	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
M.	O
Pratt	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
box	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
He	O
drank	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
'd	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
their	O
tankard	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
not	O
hold	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
some	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
the	O
pint	O
pot	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
to	O
tap	O
a	O
butt	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
About	O
what	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
M.	O
Pratt	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
In	O
going	O
out	O
in	O
haste	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
left	O
this	O
hat	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
)	O
I	O
stumbled	O
over	O
it	O
as	O
it	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
doors	O
.	O
I	O
immediately	O
saw	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
tankard	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
M.	O
Pratt	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
advertisement	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
any	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
might	O
apply	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
(	O
that	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
)	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
answer	O
?	O
M.	O
Pratt	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
ask	O
?	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
tap	O
the	O
vessel	O
?	O
M.	O
Pratt	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
gone	O
ten	O
minutes	O
before	O
they	O
and	O
the	O
mug	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mistrust	O
of	O
them	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
by	O
hearing	O
them	O
say	O
as	O
I	O
passed	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
``	O
If	O
we	O
a	O
n't	O
him	O
to-night	O
we	O
'll	O
have	O
him	O
another	O
night	O
;	O
''	O
from	O
which	O
I	O
imagined	O
they	O
were	O
three	O
baliffs	O
,	O
or	O
somebody	O
no	O
better	O
than	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
man	O
ever	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
before	O
?	O
M.	O
Pratt	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
pay	O
their	O
reckoning	O
?	O
M.	O
Pratt	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
irons	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
?	O
M.	O
Pratt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
pointed	O
out	O
to	O
you	O
as	O
a	O
person	O
suspected	O
?	O
M.	O
Pratt	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
M.	O
Pratt	O
.	O
Of	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
face	O
and	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
point	O
him	O
out	O
?	O
M.	O
Pratt	O
.	O
He	O
pointed	O
me	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
first	O
question	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
answer	O
?	O
M.	O
Pratt	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
again	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
declare	O
that	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
M.	O
Pratt	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Celina	B-pers
Mowet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
(	O
looking	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
boxes	O
drinking	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
silver	O
mug	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Be	O
careful	O
,	O
look	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
consider	O
.	O
C.	O
Mowet	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
two	O
tankards	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
almost	O
every	O
moment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
mug	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
C.	O
Mowet	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
quart	O
silver	O
mug	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
go	O
away	O
?	O
C.	O
Mowet	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
being	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
helping	O
to	O
tap	O
a	O
butt	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
We	O
made	O
what	O
haste	O
we	O
could	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
afraid	O
something	O
would	O
be	O
lost	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
ill	O
a	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dress	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
C.	O
Mowet	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
blue	O
futcout	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
they	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
C.	O
Mowet	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
exactly	O
know	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
after	O
candles	O
were	O
lighted	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
?	O
C.	O
Mowet	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
at	O
first	O
sight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
so	O
then	O
?	O
C.	O
Mowet	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
one	O
time	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
men	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
C.	O
Mowet	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
ship	O
which	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
here	O
in	O
irons	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
of	O
tankards	O
.	O
My	O
irons	O
made	O
me	O
remarkable	O
to	O
be	O
known	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
it	O
cost	O
him	O
a	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
he	O
'd	O
have	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
He	O
ordered	O
every	O
person	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
)	O
into	O
his	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
open	O
to	O
them	O
a	O
great	O
scene	O
of	O
villainy	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
certainly	O
be	O
hanged	O
,	O
unless	O
I	O
discovered	O
my	O
accomplices	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
same	O
name	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Aaron	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Aaron	O
,	O
Oct.	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
Aaron	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
a	O
man	O
well	O
dressed	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
scollop	O
'd	O
laced	O
hat	O
on	O
,	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
look	O
'd	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
company	O
.	O
He	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
to	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
light	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Young	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Checquer	O
,	O
in	O
Checquer-Court	B-place
,	I-place
Charing-Cross	I-place
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
my	O
servant	O
to	O
carry	O
in	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
with	O
my	O
tankard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
your	O
tankard	O
again	O
?	O
Young	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Young	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
that	O
man	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
man	O
described	O
by	O
those	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
tankard	O
advertised	O
.	O
Dorothea	B-pers
Young	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
house	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
speak	O
with	O
certainty	O
,	O
or	O
can	O
you	O
not	O
?	O
D.	O
Young	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
pen	O
,	O
ink	O
and	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
room	O
by	O
himself	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
way	O
of	O
making	O
an	O
escape	O
without	O
being	O
discovered	O
,	O
except	O
that	O
of	O
jumping	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
(	O
waiting	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
)	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
tankard	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
cost	O
me	O
nine	O
pounds	O
five	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
D.	O
Young	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
window	O
?	O
D.	O
Young	O
.	O
The	O
sash	O
was	O
quite	O
thrown	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
a	O
writing	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
D.	O
Young	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
wrote	O
two	O
lines	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
on	O
the	O
paper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
he	O
quitted	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
D.	O
Young	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
tankard	O
not	O
three	O
minutes	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Saul	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
one	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Saul	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
sight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
Saul	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
of	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
'd	O
please	O
to	O
have	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
lad	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
or	O
porter	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
which	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
lad	O
,	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
pen	O
,	O
ink	O
and	O
sheet	O
of	O
paper	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
one	O
Williamson	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
ask	O
for	O
one	O
Williams	O
,	O
shew	O
him	O
in	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
left	O
word	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
with	O
my	O
mistress	O
immediately	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
snuff	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
came	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
my	O
mistress	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
change	O
ready	O
against	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
beer	O
;	O
immediately	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
Joe	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
candle	O
burning	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
catch	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
see	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
sash	O
was	O
down	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Saul	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shutters	O
put	O
to	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
bolted	O
within	O
side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
tankard	O
last	O
?	O
Saul	O
.	O
The	O
tankard	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
him	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
snuff	O
the	O
candle	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
me	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
me	O
?	O
Saul	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
face	O
I	O
told	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
knew	O
his	O
face	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Hewit	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
parlour	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
saw	O
any	O
body	O
knock	O
at	O
that	O
window	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
back	O
,	O
seemingly	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
instead	O
of	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
directly	O
away	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
minded	O
to	O
have	O
got	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
easy	O
for	O
him	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Hewit	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
very	O
easy	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
None	O
of	O
these	O
people	O
ever	O
saw	O
me	O
before	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
;	O
even	O
that	O
Saul	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
positively	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
call	O
'd	O
them	O
all	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
their	O
knowledge	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Saul	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
positive	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
had	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
10	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
21	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
ditto	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wooley	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
Nov.	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
Mr.	O
Edlington	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
served	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
capacity	O
of	O
a	O
porter	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
we	O
had	O
much	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
his	O
fidelity	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
month	O
of	O
May	O
he	O
left	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wooley	O
,	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
refused	O
him	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
would	O
see	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
it	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
the	O
key	O
about	O
him	O
at	O
this	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
time	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
past	O
on	O
for	O
4	O
months	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wooley	O
was	O
disatisfied	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Lord-mayor	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
we	O
found	O
21	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
ones	O
,	O
and	O
sundry	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
our	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
are	O
your	O
partners	O
?	O
Edlington	O
.	O
Wooley	O
and	O
Hopkins	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
goods	O
?	O
Edlington	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
of	O
our	O
own	O
manufacturing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
box	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Edlington	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
about	O
the	O
begining	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wooley	O
's	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
given	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
break	O
a	O
box	O
open	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
said	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
these	O
stockings	O
(	O
producing	O
25	O
pair	O
)	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
muffatees	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
breeches	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-mayor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
Compton	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
his	O
master	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
never	O
do	O
the	O
like	O
again	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
ever	O
did	O
so	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
box	O
lying	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
some	O
body	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
spite	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
put	O
such	O
things	O
in	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Townsend	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
Mr.	O
Butler	O
wanting	O
a	O
footman	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
offer	O
himself	O
as	O
such	O
.	O
I	O
lik	O
'd	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
the	O
lad	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
hired	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
footman	O
(	O
all	O
but	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wooley	O
's	O
house	O
for	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
partners	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
if	O
he	O
thought	O
him	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
replied	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
hired	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
from	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
May	O
to	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
Nov	O
following	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
justly	O
fulfill	O
'd	O
his	O
trust	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
twice	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
change	O
bank	O
notes	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
30	O
l.	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
change	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
once	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
with	O
our	O
plate	O
to	O
the	O
silversmith	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
weigh	O
'd	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
plate	O
act	O
commenced	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
safe	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
we	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
we	O
lost	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
in	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
He	O
behav	O
'd	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
at	O
my	O
lord	O
Arran	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
plate	O
;	O
we	O
lost	O
nothing	O
there	O
.	O
John	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
my	O
lord	O
Arran	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
liquor	O
;	O
he	O
behav	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
sobriety	O
and	O
order	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
I	O
ever	O
heard	O
him	O
swear	O
an	O
oath	O
,	O
he	O
gain	O
'd	O
the	O
esteem	O
of	O
every	O
person	O
for	O
a	O
sober	O
diligent	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
no	O
body	O
,	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
either	O
heard	O
him	O
swear	O
or	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
11	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Burch	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fenchurch-street	B-place
,	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
knowing	O
it	O
worth	O
but	O
little	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
it	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
after	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Sherlock	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Sherlock	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
,	O
Betwixt	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Philpot-lane	O
,	O
making	O
water	O
:	O
going	O
on	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
prisoner	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
make	O
a	O
motion	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
draw	O
out	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
drop	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
which	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
accomplice	O
;	O
he	O
seeing	O
me	O
come	O
up	O
at	O
that	O
instant	O
,	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
off	O
with	O
some	O
precipitation	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
about	O
40	O
yards	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
collar	O
.	O
I	O
tap	O
'd	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
on	O
the	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
this	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
12	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Peck	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Bodeaur	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Lewis	B-pers
Bodeaur	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
1	O
and	O
2	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Guildhall	B-place
;	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
perceiv	O
'd	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
who	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
near	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
13	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Ware	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Dagg	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Dagg	O
More	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
St.	I-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
,	O
and	O
had	O
just	O
roll	O
'd	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
endeavoured	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
push	O
betwixt	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
wail	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
while	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
own	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
going	O
along	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
he	O
'd	O
never	O
do	O
so	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
the	O
two	O
initial	O
letters	O
to	O
my	O
name	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
D.	B-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
(	O
produc	O
'd	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
him	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
More	O
.	O
I	O
perceived	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
go	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
by	O
this	O
gentleman	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
picked	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
touch	O
'd	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Ambrose	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
business	O
?	O
Price	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
watch	O
way	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
High	O
Holbourn	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
half	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
he	O
behav	O
'd	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
sober	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
watch	O
gilder	O
by	O
trade	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Seybourn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
lad	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cordwainer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
lad	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Hebirt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
enameller	O
.	O
I	O
employ	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
learn	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
with	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Hebirt	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
very	O
good	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Welch	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Butcher	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Whay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
market	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
child	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
14	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
odd	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Mairis	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Parker	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
set	O
to	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Mairis	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Oct.	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
Parker	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
'd	O
measure	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
measur	O
'd	O
his	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
odd	O
shoes	O
,	O
made	O
of	O
callimanco	O
;	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
where	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
odd	O
shoes	O
(	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
fellows	O
to	O
cach	O
to	O
produce	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gibons	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
two	O
shoes	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
shoes	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
name	O
on	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Gibons	O
.	O
Parker	O
brought	O
these	O
shoes	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
come	O
alone	O
?	O
Gibons	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
the	O
shoes	O
had	O
been	O
made	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
made	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
laid	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
made	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
to	O
Simpson	O
,	O
Damnation	O
to	O
the	O
shoes	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
stopt	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
took	O
Simpson	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pursued	O
Parker	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
a	O
run	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
very	O
near	O
my	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Simpson	O
when	O
Parker	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Gibons	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
walking	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
,	O
within	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
yards	O
of	O
my	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
.	O
Gibons	O
the	O
Elder	O
.	O
Parker	O
brought	O
these	O
shoes	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
given	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
countryman	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
my	O
son	O
looked	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
another	O
man	O
join	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
parted	O
.	O
Parker	O
went	O
down	O
Little	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
and	O
Simpson	O
cross	O
'd	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
to	O
Simpson	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
that	O
gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
what	O
gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
gentleman	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Simpson	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
and	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
gentleman	O
;	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
character	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
son	O
had	O
taken	O
Parker	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Simpson	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
he	O
can	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
shoes	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
committed	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
out	O
by	O
his	O
name	O
being	O
on	O
the	O
shoes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Parker	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
this	O
shoemaker	O
's	O
shop	O
to	O
bespeak	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
pledge	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
an	O
execution	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
bid	O
me	O
stay	O
without	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
16	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
sell	O
fruit	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
;	O
we	O
let	O
her	O
lie	O
in	O
our	O
room	O
out	O
of	O
pity	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
lay	O
there	O
from	O
Tuesday	O
till	O
Saturday	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
time	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
Because	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
whence	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
them	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
governor	O
of	O
the	O
workhouse	O
of	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
parish	O
caused	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
lie	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
No	O
one	O
but	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
child	O
of	O
about	O
eleven	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
ring	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprehended	O
,	O
being	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
beadles	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
charge	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
some	O
questions	O
about	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
ring	O
from	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
spent	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
own	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
ring	O
and	O
money	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
ring	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
ring	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
ring	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
17	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Ilford	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
Nov.	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Elias	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
my	O
wife	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
partly	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
words	O
did	O
he	O
partly	O
own	O
it	O
?	O
Pugh	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
any	O
where	O
to	O
serve	O
his	O
majesty	O
,	O
by	O
land	O
or	O
sea	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
'd	O
release	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
He	O
equivocated	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
First	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Ilford	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
Ilford	O
was	O
his	O
real	O
or	O
his	O
travelling	O
name	O
;	O
but	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Shepherd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
wife	O
here	O
?	O
Pugh	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
very	O
ill.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
?	O
Pugh	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
information	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
present	O
when	O
your	O
wife	O
gave	O
you	O
this	O
account	O
?	O
Pugh	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
may	O
tell	O
the	O
court	O
what	O
your	O
wife	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Pugh	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
watches	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
that	O
would	O
come	O
pretty	O
cheap	O
.	O
She	O
seeing	O
him	O
look	O
like	O
a	O
countryman	O
,	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
large	O
one	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
too	O
big	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
a	O
less	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
coming	O
to	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
staircase	O
,	O
and	O
calling	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Are	O
you	O
coming	O
down	O
he	O
laid	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
this	O
watch	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
[	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
]	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
skream	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
She	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
person	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
on	O
my	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
wife	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
Pugh	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
mention	O
the	O
same	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
presence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Pugh	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Betsworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Pugh	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
it	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Coming	O
back	O
again	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
say	O
,	O
Are	O
you	O
coming	O
down	O
?	O
I	O
passed	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
minute	O
's	O
time	O
she	O
cry	O
'd	O
thief	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
about	O
ten	O
paces	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Madam	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
villain	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
for	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lesley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
evidence	O
Mrs.	O
Pugh	O
gave	O
there	O
?	O
Lesley	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
Lesley	O
.	O
He	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
he	O
might	O
go	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
design	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
very	O
well	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
know	O
a	O
watch	O
much	O
better	O
than	O
I	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
watch	O
case	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Q	O
to	O
Betsworth	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
in	O
but	O
one	O
case	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
?	O
Betsworth	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
18	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Plumber	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Adkinson	I-pers
.	O
Oct.	O
12	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Adkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
brecches	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chappel	I-pers
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
both	O
lodged	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
lock	O
'd	O
my	O
room	O
door	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
by	O
Mr	O
Doleman	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Doleman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale-shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
this	O
coat	O
to	O
sale	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
much	O
more	O
than	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
see	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
led	O
me	O
about	O
to	O
many	O
places	O
:	O
First	O
to	O
Charterhouse	O
Square	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
into	O
Oxford	O
Market	O
.	O
There	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
drop	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
known	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Piper	I-pers
lived	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
over	O
against	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
.	O
She	O
desired	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
coat	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
black	O
eye	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
go	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
stop	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Doleman	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Doleman	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
talk	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
having	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Piper	I-pers
?	O
Doleman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
she	O
said	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Piper	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
19	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
.	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
November	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
victualler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Temple-Bar	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
and	O
seldom	O
missed	O
coming	O
every	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
being	O
Sunday	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
drew	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
.	O
He	O
drank	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
not	O
seeing	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
mug	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
drink	O
alone	O
,	O
or	O
in	O
company	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
no	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
sat	O
alone	O
at	O
a	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
might	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
mug	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
pay	O
for	O
his	O
beer	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
always	O
used	O
to	O
pay	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
always	O
.	O
I	O
made	O
inquiry	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
satisfaction	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
confess	O
this	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
tavern	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
also	O
he	O
had	O
crased	O
my	O
name	O
from	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
my	O
name	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
might	O
come	O
in	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
company	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
for	O
the	O
beer	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
might	O
there	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
There	O
might	O
be	O
half	O
a	O
score	O
or	O
a	O
dozen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
sit	O
near	O
him	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
sat	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
sat	O
opposite	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
two	O
yards	O
distance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
used	O
your	O
house	O
did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
regard	O
to	O
his	O
mind	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
something	O
odd	O
in	O
his	O
behaviour	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
think	O
he	O
behaved	O
oddly	O
sometimes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
owing	O
to	O
liquor	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
would	O
he	O
behave	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
call	O
oddly	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
very	O
odd	O
in	O
contradicting	O
people	O
,	O
or	O
so	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
at	O
all	O
other	O
times	O
pay	O
you	O
punctually	O
for	O
your	O
liquor	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Always	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Plumber	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
room	O
opposite	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
mug	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Plumber	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
hide	O
it	O
as	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
out	O
?	O
Plumber	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
gentleman-like	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
bar	O
from	O
the	O
common	O
room	O
you	O
were	O
drinking	O
in	O
?	O
Plumber	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
In	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
missed	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
inquire	O
after	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
publick	O
room	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
offer	O
at	O
all	O
to	O
hide	O
it	O
?	O
Plumber	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
mug	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
?	O
Plumber	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
within	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Plumber	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
or	O
since	O
,	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hastings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Charing-Cross	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
plate	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
buy	O
a	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Hastings	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
one	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
mug	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
erased	O
out	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
must	O
own	O
myself	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
beg	O
the	O
court	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
21	O
or	O
22	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
,	O
far	O
from	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
first	O
knew	O
him	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
rank	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
good	O
reputation	O
,	O
and	O
character	O
.	O
But	O
latterly	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
transactions	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
really	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
of	O
sound	O
mind	O
,	O
from	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
actions	O
of	O
his	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
mention	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apothecary	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
the	O
court	O
some	O
instances	O
wherein	O
you	O
have	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
of	O
sound	O
mind	O
.	O
Harris	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
have	O
came	O
to	O
talk	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
has	O
sometimes	O
threatened	O
to	O
destroy	O
himself	O
,	O
declaring	O
he	O
was	O
tired	O
of	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
argued	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
self-murder	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
tired	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
really	O
be	O
glad	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
convicted	O
for	O
any	O
capital	O
offence	O
,	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
When	O
there	O
has	O
been	O
any	O
thing	O
taken	O
out	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
informed	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
immediately	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
has	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
formerly	O
bred	O
to	O
a	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
on	O
his	O
estate	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
genteel	O
manner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Reeves	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
family	O
of	O
this	O
gentleman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
sometimes	O
thought	O
him	O
not	O
quite	O
in	O
his	O
right	O
mind	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
owing	O
to	O
liquor	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
no	O
liquor	O
at	O
all	O
those	O
days	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
informed	O
.	O
Several	O
times	O
his	O
discourse	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
gaol	O
?	O
Reeves	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
gaol	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
believe	O
him	O
right	O
in	O
his	O
mind	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
20	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Arthur	I-pers
Fauklin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
caps	O
and	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
.	O
Oct.	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
Sarah	O
Bayley	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
for	O
my	O
livelihood	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
does	O
Ann	B-pers
Fauklin	I-pers
.	O
She	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
rid	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
October	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
where	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
window	O
and	O
door	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
window	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
doing	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
gown	O
,	O
shift	O
,	O
caps	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
my	O
gown	O
and	O
shift	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
drop	O
'd	O
my	O
caps	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
carrying	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Charle	O
Crowson	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
delivered	O
the	O
gown	O
and	O
shift	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bayley	I-pers
in	O
my	O
sight	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
four	O
caps	O
,	O
and	O
promised	O
to	O
pay	O
two-shillings	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Crowson	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
One	O
Betty	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
brought	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	O
Bayley	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
21	O
,	O
22	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
and	O
Jane	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Charles	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
one	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
cuff	O
of	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
October	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
October	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
White-Lion	B-place
Street	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Cable-Street	I-place
,	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
women	O
standing	O
together	O
,	O
who	O
followed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
tied	O
over	O
my	O
breast	O
behind	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
tried	O
to	O
untie	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
my	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
took	O
off	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cuff	O
of	O
my	O
gown	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
three	O
all	O
struck	O
me	O
after	O
this	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
murder	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
cloaths	O
shop	O
door	O
open	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Jeshua	O
Lynch	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
in	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
Court	O
,	O
Church	O
Street	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
struck	O
me	O
three	O
time	O
after	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
I	O
met	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
standing	O
by	O
an	O
oyster	O
basket	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
the	O
officer	O
of	O
two	O
others	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
Davis	O
told	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
Jane	O
Harding	O
had	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
I	O
knew	O
she	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
struck	O
me	O
;	O
but	O
who	O
had	O
my	O
hat	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
demand	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
you	O
when	O
they	O
struck	O
you	O
?	O
E.	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
you	O
was	O
thus	O
used	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
Elizabeth	O
Davis	O
at	O
an	O
oyster	O
basket	O
afterwards	O
?	O
E.	O
Jones	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
five	O
yards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
you	O
was	O
robbed	O
was	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
E.	O
Jones	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
your	O
hat	O
again	O
?	O
E.	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeffs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
serve	O
a	O
warrant	O
in	O
Church-Street	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
and	O
Lynch	O
together	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
of	O
her	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cuff	O
of	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
.	O
We	O
turned	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
this	O
Davis	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
girl	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
oysters	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
Davis	O
was	O
one	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
made	O
off	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
stubborn	O
,	O
and	O
threaten	O
'd	O
she	O
would	O
stab	O
the	O
woman	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
gaol	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
more	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
hat	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
us	O
of	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
cleared	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
Davis	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
tossed	O
it	O
to	O
Harding	O
;	O
so	O
Harding	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Davis	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
with	O
another	O
young	O
woman	O
with	O
some	O
oysters	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
mob	O
about	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
put	O
our	O
basket	O
down	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
woman	O
[	O
meaning	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
]	O
without	O
either	O
hat	O
or	O
cap	O
on	O
.	O
She	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
hat	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Harding	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
23	O
,	O
24	O
,	O
25	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
four	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
tablecloths	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
four	O
napkins	O
,	O
two	O
towels	O
and	O
three	O
prints	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
rev	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stennett	I-pers
,	O
D.	O
D.	O
Dr.	O
Stennett	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
weeks	O
ago	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Warburton	O
,	O
two	O
strangers	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
inquired	O
whether	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
had	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
they	O
believed	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
had	O
been	O
sold	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
linen	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
pretend	O
to	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
are	O
three	O
prints	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
be	O
positive	O
to	O
.	O
(	O
Three	O
prints	O
of	O
the	O
duke	O
of	O
Marlborough	O
's	O
battles	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
I	O
know	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
these	O
prints	O
found	O
?	O
Dr.	O
Stennett	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
where	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Dr.	O
Stennett	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
Bath	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
left	O
in	O
trust	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Dr.	O
Stennett	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
goods	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stennett	O
.	O
Last	O
year	O
about	O
the	O
5th	O
or	O
6th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
Doctor	O
's	O
health	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bath	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Paul	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
in	O
my	O
service	O
then	O
;	O
we	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
whole	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
plate	O
and	O
other	O
particular	O
things	O
.	O
We	O
staid	O
longer	O
than	O
we	O
intended	O
,	O
for	O
going	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
in	O
Wales	O
we	O
were	O
detain	O
'd	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
home	O
till	O
the	O
begining	O
of	O
Oct	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
return	O
'd	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
by	O
herself	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
think	O
of	O
discharging	O
her	O
immediately	O
,	O
by	O
reason	O
of	O
the	O
extravagancy	O
of	O
her	O
bills	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Dr.	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
'd	O
keep	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
longer	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
long	O
before	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
little	O
linen	O
,	O
sheets	O
,	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
napkins	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
solicitous	O
,	O
and	O
inquir	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
I	O
suspected	O
my	O
own	O
memory	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
misplaced	O
things	O
,	O
rather	O
than	O
accuse	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
she	O
should	O
lose	O
her	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
missed	O
more	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
not	O
all	O
done	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
but	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
have	O
confessed	O
)	O
it	O
was	O
committed	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
out	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
what	O
was	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
linen	O
till	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
mark	O
'd	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Warburton	O
gave	O
us	O
the	O
first	O
intelligence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
missed	O
much	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
have	O
mentioned	O
nothing	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
but	O
what	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
(	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
linen	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
all	O
mark	O
'd	O
by	O
myself	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
sheet	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
parcel	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
Miss	O
Overal	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Tisey	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
an	O
under-petticoat	O
,	O
a	O
breakfast	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
towels	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
overlook	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
mark	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
own	O
,	O
but	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
mark	O
,	O
an	O
S	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
was	O
being	O
in	O
white	O
silk	O
they	O
had	O
not	O
observed	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
give	O
Mary	O
an	O
'	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stennett	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
character	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
dishonestly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
own	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stennett	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
own	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
that	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
words	O
did	O
she	O
own	O
first	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stennett	O
.	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
who	O
took	O
these	O
goods	O
out	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Stennett	O
's	O
house	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Field	O
did	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
said	O
woman	O
;	O
)	O
the	O
justice	O
said	O
who	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
.	O
Last	O
July	O
was	O
twelvemonth	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
the	O
elder	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
brought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
linen	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
for	O
a	O
friend	O
;	O
upon	O
inquiring	O
whose	O
property	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
she	O
hesitated	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
my	O
insisting	O
upon	O
knowing	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
Miss	O
Ann	B-pers
Overal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
her	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upwards	O
of	O
5	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
nursed	O
my	O
wife	O
in	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
lyings-in	O
;	O
during	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
suspecting	O
the	O
truth	O
of	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
purchased	O
the	O
linen	O
,	O
which	O
consisted	O
of	O
2	O
odd	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
night	O
shirt	O
and	O
dresser	O
cloth	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
16	O
shillings	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stennett	O
.	O
The	O
coarse	O
shirts	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Morris	O
.	O
In	O
Nov.	O
following	O
she	O
brought	O
some	O
more	O
linen	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
said	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
consisting	O
of	O
2	O
shirts	O
,	O
a	O
damask	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
damask	O
napkins	O
;	O
for	O
this	O
parcel	O
she	O
asked	O
more	O
than	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
give	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
price	O
was	O
set	O
upon	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
owner	O
.	O
She	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
after	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
person	O
was	O
contented	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
price	O
offer	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
22	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
so	O
I	O
paid	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
my	O
great	O
surprise	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
the	O
servant	O
maid	O
who	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
whom	O
all	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
were	O
acquainted	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
linen	O
I	O
had	O
purchased	O
was	O
stolen	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Stennett	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
name	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
Her	O
name	O
is	O
Rachael	B-pers
Atkerson	I-pers
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
inquire	O
of	O
Miss	O
Overal	O
,	O
who	O
declared	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
given	O
Field	O
any	O
such	O
things	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
waited	O
on	O
Dr.	O
Stennett	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
this	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
linen	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
sheet	O
and	O
shirt	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
bring	O
them	O
?	O
R.	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
parcel	O
she	O
brought	O
I	O
think	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Nov.	O
following	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
such	O
an	O
opinion	O
of	O
her	O
honesty	O
that	O
I	O
recommended	O
her	O
wherever	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Tisey	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
some	O
things	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
some	O
time	O
last	O
summer	O
was	O
12	O
months	O
,	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
the	O
exact	O
time	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
friend	O
's	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
that	O
wanted	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
them	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
judge	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
that	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
16	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
my	O
friend	O
valued	O
them	O
at	O
15	O
s.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
daughter	O
Ann	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
told	O
they	O
were	O
valued	O
at	O
15	O
s.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
dare	O
say	O
the	O
person	O
whose	O
they	O
were	O
would	O
not	O
stand	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
(	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
were	O
4	O
napkins	O
and	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
.	O
)	O
Rachael	B-pers
Atkerson	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
told	O
me	O
about	O
4	O
months	O
ago	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Field	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
advised	O
her	O
to	O
rob	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
discover	O
it	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
also	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
pictures	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Field	O
's	O
room	O
that	O
came	O
from	O
Dr.	O
Stennett	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
Mrs.	O
Field	O
's	O
daughter	O
where	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
bought	O
in	O
Moorfields	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stennett	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
these	O
pictures	O
being	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Field	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
3	O
pictures	O
in	O
the	O
lodgings	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
by	O
Rachael	B-pers
Atkerson	I-pers
that	O
they	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Doctor	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Atkerson	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prints	O
again	O
?	O
R.	O
Atkerson	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
these	O
pictures	O
in	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
's	O
room	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Overal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
purchased	O
3	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
,	O
in	O
July	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
A.	O
Overal	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
30	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
lady	O
's	O
that	O
had	O
more	O
than	O
she	O
had	O
occasion	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Stennett	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Field	I-pers
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
one	O
bundle	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Sarah	B-pers
Field	I-pers
own	O
that	O
.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
some	O
things	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
them	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Field	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
dish	O
of	O
tea	O
with	O
her	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
a	O
bundle	O
and	O
carry	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
linen	O
for	O
my	O
mother	O
to	O
mend	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
once	O
to	O
our	O
room	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
outside	O
was	O
an	O
under-petticoat	O
.	O
For	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Overal	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
some	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Overal	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Overal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
at	O
St.	O
Ives	O
,	O
in	O
Huntingtonshire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Overal	O
.	O
Her	O
character	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Thebolds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
and	O
her	O
friends	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
For	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Warburton	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
nursed	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
lying-in	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
exceeding	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
her	O
?	O
A.	O
Warburton	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Elpingstone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
about	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
M.	O
Elpingstone	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
Mrs.	O
Stennett	O
.	O
I	O
beg	O
leave	O
to	O
mention	O
the	O
old	O
woman	O
sold	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
linen	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Warburton	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
she	O
sold	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Morris	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Miss	O
Overal	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Shewsmith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
known	O
Mary	O
Field	O
by	O
sight	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
nursed	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
good	O
nurse	O
.	O
I	O
trusted	O
her	O
where	O
is	O
seldom	O
less	O
than	O
forty	O
or	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
worth	O
of	O
plate	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
nothing	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Shewsmith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
,	O
said	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
this	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Field	I-pers
guilty	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Field	I-pers
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Paul	O
:	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Field	O
:	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
26.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Quince	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
recognizance	O
order	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Arthur	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
brass	O
pot-lid	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
copper	O
stew-pan	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
27	O
.8	O
William	O
Clark	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
November	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
a	O
pot-lid	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
stew-pan	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
witness	O
here	O
that	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
pot-lid	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Frankline	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
this	O
pot-lid	O
(	O
holding	O
one	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
stop	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
dust	O
hole	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Frankline	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
this	O
pot	O
lid	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
till	O
old	O
Michaelmas	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
about	O
three	O
week	O
after	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Deadley	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
brought	O
a	O
stew-pan	O
and	O
candlesticks	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
M.	O
Dindes	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
one	O
shilling	O
and	O
six-pence	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
he	O
sent	O
his	O
wife	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
William	O
Corner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
seven	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
wife	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
committed	O
him	O
for	O
farther	O
examination	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
stewpan	O
and	O
candlestick	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
there	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
28	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Moses	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
Nov.	O
8	O
.	O
William	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
mayor	O
's	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
Lord	O
mayor	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-House	B-place
,	O
having	O
been	O
at	O
Guild	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pick	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
thickest	O
of	O
the	O
mob	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
having	O
but	O
one	O
leg	O
could	O
not	O
follow	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
officer	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
described	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
others	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Martindale	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
evidence	O
pointed	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
pick	O
'd	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
four	O
others	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
should	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
deprive	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
market	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
street	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
nor	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
into	O
Cheapside	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
out	O
to	O
wipe	O
my	O
face	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
stop	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
they	O
not	O
stop	O
the	O
gentleman	O
as	O
we	O
I	O
as	O
me	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
prize	O
the	O
gentleman	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
would	O
have	O
got	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
You	O
ran	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
why	O
could	O
not	O
you	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
?	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
29.	O
Mary	B-pers
Meekham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
privately	O
stealing	O
4	O
s	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Whittle	I-pers
,	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
30	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Callaham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
s	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Vaughan	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Vaughan	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
below	O
in	O
my	O
cellar	O
on	O
the	O
2th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
cutting	O
some	O
wood	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
go	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
customer	O
;	O
I	O
hearkened	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
to	O
hear	O
if	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
behind	O
my	O
counter	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
.	O
He	O
held	O
up	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
``	O
Say	O
nothing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
half	O
''	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
half	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
he	O
put	O
5	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
till	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
lock	O
the	O
till	O
?	O
Vaughan	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
never	O
a	O
lock	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
ordered	O
a	O
neighbour	O
to	O
put	O
one	O
upon	O
it	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
till	O
drawn	O
out	O
?	O
Vaughan	O
.	O
The	O
till	O
was	O
standing	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
in	O
half-pence	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
laid	O
against	O
me	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
sea	O
.	O
His	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
live	O
near	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
31	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Golding	I-pers
stealing	O
4l	O
.	O
11s	O
.	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
Joseph	O
Harison	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Joseph	O
,	O
Nov.	O
17	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Harison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Royal	B-place
Oak	I-place
a	I-place
publick	I-place
house	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
A	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
crown	O
pieces	O
and	O
being	O
,	O
