TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
29th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
1st	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
MAY	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Twenty-ninth	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1756	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
SLINGSBY	O
BETHELL	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
ROBINSON	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Lion	O
,	O
in	O
Ludgate-Street	O
,	O
1756	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
SLINGSBY	O
BETHELL	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
My	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Ryder	O
,	O
*	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Clive	O
,	O
+	O
the	O
hon	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baron	O
Legge	O
,	O
||	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
++	O
Recorder	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
,	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Ayscough	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Rolfe	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
Philip	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
John	B-pers
Fowler	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Winterburn	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Shergold	I-pers
John	B-pers
Appleton	I-pers
William	B-pers
Battman	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
York	I-pers
Christopher	O
Norris	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
Steven	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Lees	I-pers
James	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
Jonathan	B-pers
Theobald	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Caigow	I-pers
Joshua	B-pers
Lascelles	I-pers
George	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
William	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
Patrick	B-pers
Lutterell	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
170	O
,	O
171	O
,	O
172	O
,	O
173	O
,	O
174	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Sawyer	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Dobins	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
gallons	O
of	O
strong	O
beer	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cumberledge	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
March	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Cumberledge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
store-cellar	O
in	O
Peter-Street	B-place
,	I-place
Westminster	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
quantity	O
of	O
beer	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
store-cellar	O
;	O
but	O
am	O
not	O
a	O
judge	O
how	O
much	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
my	O
butts	O
had	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
should	O
have	O
when	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
all	O
the	O
beer	O
in	O
that	O
cellar	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Cumberledge	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
cooper	O
to	O
Mess	O
.	O
Cousemaker	O
and	O
Co.	O
who	O
serve	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
with	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
starting	O
beer	O
in	O
this	O
store-cellar	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
several	O
of	O
the	O
butts	O
were	O
peg	O
'd	O
clandestinely	O
,	O
the	O
beer	O
was	O
much	O
of	O
it	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
started	O
two	O
barrels	O
of	O
beer	O
into	O
four	O
butts	O
,	O
to	O
fill	O
them	O
up	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
butts	O
had	O
been	O
peg	O
'd	O
again	O
afresh	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
broken	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
persons	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
of	O
the	O
beer	O
was	O
missing	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
of	O
two	O
butts	O
there	O
were	O
near	O
18	O
gallons	O
missing	O
in	O
two	O
days	O
time	O
;	O
which	O
were	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
butts	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
fill	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
had	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
Either	O
Mr.	O
Cumberledge	O
or	O
I	O
always	O
kept	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Describe	O
the	O
place	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cumberledge	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
board	O
broke	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
floor	O
over	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
in	O
its	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
fasten	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
some	O
nails	O
,	O
and	O
nail	O
'd	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
soldiers	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
[	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
all	O
soldiers	O
.	O
]	O
Edwards	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
way	O
the	O
liquor	O
went	O
till	O
the	O
evidence	O
here	O
(	O
another	O
soldier	O
)	O
confess	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
themselves	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soldier	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
quarter	O
'd	O
in	O
Dean-Street	O
,	O
Soho	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
money	O
quarters	O
;	O
so	O
William	O
Dobins	O
and	O
I	O
lodged	O
over	O
this	O
cellar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
February	O
when	O
the	O
board	O
over	O
the	O
cellar	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
exactly	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
it	O
open	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Rivers	O
,	O
Dobins	O
,	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
poker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
you	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
some	O
beer	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pull	O
'd	O
me	O
up	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
at	O
the	O
beer	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
tap	O
'd	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
butts	O
with	O
a	O
gimblet	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
it	O
off	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
brass	O
kettle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
did	O
you	O
deliver	O
it	O
to	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Dobins	I-pers
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
might	O
the	O
kettle	O
hold	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
It	O
held	O
about	O
a	O
full-pot	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
better	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
times	O
might	O
you	O
fill	O
it	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
down	O
after	O
that	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Rivers	O
and	O
Dobins	O
were	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
liquor	O
might	O
you	O
draw	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Much	O
about	O
the	O
same	O
quantity	O
as	O
we	O
did	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
board	O
loose	O
then	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
we	O
only	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Rivers	O
and	O
Dobins	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
drew	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
emptied	O
it	O
into	O
another	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
times	O
might	O
you	O
go	O
down	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
drew	O
near	O
the	O
same	O
quantity	O
cach	O
time	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
an	O
iron	O
pot	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
,	O
that	O
would	O
hold	O
about	O
five	O
quarts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
times	O
did	O
you	O
fill	O
that	O
in	O
a	O
night	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
We	O
fill	O
'd	O
it	O
twice	O
in	O
a	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
prisoners	O
with	O
you	O
there	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
of	O
them	O
drinking	O
with	O
us	O
there	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
all	O
saw	O
the	O
beer	O
deliver	O
'd	O
up	O
.	O
Burch	O
and	O
Yates	O
have	O
been	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
and	O
drawn	O
beer	O
themselves	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
did	O
they	O
go	O
down	O
.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Yates	O
went	O
down	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
Burch	O
might	O
go	O
down	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
times	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
deliver	O
'd	O
up	O
beer	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
we	O
laid	O
the	O
board	O
down	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
five	O
prisoners	O
and	O
you	O
all	O
there	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
never	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Sawyer	O
once	O
tried	O
to	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
drawn	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
drank	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
there	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
butt	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
drank	O
and	O
wasted	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Morgan	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
justice	O
Carkass	O
's	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
evidence	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
prisoners	O
(	O
except	O
Dobins	O
)	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
in	O
the	O
Infirmary	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
charged	O
with	O
robbing	O
the	O
cellar	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
drinking	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
stolen	O
.	O
Taylor	O
said	O
then	O
he	O
thought	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
butts	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
drank	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
it	O
could	O
be	O
by	O
six	O
men	O
in	O
five	O
weeks	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
wasted	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
swore	O
to	O
a	O
butt	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alixander	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
carried	O
Dobins	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
going	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
Yates	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Taylor	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
full-pot	O
of	O
beer	O
on	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
drank	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
three	O
fullpots	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
.	O
Rivers	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
quarters	O
and	O
received	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
Dobins	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
brought	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
Taylor	O
was	O
drunk	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
glad	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
us	O
to	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Sawyer	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
After	O
Dobins	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
lodge	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
more	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Burch	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Taylor	O
's	O
room	O
and	O
enquired	O
for	O
Dobins	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
in	O
a	O
cupboard	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
friend	O
with	O
him	O
overnight	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
dead	O
in	O
the	O
pot	O
.	O
Dobins	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
Taylor	O
.	O
Rivers	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
quarters	O
to	O
receive	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
my	O
return	O
Taylor	O
drunk	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
as	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
some	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
care	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
beer	O
by	O
the	O
bed-side	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
drank	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
All	O
five	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
175	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Girolamo	B-pers
Ferri	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
9	O
holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
I	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
1	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
15	O
diamonds	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
and	O
1	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
an	O
amethyst	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ricciarelli	I-pers
,	O
March	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
both	O
foreigners	O
,	O
an	O
interpeter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Ricciarelli	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
valet	O
de	O
chamber	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
shirts	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
exactly	O
how	O
many	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
lost	O
to	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
nine	O
?	O
Ricciarelli	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
15	O
diamonds	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
amethyst	O
ring	O
.	O
On	O
missing	O
the	O
rings	O
,	O
I	O
taxed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
charging	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
my	O
shirts	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
accordingly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
produced	O
them	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
rings	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
carried	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
the	O
prisoner	O
directions	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
shirts	O
?	O
Ricciarelli	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
order	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
once	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
louisd'ors	O
to	O
change	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
been	O
your	O
servant	O
?	O
Ricciarelli	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
four	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
bring	O
him	O
into	O
England	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Ricciarelli	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
from	O
Germany	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
deliver	O
your	O
rings	O
upon	O
your	O
asking	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Ricciarelli	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
or	O
no	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
intrusted	O
with	O
your	O
goods	O
?	O
Ricciarelli	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
with	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
a	O
reason	O
why	O
he	O
pawned	O
the	O
shirts	O
?	O
Ricciarelli	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
James	B-pers
Cammel	I-pers
?	O
Ricciarelli	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
my	O
footman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
have	O
not	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
pawned	O
things	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
by	O
your	O
orders	O
?	O
Ricciarelli	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
missed	O
the	O
shirts	O
before	O
you	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
you	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
before	O
you	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
?	O
Ricciarelli	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
look	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
things	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrache	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
servant	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
prisoner	O
myself	O
,	O
who	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
ten	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
shirts	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
his	O
taking	O
the	O
two	O
rings	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
first	O
singer	O
at	O
the	O
opera	O
.	O
Jr.	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
One	O
Dr.	O
Griffin	O
pledged	O
two	O
shirts	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
two	O
different	O
times	O
,	O
in	O
November	O
and	O
December	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
Dr.	O
Griffin	O
,	O
and	O
claimed	O
them	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parshal	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
8	O
shirts	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
these	O
shirts	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
because	O
my	O
master	O
owned	O
me	O
two	O
months	O
wages	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
bid	O
me	O
do	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
benefit	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cammel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
interpreter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
once	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
two	O
double	O
French	O
louisd'ors	O
,	O
desiring	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
get	O
two	O
guineas	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
they	O
worth	O
?	O
Cammel	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
worth	O
about	O
forty	O
shillings	O
each	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
pledge	O
or	O
change	O
the	O
louisd'ors	O
?	O
Cammel	O
.	O
I	O
pledg	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Crawford	O
.	O
The	O
prosecuter	O
has	O
sometimes	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
advance	O
money	O
on	O
his	O
note	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
due	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
has	O
wanted	O
money	O
generally	O
before	O
it	O
was	O
due	O
.	O
Lazarus	O
Bartovalle	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
2	O
double	O
French	O
louisd'ors	O
by	O
order	O
of	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
2	O
guineas	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
sometimes	O
lent	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
10	O
guineas	O
,	O
sometimes	O
6	O
,	O
and	O
often	O
paid	O
the	O
coach	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
often	O
wanted	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
always	O
paid	O
me	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
first	O
coming	O
to	O
England	O
;	O
his	O
master	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
him	O
like	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
but	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
companion	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
dined	O
with	O
his	O
master	O
and	O
him	O
together	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cap	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
fifty-four	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
dined	O
with	O
them	O
both	O
at	O
one	O
table	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
companion	O
and	O
not	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jackson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
12	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Willer	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
2	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Tilley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
trusted	O
him	O
alone	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
were	O
many	O
jewels	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
wrong	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
176	O
,	O
177	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Mores	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mores	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
weather	O
sheep	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
Jane	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
to	O
sheep	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hebert	I-pers
my	O
shepherd	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
live	O
about	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
butchers	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
mistrusting	O
them	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
mutton	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
that	O
my	O
shepherd	O
might	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
sheep	O
,	O
and	O
enquire	O
if	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
Uxbridge-market	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
follow	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
of	O
they	O
had	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
skin	O
there	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Uxbridge-market	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
skin	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
I.	O
S.	O
and	O
the	O
trade	O
mark	O
produced	O
with	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
Branded	O
.	O
)	O
They	O
both	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
they	O
both	O
confessed	O
stealing	O
of	O
the	O
sheep	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
field	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
carry	O
'd	O
it	O
home	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Mores	I-pers
.	O
What	O
is	O
my	O
character	O
as	O
to	O
honestly	O
?	O
J	O
.	O
Savage	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
drunken	O
idle	O
thief	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
much	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Hebert	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Arlington	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
her	O
shepherd	O
.	O
Her	O
sheep	O
generally	O
go	O
upon	O
Hounslow	O
beach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
sheep	O
has	O
she	O
?	O
Hebert	O
.	O
Eight-score	O
and	O
13	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
sheep	O
at	O
telling	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
sold	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
set	O
my	O
sold	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
them	O
as	O
they	O
went	O
through	O
a	O
gap	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
particular	O
sheep	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
mistress	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
I	O
'd	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
prisoners	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
mutton	O
.	O
Their	O
mother	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
I	O
found	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
kill	O
a	O
kog	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Uxbridge	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
at	O
John	B-pers
Hailey	I-pers
's	O
the	O
sellmonger	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
skin	O
?	O
Hebert	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
sheep	O
that	O
I	O
missed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
own	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
they	O
took	O
away	O
this	O
sheep	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
shoulder	O
of	O
the	O
mutton	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
This	O
skin	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
custody	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hailey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
High-Wickham	O
,	O
am	O
a	O
sellmonger	O
,	O
and	O
frequent	O
Uxbridge-market	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
dealings	O
with	O
the	O
prisoners	O
for	O
sheep	O
skins	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
7	O
sheep-skins	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mores	I-pers
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
seven	O
skins	O
you	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Hailey	O
.	O
It	O
might	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
buy	O
so	O
many	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
The	O
shepherd	O
here	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
into	O
my	O
cart	O
amongst	O
my	O
skins	O
,	O
or	O
if	O
any	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
town	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
skins	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
this	O
skin	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
the	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
1	O
.	O
S.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
skins	O
had	O
you	O
bought	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Hailey	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
fourscore	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mores	I-pers
.	O
What	O
is	O
my	O
character	O
as	O
to	O
honestly	O
?	O
Hailey	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
by	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Thomas	B-pers
Mores	I-pers
and	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Hailey	O
,	O
go	O
down	O
the	O
yard	O
together	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
seven	O
sheep	O
skins	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hatchet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoners	O
confess	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
sheep	O
sold	O
.	O
Thomas	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
sold	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
the	O
sheep	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
.	O
John	O
said	O
Thomas	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
there	O
together	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
agreed	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
sheep	O
.	O
Hebert	O
.	O
Thomas	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
sheep	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
John	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
two	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
together	O
or	O
separate	O
?	O
Hebert	O
.	O
Together	O
.	O
William	O
Petit	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoners	O
are	O
drunken	O
fellow	O
and	O
the	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
how	O
they	O
live	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
them	O
both	O
confess	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
that	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
sheep	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
skin	O
to	O
this	O
fellmonger	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
their	O
confession	O
before	O
Burkhead	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
owned	O
seperate	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
snatched	O
the	O
sheep	O
in	O
the	O
fold	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
and	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
the	O
skin	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hailey	O
,	O
the	O
skin	O
was	O
brought	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
skin	O
that	O
they	O
sold	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jarvis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoners	O
confess	O
that	O
they	O
stole	O
the	O
sheep	O
from	O
the	O
sold	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
and	O
kill	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
one	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
sold	O
the	O
skin	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hailey	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
skin	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
said	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
laid	O
to	O
their	O
charge	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
178	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
laced	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Davinant	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
March	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
Jeremiah	O
Davinant	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquire	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
'	O
had	O
been	O
pawn	O
'd	O
there	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
her	O
mother	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
saw	O
me	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
there	O
confessed	O
the	O
same	O
(	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
flat	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
?	O
Davinant	O
.	O
I	O
value	O
it	O
at	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
flat	O
iron	O
at	O
4	O
d.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Davinant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
missed	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
enquired	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
;	O
then	O
Mrs.	O
Roberts	O
,	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
's	O
mother	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
key	O
;	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
under	O
lock	O
and	O
key	O
;	O
so	O
a	O
woman	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
flat	O
iron	O
was	O
pawned	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Roberts	O
's	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
justice	O
Welch	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
saw	O
ply	O
husband	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
flat	O
iron	O
away	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
in	O
Catherine-Street	O
,	O
by	O
Leicester	O
fields	O
;	O
the	O
child	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
shilling	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
again	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
we	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
things	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
S.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
said	O
no	O
body	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
but	O
herself	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Tempest	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
iron	O
also	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Tempest	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodges	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
She	O
does	O
not	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
do	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
an	O
utter	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
but	O
for	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
father	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
girl	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
know	O
but	O
little	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
girl	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
Johnson	O
.	O
About	O
eleven	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
of	O
the	O
former	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
people	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
father	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
has	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
to	O
get	O
money	O
to	O
stop	O
proceedings	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
none	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
unkind	O
father	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
designed	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
served	O
a	O
warrant	O
on	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
and	O
had	O
superseded	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ever	O
ask	O
any	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Tompson	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
expence	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
name	O
what	O
sum	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
179.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ellis	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
woman	O
's	O
beaver	O
that	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
woman	O
's	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
one	O
woolen	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
January	O
6	O
*	O
Charles	O
Rogers	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milk-man	O
.	O
I	O
hired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
as	O
servant	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
I	O
filled	O
ber	O
belly	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
to	O
bed	O
to	O
my	O
children	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawned	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
for	O
what	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
the	O
apron	O
and	O
petticoat	O
on	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
last	O
February	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
through	O
Thames-Street	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
accused	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
saying	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
somewhere	O
in	O
Thieving-Lane	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
person	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
my	O
apron	O
and	O
petticoat	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
lay	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
180	O
,	O
181	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
Christopher	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
in	O
White-Friars	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
morning	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
,	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	B-place
;	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
their	O
lodgings	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
with	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
on	O
my	O
right	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
Jones	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mathews	I-pers
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
do	O
it	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
hand	O
come	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
what	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
her	O
hand	O
was	O
clinch	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
take	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
a	O
shillings	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
something	O
above	O
a	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
I	O
lost	O
that	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
lock	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
foot	O
against	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
;	O
there	O
sat	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
watchman	O
charge	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
compter	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-mayor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
pretended	O
over-night	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
cut	O
off	O
their	O
capuchines	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
them	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
they	O
ask	O
you	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
consenting	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
About	O
2	O
o'clock	O
that	O
Monday	O
morning	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
rob	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
charged	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Salisbury-court	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
key	O
and	O
unlock	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
his	O
appearing	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I'am	O
an	O
enameller	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Salisbury-court	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
182	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Richard	I-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
.	O
April	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Nag	B-place
's	I-place
head	I-place
an	I-place
inn	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Orange-street	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
mug	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
chairwoman	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
?	O
M.	O
Bowman	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
saw	O
my	O
mug	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
my	O
name	O
is	O
on	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
there	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
?	O
M.	O
Bowman	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Powel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
a	O
guineas	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
First	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
from	O
Mary	B-pers
Bayment	I-pers
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
183	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Commin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
34	O
candles	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
towel	O
,	O
one	O
damask	O
napkin	O
,	O
2	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
garters	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
brass	O
sockets	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
April	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
Samuel	B-pers
Underhill	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
box	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
care	O
to	O
send	O
from	O
my	O
country	O
house	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
that	O
box	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
then	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
we	O
open	O
'd	O
another	O
little	O
box	O
of	O
his	O
(	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
)	O
there	O
were	O
2	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
towel	O
,	O
napkin	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
napkin	O
is	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
set	O
.	O
The	O
towel	O
has	O
my	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
U	O
12	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
2	O
pocket	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
a	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
leather	O
garters	O
are	O
what	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
do	O
up	O
my	O
boots	O
with	O
.	O
The	O
3	O
brass	O
sockets	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
candles	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
at	O
the	O
opening	O
of	O
his	O
box	O
?	O
Underhill	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
master	O
the	O
garters	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
by	O
?	O
Underhill	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
leave	O
Warwickshire	O
?	O
Underhill	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
at	O
Christmas	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
customary	O
for	O
your	O
servants	O
to	O
have	O
napkins	O
to	O
clean	O
their	O
plate	O
?	O
Underhill	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
proper	O
plate	O
cloths	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
such	O
as	O
these	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
trusted	O
with	O
your	O
plate	O
?	O
Underhill	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
ever	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
that	O
missing	O
?	O
Underhill	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
dealt	O
in	O
smaller	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
things	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
your	O
butler	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
?	O
Underhill	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
have	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
minded	O
?	O
Underhill	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
go	O
without	O
his	O
wages	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
opened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
?	O
Symonds	O
.	O
In	O
Mr.	O
Underhill	O
's	O
parlour	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
powder	O
mills	O
on	O
Hounslow-heath	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
open	O
'd	O
it	O
himself	O
.	O
The	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Underhill	O
said	O
were	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
taking	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bruce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
my	O
lord	O
Bristol	O
's	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gaul	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
6	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
faithful	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
trusted	O
with	O
hundreds	O
of	O
pounds	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
captain	O
Fowler	O
and	O
my	O
lord	O
Bristol	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
universal	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Burgin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
a	O
man	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
intrusted	O
largely	O
with	O
money	O
and	O
effects	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bestern	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
year	O
forty-two	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
charge	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
's	O
plate	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
chaplain	O
to	O
the	O
carl	O
of	O
Stairs	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Murray	O
say	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
honestest	O
servant	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
year	O
forty	O
five	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
lad	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
year	O
forty	O
two	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
with	O
decency	O
and	O
sobriety	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Murry	O
,	O
Capt	O
.	O
Fowler	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Plunket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
lord	O
Bristol	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
where	O
ever	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
just	O
and	O
good	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Grant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
himself	O
well	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Barrin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
my	O
lord	O
Bristol	O
's	O
place	O
with	O
credit	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
184	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
business	O
of	O
coals	O
call	O
'd	O
sea-coal	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
185	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sandiland	B-pers
Walbark	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
vessel	O
called	O
a	O
hogshead	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cousemaker	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
March	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
186	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Grubb	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
vessel	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
kilderkin	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Cousemaker	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pitt	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
187	O
,	O
188	O
,	O
189	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Esther	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
lawn	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
one	O
doll	O
's	O
muslin	O
apron	O
.	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
holland	O
,	O
one	O
ticken	O
pocket	O
,	O
one	O
towel	O
,	O
5	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
20	O
gallons	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
20	O
gallons	O
of	O
strong	O
beer	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wyate	I-pers
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Elmes	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Duke	I-place
of	I-place
Marlborough	I-place
's	I-place
Head	I-place
by	I-place
Shadwell-Church	I-place
,	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Taylor	O
,	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
liquors	O
at	O
divers	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
her	O
by	O
our	O
finding	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
in	O
her	O
bed	O
,	O
under	O
her	O
head	O
.	O
We	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
missed	O
no	O
opportunity	O
of	O
robbing	O
me	O
since	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
things	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
then	O
.	O
She	O
signed	O
her	O
confession	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
justice	O
sign	O
it	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
The	O
voluntary	O
confession	O
of	O
Esther	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
made	O
before	O
Walter	B-pers
Bury	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
March	O
1	O
,	O
1756.	O
``	O
The	O
said	O
Esther	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
maketh	O
oath	O
and	O
faith	O
,	O
``	O
that	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
Christmas	O
last	O
she	O
did	O
feloniously	O
``	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
``	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
dwelling-house	O
one	O
lawn	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
``	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
ribbons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
prayer-book	O
,	O
``	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
3-qrs	O
of	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
``	O
three	O
womens	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
an	O
old	O
work	O
'd	O
``	O
border	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
towel	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
her	O
master	O
;	O
``	O
and	O
about	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
she	O
at	O
divers	O
``	O
times	O
did	O
steal	O
and	O
take	O
away	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
``	O
house	O
one	O
bottle	O
of	O
gin	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
her	O
master.	O
``	O
And	O
further	O
faith	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
she	O
``	O
had	O
laid	O
under	O
her	O
head	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
that	O
``	O
would	O
open	O
the	O
places	O
where	O
her	O
said	O
master	O
kept	O
``	O
his	O
liquor	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
of	O
liquor	O
upwards	O
``	O
of	O
100	O
gallons	O
,	O
besides	O
candles	O
and	O
other	O
``	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
committed	O
divers	O
other	O
robberies	O
``	O
and	O
felonies	O
in	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
``	O
commission	O
of	O
which	O
her	O
memory	O
greatly	O
fails	O
``	O
her	O
.	O
''	O
Mary	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
(	O
some	O
linen	O
produced	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
.	O
)	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
Taylor	O
,	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
stole	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
?	O
M.	O
Mason	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
Taylor	O
confessed	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
E.	O
Mason	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
the	O
other	O
prisoners	O
?	O
E.	O
Mason	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
Taylor	O
has	O
said	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Parrot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Taylor	O
's	O
confession	O
both	O
at	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Princess	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Taylor	O
say	O
she	O
took	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
an	O
apron	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
prisoners	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Evdit	I-pers
I	O
heard	O
Taylor	O
confess	O
she	O
stole	O
an	O
apron	O
and	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
from	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
prisoners	O
used	O
to	O
ask	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
liquor	O
at	O
all	O
opportunities	O
.	O
Wyate	O
and	O
Elmes	O
declared	O
they	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
charged	O
with	O
.	O
Taylor	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Wyate	O
and	O
Elmes	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
190	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
laced	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
April	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
191	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Albert	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
callimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
petticoat	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
March	O
27	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
them	O
from	O
?	O
M.	O
Eaton	O
.	O
From	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
trunk	O
at	O
my	O
lodging	O
in	O
Shug-Lane	B-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
away	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
suspecting	O
him	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Wright	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
in	O
Copeland-Street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
liberty	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
cloaths	O
?	O
You	O
know	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
as	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
we	O
cohabited	O
together	O
.	O
M.	O
Eaton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
wife	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
week	O
and	O
four	O
days	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
criminal	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
his	O
wife	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
when	O
he	O
pleased	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
in	O
Shug-Lane	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
for	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
these	O
things	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shug-Lane	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
first	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
lodging	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
wife	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
see	O
her	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
lodgings	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
there	O
about	O
seven	O
days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
lie	O
together	O
?	O
Edler	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
week	O
was	O
out	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
a	O
service	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
week	O
's	O
lodging	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
at	O
church	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
church	O
was	O
married	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
192	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Benton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
stuff	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Isabelia	B-pers
Wishart	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
193.	O
John	B-pers
Brice	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
not	O
surrendering	O
himself	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
order	O
in	O
council	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
produced	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
194	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Arthur	B-pers
Floyd	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthias	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
Berkenhout	I-pers
,	O
April	O
23	O
++	O
Matthias	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
Berkenhout	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
coming	O
under	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
near	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
him	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
convey	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
which	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
a	O
boy	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Berkenhout	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Another	O
lad	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
clear	O
'd	O
here	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
195	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
four	O
silk	O
and	O
3	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
privately	O
in	O
her	O
shop	O
,	O
March	O
20	O
||	O
Ann	B-pers
Alcock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoreditch	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
my	O
windows	O
were	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
drop	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Tatertop	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
almost	O
facing	O
Mrs.	O
Alcock	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
boys	O
run	O
across	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
some	O
glass	O
break	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Alcock	O
's	O
young	O
man	O
open	O
her	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
a	O
man	O
darted	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
white	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
it	O
drew	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
channel	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
walked	O
gently	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
past	O
me	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
score	O
yards	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
cry	O
of	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
pointed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
thing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Talerton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Law	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Alcock	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
window	O
break	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
forwards	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
take	O
out	O
some	O
printed	O
linen	O
through	O
the	O
square	O
that	O
was	O
broke	O
;	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
that	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
piece	O
,	O
drop	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
pathway	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
ran	O
cross	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
:	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
almost	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
channel	O
,	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
the	O
printed	O
linen	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
ran	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
Then	O
Mr.	O
Taterton	O
pointed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Wamsley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
printed	O
linen	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Law	O
.	O
This	O
piece	O
of	O
linen	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Wimesley	O
.	O
These	O
goods	O
I	O
had	O
deliver	O
'd	O
into	O
my	O
care	O
,	O
before	O
justice	O
Withers	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
as	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
earn	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
maintain	O
my	O
family	O
,	O
without	O
doing	O
any	O
such	O
things	O
as	O
these	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bull-head	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Dean-Street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
weaver	O
,	O
pays	O
honestly	O
for	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
hard	O
for	O
his	O
living	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Horrucks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
always	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Ashton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
14	O
and	O
15	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
a	O
considerable	O
time	O
at	O
weaving	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
As	O
far	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
just	O
man	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Tompson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
pays	O
every	O
on	O
their	O
own	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
reel	O
'd	O
against	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
196	O
,	O
197	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Wells	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
George	O
Barker	O
,	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
5	O
kersey	O
jackets	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
kersey	O
drawers	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Alexander	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Feb.	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale	O
shop	O
in	O
Chick-lane	B-place
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
missed	O
5	O
jackets	O
and	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
drawers	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
who	O
took	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
stood	O
me	O
in	O
1	O
l.	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
W	O
illiam	O
Richardson	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
Wells	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
down	O
Chick-lane	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
shop	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Wells	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
a	O
jacket	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
4	O
jackets	O
and	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Alexander	O
Abrahams	O
for	O
8	O
s.	O
who	O
knew	O
we	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
wish	O
'd	O
us	O
good	O
luck	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
hoped	O
to	O
deal	O
with	O
us	O
again	O
.	O
Wells	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
that	O
evidence	O
,	O
or	O
bought	O
things	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
For	O
Abrahams	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Abrahams	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
months	O
.	O
He	O
travelled	O
the	O
country	O
with	O
hard	O
ware	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Lovi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
anchovies	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Israel	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
pickles	O
and	O
anchovies	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
this	O
last	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
198.	O
John	B-pers
Venters	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
vessel	O
.	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
leaden	O
sink	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
iron	O
grate	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
laid	O
over	O
again	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
another	O
indictment	O
prefer	O
'd	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
stealing	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
200	O
l.	O
but	O
it	O
being	O
laid	O
as	O
a	O
high	O
felony	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
upon	O
that	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
199	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mohan	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
two	O
caps	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
rushes	O
,	O
one	O
gause	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
other	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
stomacher	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Feb.	O
9	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
200	O
,	O
201	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	O
Roberts	O
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
20	O
pair	O
of	O
worstead	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
worstead	O
waistcoat	O
piece	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
capuchine	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Clare	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
Feb.	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
Clare	O
Reeve	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
did	O
they	O
lie	O
in	O
?	O
Reeve	O
.	O
The	O
lawn	O
and	O
3	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
were	O
at	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
windows	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
piece	O
,	O
capuchine	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
stockings	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
window	O
I	O
lost	O
all	O
the	O
stockings	O
at	O
that	O
window	O
,	O
except	O
one	O
single	O
stocking	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
them	O
?	O
Reeve	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
in	O
about	O
3	O
minutes	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
gone	O
backwards	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
About	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
affair	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Cane	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
him	O
before	O
him	O
;	O
directing	O
me	O
to	O
enquire	O
in	O
Chick-Lane	O
of	O
people	O
that	O
bought	O
stolen	O
goods	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
but	O
found	O
none	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
me	O
who	O
had	O
some	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Cane	O
,	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
One-Tun	O
in	O
George	O
Alley	O
.	O
Cane	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
over	O
a	O
wall	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
we	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
got	O
from	O
us	O
,	O
who	O
order	O
'd	O
his	O
men	O
to	O
be	O
diligent	O
in	O
searching	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
Williams	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
afterwards	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
brought	O
chither	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
confessed	O
nothing	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
set	O
at	O
liberty	O
.	O
Then	O
Cole	O
and	O
Roberts	O
were	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
this	O
a	O
man	O
belonging	O
to	O
New-Prison	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
thought	O
if	O
Cole	O
could	O
be	O
taken	O
he	O
would	O
squeak	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
and	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
2	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
Cane	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
justice	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
about	O
to	O
admit	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
Cole	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
pointed	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Cole	O
in	O
robbing	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
of	O
what	O
?	O
Reeve	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
mention	O
'd	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
wrote	O
an	O
order	O
for	O
Cane	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
after	O
Cole	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
messenger	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Cane	O
there	O
discover	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
our	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
lawn	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
10	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
and	O
an	O
odd	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
might	O
these	O
goods	O
be	O
worth	O
?	O
Reeve	O
.	O
They	O
lay	O
me	O
in	O
5	O
l.	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Williams	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Reeve	O
.	O
Williams	O
confessed	O
at	O
the	O
Bear	O
in	O
Bow-Street	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
with	O
Cane	O
and	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
particulars	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
every	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
manner	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
Reeve	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
all	O
coming	O
along	O
Theobalds-Row	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
without	O
a	O
light	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Cane	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
capuchine	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
stockings	O
;	O
then	O
Roberts	O
and	O
Williams	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
lawn	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
19	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
and	O
an	O
odd	O
one	O
,	O
a	O
capuchin	O
,	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
black	O
piece	O
of	O
stuff	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
George	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
them	O
over	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Alexander	O
the	O
Jew	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
In	O
Hounsditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
the	O
stockings	O
for	O
18	O
pence	O
per	O
pair	O
,	O
the	O
capuchine	O
for	O
9	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
piece	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
justice	O
made	O
me	O
evidence	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
confessed	O
.	O
Cane	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
justice	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
did	O
steal	O
24	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tolley	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
Feb.	O
5	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Tolley	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
selling	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
having	O
time	O
to	O
tie	O
the	O
rest	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
string	O
about	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
round	O
amongst	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
who	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
papers	O
,	O
with	O
five	O
guineas	O
reward	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
When	O
Cane	O
and	O
Williams	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
taking	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
I	O
proffer	O
'd	O
Cane	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
concern	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
if	O
possible	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
give	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
they	O
were	O
discharged	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
,	O
Cole	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
who	O
directly	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Cane	O
and	O
Roberts	O
were	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
and	O
justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
Then	O
Cane	O
and	O
Williams	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Cane	O
in	O
Tothillfields	O
bridewell	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
put	O
several	O
pair	O
into	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
rest	O
to	O
his	O
companions	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
two	O
dozen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
how	O
many	O
pair	O
he	O
put	O
into	O
his	O
breeches	O
?	O
Tolley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
fill	O
'd	O
his	O
breeches	O
as	O
full	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
pair	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
2	O
dozen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
from	O
what	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Tolley	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
what	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Tolley	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Alexander	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
the	O
Jew	O
for	O
2	O
shillings	O
and	O
3	O
pence	O
per	O
pair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
they	O
worth	O
?	O
Tolley	O
.	O
Some	O
cost	O
me	O
15	O
shillings	O
per	O
pair	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
The	O
cheapest	O
cost	O
me	O
above	O
10	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Tolley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
the	O
Jew	O
's	O
apartment	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
selling	O
of	O
goods	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
swore	O
to	O
more	O
goods	O
by	O
half	O
than	O
ever	O
he	O
lost	O
.	O
Tolley	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
3	O
other	O
witnesses	O
that	O
heard	O
his	O
confession	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
any	O
occasion	O
for	O
them	O
here	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
Cane	O
,	O
Roberts	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
Strand	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
the	O
fast	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
get	O
anything	O
.	O
Cane	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
farthest	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
stockings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
Because	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
did	O
he	O
take	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
24	O
pair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
stockings	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
Silk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Alexander	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
the	O
Jew	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
us	O
2	O
shillings	O
and	O
3	O
pence	O
per	O
pair	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
[	O
See	O
him	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
West	O
and	O
Pryer	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
179	O
and	O
180	O
,	O
in	O
alderman	O
Jansien	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
against	O
Banks	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
80	O
,	O
in	O
this	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
]	O
202	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Henry	I-pers
Powel	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
March	O
5	O
.	O
||	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wagstaff	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
there	O
came	O
Charles	O
Cane	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
about	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Williams	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
shop	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
?	O
E.	O
Wagstaff	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
the	O
minute	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
.	O
Cane	O
staid	O
longer	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
than	O
the	O
other	O
did	O
.	O
Upon	O
missing	O
the	O
goods	O
I	O
pursued	O
,	O
and	O
Cane	O
was	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
fight	O
,	O
so	O
got	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
take	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
E.	O
Wagstaff	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
(	O
not	O
Cane	O
)	O
sambling	O
at	O
his	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
own	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
other	O
notice	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Cole	O
the	O
evidence	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
that	O
same	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
again	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
along	O
with	O
Charles	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
and	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Charles-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
out	O
7	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
5	O
silk	O
and	O
2	O
cotton	O
ones	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
Williams	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
out	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
out	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Cane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Powel	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
203	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
yards	O
of	O
sattin	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
Widow	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
shop	O
,	O
February	O
13	O
.	O
||	O
Elizabeth	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
warehouse	O
for	O
capuchines	O
,	O
bonnet	O
,	O
cloaks	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
articles	O
,	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
Court	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
16	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
sattin	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
know	O
not	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Creamer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Williams	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
when	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
a	O
tall	O
one	O
and	O
a	O
short	O
one	O
.	O
[	O
Note	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
were	O
such	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
tallest	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
some	O
ribband	O
.	O
I	O
arose	O
up	O
from	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
some	O
.	O
They	O
bought	O
none	O
,	O
but	O
assoon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
sattin	O
,	O
of	O
about	O
10	O
yards	O
,	O
which	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
acquainted	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
brother	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
men	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Monkford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
say	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
such	O
men	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
ribbands	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
looked	O
earnestly	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
particularly	O
observed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
saw	O
the	O
sattin	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
before	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
reason	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
S.	O
Monkford	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Sarah	O
Creamer	O
that	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
sattin	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
went	O
in	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
black	O
sattin	O
ribband	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seeing	O
an	O
opportunity	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
there	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
16	O
yard	O
,	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Alexander	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
the	O
Jew	O
,	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
per	O
yd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
We	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
equally	O
.	O
We	O
thought	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
price	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
came	O
back	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
at	O
another	O
shop	O
to	O
cheapen	O
some	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
thought	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
pretty	O
good	O
price	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
having	O
ask	O
'd	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
yard	O
for	O
some	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
this	O
Alexander	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
the	O
Jew	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
He	O
fells	O
things	O
about	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
things	O
to	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
if	O
we	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
fell	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
be	O
it	O
what	O
it	O
would	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
swore	O
before	O
justice	O
Welch	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
so	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
Cole	O
swear	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
swear	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Cole	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
more	O
Richard	B-pers
Munday	I-pers
's	O
than	O
one	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Cole	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Cole	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
villain	O
;	O
he	O
will	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
own	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
204	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Montgomery	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Maddin	I-pers
.	O
April	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Maddin	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
sale	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	B-place
Minories	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
coat	O
lying	O
on	O
a	O
chest	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
taken	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
that	O
were	O
brought	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
an	O
alderman	O
at	O
Guildhall	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
swore	O
to	O
my	O
coat	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
tell	O
it	O
for	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
your	O
servant	O
?	O
Maddin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Maddin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
yard	O
,	O
but	O
on	O
turning	O
my	O
head	O
about	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
mistress	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
doing	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
coat	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
D.	O
Maddin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
got	O
another	O
coat	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
her	O
till	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lloyd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
out	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Maddin	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
doing	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
coat	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
steal	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
into	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
the	O
lane	O
;	O
at	O
another	O
time	O
she	O
said	O
some	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
had	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
price	O
of	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
that	O
coat	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
stockings	O
and	O
shirts	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
Gibrakar	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
one	O
before	O
of	O
a	O
Jew	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
call	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
light	O
because	O
the	O
shop	O
was	O
dark	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
205	O
,	O
206	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Pool	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
six	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
seventeen	O
shillings	O
,	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
April	O
25	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
not	O
appearing	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
207	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Borroughs	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bullock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hickby	I-pers
,	O
March	O
1	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Ireland	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
oxen	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hickby	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
William	B-pers
Jefferson	I-pers
,	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
missing	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
about	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
near	O
Swan-Alley	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
,	O
a	O
slaughterman	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
bullock	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
Smithfield	B-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
there	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
bullock	O
through	O
Islington	O
turnpike	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
Eakins	O
,	O
a	O
west-country	O
man	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
18	O
l.	O
to	O
drive	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
slaughter	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Weston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
bullock	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
others	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ireland	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
marked	O
upon	O
the	O
rump	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
clips	O
on	O
the	O
thigh	O
under	O
the	O
off-seat	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Ireland	O
's	O
mark	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
grasier	O
's	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
slaughter-house	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
ox	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
white	O
on	O
its	O
tail	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jefferson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Ireland	O
's	O
drover	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
bullock	O
out	O
of	O
Smithfield	O
from	O
amongst	O
others	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Hickby	I-pers
;	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
came	O
and	O
inquired	O
who	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
bullock	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
slaughter	O
house	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gordon	O
told	O
me	O
John	O
Borroughs	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
brought	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
one	O
Eakins	O
of	O
Devonshire	O
,	O
for	O
driving	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Keeling	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
cow	O
to	O
kill	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
about	O
eleven	O
or	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
following	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
this	O
bullock	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
black	O
bullock	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
white	O
on	O
the	O
tip	O
of	O
the	O
tail	O
,	O
two	O
clips	O
under	O
the	O
teat	O
on	O
the	O
thigh	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
upon	O
the	O
rump	O
)	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
kill	O
it	O
directly	O
,	O
to	O
cleave	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
quarter	O
and	O
weigh	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
wager	O
laid	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
make	O
haste	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Upon	O
seeing	O
no	O
country	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
enquire	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
bullock	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Ireland	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jefferson	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
bullock	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
having	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
soon	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
weigh	O
'd	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Jefferson	O
staid	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
kill	O
'd	O
the	O
bullock	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
how	O
long	O
will	O
it	O
be	O
first	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
stay	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
bullock	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
another	O
man	O
hired	O
him	O
for	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
kill	O
'd	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
through	O
Islington	O
turnpike	O
that	O
morning	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
who	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
charge	O
,	O
confirm	O
'd	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
about	O
the	O
bullock	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
saw	O
me	O
bargain	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
bullock	O
through	O
the	O
turnpike	O
to	O
the	O
slaughter-house	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
my	O
trial	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
on	O
till	O
Friday	O
.	O
The	O
bullock	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
killed	O
for	O
a	O
wager	O
,	O
which	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Eakins	I-pers
laid	O
about	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Slingsby	I-pers
.	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
iron	O
keys	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sutherland	I-pers
,	O
April	O
19	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
209	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Kemp	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Josian	B-pers
Drain	I-pers
,	O
April	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
210	O
,	O
211	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Agnes	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Walter	I-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Abraham	I-pers
Hardis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
other	O
lawn	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
chints	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Francis	O
,	O
April	O
22	O
.	O
*	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
212	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Alexander	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
24	O
pair	O
of	O
worstead	O
stockings	O
,	O
1	O
worstead	O
waistcoat	O
piece	O
,	O
1	O
silk	O
capuchine	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
Charles	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Clare	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Clare	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
the	O
evidence	O
deposed	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
former	O
trial	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
declared	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Cole	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Then	O
William	O
Richardson	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Abraham	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
when	O
Cole	O
,	O
Cane	O
,	O
and	O
Williams	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Harvest	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
One	O
Tun	O
in	O
George-Alley	O
,	O
bargaining	O
for	O
goods	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
213	O
,	O
214	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Shilock	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
steal	O
out	O
thence	O
8	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Alice	O
.	O
*	O
Alice	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
slop	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
lower	O
end	O
of	O
Wapping	B-place
.	O
My	O
shop	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
of	O
8	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
not	O
the	O
persons	O
till	O
the	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Shilock	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
three	O
officers	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
my	O
shop	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
conforts	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
drew	O
out	O
a	O
window	O
shutter	O
(	O
shewing	O
me	O
how	O
)	O
then	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
hook	O
at	O
a	O
broken	O
glass	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
8	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
one	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
6	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
heard	O
his	O
confession	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
sign	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
broke	O
the	O
glass	O
?	O
A.	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Watts	O
was	O
examined	O
also	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
he	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
Shilock	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
.	O
James	O
May	O
.	O
I	O
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hale	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Churgen	I-pers
,	O
being	O
all	O
officers	O
,	O
had	O
warrants	O
for	O
impressing	O
disorderly	O
men	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Cable-Street	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
houses	O
of	O
ill	O
same	O
open	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
house	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
a	O
stop	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bolt	O
and	O
lock	O
drawn	O
back	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
open	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
staff	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
scream	O
'd	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
lads	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
who	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
open	O
'd	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
them	O
;	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
necessary	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hole	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
might	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
vault	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
staff	O
down	O
,	O
then	O
look	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
.	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
look	O
red	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
people	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
theirs	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
secured	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
watch	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
the	O
parcel	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
came	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
men	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
6	O
men	O
.	O
They	O
desir	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
see	O
the	O
2	O
lads	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
not	O
the	O
men	O
we	O
want	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
2	O
notorious	O
thieves	O
;	O
let	O
's	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
little	O
one	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
Shilock	O
)	O
and	O
examine	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
for	O
a	O
long	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
confess	O
and	O
impeach	O
Watts	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
impeach	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
transported	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
like	O
to	O
have	O
done	O
the	O
same	O
by	O
his	O
mother	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
ago	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
parcel	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
in	O
Wapping	O
,	O
at	O
Execution-Dock	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
parcel	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Pell	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
worship	O
what	O
the	O
lad	O
had	O
inform	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
desir	O
'd	O
us	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
parcel	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
Shilock	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
10	O
of	O
them	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
Shilock	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Watts	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
committed	O
several	O
robberies	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Griffith	O
's	O
shop	O
at	O
Execution-Dock	O
of	O
14	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
desir	O
'd	O
we	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
us	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
Mrs.	O
Griffith	O
was	O
crying	O
.	O
We	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Shilock	O
confessed	O
also	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
that	O
they	O
rob	O
'd	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
there	O
by	O
his	O
direction	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
.	O
Her	O
daughter	O
told	O
us	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
handkerchiefs	O
some	O
time	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
within	O
8	O
or	O
10	O
days	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
at	O
first	O
.	O
Then	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
said	O
they	O
stole	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
8	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
daughter	O
said	O
she	O
missed	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
her	O
mother	O
being	O
ill	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
fear	O
of	O
disturbing	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
boy	O
shew	O
'd	O
us	O
how	O
he	O
drew	O
back	O
the	O
window	O
shutter	O
,	O
putting	O
in	O
a	O
hooked	O
stick	O
at	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
boy	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
again	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
also	O
Mrs.	O
Griffith	O
.	O
Then	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
confessed	O
the	O
2	O
robberies	O
.	O
The	O
confession	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
and	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
following	O
purport	O
:	O
``	O
The	O
voluntary	O
confession	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
,	O
``	O
taken	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1756.	O
``	O
who	O
faith	O
,	O
that	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
he	O
got	O
acquainted	O
``	O
with	O
Shilock	O
at	O
the	O
Glass-house	O
,	O
and	O
``	O
that	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
they	O
went	O
together	O
``	O
to	O
a	O
shop	O
opposite	O
