TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Thirty-first	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
,	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1757	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
MARSHE	O
DICKINSON	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
J.	O
ROBINSON	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Lion	O
,	O
in	O
Ludgate-Street	O
,	O
1757	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
General	O
Sessions	B-pers
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
MARSHE	O
DICKINSON	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
;	O
*	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dennison	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
;	O
+	O
Sir	O
Richard	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
||	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
++	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
,	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
John	B-pers
Child	I-pers
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
William	B-pers
Raiment	I-pers
George	B-pers
Coulton	I-pers
James	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
William	B-pers
Merryweather	I-pers
John	B-pers
Seymore	I-pers
John	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
Daniel	B-pers
Wiltshire	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
John	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
Cornelius	B-pers
Vanderstop	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
William	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
Jason	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
Alexander	B-pers
Schollar	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cabit	I-pers
John	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
was	O
taken	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
was	O
sworn	O
in	O
his	O
stead	O
.	O
297	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Grimstead	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
woollen	O
tilt	O
for	O
a	O
boat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
,	O
August	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Turpin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
only	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
tilt	O
being	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
my	O
name	O
upon	O
it	O
at	O
length	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
waterman	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
his	O
tilt	O
into	O
the	O
crane-house	B-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
Custom-house	I-place
Keys	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	B-pers
The	I-pers
next	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
also	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
tilt	O
upon	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
there	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
tilt	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Norman	O
at	O
Execution-Dock	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
looking	O
upon	O
it	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Simkins	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
fellowship	O
porter	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
do	O
a	O
chare	O
for	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
Customhouse	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
tilt	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
nobody	O
by	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
298	O
,	O
299	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
More	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Eyles	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
set	O
with	O
Bristol	O
stones	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
July	O
25	O
.	O
+	O
Peter	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clerk	O
in	O
the	O
secretary	O
's	O
office	O
at	O
the	O
Custom-house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
early	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
street	B-place
near	I-place
Saltpetre-bank	I-place
,	O
being	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
and	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
way	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
awaked	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
silver	O
shoe	O
and	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
set	O
with	O
Bristol	O
stones	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
Eyles	O
confessed	O
her	O
taking	O
four	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
how	O
much	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
at	O
Law	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Boswell	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
one	O
Mary	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
by	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
not	O
taken	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Eyles	O
take	O
his	O
silver	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
More	O
one	O
buckle	O
from	O
his	O
knee	O
,	O
and	O
Steward	O
took	O
the	O
other	O
knee	O
buckle	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
ashamed	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
man	O
so	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
something	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
they	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
More	O
.	O
Then	O
Ann	O
Eyles	O
took	O
four	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
one	O
Atkins	O
by	O
who	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
so	O
got	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Eyles	I-pers
secured	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
and	O
saw	O
Mary	B-pers
Ann	I-pers
Eyles	I-pers
with	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeffs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
for	O
White-Chapel	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Eyles	O
delivered	O
into	O
my	O
charge	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Eyles	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Ann	B-pers
Dyer	I-pers
take	O
the	O
buttons	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
sleeves	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
threw	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
300	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Bradbury	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
field	O
or	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
Stile	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
6	O
s.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Aug.	O
26	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Stile	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Suppose	O
you	O
were	O
to	O
forswear	O
yourself	O
in	O
accusing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
of	O
a	O
felony	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
become	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
d	O
-	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Christ's-Hospital	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
the	O
school	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
read	O
your	O
Bible	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
,	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
be	O
sure	O
say	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
is	O
truth	O
.	O
Stile	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Charlton	O
.	O
Returning	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
August	O
to	O
Christ's-Hospital	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
leave	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
visit	O
your	O
father	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
meet	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
Between	B-place
Twickenham	I-place
and	I-place
Isteworth	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
a	I-place
little	I-place
narrow	I-place
lane	I-place
,	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
friends	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
tinker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
By	O
his	O
budget	O
and	O
blackness	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
bluish	O
coat	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
meet	O
or	O
overtake	O
you	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
He	O
first	O
past	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
round	O
and	O
met	O
me	O
another	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
answer	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
him	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
money	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
none	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
never	O
come	O
so	O
far	O
without	O
my	O
friends	O
giving	O
me	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
search	O
'd	O
my	O
pockets	O
.	O
Finding	O
nothing	O
there	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
off	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
tell	O
him	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
noise	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
towards	O
the	O
Thames	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
Isleworth	O
fields	O
of	O
what	O
had	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
brothers	O
that	O
live	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
(	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Aldermanbury	O
,	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
chair	O
carver	O
)	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
After	O
which	O
my	O
brother	O
came	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
me	O
from	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
that	O
lives	O
with	O
a	O
farmer	O
at	O
Walton	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Moulsey	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
dressed	O
just	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
now	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
blue	O
patch	O
'd	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
long	O
brown	O
stick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
capacity	O
is	O
your	O
brother	O
at	O
Walton	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
with	O
a	O
farmer	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
this	O
money	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
My	O
father	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
my	O
mother	O
another	O
,	O
my	O
cousin	O
Stile	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
farmer	O
just	O
by	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
:	O
my	O
cousin	O
Lenton	O
,	O
at	O
Sunbury-Green	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
madam	O
Brest	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
cousin	O
Spencer	O
,	O
at	O
Hampton-Court	O
,	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
not	O
you	O
talk	O
'd	O
something	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
your	O
friends	O
had	O
given	O
you	O
some	O
money	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
he	O
committed	O
to	O
?	O
Stile	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
Kingston	O
Gaol	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Stile	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Charlton	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Sunbury	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
father	O
to	O
the	O
lad	O
.	O
My	O
son	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
more	O
sons	O
than	O
this	O
?	O
I.	O
Stile	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
three	O
sons	O
in	O
London	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
a	O
chair	O
carver	O
in	O
Aldermanbury	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
this	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
coming	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
My	O
other	O
son	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
begging	O
in	O
Walton	O
church-yard	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
this	O
witness	O
from	O
London	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
rob	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Kingston	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rowl	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
?	O
I.	O
Stile	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
each	O
,	O
my	O
landlord	O
's	O
mother	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
farmer	O
his	O
nephew	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
a	O
butcher	O
(	O
named	O
Spencer	O
,	O
who	O
married	O
my	O
niece	O
)	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
relation	O
that	O
keeps	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
George	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
where	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
?	O
I.	O
Stile	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
putting	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
shoe	O
?	O
I.	O
Stile	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bliss	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Rowl	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
there	O
as	O
here	O
.	O
The	O
tinker	O
could	O
not	O
contradict	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
in	O
different	O
stories	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
lad	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
Moulsey	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
brasier	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
from	O
farm	O
house	O
to	O
farm	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
mend	O
brass	O
saucepans	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
301	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Humphry	I-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
iron	O
pottage	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
September	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
302	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susannah	B-pers
Fifield	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
one	O
copper	O
coffee	O
pot	O
,	O
one	O
china	O
punch	O
bowl	O
,	O
five	O
china	O
coffee	O
cups	O
,	O
four	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
frock	O
,	O
twelve	O
linen	O
clouts	O
,	O
one	O
woollen	O
blanket	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
bed	O
gown	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
two	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
one	O
mahogany	O
waiter	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
one	O
quilted	O
petticoat	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Sqursefigi	I-pers
,	O
August	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Sqursefigi	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Charles	B-pers
Sqursefigi	I-pers
.	O
We	O
live	O
in	O
Cock	B-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
Broad	I-place
Saint	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
June	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
little	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
August	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
she	O
brought	O
a	O
tablecloth	O
of	O
another	O
person	O
to	O
be	O
used	O
at	O
table	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
own	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
and	O
could	O
get	O
none	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
two	O
guineas	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
seven	O
shillings	O
per	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
her	O
eleven	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
and	O
missed	O
several	O
things	O
.	O
Two	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
lady	O
Cardagan	O
's	O
with	O
a	O
bill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
M.	O
Spursefigi	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
mantuamaker	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
missed	O
two	O
table	O
spoons	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tea	O
tongs	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
leave	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
tea	O
tongs	O
afterwards	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Squires	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Crown-Court	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledg	O
'd	O
the	O
china	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shepherd-street	O
,	O
Hanover-square	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
and	O
tea	O
tongs	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
sixteen	O
or	O
eighteen	O
shillings	O
.	O
She	O
gave	O
in	O
her	O
name	O
Ann	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
were	O
many	O
other	O
witnesses	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
court	O
thought	O
it	O
unnecessary	O
to	O
examine	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
303	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Martha	B-pers
Dobbin	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
with	O
two	O
silver	O
seals	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worstead	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
shag	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
copper	O
pot	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
May	O
3	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gilbert-street	B-place
,	I-place
Bloomsbury	I-place
.	O
I	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
except	O
the	O
copper	O
pot	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
after	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
kept	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
and	O
the	O
copper	O
pot	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bill	O
upon	O
my	O
door	O
to	O
lett	O
a	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
lodging	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
call	O
the	O
next	O
week	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
little	O
boy	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
both	O
ill	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
we	O
should	O
be	O
lost	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
somebody	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
nobody	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
trust	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
the	O
lodging	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
per	O
week	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
per	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
sick	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
Between	O
a	O
month	O
and	O
five	O
weeks	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
shirts	O
,	O
mark	O
'd	O
W.	O
F.	O
one	O
mark	O
'd	O
George	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
little	O
boy	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
of	O
my	O
little	O
girl	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
mark	O
'd	O
W.	O
F.	O
a	O
watch-with	O
two	O
silver	O
seals	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shag	O
breeches	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
pot	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
wound	O
my	O
watch	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
breeches	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
my	O
breeches	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
looked	O
about	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
gone	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
since	O
,	O
till	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'n-night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
after	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
sweat	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
lodge	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
abroad	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
set	O
up	O
with	O
us	O
six	O
nights	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
to	O
lock	O
us	O
in	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
key	O
under	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
shag	O
breeches	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Lumber-Court	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Seven-Dials	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
copper	O
pot	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
seal	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
I	O
getting	O
intelligence	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
being	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Dobson	O
,	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
people	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
that	O
morning	O
;	O
but	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
after	O
the	O
constable	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
began	O
to	O
blaspheme	O
and	O
make	O
a	O
great	O
noise	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
but	O
the	O
seal	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Saunders	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
seal	O
to	O
keep	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Ansel	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
this	O
copper	O
pot	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
breeches	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
described	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
lodging	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
take	O
me	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
lodger	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
and	O
companion	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
his	O
child	O
being	O
sick	O
,	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
my	O
linen	O
gown	O
to	O
support	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
brings	O
home	O
his	O
lawful	O
wife	O
,	O
dressed	O
in	O
green	O
.	O
The	O
child	O
met	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
mamma	O
is	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
proper	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
received	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
single	O
shilling	O
for	O
the	O
child	O
and	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
pleasure	O
in	O
a	O
walk	O
to	O
Hampstead	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
and	O
met	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
who	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
how	O
I	O
liked	O
my	O
old	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
his	O
wife	O
would	O
send	O
me	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
come	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
seal	O
above	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cobler	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
under	O
the	O
Blue-Lion	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Gray's-Inn	O
passage	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
she	O
bore	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
,	O
only	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
about	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
last	O
?	O
C.	O
Evans	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
for	O
five	O
months	O
last	O
past	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Connel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Leadenhall-Market	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
some	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
except	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
speak	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
she	O
deserves	O
:	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
304	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
sattin	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
,	O
July	O
19	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Portugal-street	B-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
for	O
a	O
tray	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
lying	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
backwards	O
just	O
before	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
shop	O
with	O
some	O
thing	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
after	O
and	O
stop	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
somebody	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
back	O
also	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Corp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
drop	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
running	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
305	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Felton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
scarf	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
muslin	O
hood	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
muslin	O
ruffles	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
shifts	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
guineas	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Marser	I-pers
,	O
August	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Marser	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New	B-place
Court	I-place
,	I-place
Cary-street	I-place
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
three	O
days	O
before	O
I	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
ago	O
?	O
M.	O
Marser	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
only	O
my	O
husband	O
lives	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
mind	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
her	O
wages	O
,	O
saying	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
door	O
on	O
my	O
ground	O
floor	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
as	O
also	O
a	O
trunk	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
spent	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
behind	O
the	O
Alms-houses	O
I	O
should	O
find	O
some	O
of	O
it	O
conceal	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
knife	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
four	O
guineas	O
in	O
a	O
knife	O
box	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
bed	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
pence	O
half	O
penny	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
a	O
muslin	O
hood	O
and	O
a	O
silk	O
scarf	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
her	O
mistress	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
silk	O
gown	O
and	O
two	O
shifts	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
grandmother	O
brought	O
to	O
us	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Miles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Hog-lane	O
at	O
the	O
Alms-houses	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
at	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
silk	O
gown	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
after	O
she	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
her	O
grandmother	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
306	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Bartholomew	B-pers
Godfield	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
stuff	O
damask	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Stainton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Scandret	I-pers
,	O
August	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Stainton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Clement	B-place
's	I-place
lane	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Scandret	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
and	O
lay	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
about	O
seven	O
nights	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	B-pers
.	O
He	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
taught	O
the	O
French	O
language	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
betwixt	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
I	O
awak	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
chest	O
.	O
My	O
landlord	O
ran	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
shirt	O
of	O
mine	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
landlord	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
where	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
David	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
this	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
like	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
he	O
,	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Joyce	B-pers
Scandret	I-pers
.	O
The	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
lay	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
before	O
five	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
rob	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
then	O
was	O
very	O
ill	O
of	O
a	O
fever	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
fetching	O
the	O
cloaths	O
from	O
the	O
Minories	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
no	O
guilty	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
can	O
swear	O
they	O
saw	O
me	O
take	O
a	O
de	O
tings	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
307	O
,	O
308	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Hails	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
l.	O
16	O
s.	O
in	O
pieces	O
of	O
Foreign	O
and	O
English	O
gold	O
coin	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Coine	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
July	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Coine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
upon	O
Tower-Hill	B-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
sixteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
not	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Coine	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
pieces	O
of	O
coin	O
?	O
Coine	O
.	O
Both	O
English	O
and	O
Foreign	O
.	O
A	O
two	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
Portugal	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
justly	O
say	O
what	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
29	O
l.	O
all	O
but	O
4	O
s.	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
by	O
what	O
remain	O
'd	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
took	O
,	O
but	O
ca	O
n't	O
mention	O
the	O
pieces	O
missing	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
turn	O
'd	O
the	O
wheel	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
polishing	O
something	O
in	O
the	O
gunsmith	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
Lee	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
1	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
which	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Hails	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
half	O
pence	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Pratt	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
master	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
named	O
Padget	O
,	O
had	O
the	O
upper	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
had	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
Hails	O
came	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
they	O
staid	O
there	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
came	O
down	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
might	O
stay	O
there	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
little	O
deaf	O
,	O
and	O
Lee	O
kept	O
me	O
in	O
discourse	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
if	O
Hails	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Hails	I-pers
swore	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
his	O
soul	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
money	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
understood	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
working	O
and	O
earning	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
together	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jenour	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Coine	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Lee	O
in	O
Golden-Lane	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Lee	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Hails	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
Lee	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
that	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Lee	O
owes	O
me	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
money	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
at	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
not	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
Lee	O
guilty	O
,	O
1	O
l.	O
18	O
s.	O
5	O
d	O
.	O
Hails	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
309	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Mooring	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
50	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Domonick	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
July	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
310	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Gilford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
61	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
August	O
4	O
.	O
||	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
311	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eighty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Budworth	I-pers
,	O
August	O
29	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Butler	I-pers
.	O
This	O
iron	O
(	O
a	O
crane	O
of	O
a	O
chariot	O
)	O
is	O
my	O
partner	O
's	O
and	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
stealing	O
it	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
his	O
confessing	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
New-Prison	O
that	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Backhouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Butler	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coach-maker	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
it	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
this	O
crane	O
,	O
near	O
Holbourn-Bars	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
Butler	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
312	O
,	O
313.	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
chesnut	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Alington	I-pers
and	O
Barnard	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
,	O
August	O
the	O
8th	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Alington	I-pers
.	O
Long	O
used	O
to	O
help	O
in	O
a	O
stable	O
,	O
that	O
captain	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
rents	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stable-keeper	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
ride	O
a	O
chesnut	O
gelding	O
in	O
the	O
ride	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Barnard	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
and	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
ride	O
him	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
him	O
out	O
and	O
rode	O
him	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
after	O
,	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
justice	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
Richard	B-pers
Pacey	I-pers
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
ten	O
minutes	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
returned	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
horse	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	O
in	O
Mr	O
.	O
Gay	O
's	O
possession	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
stable	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
our	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
home	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
alone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
took	O
witnesses	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
him	O
without	O
I	O
'd	O
pay	O
him	O
eight	O
pounds	O
,	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
paid	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
Long	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
sell	O
him	O
for	O
fifteen	O
pounds	O
or	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
bid	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
him	O
without	O
I	O
'd	O
pay	O
him	O
that	O
money	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Gay	O
say	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
for	O
himself	O
,	O
or	O
his	O
master	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
?	O
Alington	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
me	O
who	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
for	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
Long	O
up	O
?	O
Alington	O
.	O
Gay	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
To	O
what	O
purpose	O
did	O
you	O
order	O
Long	O
to	O
ride	O
your	O
horse	O
?	O
Alington	O
.	O
To	O
settle	O
his	O
legs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
say	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
you	O
sent	O
him	O
out	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
?	O
Alington	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
bought	O
nor	O
sold	O
for	O
me	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Long	O
say	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
Alington	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
a	O
bad	O
thing	O
and	O
must	O
answer	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Barnard	B-pers
Dew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
horse	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
sometimes	O
in	O
my	O
stable	O
and	O
sometimes	O
in	O
my	O
partner	O
's	O
.	O
We	O
live	O
two	O
miles	O
distance	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
May	O
Gay	O
bid	O
me	O
ten	O
pounds	O
for	O
him	O
twice	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
remarkable	O
horse	O
,	O
chesnut	O
colour	O
,	O
a	O
white	O
fundament	O
,	O
and	O
pidgeon	O
eyed	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
usual	O
for	O
helpers	O
to	O
sell	O
horses	O
for	O
their	O
masters	O
?	O
Dew	O
.	O
We	O
do	O
order	O
grooms	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
sometimes	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
helpers	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pacey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
coachman	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayhew	O
,	O
and	O
our	O
horses	O
stand	O
at	O
Alington	O
's	O
stables	O
.	O
Long	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
helper	O
there	O
sometimes	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
ride	O
this	O
chesnut	O
horse	O
in	O
the	O
ride	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alington	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
ride	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
Queen-street	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
August	B-pers
He	I-pers
did	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
him	O
in	O
about	O
fifteen	O
minutes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
not	O
helpers	O
frequently	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
horses	O
?	O
Pacey	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grafton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
captain	O
Clark	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
brought	O
the	O
horse	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
to	O
ride	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
whip	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
help	O
'd	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
He	O
rode	O
him	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
up	O
the	O
ride	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
from	O
prisoner	O
to	O
Alington	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
spurs	O
to	O
ride	O
him	O
?	O
Alington	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Gay	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Long	O
going	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
horse	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
buy	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
set	O
the	O
lowest	O
price	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
buy	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
sold	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
for	O
that	O
money	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
bought	O
him	O
for	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
gave	O
Long	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Alington	O
call	O
'd	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
ride	O
for	O
him	O
had	O
rode	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
horse	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
fraud	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
fraud	O
nor	O
a	O
felony	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
trusted	O
that	O
man	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
Gay	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
since	O
the	O
fifth	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
I	O
trusted	O
him	O
to	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
horses	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
seldom	O
go	O
to	O
market	O
myself	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
other	O
employment	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
hears	O
of	O
a	O
horse	O
he	O
comes	O
and	O
tells	O
me	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
sometimes	O
he	O
gives	O
earnest	O
first	O
,	O
sometimes	O
he	O
buys	O
and	O
never	O
comes	O
to	O
inform	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
before-hand	O
.	O
This	O
horse	O
was	O
bought	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
acquaint	O
you	O
before-hand	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
horse	O
to	O
be	O
sold	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
horse	O
before	O
he	O
bought	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
seven	O
guineas	O
myself	O
to	O
Long	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
Gay	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
to	O
sell	O
him	O
about	O
five	O
that	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
horse	O
before	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Dew	O
's	O
stables	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Long	O
had	O
been	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
horses	O
for	O
other	O
people	O
,	O
for	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
in	O
particular	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
Long	O
who	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
horse	O
for	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
neither	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
bid	O
10	O
l.	O
for	O
the	O
horse	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
broken	O
knee	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
gave	O
full	O
too	O
dear	O
for	O
him	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
Gay	O
any	O
profit	O
in	O
your	O
horses	O
he	O
buys	O
?	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
give	O
him	O
9	O
s.	O
per	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
s.	O
per	O
horse	O
he	O
buys	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rayne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
horses	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
horse	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
the	O
price	O
given	O
for	O
him	O
is	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
will	O
fetch	O
in	O
any	O
market	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
above	O
eight	O
guineas	O
for	O
him	O
the	O
best	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
Cook	I-pers
has	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tobacco	O
merchant	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
thousands	O
of	O
pounds	O
in	O
his	O
hands	O
of	O
mine	O
every	O
day	O
untold	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
strictly	O
honest	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Gay	O
,	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
four	O
years	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
almost	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Cook	O
.	O
The	O
lad	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
soberest	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
stables	O
,	O
he	O
'll	O
not	O
drink	O
nor	O
swear	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Long	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
Gay	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
314	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jacob	B-pers
Openham	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bently	I-pers
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Bently	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
was	O
looking	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
iron	O
rails	O
on	O
London	B-place
Bridge	I-place
.	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
me	O
putting	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
my	O
pardon	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
him	O
pulling	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
My	O
pocket	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
inside	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
315.	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
quarts	O
of	O
lamp	O
oil	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
and	I-pers
John	I-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
May	O
20	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
branded	O
immediately	O
.	O
316	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Weller	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
lamp	O
oil	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
by	O
Morris	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
My	O
brother	O
John	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
partners	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Carnaby	O
Market	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
tin	O
plate	O
worker	O
and	O
lamp	O
lighter	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
of	O
late	O
lost	O
several	O
quantities	O
of	O
oil	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
July	O
my	O
servant	O
Richard	B-pers
Parks	I-pers
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
pot	O
with	O
six	O
quarts	O
of	O
oil	O
conceal	O
'd	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
suspected	O
was	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
watch	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
without	O
his	O
seeing	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
inquire	O
of	O
all	O
the	O
others	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
that	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
has	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
to	O
the	O
indictment	O
(	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
apprentices	O
)	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
two	O
quarts	O
of	O
my	O
lamp	O
oil	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
for	O
two	O
pence	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
him	O
two	O
quarts	O
for	O
a	O
penny	O
a	O
quart	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
oil	O
worth	O
per	O
quart	O
?	O
Richard	O
's	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
worth	O
7	O
d.	O
or	O
8	O
d.	O
per	O
quart	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
two	O
sorts	O
at	O
those	O
prices	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
justice	O
St.	O
Lawrance	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
beg	O
'd	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
never	O
buy	O
any	O
stolen	O
oil	O
any	O
more	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
that	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
buy	O
any	O
oil	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
drunk	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
pray	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
forgive	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
Weller	O
live	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
He	O
lives	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
master	O
lamp	O
lighter	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
few	O
lamps	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
parish	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
boy	O
committed	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
continue	O
there	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
kept	O
there	O
till	O
sessions	O
he	O
'd	O
be	O
spoil	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
be	O
sit	O
for	O
my	O
service	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
his	O
word	O
for	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
give	O
7	O
d.	O
per	O
quart	O
for	O
lamp	O
oil	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
can	O
be	O
calculated	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
20	O
l.	O
note	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
committed	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
note	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
bail	O
'd	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
value	O
the	O
oil	O
at	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
At	O
7	O
d.	O
or	O
8	O
d.	O
per	O
quart	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
commitment	O
1	O
s.	O
value	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
,	O
valued	O
the	O
two	O
quarts	O
at	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
14	O
d.	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
it	O
cost	O
me	O
14	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
but	O
2	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
two	O
quarts	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
boy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
He	O
agreed	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
the	O
court	O
the	O
very	O
words	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
.	O
Richards	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
2	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
under	O
such	O
a	O
gateway	O
in	O
Portland-street	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
mentioned	O
something	O
of	O
his	O
saying	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
drunk	O
,	O
mention	O
that	O
again	O
.	O
Richards	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
buy	O
it	O
for	O
that	O
price	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
drunk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
say	O
he	O
did	O
buy	O
it	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
He	O
immediately	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
proceed	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
lamps	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Portland-street	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
oil	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
some	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
much	O
to	O
spare	O
.	O
He	O
beg	O
'd	O
I	O
'd	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
some	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
two	O
quarts	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
2	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
sold	O
him	O
any	O
before	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
since	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
putting	O
oil	O
into	O
lamps	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
measured	O
it	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
measure	O
that	O
I	O
think	O
held	O
rather	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
;	O
he	O
himself	O
measured	O
out	O
eight	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
desire	O
you	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
any	O
more	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
know	O
you	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
He	O
knew	O
who	O
I	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
,	O
by	O
seeing	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
before	O
,	O
doing	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
business	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
enquire	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
or	O
he	O
whose	O
servant	O
you	O
was	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
frequently	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
many	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
almost	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
before	O
you	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Morris	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Seymore	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
before	O
justice	O
St.	O
Lawrance	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
buying	O
two	O
quarts	O
of	O
lamp	O
oil	O
of	O
this	O
boy	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
certainly	O
drunk	O
if	O
he	O
bought	O
oil	O
of	O
that	O
boy	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
wrote	O
his	O
mittimus	O
to	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
.	O
He	O
beg	O
'd	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
ever	O
bought	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
boy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
stolen	O
oil	O
?	O
Seymore	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
knowing	O
the	O
oil	O
being	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
boy	O
being	O
his	O
servant	O
?	O
Seymore	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
buying	O
the	O
oil	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
bought	O
any	O
oil	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
20	O
l.	O
note	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
on	O
condition	O
he	O
ever	O
bought	O
oil	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
servants	O
?	O
Seymore	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
``	O
Mr.	O
Richards	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
``	O
a	O
note	O
under	O
my	O
hand	O
never	O
to	O
buy	O
any	O
more	O
``	O
oil	O
of	O
your	O
boy	O
.	O
''	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lives	O
?	O
Seymore	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
bail	O
'd	O
?	O
Seymore	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
about	O
frequently	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
bail	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
surrender	O
here	O
?	O
Seymore	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
two	O
bail	O
coming	O
from	O
his	O
house	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
surrender	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
make	O
any	O
attempt	O
to	O
escape	O
?	O
Seymore	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Sumerset	O
.	O
Lamp	O
oil	O
at	O
present	O
is	O
worth	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
a	O
gallon	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
it	O
was	O
worth	O
7	O
d.	O
per	O
quart	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
that	O
boy	O
,	O
nor	O
bought	O
a	O
drop	O
of	O
oil	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
days	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
call	O
'd	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Slone	I-pers
,	O
four	O
;	O
Henry	B-pers
Bevin	I-pers
,	O
about	O
eight	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Savage	I-pers
,	O
five	O
;	O
Richard	B-pers
Cruson	I-pers
,	O
about	O
nine	O
;	O
Robert	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
about	O
eight	O
;	O
Jacob	B-pers
Lewin	I-pers
,	O
twelve	O
;	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Rhodes	I-pers
,	O
near	O
eight	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Blisden	I-pers
,	O
above	O
five	O
;	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
almost	O
two	O
;	O
and	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
317	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
6	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Clare-Market	B-place
.	O
This	O
Ann	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
stole	O
a	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
this	O
gown	O
?	O
Cane	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'n-night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
it	O
from	O
?	O
Cane	O
.	O
From	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cellar	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'n-night	O
?	O
Cane	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
there	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'n-night	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
that	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
so	O
?	O
Cane	O
.	O
Last	O
Wednesday	O
was	O
se'n-night	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
gown	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
Cane	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
gown	O
was	O
found	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
gown	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'n-night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
?	O
C.	O
Cane	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
cellar	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
it	O
before	O
you	O
missed	O
it	O
?	O
C.	O
Cane	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
about	O
ten	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
C.	O
Cane	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
again	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Cane	O
.	O
Because	O
the	O
man	O
next	O
door	O
pected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
nobody	O
went	O
out	O
but	O
she	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
in	O
;	O
and	O
mistrusting	O
her	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
gown	O
?	O
Cane	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
that	O
she	O
pledg	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
has	O
it	O
here	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
gown	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
and	O
never	O
was	O
mended	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
's	O
servants	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
gown	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'n-night	O
,	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
September	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
before	O
ten	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
?	O
Coates	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
before	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
?	O
Coates	O
.	O
Another	O
woman	O
,	O
named	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
me	O
for	O
the	O
gown	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
reckon	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
this	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
property	O
.	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
sent	O
his	O
man	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
speak	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
as	O
possible	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
gown	O
if	O
she	O
work	O
'd	O
her	O
fingers	O
to	O
the	O
bone	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
interceed	O
with	O
the	O
justice	O
to	O
forgive	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
compound	O
felony	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
Coates	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
her	O
say	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
had	O
two	O
shillings	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
acknowledge	O
that	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
from	O
Cane	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
318	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Israel	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
gold	O
headed	O
cane	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
10	O
,	O
1756	O
.	O
+	O
Christopher	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Black-Fryars	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Hatfield	O
Street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
1756	O
.	O
He	O
followed	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
at	O
ten	O
or	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
says	O
he	O
,	O
``	O
What	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
?	O
''	O
Says	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know.	O
``	O
By	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
says	O
he	O
but	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
''	O
and	O
snatched	O
my	O
cane	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
by	O
main	O
force	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
a	O
gold	O
head	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
this	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
from	O
whence	O
he	O
came	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
cane	O
.	O
He	O
wrap	O
'd	O
the	O
string	O
round	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
wife	O
there	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
any	O
words	O
or	O
threatenings	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
landlord	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
there	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
nor	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
nor	O
his	O
servants	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
had	O
any	O
quarrel	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
He	O
defrauded	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
20	O
l.	O
bank	O
note	O
just	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
myself	O
down	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
cane	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Walker	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
cane	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
amends	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
another	O
cane	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
cane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
it	O
by	O
force	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
this	O
happen	O
'd	O
you	O
had	O
an	O
inclination	O
to	O
marry	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
not	O
lend	O
you	O
some	O
money	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
licence	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
two	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
arrested	O
me	O
for	O
42	O
l.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
settle	O
accounts	O
together	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
We	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
accounts	O
to	O
settle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
not	O
married	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
call	O
it	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
who	O
gave	O
your	O
wife	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
father	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
this	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
he	O
took	O
your	O
cane	O
,	O
by	O
force	O
as	O
you	O
say	O
.	O
Barnard	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
before	O
No	O
.	O
63	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Rawlinson	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
]	O
319	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Singleton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Timothy	B-pers
Lebeau	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Timothy	O
,	O
August	O
3	O
.	O
*	O
Timothy	O
Lebeau	O
.	O
I	O
keep	B-place
a	I-place
publick-house	I-place
the	I-place
upper	I-place
end	I-place
of	I-place
Brick-Lane	I-place
,	I-place
Bethnal-Green	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
about	O
six	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
people	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
missing	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
described	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
a	O
lad	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
believed	O
his	O
father	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
tankard	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
sale	O
,	O
cut	O
in	O
pieces	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
lad	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Lebeau	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
's	O
father	O
met	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Gun	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Thistle	O
and	O
Crown	O
in	O
Kingsland	O
Road	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
gentleman	O
described	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
next	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
answer	O
'd	O
the	O
description	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
greasy	O
place	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
shoulder	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
where	O
is	O
the	O
plate	O
which	O
you	O
offer	O
'd	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
little	O
hesitation	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
named	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mercier	I-pers
and	O
Stephen	O
Dempure	O
,	O
witnesses	O
here	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
they	O
knew	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
would	O
swear	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
they	O
suspected	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Keys	O
charge	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
.	O
This	O
plate	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
being	O
afraid	O
the	O
building	O
would	O
fall	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
old	O
place	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
people	O
followed	O
him	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up-stairs	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
open	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
cypher	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
takes	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
)	O
There	O
was	O
only	O
this	O
cypher	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
late	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
.	O
While	O
we	O
were	O
waiting	O
at	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
saw	O
Sir	O
Samuel	O
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
handle	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
tankard	O
?	O
Lebeau	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
bag	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
ask	O
'd	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
carry	O
it	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
fuddled	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
.	O
Sir	O
Samuel	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
these	O
small	O
pieces	O
:	O
He	O
said	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
that	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
cut	O
it	O
into	O
these	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
off	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Mercier	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
my	O
landlord	O
's	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
some	O
drummers	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
made	O
a	O
collection	O
upon	O
the	O
drum	O
head	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
down	O
a	O
penny	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
full	O
pots	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
they	O
been	O
beating	O
there	O
on	O
any	O
occasion	O
?	O
Mercier	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
had	O
been	O
married	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
beat	O
.	O
After	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
the	O
beer	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
two	O
pots	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
tankard	O
had	O
they	O
their	O
beer	O
in	O
,	O
that	O
which	O
was	O
missing	O
or	O
another	O
?	O
Mercier	O
.	O
In	O
that	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
only	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
then	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
missed	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
Mercier	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodgings	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
suspected	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
missing	O
when	O
the	O
tankard	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
Then	O
fifteen	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
officer	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
?	O
Mercier	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
past	O
there	O
?	O
Mercier	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
recollect	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dempure	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
drummers	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
during	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
bag	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
round	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
carroty	O
beard	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
collection	O
made	O
for	O
money	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
drummers	O
drink	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
round	O
with	O
his	O
drum	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
a	O
penny	O
on	O
the	O
drum	O
head	O
,	O
we	O
gather	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
spent	O
it	O
in	O
beer	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
tankard	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
silver	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
lid	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
handed	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
turn	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
him	O
the	O
tankard	O
;	O
so	O
it	O
went	O
about	O
from	O
one	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sat	O
upon	O
a	O
chair	O
with	O
his	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
chimney	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
to	O
him	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
got	O
talking	O
about	O
one	O
thing	O
or	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
tankard	O
afterwards	O
,	O
nor	O
did	O
I	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
but	O
soon	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
tankards	O
was	O
missing	O
by	O
his	O
maid	O
;	O
he	O
inquir	O
'd	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
people	O
.	O
I	O
described	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
.	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
)	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
note	O
his	O
tankard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
whom	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
tankard	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
drinking	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Mercier	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
maid	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
tankard	O
must	O
have	O
stuck	O
to	O
his	O
bag	O
,	O
for	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
who	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
d	O
-	O
'd	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
to	O
him	O
work	O
'd	O
about	O
it	O
all	O
night	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
Dempure	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
understand	O
what	O
he	O
meant	O
by	O
that	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
to	O
carry	O
some	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Reeve	O
.	O
In	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
pewterer	O
's	O
shop	O
My	O
wife	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Reeve	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
He	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
this	O
bit	O
of	O
silver	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
handle	O
)	O
I	O
touch	O
'd	O
it	O
upon	O
an	O
oil	O
stone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
desire	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
he	O
offer	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
Reeve	O
.	O
He	O
offer	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
silver	O
;	O
he	O
weigh	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
about	O
4	O
s.	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
may	O
venture	O
to	O
give	O
3	O
s.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
tom-turd-hole	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
scrupulous	O
of	O
buying	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
read	O
in	O
the	O
Newspaper	O
of	O
a	O
quart	O
silver	O
tankard	O
being	O
stole	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
thither	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
affair	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
said	O
was	O
truth	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cavit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
was	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
this	O
silver	O
(	O
here	O
produced	O
)	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gower	I-pers
,	O
where	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
stuck	O
to	O
his	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
more	O
?	O
Cavit	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
crowd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
hits	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
I	O
make	O
pegs	O
for	O
the	O
heels	O
for	O
shoemakers	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
like	O
a	O
fair	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
coming	O
in	O
and	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
39	O
s	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
320	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Curry	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
forty	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
cherries	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
wicker	O
sieve	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
July	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
The	O
cherries	O
belong	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Kent	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
Isaac	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
,	O
who	O
are	O
watchmen	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-Market	O
;	O
and	O
what	O
is	O
lost	O
we	O
are	O
obliged	O
to	O
answer	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
cherries	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
he	O
drop	O
'd	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Goodman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
assist	O
Garret	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
cherries	O
?	O
Goodman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
thrown	O
them	O
down	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
cherries	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
carrying	O
a	O
load	O
from	O
the	O
water	O
side	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
crowd	O
of	O
us	O
all	O
together	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
has	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
spight	O
these	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
spight	O
.	O
He	O
call	O
'd	O
Bridget	B-pers
Rion	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Branagan	I-pers
,	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Fitzpatrick	I-pers
,	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
who	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
321	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dumble	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
dozen	O
of	O
concave	O
glasses	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
temple	O
spectacles	O
,	O
two	O
fishskin	O
cases	O
,	O
twelve	O
spectacles	O
,	O
six	O
dozen	O
of	O
horn	O
frames	O
for	O
spectacles	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
reading	O
glass	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Leonard	B-pers
Ballit	I-pers
,	O
July	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
Leonard	B-pers
Ballit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
optician	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Crown	B-place
alehouse	I-place
in	I-place
Duck-Lane	I-place
with	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
occasion	O
to	O
step	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
goods	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
Mr.	O
Owen	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
coming	O
out	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
landlady	O
to	O
know	O
where	O
my	O
friend	O
was	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
landlady	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
flung	O
down	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
his	O
liquor	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
before	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Ballit	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
but	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
Bride	O
's	O
Alley	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-mayor	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
the	O
words	O
he	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
?	O
Ballit	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
them	O
lie	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
knowing	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
take	O
them	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
parcel	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
backwards	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
parcel	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
him	O
out	O
from	O
a	O
dozen	O
people	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Mansion-House	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Vanderbus	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
flung	O
down	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wigget	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
barber	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
taylor	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
one	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
something	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
them	O
and	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
spectacles	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
another	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
branch	O
of	O
the	O
trade	O
,	O
who	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
advised	O
us	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
alone	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
they	O
would	O
be	O
advertised	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
want	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
pawn	O
them	O
till	O
we	O
can	O
hear	O
farther	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wilmot	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
pawnbroker	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
One	O
pair	O
of	O
spectacles	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
and	O
given	O
to	O
other	O
persons	O
:	O
When	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
own	O
'd	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
tell	O
you	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
?	O
Wigget	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
over-against	O
the	O
Golden-Lion	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
upon	O
Holbourn-Hill	O
,	O
three	O
doors	O
beyond	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
's	O
Church	O
gate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
Crown	O
in	O
Duck-Lane	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
doors	O
,	O
one	O
goes	O
out	O
into	O
Bartholomew-Close	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Polock	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
Mr.	O
Wigget	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wigget	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
has	O
had	O
the	O
luck	O
to	O
find	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
them	O
;	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
judge	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
be	O
so	O
good	O
as	O
to	O
tell	O
us	O
what	O
they	O
are	O
worth	O
.	O
I	O
advised	O
them	O
not	O
to	O
part	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
stay	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
advertised	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
door	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
about	O
some	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
come	O
to	O
us	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Wigget	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Wigget	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
put	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
paper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
whose	O
direction	O
did	O
you	O
pawn	O
them	O
?	O
Polock	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
direction	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
Mr.	O
Wigget	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
we	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
somewhere	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
opposite	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
beer	O
was	O
out	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Wigget	O
paid	O
3	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
r	O
est	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pearcey	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Wigget	O
came	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Polock	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
these	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Wigget	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
poor	O
man	O
that	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
was	O
in	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
would	O
be	O
acceptable	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
pinch	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Wigget	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
some	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
workmen	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
more	O
.	O
These	O
goods	O
lay	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
lay	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
some	O
strange	O
person	O
had	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
people	O
that	O
work	O
'd	O
in	O
these	O
sort	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
they	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ballit	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
shaved	O
at	O
this	O
Mr.	O
Wigget	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
.	O
They	O
would	O
have	O
me	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
kept	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
Saturday	O
till	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
thinking	O
they	O
might	O
be	O
advertised	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
own	O
'd	O
them	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
consented	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
322.	O
Robert	B-pers
Boyd	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
trunk	O
,	O
cover	O
'd	O
with	O
leather	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
suit	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
cloth	O
apparel	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
six	O
ruffled	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
five	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
four	O
holland	O
night-caps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
nine	O
pair	O
of	O
worstead	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
laced	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
full	O
suits	O
of	O
silk	O
women	O
's	O
apparel	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
two	O
linen	O
sacks	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
three	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
nine	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
ten	O
linen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
gloves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
ten	O
night-caps	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
pocket	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Edmund	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
,	O
August	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Edmund	B-pers
Francis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
hired	O
a	O
hackney	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
were	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
fasten	O
the	O
trunk	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Saracen's-Head	O
in	O
Friday-Street	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
The	O
trunk	O
with	O
all	O
in	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
Church	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Francis	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-mayor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
the	O
greatest	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
there	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Francis	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
answer	O
did	O
he	O
make	O
?	O
Francis	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
his	O
answer	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
trunk	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
August	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
E.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Field	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
sale	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
some	O
shirts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
E.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
nor	O
since	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dress	O
'd	O
?	O
E.	O
Wood	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
laced	O
hat	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
footman	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
see	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
these	O
are	O
too	O
good	O
for	O
left	O
off	O
shirts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
court	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
laced	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
.	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
these	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
trunk	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
bring	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
them	O
here	O
.	O
This	O
hat	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stockings	O
on	O
his	O
legs	O
when	O
taken	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Holland	O
since	O
the	O
trunk	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
E.	O
Wood	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
if	O
the	O
shirts	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
truth	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
lieutenant	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
away	O
for	O
debt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
well	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
he	O
could	O
shew	O
me	O
his	O
protection	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
read	O
.	O
He	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
I	O
read	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
Edmburgh	O
,	O
Alexander	O
Robertson	O
discharg	O
'd	O
,	O
dated	O
1755	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
understand	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
whether	O
these	O
shirts	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
or	O
waggon	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
by	O
the	O
Chester	O
waggon	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
put	O
up	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
Inn	O
,	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
were	O
there	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
E.	O
Wood	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
agreed	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
change	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
change	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
more	O
things	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
spare	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'd	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
might	O
let	O
it	O
alone	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
.	O
So	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
guinea	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
box	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
but	O
just	O
come	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
a	O
box	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
an	O
inn	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
that	O
to	O
save	O
charges	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
return	O
'd	O
with	O
a	O
great	O
trunk	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
big	O
enough	O
to	O
hold	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
people	O
.	O
He	O
put	O
it	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
six	O
shifts	O
,	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
six	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
border	O
'd	O
with	O
red	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
up	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
brother	O
at	O
the	O
Indies	O
made	O
him	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
neckcloths	O
and	O
some	O
stockings	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
some	O
womens	O
cloaths	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
womens	O
coaths	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
got	O
a	O
wife	O
I	O
said	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
far	O
off	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
Inn	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
touch	O
them	O
till	O
you	O
bring	O
her	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
afraid	O
you	O
have	O
strip	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
her	O
behind	O
you	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
41	O
s.	O
for	O
six	O
shifts	O
,	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
.	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
surprised	O
,	O
having	O
nobody	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
a	O
Barber	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
the	O
prisoner	O
but	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
So	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
come	O
again	O
for	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
He	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
leave	O
the	O
trunk	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
permit	O
that	O
,	O
it	O
having	O
been	O
left	O
at	O
a	O
cellar	O
unlock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
be	O
blam	O
'd	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
any	O
paper	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Printer	O
of	O
the	O
Daily	O
Advertiser	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
three	O
shillings	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
put	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
paper	O
being	O
full	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
till	O
the	O
Friday	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Advertiser	O
a	O
trunk	O
lost	O
,	O
the	O
size	O
of	O
this	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
as	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
glad	O
to	O
deliver	O
him	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
bought	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Thornber	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Black	O
Bull	O
in	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
smoaking	O
a	O
pipe	O
with	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
came	O
a	O
porter	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
trunk	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
August	B-pers
He	I-pers
asked	O
me	O
if	O
a	O
gentleman	O
could	O
have	O
a	O
lodging	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
nobody	O
but	O
himself	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
the	O
trunk	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
then	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
wanted	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
I	O
chang	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
porter	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
porter	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
drink	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
full	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
eat	O
some	O
buttock	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
hungry	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
shoes	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
stockings	O
here	O
produc	O
'd	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
dirty	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
laced	O
hat	O
(	O
thinks	O
I	O
this	O
is	O
some	O
post	O
chaise	O
affair	O
)	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
questions	O
,	O
first	O
what	O
countryman	O
,	O
-	O
Chester	O
,	O
-	O
how	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
,	O
-	O
by	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
-	O
how	O
far	O
have	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
day	O
,	O
-	O
twenty	O
miles	O
,	O
-	O
that	O
stage	O
must	O
run	O
fifty	O
or	O
sixty	O
miles	O
a	O
day	O
,	O
-	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
-	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
up	O
,	O
-	O
