TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
13th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Thirty-second	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1758	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ASGILL	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
.	O
1758	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
General	O
Sessions	B-pers
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
,	O
the	O
Right-Honourable	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ASGILL	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
JOHN	B-pers
WILLES	I-pers
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common-Pleas	O
*	O
;	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
and	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Streams	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Stagg	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bundey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Burdett	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Ringwood	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Weal	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beatson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fletcher	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pultney	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cooke	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Simmons	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Wale	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wesly	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Filewood	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
.	O
257	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Isabella	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Butler	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
August	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
being	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
she	O
carried	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
carried	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
hours	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
trifle	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
got	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
her	O
name	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
Margaret	O
or	O
Mary	B-pers
Cuddy	I-pers
;	O
the	O
house	O
is	O
on	O
Salt-petre-bank	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Carty	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
,	O
by	O
Mr.	O
King	O
's	O
order	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Worcester-street	O
,	O
Old-Gravel-lane	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
Scott	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
afterwards	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
bring	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
small	O
trifle	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
back	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
print	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
feet	O
going	O
out	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
258.	O
Millicent	B-pers
Elisby	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
tabby	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Letitia	B-pers
Badslade	I-pers
,	O
May	O
25	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
acquitted	O
;	O
the	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
259.	O
Mary	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Douglass	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Lardeer	I-pers
,	O
July	O
5	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
acquitted	O
;	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
260.	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joshua	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
acquitted	O
;	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
261.	O
Anne	B-pers
Sewton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
cap	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
four	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
acquitted	O
;	O
his	O
recognizance	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
262.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
allopean	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Graven	I-pers
,	O
June	O
25	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
263.	O
Edward	B-pers
Barton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
trusses	O
of	O
hay	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
August	O
8	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
appeared	O
,	O
acquitted	O
.	O
264	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Michael	B-pers
Drawater	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
wooden	O
chest	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
one	O
fustian	O
frock	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
fustian	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
four	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
,	O
July	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
Abraham	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Haunch	B-place
of	I-place
Venison	I-place
Yard	I-place
,	I-place
Lower	I-place
Brook-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
post-chaises	O
and	O
saddle-horses	O
to	O
let	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
locked	O
up	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
names	O
them	O
over	O
with	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
each	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
seven	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
at	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
liberty	O
to	O
lie	O
a	O
night	O
or	O
two	O
in	O
my	O
hay-loft	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
fellow	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
missing	O
when	O
the	O
chest	O
was	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
coats	O
and	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
also	O
told	O
us	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Procter	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
sold	O
me	O
this	O
frock	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
13	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
the	O
frock	O
and	O
breeches	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
but	O
a	O
9	O
s.	O
piece	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
265	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Wyman	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
china	O
coffee-cups	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
seventy-two	O
china	O
tea-cups	O
,	O
and	O
seventy-two	O
china	O
saucers	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Vere	I-pers
,	O
July	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Vere	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
china-shop	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
China	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
between	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
detected	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
produced	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
them	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
divers	O
others	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
a	O
declaration	O
who	O
was	O
the	O
receiver	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
;	O
the	O
court	O
of	O
Conservancy	O
was	O
sitting	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
city	O
magistrate	O
,	O
so	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Anson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Vere	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
china	O
dish	O
missing	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
examined	O
us	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
sent	O
us	O
down	O
after	O
this	O
into	O
the	O
warehouse	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
farther	O
in	O
it	O
then	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
some	O
time	O
there	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
set	O
my	O
foot	O
on	O
his	O
basket	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
china	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
coffee-cup	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
take	O
the	O
rest	O
out	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
nine	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
before	O
seventy	O
two	O
cups	O
,	O
and	O
seventy	O
two	O
saucers	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
Guilty	O
;	O
he	O
received	O
sentence	O
to	O
be	O
branded	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
branded	O
accordingly	O
.	O
266	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Briner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
seventy	O
two	O
cups	O
,	O
and	O
seventy	O
two	O
saucers	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
said	O
Richard	B-pers
Wyman	I-pers
,	O
July	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
[	O
The	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
trial	O
and	O
conviction	O
of	O
Wyman	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
wherein	O
it	O
specifies	O
he	O
pleaded	O
not	O
guilty	O
,	O
put	O
himself	O
upon	O
his	O
country	O
,	O
the	O
jurors	O
say	O
Guilty	O
;	O
judgment	O
to	O
be	O
branded	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
branded	O
accordingly	O
.	O
]	O
Richard	B-pers
Wyman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Vere	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
convicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
seventy	O
two	O
cups	O
and	O
seventy	O
two	O
saucers	O
,	O
laid	O
in	O
this	O
indictment	O
.	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
coffee-cups	O
,	O
the	O
coffee-cups	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
basket	O
unknown	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
intention	O
of	O
stealing	O
them	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
happened	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
missed	O
a	O
blue	O
china	O
dish	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
seventy	O
two	O
china	O
cups	O
,	O
and	O
seventy	O
two	O
saucers	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
them	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
9th	O
or	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
them	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
cost	O
you	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
Some	O
cost	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
4	O
s.	O
a	O
half	O
dozen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
buy	O
them	O
all	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
at	O
two	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
seven	O
half	O
dozens	O
at	O
one	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
the	O
first	O
parcel	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
but	O
one	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
parcel	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
per	O
half	O
dozen	O
for	O
part	O
of	O
each	O
parcel	O
.	O
They	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
July	O
cost	O
me	O
25	O
s.	O
the	O
other	O
cost	O
me	O
16	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
buy	O
both	O
parcels	O
of	O
one	O
woman	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
the	O
first	O
parcel	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
buy	O
the	O
second	O
parcel	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
forenoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
going	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
met	O
this	O
woman	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
some	O
business	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
into	O
the	O
town	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
which	O
way	O
you	O
was	O
going	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Cheapside	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
was	O
you	O
going	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
her	O
without	O
Temple-bar	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
appoint	O
her	O
to	O
meet	O
you	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
her	O
both	O
times	O
by	O
accident	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
offer	O
these	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
ask	O
her	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
She	O
offered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
saw	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
china-basket	O
on	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
she	O
carry	O
her	O
china	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
these	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
this	O
sessions	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
after	O
you	O
bought	O
them	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Briner	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
business	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
He	O
keeps	O
an	O
earthen-ware	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
one	O
parcel	O
the	O
12th	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
him	O
some	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
sell	O
the	O
first	O
parcel	O
for	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
the	O
first	O
seven	O
sets	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
agreed	O
,	O
some	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
some	O
3	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
per	O
set	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
guinea	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
part	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
agree	O
on	O
that	O
the	O
next	O
time	O
we	O
met	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
deal	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
deliver	O
them	O
without	O
making	O
an	O
absolute	O
bargain	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
then	O
in	O
part	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
that	O
you	O
bought	O
them	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
but	O
one	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
between	O
the	O
9th	O
and	O
the	O
12th	O
.	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
shew	O
them	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
carried	O
them	O
directly	O
to	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
sell	O
the	O
rest	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
afterwards	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
truly	O
say	O
which	O
day	O
that	O
was	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
five	O
sets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
For	O
how	O
much	O
did	O
you	O
sell	O
them	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Briner	O
was	O
not	O
within	O
when	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
them	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
any	O
word	O
with	O
her	O
when	O
you	O
left	O
them	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
call	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Briner	O
ever	O
receive	O
of	O
you	O
any	O
cups	O
or	O
saucers	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
I	O
stole	O
any	O
.	O
C.	O
for	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
steal	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
wronged	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
this	O
two	O
years	O
or	O
better	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
before	O
you	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Vere	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
I	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
silversmith	O
before	O
near	O
Temple-bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
know	O
that	O
you	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Vere	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
bought	O
these	O
things	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
know	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
ask	O
you	O
any	O
questions	O
when	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
first	O
parcel	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Wyman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
asked	O
me	O
who	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
of	O
a	O
sailor	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Vere	O
.	O
This	O
evidence	O
confess	O
'd	O
the	O
taking	O
these	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
detected	O
,	O
before	O
abundance	O
of	O
witnesses	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
produce	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
besides	O
his	O
confession	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
receiving	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
?	O
Vere	O
.	O
The	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
from	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
,	O
Wyman	O
,	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
china	O
from	O
the	O
different	O
shelves	O
in	O
th	O
e	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Vere	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Arthur	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Arthur	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
those	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
on	O
different	O
shelves	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
the	O
China	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
found	O
them	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
Wyman	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
shelves	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Vere	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Vere	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
patterns	O
and	O
kinds	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
great	O
number	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
identity	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
any	O
other	O
of	O
the	O
trade	O
may	O
have	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
patterns	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
confession	O
of	O
Wyman	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
A	O
confession	O
out	O
of	O
court	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
beyond	O
what	O
he	O
swears	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Vere	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
several	O
sets	O
of	O
china	O
of	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
those	O
he	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
seven	O
sets	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
five	O
sets	O
were	O
brought	O
afterwards	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
.	O
Before	O
justice	O
Sydenham	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
Wyman	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
a	O
china-man	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
with	O
whom	O
;	O
he	O
afterwards	O
said	O
otherwise	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
by	O
the	O
price	O
that	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
intention	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
acquaint	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
second	O
time	O
of	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
five	O
sets	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
Friday	O
or	O
Saturday	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
examined	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
on	O
a	O
bulk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
those	O
seven	O
sets	O
of	O
cups	O
and	O
saucers	O
?	O
Vear	O
.	O
They	O
cost	O
me	O
on	O
an	O
average	O
about	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
set	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
part	O
for	O
the	O
first	O
parcel	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
267	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
linen	O
clouts	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
September	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Edwards	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Grays-inn-lane	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
grocer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
another	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
her	O
examined	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
none	O
of	O
her	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
(	O
she	O
produced	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
lock	O
'd	O
?	O
Evans	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Anne	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
take	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
?	O
Wood	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
268	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Butterworth	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
indico	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Longden	I-pers
,	O
July	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Longden	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
;	O
about	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
July	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
about	O
the	O
quantity	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
indico	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Longden	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
Longden	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
dye	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
blue	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Mr.	O
alderman	O
Chitty	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
enquired	O
since	O
,	O
and	O
find	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
offence	O
I	O
ever	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Badder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
company	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
belonged	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Badder	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
better	O
than	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
by	O
him	O
but	O
civility	O
and	O
honesty	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
269	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Margaret	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
did	O
burglariously	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
small	O
knife	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
gold	O
ear-ring	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
five	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
one	O
three	O
pound	O
twelve	O
,	O
eighteen	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
pieces	O
,	O
ten	O
moidores	O
,	O
fifty	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
forty	O
shillings	O
,	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Margaret	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
laid	O
over	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
,	O
did	O
burglariously	O
break	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
.	O
*	O
Margaret	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Mary	I-place
Ax	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
an	O
alehouse	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
rob	O
'd	O
of	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
who	O
rob	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
above	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
At	O
12	O
o'clock	O
;	O
and	O
arose	O
at	O
7	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
house	O
broke	O
open	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
My	O
maid	O
got	O
up	O
first	O
;	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
my	O
cellar	O
door	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
bolted	O
with	O
two	O
bolts	O
,	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
found	O
my	O
keys	O
thrown	O
about	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
brought	O
them	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
till	O
of	O
my	O
table	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
bed-side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
those	O
several	O
places	O
that	O
those	O
keys	O
lock	O
'd	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
These	O
were	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
my	O
cupboards	O
,	O
and	O
places	O
where	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
liquors	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
key	O
where	O
your	O
money	O
was	O
kept	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bureau	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
double	O
lock	O
'd	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
bureau	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
bed	O
's	O
feet	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
I	O
lie	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
lock	O
spoiled	O
and	O
all	O
my	O
money	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
all	O
this	O
money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
in	O
that	O
bureau	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
some	O
in	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
appear	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
forced	O
open	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
By	O
pulling	O
,	O
the	O
wood	O
was	O
forced	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
smith	O
to	O
mend	O
it	O
.	O
My	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
teaspoons	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
at	O
my	O
bed	O
's	O
foot	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
ear-ring	O
and	O
little	O
knife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
missed	O
all	O
this	O
money	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
friends	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
advertise	O
my	O
loss	O
.	O
After	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
out	O
of	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
this	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
gold	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
all	O
new	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
changed	O
his	O
old	O
ones	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
name	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
only	O
described	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
your	O
service	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
about	O
fourteen	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
guess	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
A	O
neighbour	O
stood	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
is	O
your	O
Jack	O
that	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
upon	O
that	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
knife	O
and	O
an	O
ear-ring	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
fetch	O
them	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
you	O
may	O
know	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
.	O
Then	O
my	O
neighbours	O
set	O
out	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
they	O
searched	O
him	O
where	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
,	O
as	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
22	O
l.	O
and	O
some	O
half-pence	O
,	O
which	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
this	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
found	O
my	O
buckles	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
along	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
changed	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
three	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
9	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Linstead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
crooked-billet	O
,	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stocking-maker	O
by	O
trade	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
little	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
sell	O
linen	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
bought	O
also	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
stock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
hat	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Boyce	O
,	O
and	O
changed	O
a	O
three	O
pound	O
twelve	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Linstead	O
.	O
Both	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Boyce	O
told	O
me	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
suit	O
of	O
cloaths	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Johnson	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
cloaths	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Johnson	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
these	O
cloaths	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
be	O
shaved	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
all	O
his	O
new	O
cloaths	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
He	O
returned	O
and	O
shifted	O
himself	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
backwards	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handful	O
of	O
broad	O
pieces	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
told	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
moment	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
five	O
hours	O
in	O
this	O
lane	O
laying	O
out	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
received	O
40	O
l.	O
and	O
have	O
taken	O
10	O
shillings	O
in	O
half-pence	O
.	O
Next	O
morning	O
I	O
read	O
the	O
advertisement	O
of	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
's	O
losing	O
130	O
l.	O
in	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Ax	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
her	O
with	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
observed	O
.	O
I	O
describ	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
mentioning	O
spoons	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
spoons	O
gone	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
She	O
and	O
the	O
servants	O
said	O
,	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
Jack	O
,	O
or	O
John	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
all	O
his	O
old	O
cloaths	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
ear-ring	O
and	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
knife	O
and	O
ear-ring	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
servants	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
put	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
square	O
silver	O
buckles	O
into	O
his	O
shoes	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
round	O
ones	O
on	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
buckles	O
were	O
yours	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
square	O
ones	O
.	O
Linstead	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
buckles	O
that	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
his	O
shoes	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
,	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
spoons	O
away	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
new	O
buckles	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
where	O
he	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
amongst	O
a	O
number	O
of	O
buckles	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
them	O
out	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
here	O
and	O
will	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
knife	O
and	O
ear-ring	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
sixteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
next	O
January	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
penny-worth	O
of	O
beer	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
drew	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
followed	O
me	O
down	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
another	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
draw	O
some	O
more	O
beer	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
left	O
below	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
candle	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
there	O
I	O
believe	O
ten	O
minutes	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
little-house	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
drank	O
his	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
afterwards	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
neighbour	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Tom	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
leave	O
your	O
cellar	O
window	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
it	O
open	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
shut	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
lock	O
to	O
that	O
cellar	O
door	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
large	O
bolts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
bolted	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
King	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
the	O
cellar	O
window	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
?	O
King	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
a	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
just	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
six	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
dial	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
cellar	O
;	O
one	O
has	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
beer	O
.	O
Going	O
to	O
step	O
into	O
the	O
necessary	O
,	O
I	O
kicked	O
something	O
before	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
keys	O
;	O
I	O
groped	O
about	O
being	O
dark	O
,	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
some	O
large	O
and	O
some	O
small	O
ones	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
keys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
window	O
bolted	O
?	O
Draper	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
bolted	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
never	O
opened	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
brewers	O
come	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
your	O
cellar	O
window	O
is	O
open	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
my	O
mistress	O
was	O
murdered	O
,	O
and	O
dared	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
her	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
before	O
she	O
answered	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
side	O
on	O
her	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
keys	O
off	O
the	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
missed	O
her	O
gold	O
and	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
her	O
things	O
on	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
flutter	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
he	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
shoes	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
down	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
money	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
half-penny	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
neither	O
gold	O
,	O
silver	O
,	O
or	O
brass	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
Mr.	O
Linstead	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
my	O
mistress	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
suspicion	O
of	O
any	O
body	O
committing	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
described	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
we	O
all	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Jack	B-pers
Downs	I-pers
.	O
He	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
ear-ring	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
knew	O
it	O
,	O
our	O
boy	O
having	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
owned	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
not	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
cellar	O
door	O
fast	O
?	O
Draper	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
chamber	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
wrench	O
'd	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
three	O
tea-spoons	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
square	O
silver	O
buckles	O
.	O
)	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
some	O
buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
golden	O
cup	O
at	O
Holborn-bridge	O
.	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
some	O
;	O
he	O
pitched	O
on	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
these	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
exchange	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
buckles	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
shoes	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
spoons	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
fellows	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
one	O
.	O
)	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
these	O
buckles	O
in	O
exchange	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
there	O
came	O
Mr.	O
Webb	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Linstead	O
to	O
demand	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
spoons	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Taylor	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
called	O
on	O
me	O
another	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Townshend	I-pers
,	O
Wine-merchant	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
we	O
had	O
intelligence	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
,	O
on	O
Sunday	O
and	O
Monday	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
of	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
neighbours	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
nineteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
four	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pence	O
in	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
found	O
several	O
bills	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
laying	O
out	O
money	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
about	O
20	O
l.	O
more	O
,	O
for	O
household	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
his	O
mistress	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
serve	O
her	O
so	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
good	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
hurt	O
you	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
above	O
70	O
l.	O
part	O
of	O
which	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
I	O
laid	O
out	O
for	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
amount	O
to	O
70	O
l.	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
spent	O
some	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Townshend	I-pers
,	O
Distiller	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
neighbour	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
gold	O
nineteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
four	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
three	O
pence	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
tradesmen	O
's	O
bills	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
21	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
++	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
upwards	O
of	O
70	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
New-market	O
;	O
the	O
buckles	O
and	O
tea-spoons	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
seventeen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
hear	O
d	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
very	O
harmless	O
lad	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
heard	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
flush	O
of	O
money	O
?	O
Hine	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
know	O
him	O
this	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Maclawlin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
almost	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
heard	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
-	O
Downs	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
father	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
seventeen	O
years	O
old	O
the	O
nineteenth	O
of	O
May	O
old	O
stile	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
270	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Finch	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
cambrick	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
bonnet	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
linnen	O
gowns	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Baptist	I-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Baptist	I-pers
Mason	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
she	O
absconded	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
my	O
wife	O
missed	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
linen	O
gowns	O
under	O
a	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
delivered	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
apron	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
ill	O
and	O
can	O
not	O
attend	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
which	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
(	O
that	O
was	O
,	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
of	O
these	O
goods	O
.	O
)	O
(	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
one	O
Frances	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
brought	O
and	O
pawned	O
this	O
gown	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
Frances	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
owned	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Frances	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
gown	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
to	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
give	O
her	O
that	O
gown	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
271	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Babb	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
sorrel	O
mare	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
August	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hackney	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
an	O
apothecary	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
mare	O
at	O
the	O
rails	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
at	O
Hackney	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
visiting	O
a	O
patient	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
hung	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
palisade	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
coming	O
by	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
again	O
held	O
by	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
observe	O
him	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
persons	O
disputing	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
one	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
good	O
reason	O
to	O
ask	O
him	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
stranger	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
purport	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
held	O
her	O
while	O
I	O
mounted	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
rode	O
on	O
2	O
or	O
300	O
yards	O
to	O
another	O
patient	O
;	O
I	O
ride	O
with	O
a	O
double	O
bridle	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
buckled	O
the	O
long	O
rein	O
to	O
a	O
rail	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
buckle	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
that	O
rein	O
.	O
I	O
staid	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
fifteen	O
minutes	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
the	O
mare	O
was	O
gone	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
bridle	O
remaining	O
on	O
the	O
rail	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
my	O
servant	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
next	O
day	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
little	O
or	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
mare	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
rein	O
of	O
the	O
bridle	O
?	O
Davis	O
.	O
The	O
rein	O
was	O
cut	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Pettit	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
the	O
mare	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
out	O
with	O
some	O
medicines	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
along	O
the	O
road	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
this	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
your	O
master	O
missed	O
her	O
?	O
Pettit	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
distance	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
lost	O
from	O
Mare-street	O
Hackney	O
,	O
opposite	O
Mr.	O
Batcheldor	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Pettit	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
going	O
towards	O
London	O
or	O
the	O
country	O
?	O
Pettit	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
towards	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
Essex	O
or	O
Hertfordshire	O
;	O
the	O
bridle	O
was	O
cut	O
and	O
hung	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
rode	O
in	O
danger	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
bridle	O
was	O
under	O
the	O
horse	O
's	O
feet	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
mare	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
near	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
satisfy	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
get	O
him	O
somebody	O
to	O
mend	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
discovered	O
the	O
mare	O
,	O
I	O
kept	O
him	O
in	O
discourse	O
till	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
mare	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Pettit	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
very	O
near	O
10	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
home	O
then	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Pettit	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
it	O
when	O
you	O
missed	O
the	O
mare	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
apprehend	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
her	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
more	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Pettit	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
that	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
mare	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
bridle	O
a	O
snatch	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Pettit	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
as	O
he	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
;	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
mare	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Covey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
the	O
second	O
Monday	O
in	O
August	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
leading	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
's	O
mare	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
leading	O
her	O
about	O
.	O
She	O
having	O
been	O
taken	O
from	O
my	O
door	O
but	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
,	O
made	O
me	O
the	O
more	O
inquisitive	O
about	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
led	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
foot	O
way	O
towards	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
one	O
Simpson	O
that	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
fancy	O
that	O
man	O
is	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
with	O
the	O
mare	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
swear	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
angry	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
troubling	O
myself	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
held	O
the	O
mare	O
while	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
mounted	O
;	O
and	O
rode	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
imagined	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
call	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
to	O
some	O
patient	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Simpson	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
we	O
first	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bosson	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Covey	O
,	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Church-road	O
at	O
Hackney	O
,	O
about	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
or	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
walking	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
's	O
horse	O
down	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
Covey	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
mare	O
was	O
stole	O
from	O
his	O
door	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
returned	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
mare	O
;	O
as	O
he	O
pass	O
'd	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
served	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
with	O
a	O
smith	O
.	O
He	O
walk	O
'd	O
her	O
into	O
Church-road	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
abuse	O
Mr	O
.	O
Covey	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
soon	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
mounted	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
away	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
told	O
Mr	O
.	O
Covey	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Hackney	O
all	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
coming	O
down	O
Mare-street	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
mare	O
loose	O
in	O
the	O
road	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
bridle	O
,	O
and	O
lead	O
her	O
down	O
towards	O
Church-street	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
past	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
mare	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
servant	O
stop	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
272	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Martin	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
,	O
June	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fenwick	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
off	O
the	O
Change	O
about	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Barnes	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
collar	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
something	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Barnes	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
this	O
person	O
has	O
got	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
his	O
feet	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barnes	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
gentleman	O
going	O
off	O
the	O
Change	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
gentleman	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
or	O
part	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
liberty	O
to	O
take	O
Mr.	O
Fenwick	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
he	O
after	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
(	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
we	O
saw	O
it	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
and	O
drop	O
it	O
down	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
saw	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
Barnes	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
time	O
enough	O
to	O
have	O
dropped	O
it	O
and	O
more	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
?	O
Barnes	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
his	O
hand	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Fenwick	O
's	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
so	O
quick	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
273	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Payne	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
pounds	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
mutton	O
fat	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Roughton	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
August	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Fleet-market	B-place
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
hundred	O
yards	O
running	O
,	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
pulled	O
out	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
keys	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
plyers	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
fourteen	O
pick-lock	O
keys	O
,	O
besides	O
one	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
taken	O
six	O
pounds	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
mutton	O
fat	O
,	O
(	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
bag	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
producing	O
one	O
,	O
)	O
the	O
fat	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
left	O
in	O
this	O
bag	O
on	O
the	O
block	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
keys	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
keys	O
?	O
Bradley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
man	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
Bradley	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
after	O
11	O
o'clock	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
young	O
man	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
we	O
searched	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
thirteen	O
keys	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
and	O
breeches	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Draper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
wardens	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
keys	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
pockets	O
,	O
and	O
breeches	O
knees	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
that	O
door	O
making	O
water	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
rush	O
'd	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
fall	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
keys	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
that	O
witness	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
business	O
I	O
had	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin's-lane	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodges	O
in	O
Castle-street	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
has	O
an	O
estate	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
about	O
30	O
l.	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
wronged	O
me	O
of	O
a	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
universal	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
his	O
estate	O
lie	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
near	O
Kingston	O
in	O
Surry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
with	O
all	O
these	O
keys	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
reputation	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Weatherly	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
does	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
fifteen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
received	O
Mrs.	O
Davis	O
's	O
rents	O
for	O
her	O
for	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
Kingston	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
oath	O
know	O
he	O
has	O
an	O
estate	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
has	O
served	O
ejectments	O
there	O
on	O
his	O
tenants	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cheesman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
fourteen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cooper	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
soberer	O
man	O
on	O
earth	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Bradley	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
you	O
saw	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Bradley	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
coming	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
274	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Newell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
leaden	O
pipe	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
cock	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
esq	O
;	O
fix	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
dwelling-house	O
in	O
the	O
occupation	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Cashen	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
August	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Cashen	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
leaden	O
pipe	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
cock	O
,	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
passage	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
landlord	O
Daniel	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
esq	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
,	O
but	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
seized	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
pipe	O
and	O
cock	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
;	O
a	O
lad	O
delivered	O
the	O
cock	O
and	O
pipe	O
in	O
Guild-Hall	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Cruse	I-pers
.	O
Acquitted	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pounds	O
of	O
leaden	O
pipe	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
cock	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hellin	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
The	O
two	O
principal	O
evidences	O
are	O
two	O
apprentices	O
that	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
lead	O
and	O
cocks	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
gone	O
from	O
us	O
since	O
we	O
have	O
been	O
attending	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
275.	O
Johanna	B-pers
Keeling	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
wilful	O
and	O
corrupt	O
perjury	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
appeared	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
276	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Burk	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Joseph	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	B-place
Butcher-row	I-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
;	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
paper	O
stomacher	O
;	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
,	O
she	O
fix	O
'd	O
upon	O
one	O
in	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
the	O
price	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
down	O
6	O
d.	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
while	O
she	O
thought	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
change	O
,	O
she	O
cheapened	O
some	O
ribbands	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
a	O
ribband	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
put	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
into	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
lie	O
?	O
Graham	O
.	O
They	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
under	O
the	O
shew-board	O
,	O
with	O
another	O
parcel	O
,	O
three	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
the	O
window	O
was	O
she	O
?	O
Graham	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Graham	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
compter	O
,	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
?	O
Graham	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
down	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
sister	O
,	O
that	O
waits	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
asked	O
another	O
gentlewoman	O
that	O
stood	O
near	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
willing	O
to	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Mistress	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
her	O
apron	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
one	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
them	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
them	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
names	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
produced	O
in	O
the	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
them	O
before	O
?	O
Graham	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
shewing	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
not	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Solomon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Graham	O
asked	O
her	O
after	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
these	O
your	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
bitch	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
them	O
at	O
her	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Graham	O
had	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
above	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
compter	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
in	O
again	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fault	O
she	O
ever	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
stomacher	O
,	O
and	O
brushing	O
against	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
fell	O
down	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
missed	O
her	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
them	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
stooped	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
crime	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
being	O
laid	O
only	O
a	O
single	O
felony	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
on	O
that	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
277	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
,	O
August	O
12	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Brick-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Old-street	I-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachmaker	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
now	O
deal	O
in	O
wood	O
for	O
the	O
coachmakers	O
use	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
sawyers	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
they	O
went	O
through	O
an	O
entry	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
worked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
door	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
opens	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
entry	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
chimney	O
,	O
hung	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
watch	O
hanging	O
there	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
,	O
my	O
maid	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
sawyers	O
were	O
gone	O
from	O
work	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
as	O
she	O
said	O
;	O
they	O
came	O
again	O
just	O
at	O
dark	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
them	O
where	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
soldiers	O
muster	O
;	O
(	O
the	O
two	O
sawyers	O
are	O
soldiers	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
need	O
not	O
have	O
taken	O
my	O
watch	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
they	O
swore	O
they	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
before	O
justice	O
Keeling	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
,	O
Thursday	O
following	O
my	O
maid	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
Evans	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
better	O
coat	O
than	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
,	O
from	O
which	O
I	O
strongly	O
suspected	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
Evans	O
confessed	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
knocked	O
the	O
milk-pot	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
hear	O
this	O
confession	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
watch	O
where	O
the	O
evidence	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Rochfort	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
afternoon	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
?	O
Rochfort	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
?	O
Rochfort	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
three	O
cups	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Rochfort	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
alone	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Rochfort	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
?	O
Rochfort	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
dressed	O
in	O
his	O
regimentals	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
it	O
?	O
Rochfort	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
he	O
dressed	O
?	O
Rochfort	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
dressed	O
in	O
a	O
brown	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Owen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
watch	O
(	O
taking	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
)	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
lost	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
evidence	O
worked	O
at	O
sawing	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
till	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
two	O
and	O
three	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
to	O
their	O
saw-pit	O
,	O
they	O
soon	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
through	O
the	O
entry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
?	O
Owen	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
through	O
the	O
window	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
saw-pit	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
watch	O
hang	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
near	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
just	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
milk-pot	O
?	O
Owen	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
standing	O
on	O
a	O
little	O
table	O
;	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
open	O
or	O
shut	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
Owen	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
wide	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
they	O
see	O
the	O
watch	O
hanging	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
as	O
they	O
passed	O
through	O
the	O
entry	O
?	O
Owen	O
.	O
They	O
might	O
easily	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
usual	O
way	O
of	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
to	O
go	O
through	O
the	O
entry	O
?	O
Owen	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
Owen	O
.	O
Not	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
room	O
?	O
Owen	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
watch	O
from	O
any	O
other	O
?	O
Owen	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
a	O
brass	O
chain	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
wind	O
it	O
up	O
every	O
day	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
to	O
our	O
work	O
about	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Haines	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
asked	O
us	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
said	O
the	O
sawyers	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
nail	O
by	O
the	O
fire-side	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
you	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Haines	O
.	O
Gee	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Haines	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
milk-pot	O
?	O
Haines	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
and	O
you	O
consulted	O
about	O
this	O
thing	O
before	O
?	O
Haines	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
willingly	O
take	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
did	O
consent	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
or	O
shut	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Haines	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
that	O
door	O
used	O
to	O
stand	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
watch	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
.	O
After	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
for	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
?	O
Haines	O
.	O
Gee	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
share	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Haines	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
milk-pot	O
?	O
Haines	O
.	O
We	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
,	O
after	O
Gee	O
had	O
stamped	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
the	O
Jew	O
live	O
?	O
Haines	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
neither	O
do	O
I	O
know	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
from	O
Snow-hill	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
an	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
Jew	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Haines	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
?	O
Haines	O
.	O
For	O
11	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
What	O
he	O
swears	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Captain	O
Wilson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
belongs	O
to	O
my	O
company	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
behaved	O
remarkably	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heand	O
him	O
suspected	O
,	O
he	O
bears	O
as	O
good	O
a	O
character	O
as	O
any	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
.	O
-	O
Dunman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
company	O
to	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
belongs	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
regiment	O
three	O
years	O
next	O
November	O
,	O
we	O
never	O
had	O
cause	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
theft	O
,	O
or	O
neglect	O
of	O
duty	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
trusted	O
in	O
the	O
barracks	O
with	O
our	O
knapsacks	O
,	O
we	O
never	O
missed	O
anything	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
evidence	O
Haines	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
that	O
he	O
himself	O
took	O
the	O
milk-pot	O
.	O
-	O
Hinemarsh	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
likewise	O
a	O
serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
company	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
first	O
inlisting	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Hinemarsh	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
an	O
extraordinary	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
our	O
cloaths	O
use	O
to	O
hang	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
barracks	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
trusted	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ledger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Ledger	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
,	O
he	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
he	O
never	O
wronged	O
me	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
him	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
opportunities	O
to	O
take	O
my	O
plate	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bar	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Casser	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
lived	O
in	O
ready-furnished	O
lodgings	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
no	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
affair	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Solomon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
well	O
beloved	O
by	O
the	O
neighbours	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
278	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Head	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
Portugal	O
pieces	O
,	O
one	O
moidore	O
,	O
two	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
moidore	O
,	O
21	O
guineas	O
,	O
4	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
13	O
s	O
6	O
d	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
John	B-pers
and	I-pers
George	I-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
My	O
son	O
George	O
and	O
I	O
are	O
partners	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cow-cross	O
,	O
beyond	O
Porter	O
's	O
Block	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
soap-maker	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
lodge	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
employ	O
him	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
employ	O
'd	O
in	O
labouring	O
business	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
way	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
make	O
our	O
soap	O
.	O
We	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
money	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
on	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Give	O
an	O
account	O
what	O
pieces	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
There	O
were	O
21	O
guineas	O
,	O
4	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
six	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
one	O
moidore	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
two	O
6	O
and	O
9	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
six-pence	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
37	O
l.	O
all	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
six	O
pence	O
;	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
halfpences	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
money	O
missing	O
from	O
?	O
John	O
Russel	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
missing	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
desk	O
in	O
the	O
compting-house	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
in	O
my	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
desk	O
lock	O
'd	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
compting-house-door	O
lock	O
'd	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
this	O
money	O
last	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
We	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
just	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
dark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
it	O
first	O
?	O
John	O
Russel	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
son	O
missed	O
it	O
first	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
George	O
.	O
We	O
apprehended	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
some	O
body-belonging	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
a	O
knife	O
being	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
to	O
force	O
it	O
open	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
suspected	O
,	O
we	O
borrowed	O
his	O
knife	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
compared	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
agree	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
had	O
his	O
lodgings	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
halfpences	O
missing	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bag	O
that	O
we	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
searched	O
the	O
lodgings	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
produc	O
'd	O
;	O
the	O
justice	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
whose	O
money	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
also	O
owned	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
this	O
money	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
desk	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
quantity	O
that	O
my	O
father	O
speaks	O
of	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
desk	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
the	O
desk	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
I	O
borrowed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
fit	O
the	O
place	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
lodging	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
returned	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
gates	O
open	O
that	O
go	O
into	O
our	O
work-house	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
to	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
he	O
tried	O
to	O
cut	O
a	O
hole	O
,	O
but	O
,	O
in	O
trying	O
,	O
found	O
it	O
loose	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
easier	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
lock	O
,	O
than	O
cut	O
a	O
hole	O
;	O
so	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
bag	O
of	O
gold	O
on	O
the	O
tester	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
halfpence	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
This	O
bag	O
that	O
the	O
gold	O
is	O
in	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
bag	O
that	O
the	O
gold	O
was	O
in	O
when	O
in	O
our	O
desk	O
,	O
our	O
property	O
.	O
Thorn	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
bag	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Russel	O
had	O
mentioned	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
to	O
so	O
good	O
a	O
master	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
offence	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
cut	O
a	O
hole	O
through	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
but	O
finding	O
the	O
lock	O
loose	O
,	O
he	O
broke	O
it	O
open	O
James	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
at	O
the	O
finding	O
of	O
this	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
tester	O
of	O
his	O
bed	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Wyate	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
compting-house	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
time	O
to	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Husford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
examined	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
money	O
was	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
night	O
through	O
the	O
great	O
gates	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
get	O
up	O
till	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
279	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
wife	I-pers
to	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Bryan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
5	O
yards	O
of	O
linnen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
,	O
August	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holmes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Joiner	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford-road	B-place
;	O
I	O
trusted	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
make	O
2	O
shirts	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
apartment	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
cloth	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
The	O
very	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
your	O
servant	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Her	O
husband	O
had	O
turn	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
deliver	O
the	O
cloth	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
it	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
7	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
left	O
me	O
but	O
two	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
also	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
away	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
but	O
one	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
wife	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
had	O
been	O
abroad	O
,	O
three	O
weeks	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
sister	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
your	O
wife	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
this	O
woman	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
By	O
her	O
transgression	O
,	O
in	O
pawning	O
my	O
tools	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
beds	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lie	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
then	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
She	O
sat	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Three	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
sit	O
up	O
in	O
your	O
room	O
the	O
whole	O
three	O
weeks	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
two	O
days	O
after	O
her	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
cloth	O
to	O
two	O
different	O
pawn-brokers	O
,	O
one	O
lives	O
in	O
Silver-street	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
near	O
Golden-square	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
cloaths	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
never	O
pawn	O
things	O
for	O
you	O
by	O
your	O
direction	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
send	O
the	O
cloth	O
to	O
your	O
wife	O
,	O
for	O
her	O
to	O
make	O
your	O
shirts	O
?	O
Holmes	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
cloth	O
again	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
pawned	O
one	O
part	O
one	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
another	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
no	O
good	O
sign	O
of	O
returning	O
them	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Mure	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
pledged	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
cloth	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
cloth	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
bell-yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Mure	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Oxford-road	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Silver-street	O
Golden-square	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
is	O
about	O
2	O
ells	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
shift	O
body	O
for	O
herself	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
has	O
been	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
custody	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
produced	O
the	O
two	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
them	O
both	O
as	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
cloth	O
to	O
be	O
yours	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
pawn-brokers	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
so	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
at	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
beat	O
his	O
wife	O
so	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
nigh	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
where	O
his	O
wife	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
this	O
out	O
of	O
spite	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
cloth	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
280	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Davy	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
ounces	O
weight	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cafe	I-pers
,	O
August	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Cafe	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
10	O
weeks	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
discharged	O
from	O
my	O
service	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Cafe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gutter-lane	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
miss	O
any	O
silver	O
?	O
Cafe	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
when	O
brought	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
owned	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
rob	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
that	O
weigh	O
12	O
ounces	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
he	O
asked	O
my	O
pardon	O
,	O
and	O
beg	O
'd	O
forgiveness	O
:	O
afterwards	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
dirt	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Cafe	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
taking	O
the	O
silver	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
wind-hole	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
we	O
melt	O
our	O
silver	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
our	O
porter	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stowers	O
.	O
I	O
sell	O
silver	O
buckles	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
melted	O
silver	O
in	O
a	O
lump	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
with	O
the	O
duke	O
of	O
Bedford	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
this	O
silver	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
sifting	O
the	O
cinders	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
acquaint	O
the	O
steward	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
men	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
:	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
leave	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
accordingly	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
7	O
s.	O
for	O
it	O
:	O
he	O
proposed	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
more	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
dirt	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
he	O
brought	O
two	O
ounces	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
leave	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
weigh	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
call	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
duke	O
of	O
Bedford	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
steward	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
such	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
stopt	O
him	O
I	O
search	O
'd	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
it	O
directed	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Cafe	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Gutter-lane	O
:	O
he	O
deliver	O
'd	O
me	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
brown	O
bear	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
8	O
ounces	O
more	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
12	O
ounces	O
4	O
penny	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
silver	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ashes	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
pewter	O
hardened	O
,	O
or	O
dross	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
grand	O
father	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
spend	O
his	O
time	O
in	O
reading	O
good	O
books	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
281	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Folliott	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Avis	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
July	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
finisher	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
David	B-pers
Rivers	I-pers
,	O
a	O
watchmaker	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
late	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
to	O
finish	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
against	O
Saturday	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
above	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Avis	I-pers
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
suspect	O
one	O
Malone	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
this	O
watch	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
He	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
else	O
could	O
come	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawn-broker	O
;	O
this	O
watch	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
Randall	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
workmens	O
work	O
for	O
some	O
master	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
it	O
on	O
suspicion	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
Randall	O
.	O
where	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
whom	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Catherine	B-pers
Folliott	I-pers
gave	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
fetch	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
gave	O
it	O
Randall	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
stop	O
'd	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
advertised	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Philips	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
such	O
proof	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
its	O
belonging	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
M.	O
Morgan	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
rag	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
spouse	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Q	O
Did	O
she	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
?	O
Anne	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
.	O
She	O
directed	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Morgan	O
's	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Morgan	O
said	O
,	O
Randall	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
this	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Catherine	B-pers
Folliott	I-pers
;	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
Mrs.	O
Morgan	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
in	O
a	O
rag	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Philips	O
as	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Rivers	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
watch	O
?	O
Philips	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
near	O
twelve	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
being	O
Saturday	O
,	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
from	O
ten	O
till	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
is	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
sick	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
an	O
hour-glass	O
to	O
watch	O
his	O
time	O
by	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Kitty	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
well	O
who	O
has	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
Jack	B-pers
Malone	I-pers
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
he	O
will	O
give	O
it	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
whenever	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
Tyburn	O
ticket	O
he	O
would	O
,	O
and	O
cant	O
him	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
is	O
come	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
sick	O
bed	O
to	O
give	O
evidence	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Dowds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
intimate	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
hers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Dowds	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Spital-fields	O
,	O
and	O
Brick-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
countryman	O
?	O
Dowds	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Irishman	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
often	O
paid	O
me	O
visits	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
of	O
any	O
business	O
?	O
Dowds	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
past	O
been	O
a	O
servant	O
;	O
but	O
now	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
keep	O
a	O
room	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
June	O
last	O
?	O
Dowds	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
no	O
particular	O
account	O
of	O
any	O
day	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
about	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
day	O
from	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
nine	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
till	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
she	O
employ	O
her	O
self	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Dowds	O
.	O
In	O
taking	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
very	O
ill	O
of	O
the	O
cholick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
send	O
for	O
her	O
?	O
Dowds	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
by	O
