TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
Country	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Thirty-first	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
V.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1758	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fifth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ASGILL	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
,	O
1758	O
.	O
(	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
)	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
General	O
Sessions	B-pers
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ASGILL	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
MICHAEL	B-pers
FOSTER	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King's-Bench	O
*	O
;	O
Sir	O
SIDNEY	O
STAFFORD	O
SMYTHE	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
+	O
;	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
and	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Vickerman	I-pers
,	O
Louis	B-pers
Benoimont	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Adams	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Woodin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Eaton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Glover	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wornel	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hartwell	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Bradley	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Carmichael	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Chipperfield	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Spinage	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Barlow	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Chilton	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Lester	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Phillips	I-pers
,	O
Simon	B-pers
Pawson	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Airey	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lugg	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
.	O
199.	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Eddington	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilmore	I-pers
,	O
April	O
8	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
recognizance	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
estreated	O
.	O
200	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Shackleton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Teise	I-pers
,	O
May	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
Frederick	B-pers
Teise	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
Night	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Post-office	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
letter	O
.	O
In	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
my	O
coat	O
being	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
felt	O
something	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
rightside	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depnsed	O
to	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
has	O
it	O
been	O
since	O
?	O
Teise	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
custody	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
near	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
nearer	O
to	O
you	O
than	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
nearest	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
court	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
very	O
good	O
friends	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
privateer	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
discharged	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mercer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
of	O
very	O
honest	O
parents	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
parish	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
dwell	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
any	O
misbehaved	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
he	O
done	O
for	O
his	O
livelihood	O
since	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
privateer	O
?	O
Mercer	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Penny-post-office	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Essex	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
between	O
twelve	O
and	O
thirteen	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Essex	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
till	O
this	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
he	O
done	O
for	O
a	O
livelihood	O
since	O
he	O
left	O
the	O
privateer	O
?	O
Essex	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Penny-post-office	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Huller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Huller	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hyne	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Hyne	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
before	O
this	O
accident	O
happened	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Ball	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Ball	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
this	O
kind	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
,	O
nobody	O
else	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
he	O
done	O
for	O
a	O
livelihood	O
lately	O
?	O
Ball	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Penny-post	O
office	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
securities	O
here	O
now	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
bound	O
in	O
a	O
bond	O
of	O
fifty	O
pounds	O
for	O
his	O
honesty	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ivey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
?	O
Ivey	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
201	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Shafield	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Shirvel	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Shovel	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
without	O
the	O
cover	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
April	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	B-place
and	I-place
Bottle	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
public-house	I-place
in	I-place
Cannon-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
and	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Some	O
company	O
had	O
left	O
this	O
tankard	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
this	O
I	O
speak	O
by	O
hear	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
named	O
Kelley	O
had	O
seized	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
tankard	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
just	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
upon	O
the	O
tankard	O
being	O
taken	O
from	O
him	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
done	O
so	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
first	O
crime	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Kelley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Bottle	O
in	O
Cannon-street	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
Mrs.	O
Wilson	O
means	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
April	O
.	O
Kelley	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
moved	O
the	O
tankard	O
to	O
where	O
he	O
sat	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
seat	O
behind	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
moved	O
from	O
one	O
box	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
,	O
being	O
told	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
time	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
this	O
tankard	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
,	O
leave	O
the	O
tankard	O
behind	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
had	O
he	O
the	O
tankard	O
?	O
Kelley	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
doors	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
door	O
way	O
,	O
that	O
door	O
stood	O
open	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Wilson	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
?	O
Kelley	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
going	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
tankard	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
Kelley	O
.	O
From	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
boxes	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
drank	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
knew	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
know	O
something	O
of	O
your	O
face	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
never	O
live	O
at	O
Hummerton	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
butcher	O
there	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
talked	O
together	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
tankard	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
beer	O
into	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
beer	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
tankard	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
ragged	O
men	O
set	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
tankard	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
safe	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
;	O
I	O
just	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
tankard	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
tankard	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
;	O
the	O
gentlewoman	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
thoughts	O
of	O
stealing	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gander	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Gander	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
pains-taking	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
business	O
?	O
Gander	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
plasterer	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Crawford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eleven	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
?	O
Crawford	O
.	O
That	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
pains-taking	O
man	O
,	O
who	O
worked	O
day	O
and	O
night	O
to	O
maintain	O
his	O
family	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Haines	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Haines	O
.	O
A	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Blane	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
202	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Bricklebank	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Quin	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
dozen	O
of	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
39	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Simon	B-pers
Havenham	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Simon	O
,	O
April	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Risby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Havenham	O
,	O
a	O
linnen-draper	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
some	O
:	O
after	O
we	O
had	O
agreed	O
for	O
one	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
a	O
frivolous	O
excuse	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
foul	O
paper	O
.	O
I	O
missing	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
went	O
out	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
as	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
)	O
here	O
are	O
our	O
private	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
left	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
to	O
be	O
changed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
change	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
my	O
going	O
out	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
that	O
other	O
woman	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
cheapened	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
Risby	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
also	O
leave	O
a	O
bundle	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
?	O
Risby	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
bundle	O
left	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
into	O
that	O
bundle	O
?	O
Risby	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
has	O
business	O
else-where	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
dirty	O
shirts	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
a	O
child	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Risby	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
one	O
in	O
her	O
arms	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
that	O
piece	O
of	O
handkerchiefs	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
by	O
mistake	O
with	O
the	O
child	O
?	O
Risby	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
because	O
she	O
begged	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
hang	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
that	O
ever	O
she	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
she	O
left	O
?	O
Risby	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
old	O
and	O
of	O
little	O
value	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eltoft	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Risby	I-pers
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Johnson	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
just	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
notice	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
take	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
a	O
dozen	O
of	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
fell	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
sake	O
of	O
her	O
children	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
bargained	O
for	O
one	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
child	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
the	O
breast	O
;	O
laid	O
down	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
child	O
had	O
fouled	O
itself	O
;	O
I	O
swept	O
its	O
things	O
up	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
clean	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
taped	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
Mind	O
to	O
have	O
defrauded	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
left	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
intended	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
cleaned	O
my	O
child	O
to	O
return	O
again	O
for	O
my	O
change	O
;	O
my	O
shirts	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
there	O
,	O
were	O
worth	O
about	O
30	O
s.	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
each	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
downright	O
innocent	O
before	O
God	O
and	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
woman	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Risby	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
shirts	O
where	O
there	O
in	O
her	O
bundle	O
?	O
Risby	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
the	O
change	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
my	O
going	O
out	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
off	O
immediately	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
?	O
Risby	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
woman	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
talked	O
together	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
recollect	O
.	O
That	O
woman	O
also	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
upon	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
change	O
because	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Rachael	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
deals	O
at	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
business	O
?	O
Rachael	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
She	O
buys	O
and	O
sells	O
things	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
her	O
.	O
Rachael	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
nine	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Rachael	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
a	O
housekeeper	O
or	O
a	O
lodger	O
?	O
Rachael	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
She	O
is	O
a	O
lodger	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Murdick	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
nine	O
months	O
,	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
Wilson's-court	O
,	O
White's-yard	O
,	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
gets	O
her	O
livelihood	O
by	O
buying	O
and	O
selling	O
linen	O
in	O
Rag-fair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
E.	O
Murdick	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prosecution	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bricklebank	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
kept	O
my	O
husband	O
company	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
not	O
mention	O
any	O
particular	O
instance	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
S.	O
Bricklebank	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
gets	O
her	O
bread	O
by	O
shop-lifting	O
and	O
bringing	O
up	O
her	O
children	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
spite	O
,	O
this	O
evidence	O
keeps	O
company	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
S.	O
Bricklebank	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
my	O
certificate	O
of	O
my	O
marriage	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
203	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Susannah	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
-	I-pers
Harrold	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pots	O
value	O
20	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pint	O
pewter	O
pot	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Motelowe	I-pers
,	O
April	O
25	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Motelowe	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
detected	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
I	O
can	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Motelowe	O
.	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
April	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
a	O
boy	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
half	O
pint	O
pot	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
boy	O
had	O
given	O
that	O
pot	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
pull	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
half	O
pint	O
pot	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
claped	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
her	O
pocket	O
and	O
felt	O
something	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pint	O
pot	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
her	O
boy	O
ran	O
away	O
immediately	O
.	O
In	O
searching	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
two	O
other	O
of	O
my	O
pots	O
were	O
found	O
under	O
her	O
bed	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Edmund	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
boy	O
take	O
the	O
half	O
pint	O
pot	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
is	O
that	O
boy	O
?	O
E.	O
Andrews	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
her	O
son	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
landlady	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
fall	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Motelowe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
se	O
arching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
at	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
pint	O
pots	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Young	O
at	O
the	O
green	O
dragon	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
broken	O
stean	O
,	O
and	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
a	O
box	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
locked	O
,	O
we	O
opened	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
pint	O
pot	O
more	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
Mr.	O
White	O
's	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
three	O
pots	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
pot	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
the	O
landlady	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
she	O
dropt	O
the	O
half	O
pint	O
pot	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
found	O
another	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
searching	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
pots	O
mentioned	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
found	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
this	O
house	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
my	O
child	O
some	O
warm	O
beer	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
held	O
the	O
pint	O
pot	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
pot	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
boy	O
that	O
handed	O
her	O
the	O
pot	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
speaks	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Consider	O
and	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
thing	O
but	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
Harold	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
my	O
mother	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
mother	O
the	O
pot	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
roll	O
.	O
Andrews	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
beer	O
in	O
the	O
pot	O
when	O
this	O
boy	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
mother	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
has	O
cost	O
me	O
within	O
these	O
five	O
years	O
almost	O
fourscoure	O
pounds	O
for	O
pots	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
204	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Andrew	B-pers
Worster	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Worcester	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
guinea	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
More	I-pers
,	O
April	O
30	O
.	O
William	O
More	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
,	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
Hedge-lane	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
woman	O
named	O
Nugent	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
and	O
she	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
box	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Nugent	I-pers
.	O
Two	O
men	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
change	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
I	O
changed	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
following	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
changed	O
a	O
guinea	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
them	O
seven	O
guineas	O
all	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
one	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
another	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
guinea	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
awaked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sleep	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
answer	O
I	O
made	O
.	O
Woodward	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
awake	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
sleep	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
up	O
in	O
his	O
bed	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
taking	O
five	O
guineas	O
at	O
four	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
scruple	O
in	O
telling	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
one	O
day	O
in	O
March	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
and	O
borrowed	O
two	O
guineas	O
of	O
me	O
saying	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Bath	O
with	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
paid	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lent	O
him	O
money	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
he	O
related	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Burch	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Padmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
in	O
all	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hubbard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pierce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
his	O
cradle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Pierce	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
what	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Dobson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
205	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
,	I-pers
Ellice	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twelve	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
,	O
April	O
22	O
.	O
*	O
Mrs.	O
Henderson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
James	B-pers
Henderson	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
goods	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
,	O
these	O
aprons	O
were	O
lying	O
upon	O
the	O
parcel	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
aprons	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
flashed	O
away	O
with	O
new	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
described	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
aprons	O
I	O
lost	O
,	O
my	O
friend	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Robertson	O
that	O
informed	O
me	O
of	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
an	O
apron	O
which	O
I	O
said	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
apron	O
on	O
much	O
like	O
one	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
darn	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
mine	O
had	O
a	O
darn	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Robertson	O
had	O
an	O
apron	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
this	O
apron	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Henderson	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
some	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
observe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
Catharine	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
borrowed	O
this	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Henderson	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
.	O
Catharine	B-pers
Brian	I-pers
.	O
I	O
borrowed	O
this	O
apron	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
I	O
borrowed	O
it	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
borrow	O
it	O
?	O
Brian	O
.	O
I	O
borrowed	O
it	O
the	O
last	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Q.	O
how	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
it	O
in	O
your	O
custody	O
?	O
Brian	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
wore	O
it	O
one	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Robertson	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
Room	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
borrow	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
?	O
Brian	O
.	O
Her	O
nurse	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
apron	O
by	O
her	O
cellar	O
window	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
leave	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Brian	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
nurse	O
ask	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
stood	O
under	O
the	O
cellar	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
?	O
Brian	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
sat	O
in	O
her	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
nurse	O
go	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
ask	O
her	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
basket	O
where	O
it	O
lay	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
rough	O
dried	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
nurse	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
ever	O
a	O
one	O
you	O
shall	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Reason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
this	O
last	O
witness	O
ask	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
lend	O
her	O
an	O
apron	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
and	O
ironed	O
it	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
on	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
particular	O
mark	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
Reason	O
.	O
Nothing	O
but	O
by	O
the	O
coarseness	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
lend	O
that	O
witness	O
an	O
apron	O
?	O
Reason	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
tuck	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
too	O
long	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
such	O
an	O
apron	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
this	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
and	O
mine	O
work	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Long	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
other	O
than	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
bears	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
amongst	O
her	O
neighbours	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
206	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
iron	O
plates	O
for	O
hoops	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cann	I-pers
,	O
April	O
22	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Cann	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Beesley	I-pers
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
stoped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
some	O
iron	O
hoops	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Cann	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cooper	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
white	O
bear	O
in	O
Kingsland-road	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
hoops	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
?	O
Cann	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
age	O
?	O
Cann	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
him	O
any	O
threats	O
or	O
promises	O
?	O
Cann	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
confess	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Beesley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
informed	O
a	O
boy	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
yard	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
hoops	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
take	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
he	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
heard	O
this	O
boy	O
is	O
sometimes	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
mind	O
?	O
Beesley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
when	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
liquor	O
he	O
is	O
subject	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Beesley	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
some	O
hoops	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Beesley	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
his	O
confession	O
?	O
Beesley	O
.	O
Cann	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
better	O
for	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
told	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Farrow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
hoops	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
tenter	O
ground	O
.	O
He	O
dropt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
brought	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
White	O
Bear	O
in	O
Kingsland	O
road	O
:	O
after	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cann	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cambridge	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
son	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
age	O
?	O
Cambridge	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
timber	O
yard	O
in	O
Kingsland	O
road	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
boy	O
drop	O
down	O
as	O
it	O
were	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
very	O
subject	O
to	O
fits	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Carter	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
May	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
boy	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
subject	O
to	O
fits	O
,	O
and	O
frequently	O
is	O
deprived	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
fall	O
down	O
like	O
a	O
stone	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Tompson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
fall	O
off	O
a	O
horse	O
in	O
a	O
fit	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
some	O
water	O
in	O
a	O
pot	O
,	O
he	O
bit	O
the	O
mug	O
in	O
twenty	O
pieces	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Thompson	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
he	O
wronged	O
any	O
body	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
207	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Albeat	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
cornelian	O
seals	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
tortoiseshell	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
rim	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
seven	O
glass	O
eggs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
stone	O
shirt	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
only	O
seeing	O
him	O
pass	O
and	O
repass	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweler	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
little	O
place	O
in	O
Bedford	B-place
court	I-place
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
glass	O
case	O
there	O
in	O
which	O
I	O
put	O
things	O
for	O
shew	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
live	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
daughter	O
about	O
13	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
have	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
day-time	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
my	O
daughter	O
having	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
daughter	O
?	O
Barrett	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
was	O
too	O
young	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
her	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
them	O
or	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Barrett	O
.	O
By	O
enquiring	O
I	O
found	O
several	O
of	O
them	O
in	O
other	O
people	O
's	O
possession	O
;	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
.	O
Reves	O
Edwards	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
with	O
most	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Name	O
what	O
you	O
saw	O
.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
tortoiseshell	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
a	O
shirt-buckle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
society	O
or	O
club	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
these	O
things	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
mentions	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
a	O
breast	O
silver	O
shirt-buckle	O
,	O
set	O
in	O
stone	O
,	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
buckle	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
myself	O
in	O
another	O
branch	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
these	O
myself	O
,	O
so	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
mine	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Gaul	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
New-Prison	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
this	O
buckle	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
silver	O
one	O
set	O
with	O
stone	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
buckle	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Mine	O
was	O
of	O
this	O
pattern	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
swear	O
positively	O
to	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
Patrick	B-pers
Rook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
snuff-box	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
tortoiseshell	O
box	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Rook	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Hatton-Garden	O
,	O
Holbourn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
sold	O
it	O
you	O
?	O
Rook	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
like	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
it	O
?	O
Rook	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
six-shillings	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
box	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
takes	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
very	O
much	O
like	O
mine	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Crisp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
a	O
seal	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
last	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
again	O
before	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
for	O
three	O
pence	O
profit	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
box	O
in	O
Mays-buildings	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
once	O
was	O
valet	O
to	O
colonel	O
Mordaunt	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
wait	O
at	O
table	O
at	O
my	O
lord	O
Oliphant	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
;	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
he	O
lived	O
servant	O
there	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
208	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Latter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
cornelian	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
forty	O
one	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
metal	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
and	O
secretly	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
March	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
Upon	O
the	O
jury	O
being	O
about	O
to	O
be	O
sworn	O
,	O
he	O
challenged	O
the	O
whole	O
twelve	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
twelve	O
following	O
were	O
sworn	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bradfield	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Catts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Numburg	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jeffreys	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Addy	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hipsey	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tolley	I-pers
,	O
Montague	B-pers
Lawrance	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilton	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
.	O
[	O
At	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
request	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
were	O
examined	O
separate	O
.	O
]	O
William	B-pers
Wallis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
Galleon	B-place
House	I-place
,	I-place
properly	I-place
called	I-place
the	I-place
Devil	I-place
's	I-place
House	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
in	O
Easter-week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
that	O
house	O
you	O
speak	O
of	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
by	O
the	O
Galleons	O
,	O
almost	O
opposite	O
Woolwich	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
plough	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
lamb	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
drinking	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
much	O
intoxicated	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
ditch	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
almost	O
suffocated	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
so	O
many	O
people	O
standing	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
nobody	O
help	O
me	O
!	O
I	O
had	O
struggled	O
and	O
swallowed	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
filth	O
and	O
stuff	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
helped	O
out	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
clapt	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
myself	O
insensible	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
water	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
senses	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
voice	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
John	B-pers
Latter	I-pers
;	O
he	O
answered	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
do	O
pray	O
see	O
me	O
home	O
some	O
how	O
,	O
or	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
no	O
further	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
leading	O
me	O
home	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
where	O
is	O
my	O
watch	O
?	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
home	O
without	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
ask	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
private	O
way	O
,	O
at	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
saying	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
it	O
at	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
help	O
me	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
his	O
trouble	O
;	O
if	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
denies	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
am	O
wrong	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
stands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
this	O
after	O
you	O
lost	O
it	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three-days	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
being	O
a	O
poor	O
man	O
did	O
not	O
give	O
myself	O
the	O
trouble	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
strict	O
enquiry	O
after	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
number	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
there	O
to	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
number	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
find	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
leave	O
word	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
neither	O
find	O
name	O
nor	O
number	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
you	O
alone	O
together	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
me	O
but	O
a	O
young	O
single	O
lamb	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
see	O
you	O
home	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
part	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
company	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
had	O
helped	O
you	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ditch	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ditch	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
fob	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
had	O
drank	O
yourself	O
insensible	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
your	O
understanding	O
so	O
soon	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
It	O
brought	O
me	O
almost	O
to	O
my	O
senses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Wallis	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Stephen	B-pers
Boswell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Breebrook	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
fell	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Goats	O
Heads	O
in	O
White	O
Chapel	O
;	O
upon	O
seeing	O
a	O
croud	O
of	O
people	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
just	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
ditch	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
edge	O
of	O
the	O
bank	O
;	O
we	O
set	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
so	O
black	O
with	O
the	O
mud	O
and	O
filth	O
of	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
that	O
nobody	O
knew	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
tongue	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
knew	O
Latter	O
's	O
tongue	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
who	O
is	O
there	O
?	O
Jack	B-pers
Latter	I-pers
!	O
Latter	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
then	O
Latter	O
said	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
done	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
business	O
for	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
lead	O
him	O
home	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
people	O
there	O
besides	O
you	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
others	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
leading	O
him	O
along	O
Montague-street	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
desirous	O
of	O
my	O
taking	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
;	O
a	O
tall	O
man	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
it	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
that	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
Latter	O
and	O
I	O
led	O
him	O
along	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
,	O
Latter	O
shoved	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
pales	O
,	O
stood	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
watch-string	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
let	O
go	O
my	O
hold	O
,	O
and	O
wiped	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
a	O
post	O
to	O
clean	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
Latter	O
let	O
go	O
and	O
wiped	O
his	O
hand	O
with	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Holding	O
his	O
hand	O
out	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
two	O
seals	O
and	O
a	O
watch-key	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
throwed	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
kennel	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
that	O
for	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
in	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
Montague-street	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
seals	O
and	O
key	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
them	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
seals	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
white	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
yellow	O
one	O
.	O
Presently	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
(	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
)	O
with	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Breebrook	O
said	O
,	O
Jack	O
has	O
certainly	O
robbed	O
that	O
man	O
.	O
Latter	O
held	O
the	O
watch	O
behind	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
unknown	O
to	O
Breebrook	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
a	O
watch	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
here	O
that	O
were	O
leading	O
him	O
along	O
,	O
or	O
attending	O
him	O
.	O
Boswell	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
there	O
are	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
reason	O
for	O
slinging	O
the	O
seals	O
and	O
key	O
away	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
towards	O
stopping	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
watch	O
then	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
string	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
The	O
seals	O
and	O
key	O
were	O
on	O
an	O
old	O
black	O
ribbon	O
;	O
the	O
ribbon	O
broke	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
in	O
pulling	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
you	O
any	O
acquaintance	O
together	O
before	O
that	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
him	O
often	O
to	O
do	O
business	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
never	O
cause	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
any	O
warrant	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
declare	O
to	O
any	O
person	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
your	O
expences	O
which	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
him	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Haywood	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
no	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
Monday	O
last	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
such	O
man	O
;	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
I	O
may	O
know	O
him	O
if	O
I	O
see	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
conversation	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
Monday	O
and	O
Sunday	O
too	O
;	O
they	O
offered	O
me	O
something	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
offered	O
that	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Ambler	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
at	O
Clay-Hall	O
by	O
Bow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
offer	O
you	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
He	O
offered	O
to	O
pay	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
expences	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
I	O
would	O
say	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
I	O
did	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
guineas	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
One	O
Wilson	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
aside	O
when	O
they	O
talked	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
this	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
meet	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
they	O
put	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
gatehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
for	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
For	O
a	O
quarrel	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
this	O
time	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
which	O
happened	O
at	O
skittles	O
;	O
they	O
gave	O
that	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
quarrelled	O
with	O
a	O
crown	O
to	O
put	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
gatehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
evening	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
with	O
none	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Ambler	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
lost	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
whether	O
or	O
no	O
I	O
and	O
you	O
and	O
others	O
were	O
not	O
in	O
company	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
in	O
Spittlefields	O
market	O
since	O
that	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
conceal	O
it	O
so	O
long	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
Because	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
put	O
in	O
gaol	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
shall	O
now	O
when	O
I	O
go	O
from	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
doubt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
fear	O
that	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
Because	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
disobliges	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
go	O
to	O
his	O
usurer	O
and	O
get	O
their	O
notes	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
gaol	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
Boswell	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
since	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
lost	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
Six	O
or	O
seven	O
times	O
,	O
or	O
more	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
pretend	O
to	O
say	O
how	O
many	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
courage	O
to	O
discover	O
this	O
matter	O
?	O
Boswell	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
a	O
man	O
into	O
gaol	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Fitz	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Spittlefields	O
market	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
bail	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
fraud	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
defrauding	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
six	O
guineas	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
between	O
my	O
two	O
rooms	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
watch	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
me	O
very	O
cheap	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
mell	O
'd	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
market	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
pray	O
who	O
was	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
Will	O
Wallis	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
understand	O
by	O
this	O
word	O
Mell	O
?	O
Fitz	O
.	O
The	O
word	O
Melling	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
said	O
Will	O
Wallis	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
must	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
get	O
it	O
clandestinely	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
you	O
in	O
a	O
language	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
say	O
who	O
?	O
Fitz	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
say	O
who	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
the	O
word	O
mell	O
'd	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
produce	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Fitz	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
surprized	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
hanged	O
or	O
transported	O
for	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
and	O
Ambler	O
lived	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
bailed	O
for	O
murder	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
so	O
many	O
boys	O
and	O
girls	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
could	O
buss	O
the	O
book	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Fitz	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Salesman	O
in	O
Spittlefields-market	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
in	O
that	O
employ	O
now	O
?	O
Fitz	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
left	O
it	O
?	O
Fitz	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
have	O
you	O
followed	O
since	O
that	O
?	O
Fitz	O
.	O
None	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
upon	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
;	O
my	O
spouse	O
died	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
some	O
hundreds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
make	O
a	O
will	O
?	O
Fitz	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
made	O
no	O
will	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
lived	O
on	O
that	O
spot	O
thirty	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
Latter	O
's	O
before	O
?	O
Fitz	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
to	O
serve	O
several	O
writs	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
think	O
you	O
a	O
proper	O
person	O
to	O
apply	O
to	O
about	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
Fitz	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
you	O
very	O
cheap	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Fitz	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
concern	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
endeavour	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
when	O
you	O
suspected	O
he	O
stole	O
it	O
?	O
Fitz	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
knocked	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
apply	O
to	O
a	O
constable	O
about	O
him	O
?	O
Fitz	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
draw	O
me	O
in	O
to	O
be	O
bail	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
dropped	O
them	O
all	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
lives	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
I	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
by	O
agreement	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
applied	O
to	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
witness	O
in	O
this	O
affair	O
?	O
Fitz	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
days	O
ago	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
The	O
night	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
fell	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
pulled	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
I	O
will	O
see	O
you	O
home	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
some	O
people	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
staunch	O
man	O
and	O
keeps	O
the	O
market	O
.	O
He	O
and	O
another	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
a	O
great	O
garden	O
to	O
Montague-street	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Key	O
in	O
that	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
about	O
forty	O
or	O
fifty	O
yards	O
before	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
sit	O
long	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
helped	O
him	O
along	O
near	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
missed	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
Latter	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
never	O
mind	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
that	O
:	O
he	O
dragged	O
him	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
further	O
.	O
Wallis	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
any	O
further	O
without	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
let	O
him	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
Boswell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
by	O
him	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Fielding	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
nearest	O
to	O
him	O
except	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
off	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
helping	O
him	O
then	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Boswell	O
had	O
helped	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Boswell	O
when	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
watch	O
?	O
Fielding	O
.	O
Boswell	O
was	O
a-head	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Fielding	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Boswell	O
by	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
?	O
Fielding	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
was	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
yards	O
a-head	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
to	O
go	O
before	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
were	O
they	O
when	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
watch	O
?	O
Fielding	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
about	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Brick-Lane	O
;	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
left	O
hand	O
in	O
Wallis	O
's	O
right	O
hand	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
hugging	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pocket	O
was	O
turned	O
inside	O
out	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
left	O
alone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
you	O
saw	O
that	O
.	O
Fielding	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
Wallis	O
said	O
he	O
missed	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
then	O
to	O
help	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
man	O
home	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
him	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
Wallis	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
under	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Key	O
,	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
by	O
him	O
besides	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Fielding	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
twenty	O
or	O
thirty	O
yards	O
before	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
Wallis	O
's	O
pocket	O
offer	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Fielding	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
because	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
what	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
dare	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
will	O
was	O
good	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Eaben	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
fall	O
into	O
the	O
ditch	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
lamb	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
lamb	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
alehouse	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Boswell	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
friends	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
that	O
alehouse	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
the	O
fire-side	O
taking	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
lamb	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
went	O
to	O
take	O
Wallis	O
's	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shoes	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
let	O
them	O
alone	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
silver	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
Mountague-street	O
,	O
Latter	O
got	O
his	O
hand	O
round	O
him	O
hugging	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
a	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
Boswell	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
before	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
Wallis	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
farther	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
's	O
Head	O
;	O
then	O
Wallis	O
asked	O
for	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
watch	O
,	O
never	O
mind	O
your	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
fifty	O
yards	O
farther	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
came	O
betwixt	O
Brick-Lane	O
,	O
and	O
Dirty-Lane	O
end	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
any	O
further	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
watch	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
Boswell	O
,	O
Boswell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
did	O
Boswell	O
assist	O
in	O
taking	O
him	O
along	O
?	O
Eaben	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
help	O
take	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Key	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
Boswell	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
Wallis	O
jostled	O
up	O
to	O
some	O
pales	O
?	O
Eaben	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Key	O
,	O
there	O
the	O
prisoner	O
set	O
him	O
down	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
was	O
you	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Eaben	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
behind	O
with	O
the	O
lamb	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
friends	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
see	O
him	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
them	O
close	O
behind	O
with	O
the	O
lamb	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
cart	O
way	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
this	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
getting	O
him	O
home	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Wallis	O
fell	O
in	O
the	O
ditch	O
where	O
was	O
you	O
?	O
Eaben	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
had	O
just	O
left	O
work	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
house	O
to	O
the	O
Dolphin	O
alehouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
near	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
they	O
led	O
him	O
?	O
Eaben	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
behind	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
lamb	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
all	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
sit	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Key	O
?	O
Eaben	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nobody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sit	O
down	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Eaben	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
watch	O
there	O
,	O
must	O
not	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
?	O
Eaben	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
think	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
then	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
questions	O
to	O
ask	O
that	O
witness	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
shall	O
call	O
some	O
witness	O
that	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
sit	O
down	O
,	O
nor	O
make	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
sit	O
down	O
on	O
that	O
bench	O
under	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Key	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
and	O
knew	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
seeing	O
him	O
lead	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
arrested	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
prosecutor	O
just	O
before	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
bench	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
speak	O
of	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
pass	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
stop	O
at	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Haywood	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
last	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
office	O
in	O
Chancery-Lane	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Ambler	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
the	O
five	O
bells	O
to	O
hear	O
what	O
past	O
,	O
being	O
informed	O
Boswell	O
was	O
discharged	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
gatehouse	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Ambler	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
suppose	O
you	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
satisfied	O
for	O
the	O
expences	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
put	O
to	O
since	O
you	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
gatehouse	O
,	O
would	O
you	O
appear	O
against	O
Latter	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
he	O
answered	O
it	O
is	O
all	O
owing	O
to	O
one	O
Briant	O
,	O
or	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
had	O
happened	O
,	O
but	O
honour	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
was	O
paid	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
say	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
209	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Herbert	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
January	O
1	O
,	O
1757	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Herbert	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
begging	O
to	O
my	O
door	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
once	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
let	O
her	O
come	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
silver	O
spoon	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
court	O
will	O
forgive	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
will	O
never	O
do	O
so	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
211	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chidley	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
and	O
secretly	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
May	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chidley	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Chidley	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Fleet-market	B-place
.	O
Going	O
out	O
to	O
bar	O
up	O
my	O
windows	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
stood	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
,	O
came	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
I	O
walk	O
'd	O
up	O
before	O
them	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
had	O
my	O
pocket	O
pick	O
'd	O
,	O
by	O
two	O
men	O
coming	O
along	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
collar	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
tin-shop	O
,	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
pull	O
'd	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Plough	O
ale-house	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
ask	O
my	O
pardon	O
if	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
feel	O
it	O
go	O
?	O
Chidley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
They	O
only	O
bresh	O
'd	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
?	O
Chidley	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Waters	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
there	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Waters	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pardon	O
if	O
that	O
would	O
do	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
the	O
alley	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
making	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
lying	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
.	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
produc	O
'd	O
it	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
body	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
212	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
designedly	O
and	O
knowingly	O
obtain	O
from	O
William	B-pers
Preist	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
,	O
goldsmiths	O
and	O
partners	O
;	O
one	O
silver	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
l.	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
defraud	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
Dec.	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Preist	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
14th	O
or	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
lend	O
him	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-kettle	O
and	O
stand	O
to	O
shew	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
one	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
spare	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
one	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
lend	O
him	O
that	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
promis	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
the	O
favour	O
in	O
lending	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
depend	O
upon	O
having	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
hours	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
why	O
do	O
you	O
come	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
having	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
at	O
your	O
own	O
home	O
?	O
his	O
answer	O
was	O
,	O
mine	O
was	O
of	O
a	O
different	O
shape	O
from	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
variety	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
kettle	O
and	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
promise	O
to	O
return	O
them	O
in	O
two	O
hours	O
;	O
but	O
before	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
weigh	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
go	O
upon	O
any	O
account	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
the	O
following	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
serve	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
in	O
keeping	O
the	O
kettle	O
so	O
long	O
;	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
am	O
sorry	O
I	O
should	O
disappoint	O
you	O
in	O
this	O
manner	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
stay	O
till	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
and	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
not	O
bringing	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
gentleman	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
butler	O
had	O
inform	O
'd	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
town	O
till	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
.	O
Not	O
bringing	O
it	O
on	O
that	O
Thursday	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
inste	O
ad	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
line	O
that	O
the	O
gentleman	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
town	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
this	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
of	O
your	O
kettle	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
became	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
a	O
few	O
days	O
after	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
silver	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
the	O
favour	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
that	O
to	O
shew	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
(	O
that	O
was	O
about	O
twenty-three	O
pounds	O
value	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
'd	O
return	O
it	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
but	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Instead	O
of	O
returning	O
with	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
carry	O
'd	O
and	O
pledg	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rochfort	O
,	O
in	O
Covent-garden	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
and	O
stand	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
's	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
says	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
and	O
stand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
which	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
weight	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
will	O
not	O
deliver	O
them	O
.	O
A	O
search	O
warrant	O
and	O
officer	O
is	O
sent	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
first	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
Through	O
Mr.	O
Gladwin	O
,	O
a	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
his	O
father-in-law	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
For	O
what	O
purpose	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
he	O
introduc	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
I	O
apprehend	O
it	O
was	O
to	O
carry	O
on	O
the	O
scheme	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
shop	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
in	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
kettle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
not	O
usual	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
of	O
trade	O
,	O
to	O
borrow	O
goods	O
of	O
one	O
another	O
to	O
shew	O
or	O
sell	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
as	O
in	O
the	O
common	O
course	O
of	O
dealing	O
,	O
as	O
one	O
silversmith	O
lending	O
to	O
another	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lend	O
it	O
him	O
to	O
take	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
could	O
have	O
sold	O
it	O
had	O
you	O
any	O
objection	O
to	O
that	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
objection	O
.	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
it	O
to	O
oblige	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
shew	O
the	O
gentleman	O
as	O
great	O
a	O
variety	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
if	O
the	O
gentleman	O
had	O
lik	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
had	O
another	O
made	O
to	O
match	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
not	O
you	O
receiv	O
'd	O
several	O
sums	O
of	O
money	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
receiv	O
'd	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
pounds	O
eight	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
not	O
receiv	O
'd	O
money	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
and	O
stand	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
common	O
course	O
of	O
dealing	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
him	O
debtor	O
for	O
them	O
in	O
your	O
book	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
charg	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
never	O
was	O
set	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
had	O
wanted	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
would	O
he	O
not	O
have	O
lent	O
them	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
such	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
I	O
apprehend	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
the	O
plate	O
is	O
not	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
expect	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
return	O
'd	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
dispos	O
'd	O
of	O
.	O
I	O
expected	O
that	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
become	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
prov	O
'd	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
prosecution	O
begun	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
he	O
became	O
a	O
bankrupt	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
begun	O
till	O
after	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
cheated	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
in	O
trade	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
you	O
have	O
charg	O
'd	O
this	O
as	O
a	O
debt	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
I	O
prov	O
'd	O
my	O
debt	O
under	O
the	O
statute	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
consider	O
this	O
as	O
a	O
debt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
partner	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Shaw	I-pers
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Dunkerly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Shaw	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Preist	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
Mr	O
.	O
Frost	O
came	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
and	O
lamp	O
away	O
;	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
eighteenth	O
or	O
twentieth	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
They	O
never	O
were	O
set	O
down	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
being	O
to	O
be	O
return	O
'd	O
in	O
so	O
short	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
conversation	O
that	O
pass	O
'd	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Dunkerly	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
borrow	O
a	O
chased	O
tea-kettle	O
and	O
stand	O
to	O
shew	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Preist	O
was	O
above	O
stairs	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
makes	O
you	O
borrow	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
have	O
so	O
many	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
will	O
make	O
a	O
variety	O
,	O
and	O
promis	O
'd	O
to	O
return	O
it	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
several	O
times	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
family	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
,	O
were	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
believ	O
'd	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
town	O
till	O
after	O
Christmas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Preist	O
to	O
that	O
purport	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
customary	O
to	O
lend	O
goods	O
to	O
a	O
Brother	O
trade	O
to	O
sell	O
?	O
Dunkerly	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
lent	O
to	O
shew	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
a	O
promise	O
of	O
being	O
return	O
'd	O
again	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
another	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
method	O
,	O
if	O
goods	O
are	O
not	O
sold	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
person	O
debtor	O
in	O
the	O
book	O
?	O
Dunkerly	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
an	O
unfinish	O
'd	O
thing	O
and	O
not	O
deliver	O
'd	O
for	O
sale	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Preist	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
(	O
The	O
letter	O
produc	O
'd	O
.	O
)	O
Preist	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
Mr	O
.	O
Frost	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
?	O
Preist	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
the	O
exact	O
day	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
Christmas	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
letter	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
)	O
Cornhill	O
,	O
Jan.	O
5	O
,	O
1757	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Preist	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
kettle	O
and	O
stand	O
;	O
the	O
family	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
butler	O
,	O
who	O
will	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
to-morrow	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
may	O
depend	O
on	O
having	O
it	O
,	O
Sir	O
yours	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Frost	I-pers
.	O
Preist	O
.	O
The	O
date	O
should	O
have	O
been	O
fifty-eight	O
,	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
fifty-seven	O
.	O
For	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
Jan.	O
57.	O
Michael	B-pers
Beadle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Price	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
tea-kettle	O
and	O
stand	O
produc	O
'd	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
remember	O
this	O
tea-kettle	O
and	O
stand	O
being	O
brought	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
not	O
enter	O
things	O
in	O
your	O
book	O
?	O
Beadle	O
.	O
We	O
do	O
;	O
but	O
my	O
master	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
?	O
Beadle	O
.	O
Yesterday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
send	O
an	O
impudent	O
answer	O
to	O
this	O
court	O
?	O
Beadle	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Owen	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Brent	O
,	O
two	O
sheriffs	O
officers	O
,	O
depos	O
'd	O
that	O
this	O
witness	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
trouble	O
himself	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
his	O
master	O
was	O
cut	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
send	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Beadle	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
pawn	O
'd	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
Christmas	O
?	O
Beadle	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
before	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
?	O
Beadle	O
.	O
A	O
month	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
lent	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Beadle	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
get	O
at	O
your	O
book	O
?	O
Beadle	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
The	O
subpoena	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
kettle	O
and	O
books	O
.	O
Beadle	O
.	O
The	O
gentlemen	O
hurry	O
'd	O
me	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
court	O
judg	O
'd	O
it	O
needless	O
to	O
try	O
him	O
upon	O
that	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
213	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Coffield	I-pers
and	O
Benj	B-pers
Edmonds	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
May	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
did	O
burglariously	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
46	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
hose	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
l.	O
28	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
l.	O
9	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
three	O
36	O
s.	O
pieces	O
,	O
one	O
moidore	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
number	O
'd	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Coffield	O
was	O
once	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
till	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
you	O
robb	O
'd	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
My	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
between	O
last	O
Thursday	O
and	O
Friday	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
fastened	O
the	O
doors	O
and	O
windows	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
the	O
doors	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
got	O
up	O
first	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
cellar-door	O
had	O
a	O
hole	O
cut	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
could	O
put	O
in	O
an	O
arm	O
and	O
unbolt	O
a	O
bolt	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
unskrew	O
a	O
skrew	O
that	O
fastened	O
down	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
;	O
the	O
hole	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
by	O
turning	O
the	O
arm	O
up	O
and	O
down	O
the	O
fastening	O
could	O
be	O
undone	O
.	O
It	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
some	O
body	O
that	O
knew	O
the	O
fastening	O
without-side	O
.	O
The	O
compting-house	O
door	O
was	O
burst	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
desk	O
broke	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
there	O
was	O
more	O
money	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
desk	O
than	O
I	O
have	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
chose	O
to	O
lay	O
the	O
indictment	O
rather	O
less	O
than	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
9	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
there	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
desk	O
lock	O
'd	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stockings	O
and	O
the	O
silk	O
pieces	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Coffield	O
discharged	O
from	O
your	O
service	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
discharg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
1755	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
He	O
had	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
again	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
from	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
Coffield	O
's	O
lodgings	O
:	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
were	O
for	O
breeches	O
and	O
waistcoats	O
.	O
His	O
wife	O
shewed	O
us	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
concealed	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
16	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
The	O
particular	O
pieces	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
makes	O
that	O
sum	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
him	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
informed	O
Edmonds	O
's	O
wife	O
offer	O
'd	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
to	O
sell	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Maschall	O
,	O
near	O
Aldgate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
as	O
there	O
are	O
so	O
many	O
magistrates	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Garret	I-pers
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
prisoners	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
two	O
women	O
also	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
wife	O
to	O
Edmonds	O
;	O
Edmonds	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
went	O
voluntarily	O
along	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Edmonds	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
these	O
stockings	O
that	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
of	O
a	O
sailor	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
his	O
wife	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
them	O
some	O
time	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
married	O
:	O
but	O
after	O
the	O
justice	O
ordered	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
irons	O
on	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
confessed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Coffield	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
Sunday	O
last	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
Coffield	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
street	O
;	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
us	O
twice	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Maschall	I-pers
.	O
The	O
day	O
before	O
yesterday	O
,	O
after	O
dinner	O
,	O
two	O
women	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
any	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
pair	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Maschall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hosier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Aldgate	O
,	O
they	O
shew	O
'd	O
me	O
this	O
pair	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
asked	O
me	O
16	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
4	O
s.	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
they	O
are	O
sold	O
for	O
in	O
the	O
shops	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
thought	O
the	O
money	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
more	O
service	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
that	O
morning	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Garret	O
's	O
shop	O
having	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
shewed	O
him	O
the	O
stockings	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
stockings	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Garret	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
stockings	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
?	O
Garret	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
these	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
may	O
be	O
like	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
parcel	O
of	O
stockings	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Coffield	O
's	O
possession	O
;	O
the	O
paper	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
are	O
has	O
my	O
hand-writing	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Maschall	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
Edmonds	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
say	O
all	O
he	O
knew	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
hand	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
only	O
would	O
declare	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
stockings	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
After	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Coffield	O
was	O
taken	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
the	O
officer	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
officer	O
had	O
got	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
,	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
down	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
St.	O
John	O
's	O
square	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
to	O
assist	O
him	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
again	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
secur	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
your	O
hear	O
his	O
examination	O
there	O
?	O
William	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Condiet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant-maid	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
go	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
no	O
body	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
shop	O
broke	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Sanders	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
Coffield	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
box	O
of	O
stockings	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
secur	O
'd	O
Coffield	O
and	O
had	O
tied	O
his	O
hands	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
them	O
almost	O
loose	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
10	O
l.	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
we	O
call	O
'd	O
a	O
coach	O
;	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
the	O
minute	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
opened	O
he	O
push	O
'd	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
they	O
brought	O
him	O
again	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
my	O
friend	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
Coffield	O
told	O
us	O
both	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
10	O
l.	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
We	O
drove	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
door	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
people	O
call	O
'd	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
witness	O
that	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
being	O
behind	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
again	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
examination	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
were	O
left	O
him	O
by	O
a	O
soldier	O
that	O
was	O
gone	O
abroad	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
some	O
tools	O
that	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
(	O
producing	O
an	O
iron	O
colt-chissel	O
about	O
14	O
inches	O
long	O
,	O
a	O
tinder-box	O
,	O
matches	O
,	O
flint	O
and	O
steel	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
gunlets	O
)	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
searching	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
had	O
brought	O
home	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
about	O
16	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
receipt	O
of	O
his	O
landlord	O
,	O
for	O
rent	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
paid	O
.	O
Coffield	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
A	O
soldier	O
came	O
and	O
left	O
these	O
things	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
.	O
Edmonds	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Coffield	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
on	O
Sunday	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Maschall	O
's	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Coffield	O
guilty	O
of	O
single	O
felony	O
.	O
Edmonds	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
214	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lovewell	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linen	O
gown	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
shift	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
April	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Jollop	I-pers
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
both	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
mention	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
missing	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jollop	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
having	O
left	O
her	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
weeding	O
the	O
gardens	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
liberty	O
to	O
pawn	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
whom	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
the	O
gown	O
in	O
Long-ditch	O
,	O
at	O
Anne	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
's	O
,	O
the	O
hat	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Gaul	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
shift	O
and	O
apron	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Crayford	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Mayor	O
's	O
.	O
(	O
Produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Plunket	I-pers
.	O
This	O
gown	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
one	O
Sarah	B-pers
Lovewell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Crayford	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
this	O
shift	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
apron	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
too	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
one	O
check	O
is	O
like	O
another	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
say	O
this	O
produced	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
delivered	O
that	O
which	O
she	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
This	O
apron	O
here	O
produced	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Crayford	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Nehemiah	O
Gaul	O
.	O
This	O
silk	O
hat	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
thieve	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
left	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
care	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
215	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Story	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Robert	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
tin	O
kettle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
,	O
Apr	O
.	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	B-place
ale-house	I-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Shadwell	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
copper	O
that	O
was	O
set	O
in	O
brickwork	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
hold	O
about	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
gallons	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
double-tin	O
fish-kettle	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
April	O
.	O
My	O
boy	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoners	O
ever	O
use	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
They	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
their	O
employment	O
?	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
They	O
go	O
with	O
gin	O
upon	O
the	O
river	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
called	O
Bum-boat	O
boys	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
all	O
four	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
My	O
boy	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
Well-Close	O
square	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
broker	O
's	O
name	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
me	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
he	O
shewed	O
it	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
my	O
boy	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
copper	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Abraham	B-pers
Harwood	I-pers
.	O
He	O
came	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
measured	O
my	O
brickwork	O
by	O
a	O
rule	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
sent	O
three	O
coppers	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
would	O
sit	O
the	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Jacobs	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
me	O
drunk	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
copper	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
brasier	O
in	O
Well-close	O
square	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
The	O
people	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
at	O
5	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
to	O
have	O
shared	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
month	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jacobs	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Heard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
that	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
copper	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
brickwork	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
Langley	O
when	O
you	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Heard	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
Thames	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
he	O
that	O
night	O
that	O
he	O
says	O
the	O
copper	O
and	O
kettle	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Heard	I-pers
.	O
We	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoners	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Jacobs	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
They	O
all	O
denied	O
it	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Roberts	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
and	O
asleep	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
three	O
prisoners	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
all	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
bed	O
at	O
their	O
respective	O
lodgings	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
Langley	O
swore	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
For	O
Roberts	O
.	O
Constant	O
Martin	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
by	O
Shadwell-Dock	O
,	O
Roberts	O
has	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
5	O
weeks	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
otherwise	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
boy	O
.	O
That	O
night	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
accused	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
at	O
9	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
till	O
10	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Abraham	B-pers
Harword	I-pers
?	O
Constant	O
Martin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Tobias	B-pers
Denn	I-pers
.	O
Roberts	O
was	O
my	O
bedfellow	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
5	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
awak	O
'd	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
him	O
in	O
bed	O
by	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
Hall	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
.	O
Robert	O
Hall	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
Langley	O
speaks	O
of	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
supper	O
and	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
