TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
5th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
6th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
7th	O
,	O
of	O
APRIL	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Thirty-first	O
Year	O
of	O
his	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1758	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
THE	O
RIGHT	O
HONOURABLE	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ASGILL	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
,	O
in	O
Pater-noster	O
Row	O
,	O
1758	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
CHARLES	B-pers
ASGILL	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Lord	O
MANSFIELD	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
*	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
CLIVE	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Justices	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
+	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Legge	I-pers
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
the	O
Exchequer	O
||	O
;	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
++	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
and	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carrington	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bolter	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Walker	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Hurls	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Brewer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Langdon	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Frith	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Joshua	B-pers
Lassels	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Fisher	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Leteral	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Faulkner	I-pers
,	O
David	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Nesbit	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
*	O
,	O
*	O
George	B-pers
Snowball	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
instead	O
of	O
William	O
Rose	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
158	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Goddey	I-pers
,	O
engraver	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
feloniously	O
,	O
and	O
designedly	O
,	O
did	O
obtain	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Underwood	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
6	O
dozen	O
of	O
stone	O
waistcoat	O
buttons	O
,	O
by	O
false	O
pretences	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
cheat	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
March	O
15	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
159	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
four	O
silver	O
salts	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
cream-pot	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
boat	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
punch-ladle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
mugs	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Deborah	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
February	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Anne	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Weaver	I-pers
;	O
she	O
carries	O
on	O
the	O
business	O
of	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
journeyman	O
with	O
her	O
for	O
about	O
ten	O
days	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
;	O
the	O
plate	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
(	O
mentioning	O
each	O
by	O
name	O
)	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
following	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
as	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
and	O
hear	O
his	O
examination	O
?	O
Anne	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
examined	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
then	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Fosset	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
,	O
and	O
lodge	O
in	O
Mrs.	O
Weaver	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
plate	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
in	O
its	O
place	O
,	O
but	O
can	O
not	O
particularize	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
saw	O
plate	O
in	O
general	O
.	O
The	O
family	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
rang	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
asked	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
our	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
Mrs.	O
Weaver	O
live	O
?	O
John	B-pers
Fosset	I-pers
.	O
She	O
lives	O
in	O
White-hart-court	B-place
,	I-place
Grace-church-street	I-place
;	O
the	O
foreman	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
watchman	O
up	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
dining-room	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
plate	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
beaufet	O
.	O
We	O
applied	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
what	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
advertise	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
being	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Weaver	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Weaver	O
being	O
a	O
quaker	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
.	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
what	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
plate	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
punch-ladle	O
and	O
spoons	O
,	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
two	O
handled	O
mug	O
,	O
or	O
rather	O
cup	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
having	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
often	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
S.	O
W.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
before	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Anne	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
of	O
this	O
plate	O
?	O
Anne	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
all	O
by	O
the	O
marks	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
produced	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
I	O
swore	O
them	O
there	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Fosset	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
examined	O
?	O
Fosset	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
it	O
.	O
he	O
said	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
concealed	O
himself	O
in	O
the	O
cellar	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
the	O
plate	O
away	O
.	O
The	O
spoons	O
were	O
there	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
likewise	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Chesson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
bought	O
three	O
table	O
spoons	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
being	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
four-pence	O
an	O
ounce	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Anne	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
three	O
silver	O
spoons	O
of	O
(	O
I	O
believe	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
has	O
been	O
filed	O
and	O
mixed	O
with	O
others	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
which	O
it	O
is	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
two	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Anne	B-pers
Peirce	I-pers
)	O
one	O
of	O
these	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
hall	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
diminished	O
,	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
both	O
bought	O
together	O
,	O
for	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
an	O
ounce	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Capreal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
very	O
near	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
I	O
shewed	O
him	O
a	O
second	O
hand	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
my	O
man	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
another	O
pair	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
present	O
to	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
a	O
life-guard-man	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
such	O
another	O
pair	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
make	O
him	O
such	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
on	O
my	O
counter	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
plate	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
grandmother	O
left	O
it	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
sister	O
,	O
and	O
brother	O
,	O
dividing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
weigh	O
it	O
separate	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
three	O
parcels	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
stopped	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
for	O
his	O
advice	O
,	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
the	O
advertisement	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
lodged	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
hid	O
himself	O
in	O
his	O
mistress	O
's	O
house	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
plate	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
all	O
but	O
the	O
spoons	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
court	O
of	O
justice	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
nor	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
160	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Greaghan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
riping	O
thirty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Devale	I-pers
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
certain	O
building	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Truelove	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
,	O
two	O
watchmen	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
stopped	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Palm-sunday	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
with	O
lead	O
on	O
his	O
shoulder	O
,	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Jenkinson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
lead	O
fitted	O
to	O
a	O
building	O
in	O
Scotland-yard	O
,	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Devale	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
nails	O
and	O
nail	O
holes	O
fitted	O
exactly	O
,	O
where	O
some	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
weighed	O
forty	O
seven	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
his	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
bargained	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
three-pence	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
from	O
Whitehall	O
to	O
Covent-garden	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
161	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Bloomer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
two	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
set	O
with	O
stones	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
25	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Star	O
and	O
Garter	O
,	O
a	O
publick-house	O
in	O
the	B-place
Strand	I-place
,	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
missing	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
customer	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
that	O
night	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
locked	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
and	O
his	O
friend	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
They	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
;	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
eight	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
down	O
about	O
ten	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
,	O
we	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
of	O
five	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
he	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
lay	O
it	O
very	O
hard	O
upon	O
the	O
other	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
seek	O
for	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
they	O
both	O
lodged	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
opened	O
a	O
drawer	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
a	O
shift	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
which	O
since	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
in	O
the	O
prison	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
might	O
not	O
appeared	O
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
five	O
crown	O
pieces	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
changed	O
them	O
to	O
different	O
people	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
gave	O
10	O
s.	O
for	O
to	O
two	O
people	O
that	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
changed	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
?	O
George	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
in	O
New-prison	O
(	O
he	O
knowing	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
had	O
got	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
them	O
two	O
he	O
might	O
keep	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
were	O
changed	O
to	O
people	O
going	O
abroad	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
shift	O
at	O
justice	O
St.	O
Lawrence	O
's	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
only	O
know	O
by	O
hearsay	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
these	O
crown	O
pieces	O
in	O
my	O
left-hand	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
drawer	O
and	O
locked	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
locked	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hanpkin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Dublin	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Hanpkin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
cabinet-maker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
he	O
been	O
in	O
London	O
?	O
James	B-pers
Hanpkin	I-pers
.	O
It	O
is	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
here	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Mackdowel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
weeks	O
;	O
his	O
character	O
was	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
162	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Hudson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linnen	O
shifts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
three	O
linnen	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
linnen	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
silver	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
leather	O
belt	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
March	O
5	O
.	O
*	O
William	O
Parker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
servant	O
:	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
discharged	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
we	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
an	O
opportunity	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
places	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Pinks	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
confirmed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
evidence	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
confession	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
163	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
bushels	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
March	O
5	O
.	O
||	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
Blackwall	O
with	O
some	O
coals	O
in	O
a	O
skiff	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
stopped	O
them	O
and	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
about	O
four	O
bushels	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
employment	O
?	O
Robert	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
blacksmith	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
offer	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Bury	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
coals	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
it	O
voluntary	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
,	O
and	O
signed	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
read	O
)	O
wherein	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
stole	O
a	O
boat	O
at	O
the	O
Horse-ferry	O
,	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
said	O
coals	O
out	O
of	O
two	O
lighters	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
river	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
justice	O
Bury	O
,	O
my	O
name	O
being	O
upon	O
the	O
skulls	O
.	O
He	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
the	O
skiff	O
was	O
mine	O
that	O
the	O
coals	O
were	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
There	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
and	O
sign	O
this	O
confession	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
now	O
read	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
These	O
coals	O
were	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
for	O
assisting	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
lighter	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
164	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Briggs	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
iron	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
2d	O
.	O
and	O
one	O
wooden	O
pail	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hyde	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
March	O
7	O
.	O
||	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
keeps	O
the	B-place
Crown	I-place
and	I-place
Sceptre	I-place
in	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
a	O
lodging	O
of	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
deserted	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
were	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pledged	O
the	O
goods	O
at	O
three	O
several	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
directions	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
.	O
The	O
three	O
pawnbrokers	O
appeared	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
165	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Eliot	B-pers
Singor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
linnen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sidgesman	I-pers
Tanner	O
,	O
March	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	B-place
Tower	I-place
,	O
between	O
the	O
18th	O
and	O
21st	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
table	O
cloths	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Margaret	B-pers
Tanner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
sheet	O
here	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
will	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
so	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
on	O
Monday	O
was	O
7-night	O
to	O
carry	O
his	O
supper	O
in	O
the	O
Tower	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
a	O
sheet	O
to	O
sell	O
or	O
pawn	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
wet	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
dry	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
(	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
here	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Blue-anchor-yard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
inquire	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
to	O
the	O
serjeant-major	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
keep	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
an	O
owner	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
serjeant-major	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
owner	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Mott	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
a	O
sheet	O
to	O
sell	O
or	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
thought	O
it	O
not	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
so	O
thought	O
it	O
her	O
duty	O
to	O
acquaint	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
heard	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
linnen	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
produce	O
a	O
sheet	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
.	O
first	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
being	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
lodgings	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
serjeant	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
examined	O
her	O
before	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
face	O
;	O
she	O
declared	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
sheet	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
it	O
before	O
then	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
him	O
in	O
prison	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
inquiring	O
,	O
found	O
Mrs.	O
Tanner	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
sheet	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Tanner	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Tanner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
;	O
my	O
linnen	O
was	O
hanging	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
house	O
to	O
dry	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
easy	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
have	O
secured	O
since	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Going	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
exercise	O
on	O
Monday	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
dog	O
that	O
belongs	O
to	O
the	O
drill	O
corporal	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
apt	O
to	O
fetch	O
and	O
carry	O
;	O
somebody	O
threw	O
a	O
stone	O
behind	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
timber	O
in	O
the	O
tower	O
,	O
the	O
dog	O
ran	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
barking	O
,	O
having	O
something	O
that	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
away	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
sheet	O
lying	O
there	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
put	O
under	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
166	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Dunning	I-pers
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lowling	I-pers
,	O
March	O
28	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lowling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
hosier's-shop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Crown-court	B-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
blue	O
stockings	O
,	O
with	O
white	O
clocks	O
;	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
her	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
notice	O
how	O
many	O
pair	O
there	O
were	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
white	O
stockings	O
with	O
pink	O
clocks	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
such	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
scarlet	O
with	O
green	O
clocks	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
myself	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
such	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
then	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
open	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
stockings	O
I	O
had	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
stopped	O
her	O
just	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
pair	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
pair	O
)	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
almost	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
lately	O
turned	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
ever	O
she	O
wronged	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
167	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Judith	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
>	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Abot	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Feb.	O
27	O
.	O
*	O
Samuel	O
Abot	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	B-place
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
sign	O
of	O
the	O
Black-horse	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
follow	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
felt	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
inquired	O
which	O
way	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gaidal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
inquired	O
after	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
her	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
description	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
King-street	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
came	O
and	O
called	O
after	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
right-hand	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
describe	O
the	O
watch	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
day	O
's	O
work	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
up	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
some	O
purl	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
pots	O
of	O
purl	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
use	O
me	O
very	O
rudely	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
hid	O
myself	O
in	O
a	O
gate-way	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
by	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barnet	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
168	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
,	O
March	O
3	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
;	O
on	O
the	O
third	O
of	O
March	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
went	O
up-stairs	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
my	O
lodger	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
turn	O
into	O
Mark-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Mark-lane	B-place
;	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
my	O
lodger	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
and	O
overtook	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Crutched-fryars	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
nothing	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
see	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
thing	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
In	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
minutes	O
time	O
some	O
body	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
woman	O
had	O
dropt	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
one	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
tea-spoons	O
drop	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Murry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mrs.	O
Bull	O
stop	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
bring	O
her	O
back	O
up	O
Mark-lane	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
fall	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
near	O
Mrs.	O
Bull	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
spoons	O
dropt	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Eutycus	O
Edge	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
say	O
give	O
me	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
or	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
which	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
Esther	O
Hall	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
or	O
better	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
or	O
heard	O
a	O
misbehaved	O
action	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
169	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Aspinal	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
unknown	O
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Julian	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silver-smith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Hanwell	O
,	O
at	O
New	O
Brentford	O
in	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
in	O
man	O
's	O
apparel	O
with	O
this	O
hatchet	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
bought	O
old	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
pieces	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
;	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
which	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
suspicion	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
several	O
questions	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
father	O
died	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
produced	O
the	O
whole	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
in	O
pieces	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
when	O
her	O
father	O
died	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
persuaded	O
to	O
cut	O
it	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
bring	O
it	O
more	O
safely	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
cut	O
it	O
to	O
pieces	O
on	O
the	O
stump	O
of	O
a	O
tree	O
.	O
Upon	O
asking	O
her	O
many	O
questions	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
by	O
her	O
voice	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
being	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
in	O
women	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
opened	O
her	O
coat	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
Pretherew	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
secured	O
,	O
and	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pretherew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Bristol	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
Tankard	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pretherew	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
looked	O
over	O
all	O
these	O
pieces	O
of	O
silver	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pretherew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
it	O
ever	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
justice	O
at	O
Hounslow	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
Newgate	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Gloucestershire	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
bringing	O
it	O
to	O
London	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
advised	O
to	O
cut	O
it	O
in	O
pieces	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
bring	O
it	O
the	O
more	O
secret	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
not	O
be	O
robbed	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
170	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Goodall	I-pers
,	O
March	O
6	O
.	O
*	O
Edward	O
Goodall	O
.	O
Coming	O
home	O
through	O
Kenister-alley	B-place
,	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
:	O
the	O
man	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
the	O
woman	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Goodall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
am	O
certain	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
get	O
your	O
watch	O
again	O
?	O
Goodall	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Goodall	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
say	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Goodall	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
it	O
before	O
justice	O
Cox	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
under	O
a	O
stair-hole	O
amongst	O
some	O
dust	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
that	O
we	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
fob	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Goodall	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
searched	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
bosom	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
searched	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
nor	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
170	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frances	B-pers
Divine	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
2	O
.	O
||	O
Frances	B-pers
Divine	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
a	O
lodging	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
one	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
she	O
took	O
a	O
sheet	O
from	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
back	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
till	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
to-morrow	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
fortnight	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
woman	O
is	O
great	O
with	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
keeps	O
him	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
could	O
have	O
no	O
claw	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
has	O
laid	O
this	O
sheet	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
all	O
spight	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
171	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
instruments	O
of	O
steel	O
,	O
with	O
ivory	O
handles	O
,	O
called	O
steels	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
March	O
14	O
.	O
||	O
Henry	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
upon	O
the	O
paved-stones	O
in	O
West	B-place
Smithfield	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
cutler's-shop	O
;	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
sash	O
was	O
lifted	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
steels	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
:	O
he	O
brought	O
one	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
swivel	O
put	O
on	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
all	O
swivels	O
on	O
them	O
when	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
steel	O
,	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
up	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
swivel	O
was	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
six-pence	O
and	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
afterwards	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
lost	O
such	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
butcher	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
father	O
deals	O
in	O
tar	O
and	O
greace	O
for	O
waggons	O
and	O
carts	O
,	O
and	O
trades	O
in	O
dog-horses	O
towards	O
making	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
offered	O
a	O
steel	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Red-cow	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
swivel	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bennet	O
to	O
have	O
one	O
put	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
stole	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
Christian	B-pers
Nicholson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	O
,	O
Clerkenwell	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
Friday	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
steel	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
all	O
over	O
muddy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
swivel	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
it	O
me	O
for	O
six-pence	O
,	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
for	O
three	O
half-pence	O
for	O
his	O
lodging	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
Monday	O
following	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Newgate	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
steel	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
Friday	O
following	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
hog	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
ruttled	O
some	O
old	O
rags	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
amongst	O
it	O
another	O
steel	O
;	O
the	O
hog	O
had	O
done	O
his	O
occasion	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
wiped	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
four	O
steels	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
each	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
respective	O
steels	O
they	O
gave	O
evidence	O
about	O
;	O
all	O
four	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
gave	O
me	O
these	O
four	O
steels	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
172	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Rustin	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Bennell	I-pers
,	O
March	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bennell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
on	O
Easter-Monday	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
perceive	O
it	O
to	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
?	O
Bennell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
is	O
produced	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
then	O
lost	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bethan	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
at	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Half-moon	O
,	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
on	O
Easter-Monday	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
picking	O
gentlemen	O
's	O
pockets	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
marked	O
J	O
.	O
B.	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
No	O
.	O
18	O
.	O
(	O
She	O
looks	O
at	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Martindale	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
Half-moon	O
tavern	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
there	O
on	O
Easter-Monday	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
another	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
bonnet	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
owned	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Groves	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
almost	O
got	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
Half-moon	O
tavern	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
by	O
women	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
soon	O
found	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Wood	O
street	O
counter	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
is	O
there	O
;	O
this	O
gentleman	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
good	O
woman	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
,	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
is	O
almost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
almost	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
the	O
Half-moon	O
tavern	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
this	O
other	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
lost	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
this	O
woman	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
his	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
then	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
she	O
has	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
that	O
handk	O
erchief	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
tavern	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
even	O
with	O
me	O
(	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
for	O
what	O
)	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
the	O
gentleman	O
gave	O
her	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
purpose	O
to	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
See	O
her	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Mary	O
,	O
wife	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Rusty	I-pers
,	O
for	O
a	O
burglary	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
134	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
paper	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
173.	O
George	B-pers
Babb	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pound	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
bell-mettle	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
d.	O
thirty	O
two	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
six	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dodson	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
174	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Morein	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
iron	O
hoops	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Esqrs	O
;	O
March	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Nicol	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
mess	O
.	O
Chase	O
and	O
Cox	O
,	O
brewers	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
employed	O
occasionally	O
as	O
a	O
porter	O
there	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
said	O
he	O
has	O
robbed	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
see	O
what	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
by	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
from	O
under	O
it	O
five	O
iron	O
butt	O
hoops	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
masters	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
2	O
parcel	O
that	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
175	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
twenty-four	O
pounds	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
lead	O
,	O
value	O
18d	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Poe	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
22	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Duncomb	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Poe	O
's	O
house	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
upon	O
the	O
premises	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
floor-cloth	O
to	O
be	O
named	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
brewhouse	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
doing	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
some	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
leaden	O
pipe	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
hid	O
it	O
near	O
the	O
New-River	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Robert	B-pers
Thralkill	I-pers
;	O
there	O
were	O
twenty-four	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
pounds	O
of	O
lead	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
three	O
farthings	O
per	O
pound	O
for	O
the	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
for	O
the	O
lead	O
;	O
it	O
came	O
to	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
country	O
lodgings	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Poe	O
's	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
a	O
journeyman	O
carpenter	O
one	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Duncomb	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
jack	O
going	O
into	O
Old-street	O
;	O
he	O
suspected	O
they	O
had	O
stole	O
it	O
;	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
Duncomb	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Poe	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
before	O
we	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stole	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
charged	O
with	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Poe	O
's	O
premises	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Thralkill	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Thralkill	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
several	O
things	O
of	O
Duncomb	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
against	O
Mead	O
of	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
?	O
Watts	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
nothing	O
but	O
what	O
Duncomb	O
said	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
there	O
acknowledge	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
Thralkill	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
money	O
the	O
evidence	O
has	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Poe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledge	O
he	O
stole	O
the	O
iron	O
and	O
lead	O
,	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
Duncomb	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
the	O
jack	O
;	O
but	O
being	O
cast	O
upon	O
this	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
tried	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
176	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Thralkill	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
so	O
stolen	O
by	O
Charles	B-pers
Mead	I-pers
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Feb.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Mr.	O
Ford	O
produced	O
and	O
read	O
the	O
minutes	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
of	O
the	O
trial	O
and	O
conviction	O
of	O
Charles	O
Mead	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Duncomb	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
Watts	O
deposed	O
as	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
177	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cameron	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
of	O
stuff	O
.	O
called	O
Scotch	O
plaid	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
duffil	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Alexander	B-pers
Mackenzey	I-pers
,	O
March	O
31	O
.	O
+	O
Margaret	B-pers
Mackenzey	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Alexander	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
lie	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Mackenzey	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
Hay	B-place
market	I-place
;	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
;	O
on	O
Friday	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
betwixt	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
for	O
some	O
snuff	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
return	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
stuff	O
,	O
called	O
Scotch	O
plaid	O
,	O
about	O
13	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
duffil	O
cloak	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
Mackenzey	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
East-Indies	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
advertised	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
after	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
plaid	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
cloak	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
now	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
that	O
again	O
?	O
Mackenzey	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
it	O
on	O
when	O
taken	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Barnewell	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
plaid	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
noon	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
advertized	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
the	O
cloak	O
on	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
only	O
to	O
raise	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
again	O
when	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
178	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
called	O
Black-bear	O
alley	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
,	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Mar	O
.	O
15	O
.	O
||	O
Gustavas	O
Forsholm	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Bond-street	B-place
,	I-place
along	I-place
Piccadilly	I-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
betwixt	O
twelve	O
and	O
one	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
going	O
through	O
an	O
alley	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
slipped	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
conversation	O
you	O
had	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Forsholm	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
conversation	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
into	O
another	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
sight	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
any	O
weapon	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
?	O
Forsholm	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
put	O
in	O
fear	O
?	O
Forsholm	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
somebody	O
else	O
might	O
be	O
thereabouts	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Lion	O
in	O
Piccadilly	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
demand	O
your	O
Watch	O
or	O
any	O
thing	O
besides	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Forsholm	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
took	O
it	O
slily	O
away	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
179	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Merriot	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
at	O
Hickes	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
29th	O
year	O
of	O
his	O
present	O
majesty	O
,	O
was	O
according	O
to	O
due	O
course	O
of	O
law	O
tried	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
year	O
,	O
one	O
diaper	O
napkin	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Reed	I-pers
,	O
did	O
steal	O
,	O
take	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
away	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
that	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
the	O
term	O
of	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
seen	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
this	O
kingdom	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
expiration	O
of	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Bonous	I-pers
produced	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
record	O
of	O
the	O
trial	O
and	O
conviction	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
a	O
true	O
copy	O
?	O
Bonous	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
it	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
clerk	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
.	O
[	O
It	O
is	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
the	O
purport	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
]	O
James	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
at	O
a	O
house	O
near	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
he	O
done	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
commit	O
a	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
detected	O
him	O
myself	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
off	O
the	O
premises	O
in	O
May	O
1756	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
doing	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
break	O
a	O
kitchen	O
window	O
in	O
Arundel-street	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
hook	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
some	O
linen	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
forgot	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
his	O
trial	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
at	O
Hickes's-hall	O
;	O
as	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
the	O
principal	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
this	O
ago	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
be	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
next	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
sentence	O
past	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
Cooper	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
my	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
.	O
James	B-pers
Emms	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
;	O
next	O
May	O
will	O
be	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
tried	O
at	O
Hickes's-Hall	O
,	O
and	O
cast	O
for	O
transportation	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Emms	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
turnkeys	O
of	O
New-Prison	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
committed	O
for	O
?	O
Emms	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
committed	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
breaking	O
a	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
and	O
hid	O
himself	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
knew	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Emms	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
any	O
where	O
lately	O
at	O
large	O
?	O
Emms	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
As	O
no	O
evidence	O
was	O
given	O
of	O
his	O
being	O
seen	O
at	O
large	O
since	O
his	O
being	O
transported	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
acquitted	O
.	O
180	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
salt-seller	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
March	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	O
Stevens	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
dine	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
After	O
dinner	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
about	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
pepper-box	O
and	O
salt	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
used	O
to	O
stand	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
the	O
pepper-box	O
and	O
salt-seller	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
we	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
to	O
Thisleworth	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
that	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
that	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
publick-house	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
stay	O
'd	O
there	O
till	O
eight	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
;	O
coming	O
home	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
gates	O
,	O
we	O
heard	O
a	O
great	O
disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
we	O
was	O
asked	O
to	O
assist	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
was	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
.	O
Going	O
along	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dropt	O
this	O
silver	O
salt	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
thinking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robbed	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
body	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
labour	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
shut	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
business	O
was	O
stopt	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Arnold	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
Arnold	O
.	O
Never	O
before	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
not	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
worked	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
pay-mistress	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
does	O
she	O
carry	O
on	O
?	O
Arnold	O
.	O
She	O
carries	O
on	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
he	O
capable	O
of	O
carrying	O
on	O
business	O
?	O
Arnold	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
or	O
no	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
.	O
Arnold	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
pull	O
this	O
pepper-box	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Ewer	I-pers
.	O
That	O
evening	O
James	B-pers
Arnold	I-pers
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
home	O
from	O
our	O
labour	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
desired	O
to	O
assist	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Cage	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dropt	O
the	O
salt	O
;	O
Arnold	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
morrow	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
till	O
the	O
afternoon	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
salt	O
and	O
pepper-box	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
disturbing	O
?	O
Ewer	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
disturbing	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
windows	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
?	O
Ewer	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
broke	O
his	O
windows	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
?	O
Ewer	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
What	O
business	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
butcher	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
your	O
husband	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acquainted	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
They	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
that	O
account	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
dine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
man	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
madman	O
really	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
acquaintance	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
madman	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
He	O
does	O
not	O
now	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
you	O
do	O
right	O
in	O
prosecuting	O
a	O
mad	O
man	O
for	O
a	O
felony	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
such	O
before	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
this	O
woman	O
's	O
husband	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
him	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
We	O
are	O
both	O
butchers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
married	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Almost	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
carry	O
on	O
business	O
now	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
off	O
my	O
business	O
almost	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
live	O
when	O
you	O
carried	O
on	O
business	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
kept	O
a	O
butcher	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Hungerford-market	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
now	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Thisleworth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
children	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
no	O
children	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
means	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
now	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
carry	O
on	O
the	O
gardening	O
business	O
.	O
I	O
purchased	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
ground	O
for	O
that	O
purpose	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
will	O
maintain	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
Upon	O
whose	O
evidence	O
was	O
he	O
committed	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
my	O
evidence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
charge	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
pepper-box	O
and	O
salt	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
signed	O
his	O
own	O
confession	O
,	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
justice	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
evidence	O
against	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
trial	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
begged	O
to	O
be	O
excused	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
charge	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
and	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
his	O
being	O
mad	O
?	O
Lewis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
understood	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
butcher	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
the	O
estate	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
at	O
Isleworth	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
purchase	O
of	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
four	O
hundred	O
and	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Webster	O
.	O
For	O
these	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
past	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
madman	O
in	O
all	O
his	O
actions	O
.	O
Q.	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
gled	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
during	O
what	O
period	O
of	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
any	O
irational	O
act	O
?	O
No	O
answer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
now	O
swear	O
that	O
man	O
is	O
now	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
?	O
Webster	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
see	O
that	O
in	O
him	O
now	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
in	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
thought	O
him	O
mad	O
for	O
this	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Any	O
particular	O
sort	O
of	O
madness	O
?	O
Webster	O
.	O
Wildness	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
used	O
to	O
see	O
him	O
often	O
?	O
Webster	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
once	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
For	O
this	O
two	O
last	O
years	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
thought	O
him	O
mad	O
?	O
Webster	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
any	O
time	O
you	O
saw	O
him	O
mad	O
?	O
Webster	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
more	O
particular	O
that	O
morning	O
he	O
did	O
this	O
fact	O
,	O
he	O
appeared	O
very	O
wild	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
was	O
very	O
troublesome	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
my	O
answer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
mention	O
any	O
other	O
time	O
?	O
Webster	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
of	O
his	O
breaking	O
his	O
wife	O
's	O
windows	O
,	O
and	O
disputes	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
I	O
judged	O
him	O
very	O
unhappy	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alleson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Boar	O
and	O
Castle	O
;	O
his	O
wife	O
made	O
complaint	O
of	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
him	O
into	O
prison	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
till	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
has	O
dined	O
at	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
,	O
by	O
four	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
declared	O
he	O
has	O
eat	O
nothing	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
.	O
He	O
would	O
catch	O
up	O
case	O
knives	O
and	O
run	O
after	O
the	O
servants	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
my	O
news-papers	O
,	O
once	O
I	O
found	O
ten	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
;	O
and	O
sometimes	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
case	O
knives	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
separation	O
between	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
agreement	O
made	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
allow	O
him	O
six	O
shillings	O
per	O
week	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
writing	O
drawn	O
up	O
?	O
Alleson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
often	O
said	O
,	O
while	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
they	O
lay	O
him	O
in	O
that	O
bed	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
lie	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
this	O
time	O
he	O
never	O
lay	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
lay	O
in	O
one	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
fly	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
behave	O
very	O
wild	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
he	O
would	O
sit	O
down	O
and	O
cry	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
together	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Sprigins	I-pers
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Boar	O
and	O
Castle	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
.	O
Sometimes	O
he	O
would	O
appear	O
very	O
sensible	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
other	O
times	O
quite	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Walton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Watford	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
thirty	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
observed	O
a	O
visible	O
alteration	O
in	O
his	O
behaviour	O
;	O
I	O
bailed	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
New	O
Prison	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
put	O
there	O
for	O
?	O
Walton	O
.	O
For	O
assaulting	O
his	O
wife	O
in	O
November	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
there	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Boar	O
and	O
Castle	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
troublesome	O
,	O
and	O
disturbed	O
the	O
customers	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
or	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
?	O
Walton	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
.	O
At	O
that	O
time	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
execute	O
the	O
writings	O
,	O
thinking	O
him	O
not	O
capable	O
to	O
sign	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
they	O
executed	O
since	O
?	O
Walton	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
they	O
executed	O
?	O
Walton	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
bound	O
to	O
forfeit	O
200	O
l.	O
if	O
he	O
ever	O
went	O
near	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
broke	O
her	O
windows	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
related	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Walton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
his	O
brother-in-law	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Boar	O
and	O
Castle	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
hallow	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
into	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
hallowing	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
this	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
distressed	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
through	O
the	O
marriage	O
settlement	O
upon	O
his	O
wife	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dagnall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
meal-man	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
at	O
Watford-mills	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
may	O
answer	O
questions	O
well	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
;	O
yet	O
I	O
know	O
he	O
is	O
mad	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
any	O
question	O
he	O
has	O
answered	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
that	O
discover	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
?	O
I	O
suppose	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
,	O
know	O
for	O
what	O
reason	O
they	O
were	O
asked	O
him	O
?	O
Dagnell	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
answered	O
every	O
question	O
well	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
found	O
your	O
opinion	O
upon	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
moment	O
he	O
is	O
mad	O
?	O
Dagnell	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
say	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
say	O
he	O
is	O
mad	O
now	O
?	O
Dagnell	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
in	O
them	O
now	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
dine	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
thing	O
pass	O
there	O
,	O
that	O
shewed	O
him	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
senses	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nothing	O
passed	O
,	O
only	O
eating	O
and	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
remember	O
a	O
word	O
he	O
said	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
comes	O
it	O
that	O
your	O
husband	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Stevens	O
.	O
He	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
business	O
prevented	O
his	O
coming	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
181	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Martendale	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
being	O
then	O
due	O
and	O
unpaid	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
December	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Daniel	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Wrexham	O
in	O
Denbighshire	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
wrote	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Greenwoller	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
York-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
letter	O
I	O
inclosed	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
24	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
another	O
of	O
10	O
l.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
paper	O
.	O
Pain	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
very	O
identical	O
bill	O
of	O
24	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
I	O
sealed	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
I	O
or	O
my	O
servant	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
;	O
but	O
this	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
of	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
send	O
any	O
to	O
town	O
with	O
a	O
bill	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
either	O
I	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
myself	O
,	O
or	O
send	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
his	O
Robert	B-pers
Lankford	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
my	O
apprentice	O
;	O
I	O
not	O
hearing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
receiving	O
it	O
,	O
wrote	O
a	O
second	O
letter	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
bills	O
inclosed	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
all	O
the	O
indorsements	O
on	O
the	O
bills	O
when	O
you	O
inclosed	O
it	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
name	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Lankford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
,	O
at	O
Wrexham	O
in	O
Denbighshire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
business	O
is	O
it	O
to	O
carry	O
and	O
put	O
letters	O
in	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
,	O
when	O
your	O
master	O
sends	O
any	O
to	O
London	O
?	O
Lankford	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
either	O
his	O
business	O
or	O
mine	O
:	O
all	O
are	O
put	O
in	O
either	O
by	O
himself	O
or	O
me	O
if	O
bills	O
are	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
?	O
Lankford	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
recollect	O
putting	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
in	O
December	O
last	O
?	O
Lankford	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
my	O
master	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
do	O
you	O
put	O
letters	O
in	O
that	O
office	O
?	O
Lankford	O
.	O
We	O
generally	O
put	O
letters	O
in	O
every	O
post	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Suppose	O
your	O
master	O
did	O
then	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
.	O
Lankford	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
particular	O
letter	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
remember	O
it	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
(	O
He	O
takes	O
the	O
bill	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
that	O
bill	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
that	O
before	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
name	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
your	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
My	O
son	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
he	O
wrote	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
My	O
hand	O
shakes	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
write	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
bill	O
ever	O
paid	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
never	O
was	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
never	O
was	O
paid	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
It	O
never	O
was	O
paid	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Pain	O
.	O
I	O
remitted	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
paid	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
(	O
He	O
takes	O
the	O
bill	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
name	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
my	O
father	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
is	O
my	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
I	O
generally	O
write	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
I	O
wrote	O
at	O
his	O
desire	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
E.	O
Jones	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
in	O
these	O
cases	O
give	O
authority	O
to	O
your	O
son	O
to	O
write	O
your	O
name	O
?	O
E.	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
is	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Pyke	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
at	O
Wrexham	O
in	O
Denbighshire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
kept	O
it	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Pyke	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
About	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
letters	O
that	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
what	O
care	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Pyke	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
particular	O
care	O
of	O
all	O
letters	O
put	O
into	O
my	O
office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
as	O
to	O
this	O
particular	O
letter	O
now	O
in	O
question	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Pyke	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
letter	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Greenwollers	O
's	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
those	O
letters	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Pyke	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
London	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
go	O
safe	O
to	O
town	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Pyke	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
no	O
stay	O
,	O
or	O
hindrance	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
heard	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
usual	O
when	O
you	O
send	O
up	O
letters	O
to	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Pyke	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
do	O
n't	O
name	O
the	O
franks	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
remember	O
this	O
in	O
particular	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Pyke	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
a	O
post	O
or	O
two	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
no	O
answer	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
this	O
letter	O
from	O
your	O
own	O
knowledge	O
,	O
or	O
from	O
his	O
telling	O
you	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Pyke	O
.	O
His	O
telling	O
me	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
uneasiness	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
recollecting	O
,	O
I	O
remembered	O
particularly	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
letter	O
in	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Greenwollers	O
's	O
.	O
Joshua	B-pers
Baker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
General	O
Post-Office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
Chester	O
mail	O
coming	O
in	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ravenhead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
Chester	O
mail	O
did	O
come	O
in	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
,	O
containing	O
all	O
the	O
bags	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
Wrexham	O
bag	O
in	O
that	O
Chester	O
bag	O
?	O
Ravenhead	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
Chester	O
bag	O
in	O
that	O
mail	O
?	O
Ravenhead	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
opened	O
the	O
Chester	O
bag	O
?	O
Ravenhead	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
does	O
the	O
Chester	O
mail	O
come	O
out	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
arrive	O
here	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
?	O
Ravenhead	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
dispatched	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
from	O
thence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
is	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
the	O
Wrexham	O
bag	O
dated	O
?	O
Ravenhead	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
dated	O
the	O
14th	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Baker	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
Chester	O
mail	O
coming	O
to	O
your	O
office	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
length	O
of	O
time	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
the	O
post-master	O
's	O
bill	O
was	O
produced	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
is	O
produced	O
,	O
he	O
takes	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
Baker	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
undoubtedly	O
my	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
these	O
Bills	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Pyke	O
has	O
already	O
declared	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
letters	O
she	O
sent	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
It	O
appears	O
what	O
number	O
there	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Pyke	O
.	O
Look	O
on	O
that	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Pyke	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
letters	O
came	O
from	O
Wrexham	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
my	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
Baker	O
.	O
These	O
were	O
received	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
writing	O
,	O
we	O
sign	O
our	O
names	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
part	O
printed	O
,	O
and	O
filled	O
up	O
by	O
the	O
postmasters	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
their	O
arrival	O
we	O
sign	O
our	O
names	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
certainly	O
received	O
these	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
have	O
signed	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
bag	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
sealed	O
as	O
usual	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
remembrance	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
we	O
always	O
look	O
at	O
those	O
things	O
then	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
comptroller	O
of	O
the	O
General	O
Post	O
Office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
employed	O
at	O
the	O
Post-Office	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Potts	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
employed	O
as	O
letter	O
carrier	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
about	O
Bloomsbury-square	O
,	O
to	O
carry	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
sick	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
concern	O
with	O
the	O
letters	O
sent	O
to	O
York-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
It	O
appears	O
this	O
letter	O
,	O
now	O
in	O
question	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
frank	O
letter	O
.	O
York-street	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
his	O
walk	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
division	O
;	O
there	O
are	O
four	O
of	O
those	O
letter	O
carriers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
remarkably	O
assiduous	O
to	O
fetch	O
the	O
frank	O
letters	O
;	O
those	O
four	O
men	O
take	O
the	O
letters	O
and	O
sort	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
any	O
one	O
may	O
have	O
those	O
frank	O
letters	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
letter	O
you	O
sent	O
in	O
a	O
frank	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
frank	O
by	O
Sir	O
Lynch	O
Cotton	O
.	O
Potts	O
.	O
I	O
apprehend	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
thought	O
this	O
was	O
for	O
his	O
purpose	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
as	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
fetches	O
the	O
letters	O
for	O
the	O
whole	O
seat	O
,	O
into	O
the	O
letter	O
carrier	O
's	O
office	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
are	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
carriers	O
.	O
I	O
only	O
prove	O
the	O
general	O
course	O
of	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
to	O
shew	O
that	O
this	O
letter	O
directed	O
to	O
York-street	O
,	O
might	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Potts	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
this	O
letter	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
he	O
told	O
an	O
odd	O
story	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
his	O
principal	O
officer	O
,	O
may	O
be	O
he	O
will	O
say	O
something	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
alone	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
together	O
into	O
a	O
closet	O
;	O
the	O
moment	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
he	O
dropped	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
flood	O
of	O
tears	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
bill	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
letter	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
any	O
other	O
letter	O
carrier	O
,	O
in	O
our	O
office	O
,	O
concerned	O
with	O
you	O
in	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
not	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
ruined	O
and	O
undone	O
himself	O
;	O
for	O
he	O
,	O
himself	O
,	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
letter	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
but	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
servant	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
that	O
persuaded	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
commission	O
of	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
he	O
repeated	O
the	O
same	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
there	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
confession	O
tell	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
mercy	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
the	O
whole	O
?	O
Baker	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nor	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
threats	O
in	O
order	O
thereto	O
.	O
Baker	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Greenwollers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
correspondence	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Pain	O
of	O
Wrexham	O
,	O
in	O
Denbighshire	O
:	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
contents	O
were	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
two	O
bills	O
in	O
a	O
letter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
that	O
letter	O
you	O
received	O
?	O
Greenwollers	O
.	O
That	O
letter	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
him	O
a	O
letter	O
the	O
post	O
following	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
such	O
letter	O
came	O
to	O
hand	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
received	O
another	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
for	O
24	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Tosier	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
payment	O
;	O
it	O
being	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Tosier	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Tosier	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Greenwollers	O
brought	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
a	O
draught	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
advice	O
of	O
a	O
draught	O
being	O
sent	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
received	O
;	O
and	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
stop	O
payment	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
told	O
him	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
brought	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
had	O
accepted	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
when	O
it	O
became	O
due	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
us	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Griffith	O
for	O
payment	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
ready	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Griffith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
linen-draper	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Clare-market	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
cloth	O
of	O
about	O
2	O
s.	O
per	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
recollect	O
the	O
exact	O
time	O
.	O
Griffith	O
.	O
As	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
recollect	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
him	O
out	O
a	O
piece	O
,	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
Muslin	O
for	O
Neck-cloths	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pocket	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
The	O
bill	O
came	O
to	O
3	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
he	O
shewed	O
me	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
accepted	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Tosier	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
bill	O
.	O
Griffith	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
bill	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
pray	O
where	O
does	O
this	O
gentleman	O
live	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
for	O
24	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
full	O
change	O
,	O
and	O
deducted	O
the	O
3	O
l.	O
6	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
for	O
my	O
goods	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
bill	O
became	O
due	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
in	O
Billiter-square	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Tosier	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
stopped	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Martendale	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
thing	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
better	O
confess	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
recommend	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
postmaster-general	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
mentioned	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Potts	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
all	O
I	O
said	O
was	O
,	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
body	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
guilty	O
;	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
of	O
use	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
discovery	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
jury	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
)	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
thirteen	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
deserved	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
before	O
this	O
thing	O
happened	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Darby	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
year	O
1741	O
;	O
his	O
behaviour	O
has	O
been	O
extremely	O
good	O
in	O
all	O
the	O
places	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
once	O
lived	O
with	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
then	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Fell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
thirteen	O
or	O
fourteen	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Fell	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
but	O
honesty	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Blaseley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
been	O
his	O
behaviour	O
?	O
Blaseley	O
.	O
He	O
behaved	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
I	O
always	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
182	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Henry	B-pers
Strickland	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
two	O
muslin	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
one	O
five	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Caleb	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
hon	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Dodington	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Mar	O
.	O
28	O
.	O
*	O
Caleb	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
where	O
I	O
do	O
almost	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
with	O
the	O
coach	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
stable-door	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
off	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
box	O
one	O
five	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
some	O
linen	O
and	O
stockings	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
box	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
stable	O
,	O
the	O
hon	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Dodington	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
my	O
helper	O
that	O
was	O
,	O
had	O
got	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lives	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
,	O
but	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
linen	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
last	O
Sunday	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
shirts	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
stockings	O
on	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Round-house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Newgate	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
my	O
stockings	O
in	O
the	O
bundle	O
which	O
I	O
found	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
a	O
watchman	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Meuse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
searched	O
when	O
taken	O
up	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
five	O
guineas	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
purse	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
the	O
watch	O
with	O
the	O
five	O
guinea	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
own	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
the	O
stable-door	O
,	O
while	O
another	O
man	O
brought	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
shared	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
ow	O
ned	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
money	O
and	O
my	O
linen	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
that	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
when	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Wheeler	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
fellow-servant	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
I	O
almost	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
coachman	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
fourteen	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
eight	O
pence	O
in	O
halfpence	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
four	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
case	O
of	O
steams	O
,	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
nut-crackers	O
,	O
a	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pocket-piece	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
changed	O
the	O
great	O
piece	O
of	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
what	O
change	O
he	O
had	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
street	O
beyond	O
,	O
St.	O
Paul	O
's	O
church-yard	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
Cheapside	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
;	O
I	O
sold	O
a	O
watch	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
which	O
answers	O
to	O
the	O
watch	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
five	O
guinea	O
piece	O
to	O
change	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
a	O
thirty-six	O
piece	O
,	O
eight	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
large	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
since	O
suppose	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
five	O
guinea	O
piece	O
;	O
he	O
proposed	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
fetch	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brumage	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
knocked	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
on	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
together	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Grimes	O
's	O
house	O
and	O
drank	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Hammersmith	O
;	O
we	O
seeing	O
he	O
had	O
money	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
drunk	O
and	O
lose	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
leave	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Grimes	O
's	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
it	O
delivered	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
which	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
He	O
left	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
with	O
two	O
shirts	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
own	O
'd	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
rob	O
the	O
coachman	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
find	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
183	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
two	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
and	O
lamp	O
,	O
one	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
two	O
damask	O
napkins	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
pillow	O
cases	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Castledine	I-pers
,	O
March	O
30	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Loat	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Castledine	O
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
the	O
bagnio	O
in	O
Leicester-fields	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
trusted	O
with	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
having	O
lost	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
woman	O
having	O
quarrelled	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
You	O
old	O
bitch	O
I	O
'll	O
blow	O
you	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
that	O
?	O
The	O
other	O
said	O
,	O
About	O
the	O
tea-spoon	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
that	O
woman	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
about	O
the	O
tea-spoon	O
?	O
So	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Castledine	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
Castle-court	O
,	O
a	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
a	O
lamp	O
,	O
two	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
linen	O
,	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Castledine	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Styles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
two	O
tea-spoons	O
to	O
the	O
evidence	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
sure	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
these	O
two	O
brass	O
candlesticks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Styles	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
this	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
many	O
things	O
taken	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Styles	O
's	O
in	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
bring	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
184	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Esther	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
March	O
2	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Edward	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
months	O
,	O
her	O
brother	O
and	O
sister	O
boarded	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
she	O
keeps	O
company	O
with	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
7	O
s.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Torneck	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
told	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
all	O
in	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
halfpence	O
in	O
my	O
right	O
side	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
silver	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
husband	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
club-room	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Torneck	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
and	O
prisoner	O
,	O
standing	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
the	O
box	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
was	O
on	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
leaning	O
over	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
talking	O
with	O
both	O
her	O
hands	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
;	O
she	O
presently	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
this	O
on	O
my	O
thigh	O
?	O
clap	O
'd	O
her	O
hand	O
down	O
and	O
seiz	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
apron	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
open	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
fingers	O
to	O
my	O
mouth	O
and	O
weted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
strove	O
to	O
screw	O
her	O
hand	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
7	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
That	O
afternoon	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
;	O
when	O
my	O
brother	O
and	O
sister	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
My	O
friend	O
stay	O
'd	O
till	O
towards	O
night	O
with	O
my	O
sister	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
sister	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
spent	O
your	O
fortune	O
?	O
(	O
I	O
having	O
broke	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
lodging	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
want	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
assist	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
very	O
acceptable	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
me	O
a	O
present	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
treated	O
us	O
with	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
rum	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
my	O
brother	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
work	O
,	O
he	O
treated	O
him	O
with	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
down	O
for	O
one	O
more	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
landlady	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
