TOKEN	NE
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
MARCH	O
1759	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Thirty-second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1759	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
GLYN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
;	O
1759	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
GLYN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
:	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
DENNISON	I-pers
Knt	O
.	O
*	O
:	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
ADAMS	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
+	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
Corenas	B-pers
Barett	I-pers
William	B-pers
Matthews	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Braint	I-pers
John	B-pers
Marquistin	I-pers
John	B-pers
Malcot	I-pers
Jacob	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
John	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
Hugh	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
William	B-pers
Judd	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Woodyer	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Parritt	I-pers
John	B-pers
Gilbert	I-pers
William	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Russel	I-pers
Jason	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
William	B-pers
Cobbot	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
William	B-pers
Dickens	I-pers
John	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
John	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
Peter	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
William	B-pers
Flambrough	I-pers
113	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Bateman	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
February	O
14th	O
,	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hatter	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Star-alley	B-place
in	I-place
Fen-church	I-place
street	I-place
;	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
cellar	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
light	O
comes	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
some	O
body	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
body	O
answered	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
follow	O
'd	O
her	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
own	O
wearing	O
hat	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
quite	O
new	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
door	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
worth	O
when	O
new	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
worth	O
12	O
shillings	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
by	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
that	O
hat	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
threshold	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
rap	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
it	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
people	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
robbery	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
114	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
,	O
May	O
24	O
,	O
1758	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Globe	B-place
ale-house	I-place
in	I-place
Hatton-Garden	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
suspect	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Bevan	O
.	O
She	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
usually	O
sit	O
on	O
a	O
bench	O
in	O
my	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
she	O
was	O
waiting	O
for	O
somebody	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sitting	O
there	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
was	O
then	O
feeding	O
the	O
children	O
with	O
the	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
the	O
spoons	O
mentioned	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
meet	O
with	O
your	O
spoons	O
again	O
?	O
Bevan	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
nor	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
'till	O
last	O
Friday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
me	O
?	O
she	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
soon	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
stay	O
'till	O
next	O
day	O
at	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
and	O
get	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Catherine	B-pers
Dun	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
several	O
times	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bevan	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
feeding	O
the	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
made	O
use	O
of	O
both	O
the	O
silver	O
spoons	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sat	O
facing	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
I	O
washed	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
so	O
placed	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
see	O
where	O
you	O
put	O
them	O
?	O
Dun	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lock	O
the	O
drawer	O
?	O
Dun	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
looked	O
for	O
them	O
in	O
about	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
ten	O
minutes	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
spoons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
them	O
?	O
Dun	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
chair	O
for	O
a	O
midwife	O
that	O
liv	O
'd	O
near	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
trust	O
me	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
stay	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
spoons	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
and	O
a	O
tankard	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
girl	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
just	O
by	O
,	O
on	O
Saffron-hill	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
absconded	O
;	O
had	O
I	O
been	O
guilty	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
staid	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
C.	O
Dun	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
spoons	O
were	O
taken	O
?	O
Dun	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
but	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
belong	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
,	O
contrary	O
to	O
the	O
opinion	O
of	O
the	O
Court	O
.	O
115	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Tracey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
callimancoe	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Newsham	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Sarah	O
Newsham	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Rober	O
Newsham	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Walbrook	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Trig	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
a	O
box	O
at	O
Thomas	B-pers
Creswell	I-pers
's	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
,	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	B-place
parish	I-place
,	O
with	O
many	O
things	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
only	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
for	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
lid	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
had	O
a	O
hinge	O
taken	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Newsham	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
last	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
leave	O
it	O
lock	O
'd	O
?	O
Newsham	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
this	O
woman	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
put	O
in	O
the	O
round-house	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
and	O
Mrs	O
Gyles	O
;	O
John	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
brought	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
.	O
Produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Herring	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Grafton	O
street	O
St	O
Ann's-Soho	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
these	O
sheets	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
19th	O
;	O
she	O
pledged	O
them	O
as	O
her	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
4	O
s.	O
on	O
them	O
.	O
Amey	O
Gyles	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Dyer	O
's	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
She	O
produced	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
petticoat	O
:	O
these	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
gown	O
on	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
petticoat	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Depos	O
'd	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Gyles	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
as	O
to	O
whose	O
property	O
they	O
were	O
?	O
Gyles	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
for	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
a	O
customer	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
room	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
another	O
woman	O
that	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
her	O
name	O
was	O
Molly	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
other	O
name	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
did	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
116	O
.	O
117	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Lovet	I-pers
and	O
Winifred	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
thirty-six	O
shilling	O
piece	O
,	O
one	O
moidore	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
moidore	O
,	O
twenty-three	O
guineas	O
and	O
one	O
half-guinea	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lateward	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	O
Lateward	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	B-place
and	I-place
Hoop	I-place
in	I-place
Holborn	I-place
,	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
evening	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
where	O
these	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
sitting	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
hickups	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
make	O
game	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
insinuated	O
themselves	O
into	O
my	O
company	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
give	O
us	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
I	O
treated	O
them	O
with	O
six	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
bag	O
with	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
so	O
much	O
money	O
about	O
you	O
?	O
Lateward	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
book-keeper	O
to	O
Mr	O
John	B-pers
Anson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
keeps	O
a	O
tea	O
ware-house	O
,	O
the	O
Green	O
Cannister	O
,	O
just	O
above	O
Middle-row	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
money	O
had	O
you	O
about	O
you	O
?	O
Lateward	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
28	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
they	O
seeing	O
this	O
,	O
one	O
kept	O
talking	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
other	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
pocket	O
had	O
you	O
it	O
in	O
?	O
Lateward	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Lateward	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
;	O
that	O
will	O
come	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
next	O
witness	O
.	O
Lovet	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Cox	O
after	O
it	O
;	O
presently	O
she	O
wheedled	O
me	O
out	O
to	O
some	O
house	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
Lovet	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
bag	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
house	O
you	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
?	O
Lateward	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
Tennis-court	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
Cox	O
for	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
Lovet	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
undress	O
yourself	O
?	O
Lateward	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
She	O
got	O
from	O
me	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
evening	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
day	O
following	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Magpye	O
and	O
Horse-shoe	O
in	O
Middle-row	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
complaining	O
of	O
my	O
loss	O
;	O
the	O
maid-servant	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
could	O
inform	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
name	O
?	O
Lateward	O
.	O
Her	O
name	O
is	O
Susanna	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hoop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
Mary	B-pers
Lovet	I-pers
take	O
the	O
bag	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hoop	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
Cox	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
secured	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
.	O
There	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
five	O
guineas	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
two-pence	O
,	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
;	O
which	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
found	O
Lovet	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Cox	O
say	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
?	O
Lateward	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
I	O
throw	O
'd	O
my	O
bag	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
might	O
pay	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
for	O
a	O
k	O
-	O
g	O
bout	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
criminal	O
conversation	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
equipped	O
her	O
self	O
out	O
very	O
fine	O
with	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
suppose	O
;	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
cardinal	O
,	O
gold	O
necklace	O
,	O
shifts	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hoop	O
drinking	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
drinking	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
sitting	O
at	O
a	O
table	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
seven-night	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
the	O
hiccups	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
made	O
game	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
them	O
bitches	O
,	O
and	O
curs	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
had	O
some	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
Lovet	O
say	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
By	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
a	O
sigh	O
out	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
pull	O
out	O
a	O
dun-coloured	O
canvass	O
bag	O
and	O
take	O
out	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
six	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
both	O
the	O
prisoners	O
sat	O
on	O
his	O
left-hand	O
side	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
sat	O
nearest	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
Winifred	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
did	O
,	O
at	O
last	O
they	O
mov	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
sat	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
bag	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
the	O
shilling	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
his	O
left-hand	O
coat-pocket	O
;	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
bag	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
words	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
Cox	O
's	O
hand	O
,	O
Lovet	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
and	O
handed	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
by	O
G	O
-	O
d	O
here	O
is	O
money	O
enough	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
both	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Susannah	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
:	O
then	O
Mary	O
Lovet	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
on	O
his	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
sat	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
shifted	O
sides	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
this	O
Lovet	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
My	O
Mother	O
came	O
to	O
call	O
me	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
Winifred	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
together	O
in	O
the	O
Alehouse	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
night	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Magpye	O
and	O
Horseshoe	O
in	O
Middle-Row	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
talking	O
to	O
the	O
company	O
of	O
his	O
loss	O
;	O
I	O
hearing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
tell	O
him	O
who	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
Alehouse	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hoop	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Lovet	O
.	O
Was	O
I	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Sus	O
.	O
Edwards	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
you	O
was	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Constable	O
belonging	O
to	O
St	O
Andrew	O
Holborn	O
:	O
on	O
Thursday	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hoop	O
in	O
Holborn	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
charge	O
of	O
Winifred	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
;	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
five	O
guines	O
,	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
two-pence	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Justice	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
come	O
here	O
and	O
give	O
evidence	O
;	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
that	O
money	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Lovet	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
Winifred	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Leather-lane	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
any	O
money	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
her	O
handkerchief	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Cock	O
and	O
Hoop	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
this	O
gentleman	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
had	O
the	O
biccups	O
;	O
we	O
made	O
game	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
winked	O
with	O
his	O
eyes	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
Winifred	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
to	O
let	O
him	O
sit	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
six-penny-worth	O
of	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
an	O
oyster-woman	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
three-penny-worth	O
of	O
oysters	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
in	O
our	O
box	O
;	O
presently	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
mi	O
ssed	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
the	O
landlady	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
near	O
him	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
bag	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
nine-pence	O
for	O
the	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
oysters	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
money	O
enough	O
;	O
Winifred	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
'till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
called	O
me	O
out	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
redeem	O
some	O
things	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
.	O
Cox	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
we	O
could	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
in	O
Tennis	O
Court	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
'till	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
my	O
commodity	O
;	O
the	O
landlady	O
being	O
willing	O
to	O
take	O
money	O
bid	O
me	O
show	O
him	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
his	O
purse	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
girl	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
money	O
enough	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
pay	O
yourself	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
fifteen	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
laid	O
me	O
down	O
and	O
-	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
five	O
pound	O
note	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
to	O
be	O
concerned	O
another	O
way	O
.	O
Both	O
guilty	O
of	O
felony	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
118	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
thirty-six	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Alice	O
,	O
Feb.	O
12	O
.	O
*	O
Alice	O
Bell	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
slop-shop	O
in	O
Shadwell	B-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
my	O
child	O
cried	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
course	O
sheet	O
of	O
paper	O
rattle	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
making	O
his	O
escape	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
thirty-six	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
they	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Bell	O
.	O
Upon	O
shelves	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchiefs	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
facing	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
:	O
the	O
boy	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
fell	O
from	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
119	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
rug	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	O
Jackson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mutton-lane	B-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
bottom	I-place
of	I-place
Clerkenwell-green	I-place
:	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
Feb	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
rug	O
,	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sheet	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodge	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
Because	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
that	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
she	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr	O
Bell	O
in	O
Peter-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
promise	O
to	O
excuse	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
you	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
these	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
pair	O
of	O
blankets	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
Mary	O
Bell	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
poor	O
woman	O
,	O
whose	O
husband	O
was	O
at	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
three	O
small	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
blankets	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
two	O
blankets	O
like	O
these	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
these	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
Are	O
there	O
any	O
marks	O
on	O
them	O
by	O
which	O
you	O
know	O
them	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
A	O
cat	O
kittened	O
on	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
stained	O
it	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
I	O
know	O
that	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
is	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
sheet	O
at	O
Mr	O
Warner	O
's	O
in	O
St	O
John's-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rug	O
at	O
Abraham	B-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Cow-cross	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
the	O
sheet	O
is	O
coloured	O
by	O
the	O
Ebony	O
wood	O
that	O
our	O
men	O
turn	O
,	O
it	O
makes	O
their	O
linnen	O
and	O
sheets	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
lie	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
yellow	O
colour	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Pawn-Broker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
St	O
John's-street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Pound	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
street	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
February	O
instant	O
:	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
eighteen-pence	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
two	O
hours	O
after	O
came	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
show	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledged	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
returned	O
me	O
a	O
shilling	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
spent	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Benjamin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Broker	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
rug	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
bedstead	O
of	O
me	O
about	O
six	O
weeks	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
the	O
rug	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
for	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Keeling	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
acquitted	O
,	O
and	O
now	O
they	O
try	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
120	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Grace	B-pers
Blackbourn	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Haseldine	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
Polonese	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
:	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Belton-street	B-place
,	I-place
St	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
:	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silk	O
polonese	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
thing	O
that	O
does	O
up	O
with	O
ribbons	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
polonese	O
up	O
and	O
look	O
'd	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
red	O
cardinal	O
on	O
;	O
she	O
pulled	O
it	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
mine	O
on	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
show	O
her	O
the	O
yard	O
backwards	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
showed	O
her	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
there	O
:	O
there	O
were	O
men	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
pull	O
the	O
cardinal	O
off	O
again	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
:	O
she	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
and	O
turned	O
short	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
looked	O
for	O
it	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
soon	O
after	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
again	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
in	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
121	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Costello	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Swain	I-pers
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Jan.	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Jos	O
.	O
Swain	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	B-place
West	I-place
's	I-place
house	I-place
in	I-place
Newgate	I-place
Market	I-place
,	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
drinking	O
of	O
punch	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sat	O
next	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
sleepy	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Swain	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
sober	O
nor	O
quite	O
drunk	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
a	O
little	O
with	O
my	O
customers	O
.	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
and	O
awaked	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
started	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
hand	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
missed	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
your	O
had	O
your	O
money	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
into	O
that	O
house	O
?	O
Swain	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
feel	O
for	O
it	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
people	O
rose	O
up	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
searching	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
hand	O
was	O
clinched	O
as	O
it	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
out	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
six-pence	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
person	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
to	O
the	O
Watch-house	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
examined	O
before	O
Sir	O
Crisp	O
Gascoyne	O
,	O
at	O
Guild-hall	O
,	O
the	O
Alderman	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
discharge	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
witness	O
appeared	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
Alderman	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
days	O
to	O
get	O
friends	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
people	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
who	O
brought	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lent	O
him	O
5	O
l.	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
;	O
the	O
Alderman	O
told	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
badness	O
of	O
the	O
crime	O
if	O
she	O
foreswore	O
herself	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
she	O
refused	O
to	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
although	O
she	O
proposed	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
before	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
drinking	O
at	O
Mr	O
West	O
's	O
in	O
Newgate-market	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
or	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
with	O
his	O
face	O
all	O
over	O
black	O
,	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
purl	O
,	O
or	O
beer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
sober	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
his	O
face	O
appear	O
dirty	O
or	O
done	O
with	O
blows	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
It	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
smut	O
of	O
a	O
chimney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
after	O
he	O
sat	O
and	O
dozed	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
,	O
Mr	O
West	O
came	O
and	O
shook	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
not	O
sleep	O
here	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
he	O
fell	O
to	O
dozing	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
awaked	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
hand	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
Mr	O
Swain	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
Mr	O
Swain	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
guineas	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
which	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
and	O
a	O
sixpence	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
pocket	O
it	O
was	O
clinched	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
asked	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
:	O
but	O
would	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
:	O
but	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
proprietors	O
of	O
the	O
St	O
George	O
or	O
Royal	O
George	O
privateer	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
to	O
receive	O
there	O
besides	O
that	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
hearing	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
prove	O
she	O
lent	O
it	O
him	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
swore	O
she	O
lent	O
him	O
five	O
guineas	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
her	O
lodgings	O
;	O
the	O
Alderman	O
telling	O
her	O
the	O
heinousness	O
of	O
her	O
crime	O
if	O
she	O
should	O
forswear	O
herself	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
lend	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
West	I-pers
.	O
This	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Newgate-market	O
,	O
about	O
two	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
;	O
Mr	O
Swain	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
his	O
face	O
all	O
smutted	O
;	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
near	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
drinking	O
punch	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Swain	O
dozing	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
awaked	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
;	O
after	O
which	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
time	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
arose	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
me	O
see	O
what	O
money	O
you	O
have	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
my	O
hand	O
close	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mr	O
Swain	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
five	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
particular	O
pieces	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
could	O
remember	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
bran	O
new	O
half-guinea	O
of	O
the	O
date	O
of	O
58	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
Mr	O
Swain	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
money	O
which	O
he	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
the	O
half-guinea	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
batter	O
'd	O
one	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
remember	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
guineas	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
positive	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
call	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
watchman	O
that	O
was	O
just	O
without	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Swain	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
happen	O
'd	O
after	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Mr	O
Swain	O
before	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
comes	O
into	O
my	O
kitchen	O
often	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
.	O
West	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
;	O
there	O
Mr	O
Swain	O
said	O
he	O
remembered	O
the	O
last	O
house	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
blacked	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
one	O
half-guinea	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
or	O
second	O
examination	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
West	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
examination	O
before	O
Sir	O
Crisp	O
Gascoyne	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
Mr	O
Swain	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
much	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
money	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
Mr	O
West	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
he	O
answered	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
sure	O
;	O
the	O
Alderman	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
house	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
tavern	O
or	O
bagnio	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
;	O
the	O
Alderman	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
girl	O
in	O
his	O
company	O
there	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
:	O
the	O
Alderman	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concern	O
'd	O
with	O
the	O
girl	O
?	O
he	O
hardly	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Wheat	O
sheaf	O
behind	O
St	O
Clement	O
's	O
church	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
Mr	O
West	O
's	O
with	O
his	O
face	O
all	O
black	O
.	O
and	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
is	O
a	O
manager	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
a	O
birth	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
started	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
had	O
your	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
you	O
have	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
your	O
hand	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
searched	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
what	O
money	O
I	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
Mr	O
West	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Jackson	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Covent-Garden	O
with	O
a	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
?	O
Jackson	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
,	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
tavern	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lent	O
her	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
given	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
half-guinea	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
of	O
58	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
an	O
old	O
or	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
(	O
I	O
mean	O
Tuesday	O
)	O
I	O
received	O
2	O
l.	O
7	O
s.	O
for	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
shalloon	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
of	O
Mr	O
Brown	O
in	O
Grace-church	O
street	O
;	O
out	O
of	O
this	O
money	O
I	O
gave	O
John	B-pers
Samuel	I-pers
's	O
son	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
for	O
his	O
Christmas-box	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
then	O
when	O
reckon	O
'd	O
it	O
must	O
stand	O
thus	O
:	O
l.	O
s.	O
d.	O
In	O
my	O
pocket	O
left	O
on	O
Monday	O
night	O
.	O
1	O
1	O
0	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
for	O
shalloon	O
2	O
7	O
0	O
-	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
3	O
2	O
0	O
which	O
amounts	O
to	O
6	O
10	O
0	O
Out	O
of	O
which	O
,	O
take	O
two	O
half-guineas	O
,	O
then	O
there	O
remains	O
5	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
of	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
four	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
divided	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
gold	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
silver	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
divide	O
it	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
the	O
half-guinea	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
gold	O
in	O
one	O
pocket	O
and	O
silver	O
in	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Wheatsheaf	O
behind	O
St.	O
Clement	O
's	O
church	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
spent	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
'till	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
was	O
sleepy	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
there	O
put	O
some	O
black	O
spots	O
on	O
my	O
face	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
thing	O
pass	O
between	O
the	O
woman	O
and	O
you	O
after	O
you	O
had	O
put	O
your	O
money	O
into	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
only	O
bidding	O
her	O
a	O
good-night	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
lose	O
your	O
money	O
at	O
the	O
Wheat-sheaf	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
with	O
none	O
there	O
but	O
gentlemen	O
of	O
credit	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
.	O
122	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Jedkins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Lady	B-pers
Charlotte	I-pers
Torrington	I-pers
;	O
and	O
one	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
and	O
one	O
cloth	O
cardinal	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Phoebe	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Jan.	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
Mr.	O
Dodkill	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
concerned	O
for	O
my	O
Lady	O
Torrington	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
inform	O
'd	O
her	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
at	O
Hendon	B-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
very	O
early	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
suspected	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
could	O
trace	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
foot	O
in	O
the	O
gravel	O
walk	O
where	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
dusk	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
over	O
night	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
looking	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
they	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
hat	O
near	O
the	O
window	O
at	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
supposed	O
to	O
enter	O
,	O
which	O
will	O
be	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
silver	O
spoons	O
missing	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
all	O
relating	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
;	O
the	O
servants	O
lost	O
other	O
things	O
which	O
they	O
will	O
speak	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
spoons	O
ever	O
found	O
again	O
?	O
Dodkill	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
Dodkill	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
witness	O
can	O
speak	O
best	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
live	O
near	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Dodkill	O
.	O
She	O
knew	O
the	O
house	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
her	O
sister	O
had	O
been	O
house-maid	O
to	O
my	O
Lady	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
married	O
away	O
.	O
Phoebe	B-pers
Brett	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
in	O
Lady	O
Torrington	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
red	O
cardinal	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
mahogany	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
tea-spoon	O
and	O
cannisters	O
belonging	O
to	O
it	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
them	O
?	O
Brett	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
they	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
Brett	O
.	O
From	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
do	O
you	O
imagine	O
they	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
?	O
Brett	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Brett	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Brett	O
.	O
We	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
because	O
her	O
hat	O
was	O
found	O
next	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
lead	O
that	O
was	O
just	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
at	O
which	O
she	O
got	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
window	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
situation	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
it	O
?	O
Brett	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
carv	O
'd	O
work	O
on	O
which	O
she	O
could	O
set	O
her	O
feet	O
and	O
so	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
knew	O
the	O
house	O
very	O
well	O
and	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Brett	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bull	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
work-house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
on	O
her	O
pretending	O
to	O
be	O
ill.	O
(	O
the	O
hat	O
produc	O
'd	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hat	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
made	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
work-house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
?	O
Bull	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
us	O
two	O
months	O
or	O
more	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
?	O
Bull	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
pieces	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gunnis	I-pers
.	O
John	B-pers
White	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
her	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
all	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
within	O
a	O
little	O
of	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Jan	O
e	O
Seney	O
.	O
(	O
She	O
takes	O
the	O
hat	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
this	O
hat	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
Seney	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
two	O
pieces	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
one	O
within	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
without	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Dugden	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
after	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
a	O
red	O
cardinal	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
her	O
business	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Dugden	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
redeem	O
some	O
things	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
red	O
cardinal	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Phoebe	O
Brett	O
's	O
cardinal	O
?	O
Dugden	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
near	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
house	O
since	O
my	O
sister	O
came	O
away	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
123	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Cunniford	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
serge	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bayton	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
+	O
John	O
Bayton	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Forestreet	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
in	O
Red-lion	B-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Whitechapel	I-place
,	O
at	O
one	O
Mr	O
Dobins	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
breakfast	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
put	O
my	O
coat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
at	O
dinner-time	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
pull	O
it	O
off	O
?	O
Bayton	O
.	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
off	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
instant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lay	O
it	O
?	O
Bayton	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Dobins	O
's	O
kitchen	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
enquiry	O
of	O
the	O
labourers	O
if	O
they	O
knew	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
let	O
in	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
breakfast	O
,	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
labourer	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
work	O
with	O
you	O
there	O
?	O
Bayton	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
since	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
business	O
there	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
him	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
stealing	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
deny	O
'd	O
it	O
'till	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
labourer	O
come	O
that	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
labourer	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Bayton	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Bayton	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
at	O
what	O
house	O
?	O
Bayton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
get	O
your	O
coat	O
again	O
?	O
Bayton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
describe	O
your	O
coat	O
to	O
him	O
when	O
you	O
accus	O
'd	O
him	O
?	O
Bayton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
own	O
what	O
time	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
?	O
Bayton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
coat	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
enquiring	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
other	O
coats	O
with	O
yours	O
.	O
Bayton	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
none	O
but	O
my	O
partner	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
not	O
taken	O
away	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
books	O
in	O
my	O
coat-pocket	O
,	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
hid	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
in	O
search	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Bayton	O
.	O
We	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
Cross	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
confess	O
this	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
accord	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
any	O
threats	O
or	O
promises	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Bayton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
neither	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Francis	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
?	O
Bayton	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Tell	O
the	O
conversation	O
that	O
past	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
him	O
.	O
Bayton	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
willing	O
to	O
satisfy	O
me	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Instant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
custody	O
in	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
deny	O
'd	O
at	O
first	O
being	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
in	O
Red-lion-street	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
the	O
labourer	O
was	O
brought	O
that	O
let	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
fell	O
a-crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
steal	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
labourer	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
?	O
Instant	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Instant	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hatcher	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
Mr	O
Dobins	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
in	O
Red-lion	O
street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
in	O
Rag-Fair	O
for	O
five	O
shilling	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
mentioned	O
two	O
pocket-books	O
being	O
in	O
the	O
coat-pocket	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
them	O
in	O
Whitechapel	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
he	O
mentioned	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
two	O
pocketbooks	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
your	O
coat-pocket	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
One	O
was	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
printed	O
book	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
not	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
has	O
had	O
the	O
calamity	O
of	O
having	O
his	O
skull	O
broke	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
sometimes	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
senses	O
?	O
Hatcher	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
hear	O
so	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
call	O
'd	O
some	O
witnesses	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
my	O
brother	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
first	O
charged	O
with	O
this	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
taking	O
the	O
coat	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
he	O
is	O
half	O
foolish	O
and	O
thick	O
of	O
hearing	O
;	O
they	O
persuaded	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
own	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
own	O
it	O
so	O
that	O
other	O
people	O
might	O
be	O
cleared	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
fearing	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
goal	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
his	O
head	O
was	O
torn	O
to	O
pieces	O
by	O
a	O
dog	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
times	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
giving	O
a	O
reasonable	O
answer	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
.	O
I	O
married	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
sister-in-law	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
see	O
this	O
poor	O
unhappy	O
creature	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
design	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
him	O
guilty	O
:	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
come	O
to	O
any	O
terms	O
,	O
satisfy	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
not	O
trouble	O
myself	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
understanding	O
?	O
I.	O
Simonds	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
an	O
idiot	O
,	O
he	O
ca	O
n't	O
give	O
a	O
rational	O
answer	O
;	O
ask	O
him	O
a	O
thing	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
will	O
give	O
two	O
different	O
answers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
?	O
I.	O
Simonds	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
felony	O
before	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Willet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
my	O
father	O
and	O
me	O
about	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
?	O
Willet	O
.	O
We	O
look	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
fellow	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
obstinate	O
insolent	O
fellow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Willet	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
plaisterer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
he	O
for	O
a	O
workman	O
?	O
Willet	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cutler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
the	O
least	O
stain	O
in	O
his	O
character	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
but	O
an	O
honest	O
fellow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
is	O
he	O
for	O
understanding	O
?	O
Cutler	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
foolish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
?	O
Cutler	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
12	O
years	O
or	O
thereabouts	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Coake	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
dozen	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
work	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
many	O
a	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
foolish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
really	O
think	O
him	O
so	O
?	O
Coake	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
next	O
kin	O
to	O
an	O
idiot	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Ticknal	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
ten	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Ticknal	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
hard	O
working	O
fellow	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
several	O
places	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Scarret	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodged	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
with	O
him	O
as	O
long	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
of	O
his	O
character	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
once	O
torn	O
to	O
bits	O
by	O
a	O
dog	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
skull	O
was	O
fractured	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
silly	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
124	O
,	O
125	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Chatlin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
iron	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
iron	O
hook	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Rickards	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Hugh	B-pers
Cavenhaugh	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Rickards	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
February	O
instant	O
,	O
late	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
Glass-house	O
to	O
see	O
how	O
the	O
work	O
went	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
Glass-house	O
?	O
Rickards	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
:	O
I	O
found	O
Chatlin	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
did	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
;	O
he	O
pleaded	O
poverty	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
lie	O
there	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
also	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
day	O
following	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
soon	O
after	O
missed	O
a	O
chain	O
and	O
hook	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
church	O
the	O
Sunday	O
following	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
people	O
were	O
accusing	O
him	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
for	O
three	O
pence	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
hook	O
was	O
made	O
to	O
take	O
on	O
and	O
off	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Blacksmith	O
to	O
have	O
it	O
made	O
into	O
a	O
poker	O
;	O
the	O
poor	O
fellow	O
Chatlin	O
is	O
a	O
foregner	O
and	O
a	O
cripple	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bowler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
Chatlin	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
Glass-house	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
there	O
a	O
night	O
or	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
chain	O
away	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
night	O
following	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
challenged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Cavenhaugh	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Cavenhaugh	O
's	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
Hawkins	O
a	O
Smith	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
a	O
poker	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
something	O
for	O
victuals	O
and	O
drink	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
three	O
pence	O
on	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Hawkins	O
's	O
and	O
found	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
chain	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
if	O
sold	O
for	O
old	O
iron	O
?	O
Bowler	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
shilling	O
or	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
there	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Bowler	O
.	O
There	O
might	O
be	O
about	O
ten	O
pounds	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
price	O
per	O
pound	O
for	O
old	O
iron	O
?	O
Bowler	O
.	O
The	O
common	O
price	O
is	O
a	O
penny	O
a	O
pound	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
cost	O
my	O
master	O
above	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
For	O
Cavenhaugh	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Cavenhaugh	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
chain	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
poker	O
of	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
always	O
bore	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Cavenhaugh	O
bears	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
understand	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
prosecuted	O
him	O
,	O
had	O
I	O
not	O
been	O
bound	O
over	O
.	O
Chatlin	O
guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Cavenhaugh	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
126	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Swinney	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
thread	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
17	O
s.	O
and	O
twelve	O
pair	O
of	O
childrens	O
yarn	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
,	O
privately	O
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
another	O
business	O
:	O
my	O
wife	O
keeps	O
a	O
Hosiers-shop	O
:	O
I	O
lost	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
brown	O
thread	O
stockings	O
yesterday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
pair	O
of	O
childrens	O
stockings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Yates	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Yates	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
see	O
her	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
:	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
quality	O
binding	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
penny	O
a	O
yard	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
served	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
you	O
then	O
?	O
Yates	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
parlour	O
near	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
she	O
bought	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
binding	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
turned	O
her	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
been	O
gone	O
out	O
long	O
?	O
Yates	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
just	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
:	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
through	O
the	O
alley	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
she	O
fell	O
to	O
running	O
;	O
she	O
threw	O
one	O
bundle	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
pursued	O
her	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
she	O
dropped	O
another	O
bundle	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
up	O
the	O
bundles	O
,	O
but	O
overtook	O
her	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Bury-street	O
;	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bundles	O
were	O
brought	O
back	O
by	O
another	O
person	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
open	O
the	O
bundles	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Yates	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
there	O
?	O
Yates	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
bundles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
were	O
there	O
?	O
Yates	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
seven	O
pair	O
of	O
mens	O
thread	O
,	O
and	O
twelve	O
pair	O
of	O
childrens	O
stockings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
stockings	O
?	O
Yates	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
to	O
the	O
mark	O
upon	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
very	O
safely	O
say	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
goods	O
and	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
stockings	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
the	O
paper	O
in	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
was	O
dirty	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
dirt	O
upon	O
the	O
paper	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
occasioned	O
by	O
their	O
being	O
dropped	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
custody	O
have	O
they	O
been	O
since	O
?	O
Yates	O
.	O
My	O
Lord-Mayor	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
produce	O
here	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
came	O
into	O
your	O
shop	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Yates	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
drop	O
the	O
stockings	O
?	O
Yates	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
both	O
parcels	O
:	O
the	O
first	O
she	O
dropped	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
distance	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Yates	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Sus	O
.	O
Yates	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
:	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
February	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
her	O
take	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
hole	O
where	O
they	O
usually	O
lie	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
for	O
a	O
pennyworth	O
of	O
quality	O
binding	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
come	O
before	O
and	O
her	O
errand	O
was	O
generally	O
for	O
a	O
half-pennyworth	O
of	O
tape	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
quality	O
binding	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
other	O
customers	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Sus	O
.	O
Yates	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
:	O
our	O
shop	O
has	O
a	O
counter	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
stockings	O
lie	O
on	O
that	O
side	O
that	O
the	O
counter	O
is	O
not	O
on	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
my	O
husband	O
ran	O
out	O
and	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
bundles	O
were	O
soon	O
brought	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
stockings	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
brought	O
in	O
by	O
a	O
child	O
about	O
eleven	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
so	O
not	O
capable	O
of	O
swearing	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Alderman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
dinner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Alderman	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Yates	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
for	O
some	O
quality	O
binding	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
dinner	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
mistress	O
say	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
haste	O
we	O
could	O
after	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
just	O
gone	O
out	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
set	O
up	O
a	O
run	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
one	O
bundle	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
another	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
come	O
back	O
willingly	O
?	O
Alderman	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
unwilling	O
to	O
come	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
two	O
bundles	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
also	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
answer	O
did	O
she	O
make	O
?	O
Alderman	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Alderman	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
our	O
shop	O
before	O
then	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
I	O
very	O
well	O
remember	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
my	O
birth-day	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
alley	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
never	O
in	O
it	O
before	O
above	O
once	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
voice	O
call	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
declare	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
boy	O
came	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
women	O
came	O
and	O
beat	O
me	O
very	O
grossly	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
bitch	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
pay	O
for	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
robbed	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
these	O
were	O
his	O
words	O
I	O
protest	O
,	O
was	O
I	O
never	O
to	O
speak	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Alderman	I-pers
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Alderman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
plain	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
there	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
the	O
bundles	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
cloak	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
127	O
,	O
128	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
saws	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wale	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wale	I-pers
I	O
am	O
a	O
Carpenter	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
a	O
building	O
in	O
Queen	B-place
Anne's-street	I-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Marybone	I-place
;	O
I	O
locked	O
up	O
my	O
tools	O
in	O
my	O
chest	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
January	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
being	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
22d	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
chest	O
had	O
been	O
brook	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
two	O
saws	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
there	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
?	O
Wale	O
.	O
About	O
six	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
it	O
broke	O
?	O
Wale	O
.	O
The	O
lid	O
was	O
chopped	O
with	O
an	O
ax	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
and	O
had	O
them	O
advertised	O
in	O
his	O
paper	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
saw	O
my	O
saws	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
them	O
examined	O
?	O
Wale	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
recollect	O
what	O
was	O
said	O
to	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
saws	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Alexander	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Monday	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
about	O
noon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Wilson	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
shop	O
do	O
you	O
keep	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
;	O
he	O
brought	O
a	O
saw	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
come	O
alone	O
?	O
Alexander	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
alone	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Pollard	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
engraved	O
on	O
the	O
saw	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
name	O
engraved	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
:	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
reading	O
the	O
Public	O
Advertiser	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
this	O
saw	O
expressed	O
particularly	O
,	O
and	O
mentioned	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
as	O
the	O
advertisement	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
next	O
evidence	O
John	O
Spence	O
with	O
another	O
saw	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
desire	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
at	O
Marybone	O
,	O
where	O
this	O
Wilson	O
did	O
use	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
where	O
his	O
lodgings	O
were	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
he	O
nor	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
were	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
Constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
broke	O
their	O
lodging-room	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
saws	O
were	O
taken	O
thereout	O
;	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
heard	O
that	O
Wilson	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
sent	O
a	O
detainer	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
name	O
Pollard	O
on	O
your	O
saw	O
when	O
you	O
lost	O
it	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spence	I-pers
.	O
(	O
he	O
produc	O
'd	O
a	O
saw	O
)	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
saw	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Spence	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Crane-court	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Crane-court	O
?	O
Spence	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
by	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
church	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
she	O
bring	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Spence	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
in	O
the	O
Advertiser	O
several	O
saws	O
were	O
advertised	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
out	O
the	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
Hog-lane	O
,	O
at	O
a	O
breeches	O
maker	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
breeches	O
maker	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
such	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
there	O
that	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
on	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
shewing	O
me	O
the	O
woman	O
's	O
lodgings	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
broke	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
some	O
tools	O
that	O
were	O
given	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
just	O
done	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
entirely	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
live	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
those	O
saws	O
of	O
one	O
Thomas	O
Parker	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ow	O
'd	O
me	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
them	O
for	O
my	O
debt	O
.	O
For	O
Harris	O
's	O
character	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
behaved	O
with	O
industry	O
'till	O
this	O
other	O
prisoner	O
seduc	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
now	O
she	O
is	O
near	O
her	O
time	O
by	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
really	O
persuaded	O
it	O
is	O
by	O
his	O
influence	O
that	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
drawn	O
into	O
this	O
.	O
Wilson	O
guilty	O
||	O
.	O
||	O
See	O
Wilson	B-pers
an	O
evidence	O
against	O
his	O
accomplice	O
Charles	O
Fendal	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
72	O
l.	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Groves	I-pers
's	O
chest	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
secreted	O
what	O
he	O
thought	O
proper	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
Fendal	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
349	O
,	O
in	O
last	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
Harris	O
acquitted	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
indicted	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	O
,	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Mary	O
Harris	O
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
diaper	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
,	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
to	O
be	O
us	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
his	O
wife	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
January	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
broad	B-place
St	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
taken	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
lodgings	O
about	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
or	O
your	O
wife	O
let	O
her	O
the	O
lodgings	O
?	O
Drew	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Drew	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
possession	O
of	O
the	O
lodging-room	O
?	O
Drew	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Drew	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
herself	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
then	O
seen	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
tried	O
with	O
her	O
just	O
now	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
some	O
things	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
proposed	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
six	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
came	O
at	O
five	O
o'clock	O
;	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
time	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
enquire	O
about	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Wilson	O
come	O
to	O
lodge	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
indictment	O
mentions	O
his	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
lodging	O
.	O
Drew	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
that	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
'till	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
they	O
lodg	O
'd	O
there	O
?	O
Drew	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
pass	O
for	O
man	O
and	O
wife	O
?	O
Drew	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prosecutors	O
came	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
lodging-room	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Wilson	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
liberty	O
to	O
break	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
her	O
,	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
where	O
Wilson	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
at	O
last	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Gatehouse	O
Westminster	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
they	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
of	O
that	O
room	O
?	O
Drew	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Drew	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Fell	O
's	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mr	O
Fielding	O
's	O
;	O
Mr	O
Fell	O
being	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
produce	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
the	O
woman	O
behave	O
?	O
Drew	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
behaved	O
herself	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
belive	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
us	O
'd	O
very	O
ill	O
by	O
the	O
fellow	O
that	O
is	O
just	O
gone	O
from	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
She	O
once	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
tea-kettle	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
all	O
again	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr	O
Fell	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
:	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
tea-kettle	O
,	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
candlestick	O
:	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
such	O
things	O
as	O
these	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
There	O
came	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
I	O
believe	O
with	O
her	O
sometimes	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Drew	O
fetch	O
'd	O
them	O
away	O
and	O
carry	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
Mr	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
ordered	O
them	O
again	O
into	O
my	O
custody	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
positive	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
identity	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
same	O
things	O
that	O
Mr	O
Drew	O
fetch	O
'd	O
away	O
the	O
same	O
things	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledg	O
'd	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Were	O
the	O
goods	O
which	O
you	O
took	O
from	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
that	O
were	O
deliver	O
'd	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
at	O
Mr	O
Fielding	O
's	O
again	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
very	O
same	O
;	O
and	O
these	O
produced	O
are	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
wife	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
let	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
could	O
not	O
come	O
here	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
saws	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Christopher	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
building	O
which	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wale	I-pers
was	O
;	O
I	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
my	O
tools	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
two	O
saws	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
my	O
chest	O
being	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
about	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
and	O
described	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
stopped	O
if	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
advertised	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Mason	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
John	O
Spensley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
saw	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
.	O
Wilson	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
saws	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
will	O
hang	O
any	O
body	O
for	O
the	O
reward	O
,	O
as	O
all	O
thief-takers	O
will	O
.	O
Wilson	O
guilty	O
.	O
Harris	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Wilson	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
,	O
and	O
Harris	O
a	O
fourth	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
saws	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
;	O
a	O
book	O
called	O
The	O
Builders	O
Jewel	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
pence	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
pence	O
;	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
this	O
building	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
files	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
chest	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
building	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
lock	O
'd	O
them	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
my	O
chest	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
saws	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spensley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
saws	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
.	O
Wilson	O
guilty	O
.	O
Harris	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Wilson	O
was	O
a	O
fourth	O
,	O
and	O
Harris	O
a	O
fifth	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
January	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Bridgman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
building	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
prosecutors	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
chest	O
a	O
trying	O
plane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
meet	O
with	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Bridgman	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
at	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
's	O
:	O
Produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spensley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
plane	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
amongst	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Wilson	O
guilty	O
.	O
Harris	O
acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Wilson	O
was	O
a	O
fifth	O
,	O
and	O
Harris	O
a	O
sixth	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
saws	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dowglas	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
22	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Dowglas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
building	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
chest	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
two	O
saws	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
Dowglas	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
by	O
the	O
constable	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
deposed	O
as	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
trials	O
.	O
Wilson	O
guilty	O
.	O
Harris	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
129	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ruth	B-pers
Child	I-pers
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
February	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
Alice	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Greek-street	B-place
,	I-place
Soho	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
A.	O
Murray	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
upon	O
my	O
fortune	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
for	O
charity	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
neither	O
shoes	O
nor	O
hardly	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
that	O
could	O
be	O
call	O
'd	O
apparel	O
;	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
pity	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
some	O
cold	O
victuals	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
old	O
curtain	O
to	O
make	O
her	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
return	O
she	O
wash	O
'd	O
my	O
door	O
down	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
down	O
into	O
my	O
kitchen	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
victuals	O
which	O
was	O
cold	O
lamb	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
did	O
you	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
into	O
your	O
kitchen	O
?	O
A.	O
Murray	O
.	O
Never	O
but	O
once	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
in	O
the	O
dish	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
eat	O
the	O
victuals	O
she	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
we	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
about	O
the	O
door	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
after	O
the	O
spoon	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
left	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
dish	O
and	O
denied	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
child	O
,	O
that	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
true	O
,	O
I	O
beg	O
you	O
will	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
truth	O
that	O
innocent	O
people	O
may	O
not	O
be	O
accus	O
'd	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
fell	O
a	O
crying	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
Kitty	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
another	O
girl	O
,	O
advis	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
ever	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
something	O
to	O
make	O
money	O
off	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
things	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
and	O
fetch	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
?	O
A.	O
Murray	O
.	O
I	O
understand	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
thirteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
spoon	O
out	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
prosecute	O
he	O
;	O
I	O
recommend	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
spoon	O
?	O
A.	O
Murray	O
.	O
At	O
Mr	O
Coolling	O
's	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
to	O
you	O
does	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
A.	O
Murray	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
two	O
doors	O
out	O
of	O
Soho	O
square	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
lives	O
opposite	O
St	O
Giles	O
's	O
church	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cooling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
;	O
(	O
a	O
spoon	O
produced	O
)	O
this	O
spoon	O
one	O
Catherine	B-pers
King	I-pers
brought	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
aunt	O
's	O
spoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
brought	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Cooling	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
fourtenth	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
February	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
her	O
upon	O
it	O
?	O
Cooling	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
six	O
shillings	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
girl	O
before	O
?	O
Cooling	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Catherine	B-pers
King	I-pers
and	O
her	O
aunt	O
too	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
her	O
aunt	O
lives	O
in	O
very	O
good	O
credit	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
spoon	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
(	O
she	O
takes	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
spoon	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
dish	O
when	O
the	O
child	O
eat	O
the	O
cold	O
lamb	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
is	O
dead	O
and	O
my	O
father	O
is	O
a	O
journeyman	O
Baker	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
Hampton-court	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
necessity	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
130.	O
William	B-pers
Ray	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
William	I-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
James	I-pers
Cockerham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
two	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
mahogany	O
tea	O
board	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
January	O
20	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
copper	O
pottage-pot	O
and	O
cover	O
,	O
value	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodhouse	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
20	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
also	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cockerham	I-pers
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
feloniously	O
make	O
,	O
forge	O
,	O
and	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
and	O
cause	O
and	O
procure	O
to	O
be	O
falsely	O
made	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
,	O
and	O
willingly	O
acting	O
therein	O
,	O
a	O
certain	O
promissory	O
note	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
:	O
No	O
.	O
1884	O
.	O
Sept.	O
18	O
,	O
1758	O
.	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr	O
James	B-pers
Cockerham	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
three	O
months	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
seven	O
pounds	O
,	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
by	O
Banjmn	O
.	O
Nassh	O
.	O
7	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
0	O
d.	O
and	O
for	O
offering	O
and	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
falsely	O
made	O
and	O
counterfeited	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
.	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
hand	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Freeman	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
was	O
so	O
kind	O
as	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
,	O
Tallow-Chandler	O
,	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
(	O
he	O
takes	O
the	O
note	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
indorsed	O
this	O
note	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
cash	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
indorse	O
it	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
friend	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
cash	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
your	O
friend	O
,	O
name	O
him	O
.	O
Howard	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
Mr	O
Richard	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
:	O
I	O
looked	O
upon	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
note	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
Mr	O
Nash	O
write	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr	O
Freeman	O
let	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
about	O
three	O
shillings	O
allowed	O
for	O
discount	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
read	O
the	O
note	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
indorsed	O
it	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
Note	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
1884	O
.	O
Sept.	O
18	O
.	O
58	O
.	O
I	O
promise	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr	O
James	B-pers
Cockerham	I-pers
,	O
or	O
order	O
,	O
3	O
months	O
after	O
date	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
7	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
for	O
value	O
received	O
by	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Nash	I-pers
.	O
7	O
l.	O
3	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
not	O
tried	O
for	O
forging	O
this	O
very	O
note	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
misfortune	O
so	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
*	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Howard	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
111.	O
in	O
last	O
Sessions	O
Papers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
Cockerham	O
might	O
have	O
absconded	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
so	O
minded	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
taken	O
him	O
before	O
they	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
hear	O
that	O
he	O
absconded	O
?	O
Howard	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
lodgings	O
afterwards	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
when	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
note	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
bringing	O
the	O
note	O
to	O
Mr	O
Freeman	O
they	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Hooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
this	O
note	O
(	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
hand	O
)	O
to	O
Mr	O
Nash	O
for	O
payment	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
upon	O
that	O
?	O
Hooper	O
.	O
Mr	O
Nash	O
stopped	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
note	O
too	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
who	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
Mr	O
Freeman	O
,	O
and	O
Howard	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr	O
Nash	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Hooper	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr	O
Nash	O
the	O
Tallow-chandler	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
been	O
from	O
his	O
infancy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
his	O
character	O
and	O
manner	O
of	O
writing	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
he	O
spell	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
Not	O
as	O
this	O
is	O
:	O
this	O
is	O
Nassh	O
,	O
he	O
spells	O
it	O
with	O
a	O
single	O
s.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
he	O
spell	O
his	O
christian	O
name	O
,	O
Ba	O
or	O
Be	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
spells	O
it	O
Ba	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
upon	O
the	O
note	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
this	O
is	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
handwriting	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
so	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
not	O
like	O
his	O
character	O
or	O
way	O
of	O
writing	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
may	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
Mr	O
Nash	O
write	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
may	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
before	O
this	O
indictment	O
was	O
laid	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
take	O
upon	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
cut	O
and	O
construction	O
of	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
from	O
only	O
seeing	O
him	O
write	O
four	O
times	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Needham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr	O
Nash	O
the	O
Tallow-chandler	O
in	O
Fetter-lane	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
him	O
write	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
before	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
it	O
about	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Publican	O
:	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
club	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
which	O
he	O
does	O
belong	O
to	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
beer	O
club	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
for	O
altering	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
wrote	O
this	O
,	O
[	O
producing	O
a	O
paper	O
writing	O
,	O
]	O
here	O
is	O
his	O
name	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
divers	O
receipts	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
write	O
before	O
September	O
last	O
?	O
*	O
*	O
*	O
The	O
Second	O
Part	O
of	O
these	O
Proceedings	O
will	O
be	O
published	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
Days	O
.	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
OF	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
28th	O
,	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
,	O
and	O
Thursday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
MARCH	O
1759	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Thirty-second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
PART	O
II	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1759	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
third	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
GLYN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
.	O
1759	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
JOHN	B-pers
NEEDHAM	I-pers
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
I	O
have	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Hooper	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
offer	O
it	O
in	O
payment	O
?	O
Hooper	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
it	O
the	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
due	O
,	O
with	O
three	O
days	O
of	O
grace	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
December	O
21	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
write	O
this	O
paper	O
you	O
produce	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
write	O
it	O
about	O
two	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
write	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
character	O
as	O
he	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
write	O
receipts	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
before	O
that	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
divers	O
times	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
note	O
(	O
in	O
question	O
)	O
he	O
takes	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
Needham	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
no	O
more	O
his	O
handwriting	O
than	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
your	O
writing	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
does	O
he	O
write	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
Benjamin	O
,	O
Ba	O
,	O
or	O
Be	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
He	O
writes	O
it	O
Be	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
s	O
's	O
in	O
Nash	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
Only	O
one	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Williams	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
at	O
most	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
seen	O
Mr	O
Nash	O
write	O
before	O
Christmas	O
last	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
five	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
his	O
name	O
Benjamin	O
at	O
length	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Needham	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
letter	O
N	O
in	O
Nash	O
as	O
he	O
usually	O
writes	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
small	O
n	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
large	O
capital	O
N.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
knowing	O
myself	O
innocent	O
,	O
never	O
kept	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
wrote	O
that	O
note	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
was	O
bound	O
in	O
a	O
bond	O
of	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
he	O
wrote	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
deficiency	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
remainder	O
I	O
put	O
to	O
the	O
use	O
that	O
I	O
wanted	O
it	O
for	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
had	O
money	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
he	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Needham	O
.	O
Is	O
Nash	O
looked	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
good	O
circumstances	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
,	O
so	O
long	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
not	O
he	O
lately	O
married	O
his	O
mistress	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
were	O
his	O
circumstances	O
before	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
apprentice	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
always	O
paid	O
me	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
a	O
poor	O
fellow	O
?	O
Needham	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
reckon	O
him	O
so	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Williams	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
marry	O
his	O
mistress	O
?	O
Williams	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
months	O
ago	O
,	O
or	O
better	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Cockerham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Horsley-down	O
,	O
Southwark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Cockerham	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighter-man	O
,	O
and	O
dealer	O
in	O
coals	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
carry	O
on	O
a	O
large	O
trade	O
?	O
Cockerham	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
a	O
wharf	O
?	O
Cockerham	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
keep	O
lighters	O
and	O
barges	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
conversation	O
has	O
past	O
between	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
you	O
relating	O
to	O
this	O
affair	O
?	O
Cockerham	O
.	O
Mr	O
Nash	O
has	O
told	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
that	O
whenever	O
the	O
note	O
became	O
due	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
a	O
hair	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
relation	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Cockerham	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
my	O
brother	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
of	O
your	O
brother	O
shifting	O
his	O
lodgings	O
?	O
Cockerham	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
because	O
the	O
person	O
where	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
was	O
in	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
the	O
Poultry	O
Compter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
the	O
note	O
?	O
Cockerham	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
the	O
day	O
it	O
became	O
due	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
Mr	O
Nash	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Cockerham	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Cockerham	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
it	O
's	O
being	O
his	O
hand	O
or	O
not	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Cockerham	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
always	O
told	O
me	O
whenever	O
the	O
note	O
became	O
due	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
read	O
the	O
warrant	O
that	O
Mr	O
Nash	O
had	O
?	O
Cockerham	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
Cockerham	O
.	O
He	O
afterwards	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr	O
Braddock	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
would	O
execute	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
look	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
his	O
attorney	O
said	O
so	O
too	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
hearing	O
has	O
Mr-Nash	O
said	O
this	O
?	O
Cockerham	O
.	O
In	O
Mr	O
Foster	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
Mr	O
Franklin	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
master	O
cooper	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodge	O
?	O
Cockerham	O
.	O
He	O
lodg	O
'd	O
with	O
his	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
arrested	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
he	O
been	O
in	O
