TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
18th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
JANUARY	O
,	O
1759	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Thirty-second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
'S	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
II	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1759	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Second	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
GLYN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
M.	O
COOPER	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Globe	O
in	O
Pater-noster-Row	O
;	O
1759	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
RICHARD	B-pers
GLYN	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord-Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
:	O
The	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
PARKER	O
*	O
:	O
The	O
Hon	O
.	O
Mr	O
Justice	O
BATHURST	O
+	O
:	O
Sir	O
J.	O
EARDLEY	O
WILMOT	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
||	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Godwin	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Meller	I-pers
Joshua	B-pers
Alvey	I-pers
Walter	B-pers
West	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Prosit	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
John	B-pers
Chasson	I-pers
Humphry	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
William	B-pers
Stone	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Price	I-pers
Joshua	B-pers
Bayzand	I-pers
John	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
White	I-pers
Charles	B-pers
Covey	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
Benjamin	B-pers
Powles	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Adkins	I-pers
John	B-pers
Bosworth	I-pers
James	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
Silver	B-pers
Crispin	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Bishop	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
John	B-pers
Salkhill	I-pers
John	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
52	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
12	O
.	O
++	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Goldsmith	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
I	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
looking	O
on	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
drawer	O
of	O
gold-rings	O
before	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
weighed	O
one	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
and	O
walked	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
missed	O
one	O
.	O
My	O
servant	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
ring	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
new	O
plain	O
gold-ring	O
on	O
her	O
finger	O
;	O
she	O
return	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
by	O
mistake	O
;	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
Alderman	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
by	O
mistake	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Chapman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
plain	O
gold-ring	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
tried	O
two	O
on	O
her	O
finger	O
;	O
she	O
kept	O
one	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
other	O
to	O
weigh	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
weigh	O
'd	O
it	O
by	O
her	O
desire	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
price	O
was	O
7	O
s.	O
she	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
we	O
missed	O
one	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
her	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
my	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
soon	O
produced	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
mine	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
rings	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
on	O
my	O
finger	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
brass	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
gold	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
my	O
own	O
off	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
by	O
mistake	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
that	O
ring	O
on	O
my	O
finger	O
thinking	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Chapman	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
ever	O
a	O
ring	O
on	O
her	O
finger	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
?	O
Chapman	O
.	O
Yes	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
two	O
rings	O
on	O
her	O
finger	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
and	O
produced	O
after	O
we	O
detected	O
her	O
with	O
this	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
53	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
20	O
.	O
||	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Brook-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
David	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
us	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
night	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
when	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
evening	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
9	O
days	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
his	O
wages	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bring	O
him	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
hat	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
but	O
little	O
reply	O
,	O
but	O
look	O
'd	O
dejected	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
away	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
;	O
he	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
it	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
soon	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
:	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
possibly	O
have	O
it	O
again	O
:	O
but	O
his	O
sister	O
should	O
buy	O
me	O
another	O
.	O
He	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Folier	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
one	O
that	O
buys	O
old	O
cloaths	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Hambleton	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
spoon	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
after	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
Mr	O
Welch	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
there	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
He	O
was	O
:	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
spoon	O
produced	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
spoon	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
it	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
spoon	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Davis	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Hambleton	O
has	O
it	O
:	O
she	O
is	O
bound	O
over	O
to	O
appear	O
,	O
but	O
is	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
here	O
are	O
two	O
witnesses	O
which	O
heard	O
him	O
own	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Constable	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Davis	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
ever	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
King	O
of	O
Prussia	O
by	O
Brooks-market	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
he	O
said	O
Williams	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
described	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
;	O
upon	O
being	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
spoon	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
same	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
by	O
Mrs	O
Hambleton	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
brought	O
another	O
to	O
match	O
it	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Howton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
spoon	O
from	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
Constable	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Hambleton	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
she	O
spoon	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
54	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Ireland	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
linnen	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
three	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Rout	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
Oct.	O
27	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Rout	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Dukes-Court	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
St	I-place
Martin	I-place
's	I-place
lane	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
a	O
lodger	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
her	O
mistress	O
left	O
the	O
lodgings	O
about	O
seven	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
me	O
for	O
her	O
lodgings	O
.	O
I	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
staid	O
one	O
day	O
longer	O
than	O
her	O
mistress	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
mistress	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
up	O
?	O
Rout	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
?	O
Rout	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
prosecuted	O
myself	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
brought	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
stopt	O
her	O
,	O
had	O
she	O
known	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Mr	O
Trip	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
these	O
things	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
and	O
27th	O
of	O
October	O
last	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
own	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
my	O
mother	O
had	O
dealt	O
with	O
Mr	O
Trip	O
,	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
in	O
her	O
name	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
fetched	O
them	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
my	O
money	O
would	O
go	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
55	O
,	O
56	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
one	O
dimity	O
petticoat	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
towel	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
2	O
.	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Limehouse	B-place
,	O
am	O
a	O
Master	O
of	O
a	O
ship	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
on	O
fire	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Conner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Herbert	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
see	O
about	O
,	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
remains	O
of	O
what	O
were	O
scattered	O
about	O
;	O
one	O
Smith	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
things	O
carried	O
into	O
Herbert	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
Justice	O
Barry	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
sheet	O
and	O
a	O
towel	O
;	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
my	O
name	O
on	O
the	O
sheet	O
;	O
we	O
could	O
see	O
a	O
name	O
had	O
been	O
picked	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Mrs	O
Herbert	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
pawn	O
a	O
petticoat	O
in	O
Long-Lane	O
,	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Conner	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
with	O
that	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
Herbert	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
petticoat	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
finished	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
pretty	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
a	O
condition	O
capable	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
so	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
more	O
wearing	O
apparel	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
great	O
reason	O
to	O
believe	O
was	O
not	O
consumed	O
in	O
the	O
flames	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
value	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Walmsley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
Mr	O
Cotes	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
;	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
after	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
,	O
Herbert	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
House	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
fit	O
some	O
things	O
on	O
a	O
lady	O
at	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
work	O
where	O
the	O
fire	O
had	O
been	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
and	O
joyner	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
concerning	O
some	O
money	O
I	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
the	O
landlord	O
Herbert	O
was	O
gone	O
off	O
with	O
some	O
things	O
stolen	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
the	O
things	O
got	O
wet	O
(	O
for	O
it	O
rain	O
'd	O
)	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
ruin	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
a	O
constable	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
word	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
he	O
would	O
call	O
again	O
at	O
two	O
o'clock	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
petticoat	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
met	O
the	O
lady	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
drank	O
two	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
things	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Walmsley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
petticoat	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
saw	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Garside	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Rose-lane	O
;	O
that	O
night	O
the	O
fire	O
broke	O
out	O
I	O
saw	O
Patrick	B-pers
Conner	I-pers
betwixt	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
about	O
20	O
or	O
30	O
rood	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
the	O
fire	O
broke	O
out	O
between	O
seven	O
and	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Conner	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
Garside	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
knew	O
he	O
worked	O
at	O
Mr	O
Turner	O
's	O
factory	O
in	O
weaving	O
sail-cloth	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
white	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
say	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
with	O
him	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
was	O
the	O
place	O
you	O
met	O
him	O
at	O
from	O
Herbert	O
's	O
?	O
Garside	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
doors	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
Herbert	O
with	O
the	O
bundle	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
at	O
Walmsley	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
,	O
What	O
had	O
I	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
could	O
charge	O
him	O
with	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
bundle	O
not	O
to	O
drop	O
it	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Cam	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
search	O
Herbert	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
made	O
a	O
diligent	O
search	O
but	O
could	O
find	O
nothing	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
for	O
taking	O
the	O
woman	O
away	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
If	O
we	O
would	O
stay	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
shew	O
us	O
something	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
.	O
A	O
sheet	O
,	O
a	O
towel	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
wrappers	O
.	O
Producing	O
them	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
prisoner	O
in	O
France	O
lately	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
purchased	O
a	O
sheet	O
to	O
use	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
cartel	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
almost	O
sure	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
Cam	O
.	O
The	O
wife	O
of	O
Herbert	O
pointed	O
to	O
Conner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
bundles	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
Conner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
fellow-prisoner	O
brought	O
the	O
goods	O
from	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
he	O
and	O
other	O
people	O
picking	O
the	O
marks	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
ow	O
'd	O
him	O
six	O
shillings	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
acquit	O
me	O
of	O
the	O
debt	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
inform	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
purl	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
drank	O
it	O
the	O
people	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
brought	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
.	O
Herbert	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drawing	O
beer	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
this	O
other	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
'till	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
things	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
.	O
He	O
being	O
debtor	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
60	O
,	O
61	O
,	O
62	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
18	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Eldred	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
;	O
and	O
Martha	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Goff	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
goods	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
December	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
John	O
Eldred	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
hatter	O
and	O
hosier	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
my	O
shop	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
18	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
we	O
made	O
no	O
talk	O
of	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
boys	O
taken	O
in	O
robbing	O
a	O
cutler	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
named	O
Turnis	O
,	O
told	O
of	O
many	O
robberies	O
they	O
had	O
committed	O
,	O
amongst	O
them	O
was	O
this	O
of	O
robbing	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
was	O
at	O
Bury	O
in	O
Suffolk	O
;	O
my	O
servant	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
knows	O
about	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turnis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
eighteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
Haynes	O
and	O
Heath	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
were	O
going	O
by	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop-door	O
stood	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
stockings	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Turnis	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
Saturday	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
,	O
about	O
six	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
p	O
arcel	O
,	O
and	O
deliverd	O
them	O
to	O
William	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Heath	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
another	O
parcel	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
eighteen	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
in	O
all	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
out	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
name	O
?	O
Turnis	O
.	O
Her	O
name	O
is	O
Mary	B-pers
Potter	I-pers
,	O
there	O
we	O
divided	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
each	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
sold	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs	O
Goff	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
one	O
pair	O
on	O
my	O
legs	O
now	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
seen	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
since	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
five	O
pair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
they	O
worth	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
different	O
prices	O
:	O
the	O
lowest	O
cost	O
2	O
s	O
3	O
d.	O
John	B-pers
Blyth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr	O
Welch	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
evidence	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
these	O
stockings	O
in	O
Fee-lane	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
that	O
would	O
fit	O
me	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Mr	O
Welch	O
.	O
She	O
keeps	O
a	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
stockings	O
she	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
remember	O
she	O
ever	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
presently	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
down	O
five	O
pair	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
have	O
been	O
produced	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
when	O
she	O
delivered	O
them	O
?	O
Blyth	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
the	O
stockings	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
boys	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
their	O
defence	O
.	O
Goff	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
To	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
that	O
boy	O
(	O
meaning	O
Turnis	O
)	O
before	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
For	O
Heath	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Father	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Heath	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
where	O
he	O
has	O
liv	O
'd	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Heath	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
:	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Heath	O
about	O
II	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
He	O
bears	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
12	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
For	O
Goff	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Peacock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
perriwig-maker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
her	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
serjeant	O
in	O
the	O
guards	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
well	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Rumart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
almost	O
30	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Rumart	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
one	O
;	O
she	O
sells	O
old	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
has	O
she	O
been	O
in	O
that	O
way	O
?	O
Rumart	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
is	O
it	O
since	O
she	O
kept	O
a	O
publick-house	O
?	O
Rumart	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Her	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
recruiting	O
serjeant	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Isaac	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
almost	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
heard	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
from	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
now	O
keeps	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Fee-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
in	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
?	O
Isaac	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
She	O
sold	O
apples	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
woman	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Eclan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
known	O
her	O
since	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
thence	O
?	O
Eclan	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
woman	O
.	O
Giles	B-pers
Rideout	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
pains-taking	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
kept	O
a	O
publick-house	O
in	O
Christopher's-Alley	O
,	O
Morefields	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
in	O
Fee-lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
in	O
Ratcliff-highway	O
?	O
Rideout	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Leanora	O
Whiting	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Whiting	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
traded	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
credit	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
I	O
take	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
27	O
or	O
28	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
industrious	O
woman	O
as	O
ever	O
lived	O
upon	O
earth	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
that	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
dishonestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
let	O
them	O
come	O
into	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
Michael	B-pers
Bilson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
seven	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
for	O
an	O
industrious	O
woman	O
.	O
Haynes	O
and	O
Heath	O
guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
Goff	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
63	O
,	O
64	O
,	O
65	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
were	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
cloak	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
dimity	O
vest	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
bed-gown	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Jer	B-pers
Wardley	I-pers
:	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Wills	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Dec.	O
16	O
.	O
*	O
Jer	O
.	O
Wardley	O
.	O
I	O
buy	O
and	O
sell	O
these	O
sort	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
)	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
same	O
quantity	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Wills	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
seven-night	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
no	O
particular	O
marks	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
judgment	O
they	O
are	O
mine	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
Turnis	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
sold	O
the	O
cloak	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
produced	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Turnis	I-pers
.	O
Haynes	O
,	O
Heath	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
through	O
the	O
Alley	O
where	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
lives	O
;	O
we	O
lifted	O
up	O
his	O
sash	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
cardinal	O
or	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Heath	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
white	O
robe	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
that	O
to	O
Heath	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
linnen	O
gown	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Wills	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
the	O
cardinal	O
;	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
:	O
then	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
we	O
came	O
upon	O
.	O
When	O
went	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
but	O
2	O
s.	O
so	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
by	O
William	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
carried	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
back	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Should	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
cardinal	O
again	O
?	O
Turnis	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
know	O
the	O
children	O
's	O
things	O
;	O
a	O
child	O
had	O
worn	O
the	O
little	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
dirty	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
sell	O
the	O
woman	O
any	O
thing	O
before	O
?	O
Turnis	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
once	O
I	O
sold	O
her	O
a	O
little	O
colour	O
'd	O
handkerchief	O
for	O
a	O
groat	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
got	O
in	O
Newgate-street	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
cardinal	O
or	O
cloak	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
well	O
worth	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Will	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
cardinal	O
is	O
not	O
what	O
I	O
bought	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
that	O
evidence	O
Turnis	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Haynes	O
us	O
'd	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
for	O
bread	O
and	O
cheese	O
,	O
and	O
small-beer	O
;	O
he	O
once	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
an	O
old	O
cardinal	O
and	O
these	O
child	O
's	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
were	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
begg	O
'd	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
that	O
cardinal	O
to	O
a	O
poor	O
woman	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
to	O
wrap	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
piec	O
'd	O
and	O
patch	O
'd	O
.	O
Turnis	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
she	O
bought	O
the	O
cardinal	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
produced	O
them	O
all	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
by	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
constable	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
,	O
she	O
produced	O
them	O
directly	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pownell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
exceeding	O
industrious	O
woman	O
.	O
She	O
keeps	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
sells	O
greens	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
body	O
speak	O
amiss	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
live	O
?	O
Pownell	O
.	O
She	O
liv	O
'd	O
in	O
Great	O
Earl-street	O
by	O
the	O
Seven-dials	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
Captain	O
William	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
now	O
at	O
Hallifax	O
;	O
she	O
bears	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
guilty	O
of	O
buying	O
goods	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
66	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
bell-mettle	O
mortar	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
Francis	B-pers
Perryham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr	O
James	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
an	O
Apothecary	O
:	O
about	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
we	O
lost	O
a	O
bell-mettle	O
mortar	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
December	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Smith	O
:	O
a	O
person	O
offered	O
me	O
this	O
mortar	O
to	O
fall	O
;	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
him	O
'till	O
he	O
produced	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
Windmill-street	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
offer	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
mortar	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
I	O
kick	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
my	O
toe	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
kept	O
it	O
about	O
month	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
advertised	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
that	O
man	O
to	O
sell	O
it	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
67	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Casey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
glass-bottle	O
filled	O
with	O
mushrooms	O
;	O
two	O
glass-bottles	O
filled	O
with	O
onions	O
;	O
and	O
five	O
blacking	O
balls	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Kitchen	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
Michael	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr	O
Kitchen	O
,	O
an	O
Oyl-man	O
in	O
St	B-place
John's-street	I-place
;	O
we	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
window	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
January	O
.	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
A	O
boy	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
hid	O
in	O
Charterhouse-lane	O
;	O
Samuel	B-pers
Price	I-pers
own	O
'd	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Price	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
fifteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
last	O
St	O
Stephen	O
's	O
day	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
Tom	B-pers
Bates	I-pers
,	O
were	O
coming	O
by	O
this	O
oyl-shop	O
;	O
I	O
cut	O
the	O
two	O
bottle-strings	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
for	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
Dean	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
us	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
some	O
blacking	O
balls	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
touched	O
the	O
bottles	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
68	O
,	O
69	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Lawrence	I-pers
Dayland	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Crouch	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buttons	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Barnaby	B-pers
Foy	I-pers
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Dec.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Barnaby	B-pers
Foy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
my	O
work	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
was	O
crying	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
pair	O
of	O
buttons	O
;	O
the	O
staple	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
knocked	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
your	O
watch	O
and	O
buttons	O
?	O
Foy	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
off	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
it	O
used	O
to	O
hang	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
buttons	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Dayland	O
before	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
knowing	O
the	O
number	O
of	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
to	O
inquire	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
found	O
that	O
at	O
Mr	O
Murphy	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
Dayland	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
suspected	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
seen	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
stairs	O
where	O
we	O
lodge	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
Justice	O
of	O
Peace	O
,	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Crouch	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Mr	O
Murphy	O
.	O
Crouch	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
the	O
same	O
name	O
and	O
number	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
Dayland	O
brought	O
the	O
buttons	O
;	O
Crouch	O
was	O
angry	O
with	O
Dayland	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
watch	O
that	O
was	O
stole	O
;	O
Dayland	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
it	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
that	O
Crouch	O
was	O
innocent	O
?	O
Murphy	O
.	O
To	O
me	O
it	O
did	O
:	O
for	O
Dayland	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
answer	O
to	O
her	O
question	O
:	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
confess	O
'd	O
she	O
did	O
steal	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
watch	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Dayland	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
lent	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
unknown	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lend	O
Dayland	O
this	O
watch	O
?	O
Answer	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
.	O
Crouch	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Dayland	O
brought	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
get	O
it	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
that	O
gentleman	O
.	O
Dayland	O
guilty	O
.	O
Crouch	O
acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
70.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Broadhead	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
five	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
two	O
tin	O
canisters	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
wooden	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Paul	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
26	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
71	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Young	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Cayton	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Richard	B-pers
Pousam	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Spencer	O
,	O
since	O
executed	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bulger	I-pers
,	O
unknown	O
to	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
Alley	O
and	O
open	O
place	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
high-way	O
,	O
on	O
Edward	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
50	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
three-pence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
July	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Hart	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
Mary	B-pers
Bulger	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
inquired	O
my	O
way	O
for	O
St	O
John's-street	O
;	O
they	O
directed	O
me	O
down	O
a	O
place	O
,	O
called	O
Thatch'd-alley	B-place
;	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
down	O
the	O
Alley	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
only	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
old	O
houses	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
my	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
turn	O
back	O
;	O
coming	O
back	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Bulger	I-pers
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
Bulger	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
beat	O
my	O
pockets	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
home	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
clear	O
my	O
way	O
;	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
and	O
d	O
-	O
d	O
my	O
eyes	O
and	O
limbs	O
;	O
I	O
struck	O
Mary	O
Bulger	O
and	O
made	O
her	O
reel	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
squeal	O
;	O
then	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
Spencer	O
,	O
since	O
executed	O
,	O
was	O
one	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
whores	O
and	O
rogues	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
here	O
;	O
Bulger	O
said	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
to	O
you	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
when	O
Spencer	O
struck	O
you	O
?	O
E.	O
Hart	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
about	O
six	O
yards	O
from	O
me	O
:	O
he	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
so	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
my	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Bulger	I-pers
came	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
Bulger	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
you	O
had	O
she	O
hold	O
on	O
?	O
E.	O
Hart	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
E.	O
Hart	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
this	O
minute	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
side	O
of	O
you	O
stood	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
E.	O
Hart	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
side	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
hold	O
you	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
prevent	O
your	O
giving	O
yourself	O
any	O
assistance	O
?	O
E.	O
Hart	O
.	O
She	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
together	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
knew	O
that	O
Bulger	O
was	O
taking	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
E.	O
Hart	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
said	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taking	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
cried	O
murder	O
once	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
cry	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
Spencer	O
clapp	O
'd	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
mouth	O
and	O
prevented	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
'till	O
after	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
cried	O
murder	O
?	O
E.	O
Hart	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
:	O
they	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
when	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
came	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
an	O
evidence	O
here	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
made	O
off	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
me	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
gore	O
blood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
persons	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
lost	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
E.	O
Hart	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
:	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
she	O
dressed	O
?	O
E.	O
Hart	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
brown	O
camblet	O
gown	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
good	O
hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
E.	O
Hart	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
duskish	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
see	O
them	O
by	O
the	O
light	O
of	O
a	O
lamp	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
with	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
pease	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
B	O
-	O
st	O
your	O
eyes	O
!	O
D	O
-	O
n	O
your	O
eyes	O
!	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
so	O
long	O
?	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Bulger	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
alley	O
where	O
the	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
at	O
your	O
first	O
seeing	O
her	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
round	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
some	O
old	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
Bulger	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
were	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
wall	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Bulger	O
make	O
her	O
any	O
answer	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
Bulger	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
Blast	O
my	O
eyes	O
!	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
doing	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
a	O
comical	O
c	O
-	O
k	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
not	O
let	O
me	O
feel	O
;	O
then	O
Dick	O
Spencer	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
down	O
directly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
?	O
Hawkins	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
there	O
;	O
just	O
as	O
Bulger	O
spoke	O
the	O
words	O
,	O
Dick	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
came	O
up	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
the	O
man	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
glad	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
light	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
thro	O
'	O
the	O
ruinated	O
alley	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
with	O
his	O
mouth	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
much	O
swelled	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
charge	O
me	O
with	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Hawkins	O
says	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
none	O
but	O
you	O
and	O
Bulger	O
together	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
along	O
that	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
Bulger	O
were	O
coming	O
one	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
the	O
alley	O
is	O
not	O
wide	O
enough	O
for	O
two	O
to	O
go	O
a-brest	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
going	O
back	O
again	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
that	O
alley	O
:	O
last	O
sessions	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Queen's-head	O
cellar	O
here	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Hawkins	O
:	O
I	O
knowing	O
her	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
Good	O
woman	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
drink	O
?	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
two	O
full	O
pots	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
troubled	O
myself	O
with	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
Thief-catchers	O
followed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
prosecute	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
troubled	O
myself	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
now	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
catch	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
get	O
your	O
living	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
go	O
a	O
cindering	O
for	O
my	O
bread	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
what	O
is	O
her	O
business	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Thatch'd-alley	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
hurt	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
high	O
the	O
man	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
upon	O
the	O
accout	O
of	O
the	O
Thief-catchers	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
Sessions-paper	O
read	O
,	O
Hawkins	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
neither	O
man	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
nor	O
child	O
,	O
was	O
near	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
Bulger	O
and	O
Spencer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
Mary	O
Hawkins	O
?	O
what	O
is	O
her	O
character	O
?	O
Harris	O
.	O
Her	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
coal-heaver	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
had	O
many	O
wives	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
as	O
many	O
husbands	O
(	O
as	O
they	O
call	O
them	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
her	O
character	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
lived	O
by	O
me	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
ill	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Clark	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
gets	O
her	O
living	O
by	O
buying	O
and	O
selling	O
of	O
old	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
summing	O
up	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Hawkins	I-pers
,	O
observed	O
,	O
wherein	O
they	O
agreed	O
and	O
disagreed	O
with	O
the	O
accounts	O
they	O
gave	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
Spencer	O
and	O
Bulger	O
,	O
by	O
referring	O
to	O
his	O
minutes	O
taken	O
on	O
that	O
tryal	O
*	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
294.	O
in	O
Sir	O
Charles	B-pers
Asgill	I-pers
's	O
Mayoralty	O
.	O
72.	O
Sibilla	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Cawhow	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
linnen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
two	O
linnen	O
petticoats	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
four	O
linnen	O
shifts	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
pockets	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
73.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
leaden	O
pump	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Swanson	I-pers
,	O
Gent	O
.	O
May	O
1	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
appeared	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
74.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Meridith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
unlawfuly	O
,	O
knowingly	O
,	O
and	O
designedly	O
,	O
did	O
obtain	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Strudwick	I-pers
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
;	O
and	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Stebs	I-pers
,	O
one	O
other	O
shilling	O
;	O
and	O
from	O
other	O
people	O
,	O
several	O
sums	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
by	O
false	O
pretences	O
.	O
No	O
evidence	O
appeared	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
75	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Pindar	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
dressing-glasses	O
,	O
value	O
25	O
s.	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
pan	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dobyns	I-pers
,	O
January	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dobyns	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
Upholsterer	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
George-street	B-place
,	I-place
near	I-place
Hanover-square	I-place
;	O
I	O
employed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
as	O
a	O
chair-woman	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
she	O
worked	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
set	O
one	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
catched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
concealed	O
between	O
her	O
legs	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
book-keeper	O
to	O
Mr	O
Dobyns	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
suspicion	O
of	O
some	O
persons	O
stealing	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
house	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr	O
Knight	O
to	O
be	O
air	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
goods	O
carried	O
in	O
:	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
air	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
something	O
stick	O
out	O
under	O
her	O
cloaths	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
looking-glass	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
we	O
had	O
miss	O
'd	O
several	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Mackenzie	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Oxford-road	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
three	O
looking-glasses	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
a	O
baking	O
pan	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
76	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Hannah	B-pers
Willers	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Gaston	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Gaston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Smith	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
where	O
were	O
three	O
beds	O
;	O
a	O
soldier	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
lay	O
in	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
another	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
robb	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday-night	O
;	O
then	O
only	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
in	O
her	O
bed	O
and	O
I	O
in	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Gaston	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Gaston	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
watch	O
with	O
a	O
black	O
shagreen	O
case	O
;	O
these	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
laid	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
breeches	O
and	O
all	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
for	O
charging	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
?	O
Gaston	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
she	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
peace	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
denied	O
having	O
taken	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
awake	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
?	O
Gaston	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
awake	O
at	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
the	O
watch	O
going	O
under	O
my	O
head	O
;	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
soldier	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
were	O
not	O
come	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
fell	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
slept	O
'till	O
near	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
ever	O
met	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Gaston	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
Gaston	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
dispose	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
?	O
Gaston	O
.	O
Her	O
husband	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
calls	O
him	O
,	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea-prison	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
person	O
that	O
lives	O
near	O
More-fields	O
,	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
or	O
another	O
man	O
from	O
the	O
Marshalsea-prison	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
that	O
man	O
that	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Gaston	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
also	O
my	O
breeches	O
return	O
'd	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Marshalsea-prison	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
room	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
lock	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
lodging-house	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
people	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
falsely	O
accused	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
77	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Maginnis	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Samuel	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Bride-lane	B-place
,	O
at	O
Mr	O
Weldey	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
bed-room	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
my	O
bed-fellow	O
;	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
Mr	O
Browne	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
;	O
where	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
design	O
to	O
bring	O
me	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
leave	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Frank	B-pers
Rochford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr	O
Browne	O
,	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
on	O
Snow-hill	O
.	O
He	O
produced	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
.	O
These	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
with	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Maginnis	I-pers
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
buckles	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
to	O
them	O
:	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
particular	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
pattern	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
you	O
had	O
your	O
's	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
acknowledge	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
buckles	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
took	O
my	O
buckles	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
there	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Rochford	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
?	O
Rochford	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
in	O
:	O
but	O
he	O
came	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
having	O
had	O
three	O
shillings	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
he	O
wanted	O
two	O
shillings	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
let	O
him	O
have	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Ca	O
n't	O
you	O
recollect	O
the	O
man	O
again	O
by	O
seeing	O
him	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Rochford	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
so	O
long	O
ago	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
:	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Here	O
are	O
some	O
gentlemen	O
that	O
will	O
give	O
me	O
a	O
character	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Tyre	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
work	O
'd	O
where	O
he	O
did	O
very	O
near	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Tyre	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
upright	O
,	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
also	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
person	O
that	O
brought	O
him	O
into	O
company	O
in	O
drinking	O
,	O
he	O
served	O
his	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Cabinet-maker	O
,	O
so	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
work	O
'd	O
and	O
lay	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Waters	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
'till	O
this	O
affair	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
civil	O
well-behav	O
'd	O
young	O
man	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
buckles	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
why	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
sooner	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
because	O
he	O
promised	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
78	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Dutton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
30	O
.	O
||	O
Joseph	B-pers
Beck	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
master	O
of	O
the	O
Work-house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
poor	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
two	O
hundred	O
shirts	O
in	O
the	O
committee-room	O
,	O
that	O
we	O
make	O
for	O
the	O
army	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
Beck	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
shirts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Beck	O
.	O
She	O
own	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
Pawn-broker	O
in	O
Golden-lane	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Red-Lion-Market	O
,	O
White-Cross-street	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
;	O
there	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
Alderman	O
;	O
there	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
we	O
have	O
threepence	O
a	O
piece	O
for	O
making	O
the	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Church-Warden	O
allows	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
makes	O
them	O
a	O
penny	O
for	O
each	O
shirt	O
.	O
Amy	B-pers
Holeman	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
going	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
(	O
we	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
daily	O
labour	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Work-house	O
to	O
lie	O
)	O
she	O
went	O
back	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
committee-room	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
what	O
business	O
have	O
you	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
it	O
out	O
when	O
she	O
got	O
on	O
the	O
out	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
gate	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
shirt	O
;	O
the	O
shirt	O
produced	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
shirt	O
?	O
Amy	B-pers
Holeman	I-pers
.	O
(	O
She	O
takes	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
)	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
letter	O
S	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
which	O
Mr	O
Beck	O
put	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
pointing	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
put	O
that	O
letter	O
on	O
it	O
?	O
Amy	B-pers
Holeman	I-pers
.	O
When	O
he	O
fetched	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
own	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
before	O
Mr	O
Beck	O
went	O
for	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
That	O
witness	O
saw	O
me	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Pawn-broker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
79	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Garland	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
pounds	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Leake	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
3	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Leake	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Robert	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Butcher	O
;	O
we	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
the	B-place
New-Market	I-place
.	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
opposite	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
throw	O
her	O
cloak	O
over	O
something	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Mary	B-pers
Leake	I-pers
.	O
This	O
was	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
the	O
meat	O
fall	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
her	O
stoop	O
for	O
it	O
and	O
take	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
thin-flank	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
80	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Drudge	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
high	O
way	O
,	O
on	O
Ann	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
her	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
her	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
her	O
person	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
her	O
said	O
husband	O
,	O
Dec.	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Thomas	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Oxford	O
Road	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
met	O
me	O
and	O
knock	O
'd	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
first	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
No	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
knock	O
you	O
down	O
with	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
With	O
his	O
fist	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
you	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
No	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
stunned	O
with	O
the	O
blow	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
before	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
light	O
or	O
dark	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
dark	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
Because	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
really	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
a	O
lamp	O
near	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
No	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
cloaths	O
had	O
he	O
on	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
The	O
same	O
as	O
now	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
his	O
regimentals	O
)	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
him	O
before	O
on	O
that	O
day	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
it	O
was	O
dark	O
,	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
There	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
faces	O
one	O
like	O
another	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
He	O
said	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
find	O
your	O
pocket	O
since	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
No	O
:	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
any	O
time	O
own	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
your	O
things	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
No	O
:	O
Q	O
.	O
By	O
what	O
can	O
you	O
tell	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
people	O
with	O
red	O
cloaths	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
So	O
there	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
speak	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
No	O
:	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
open	O
his	O
mouth	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
a	O
hat	O
on	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
He	O
had	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
laced	O
hat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
cock	O
'd	O
or	O
flapp	O
'd	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
Because	O
I	O
really	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
him	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
a	O
publick-house	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
knew	O
you	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
did	O
or	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dark	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
81	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Ascue	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
16	O
yards	O
of	O
shalloon	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Dec.	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Cloth-fair	B-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
business	O
?	O
Thorn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
trimming	O
seller	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
betwixt	O
four	O
and	O
five	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
fact	O
done	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pile	O
of	O
shalloons	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
piece	O
that	O
was	O
lost	O
was	O
the	O
uppermost	O
piece	O
of	O
sixteen	O
yards	O
.	O
John	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
servent	O
to	O
Mr	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Mercer	O
,	O
opposite	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr	O
Thorn	O
's	O
shop	O
with	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
shalloon	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
dropp	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
:	O
which	O
I	O
suppose	O
was	O
by	O
pulling	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
her	O
too	O
hastily	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
this	O
piece	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
dirt	O
on	O
the	O
paper	O
it	O
is	O
wrapped	O
in	O
:	O
and	O
also	O
by	O
dirt	O
on	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
piece	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
directly	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
Mr	O
Thorn	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
her	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
shalloon	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
informed	O
him	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
;	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
into	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
he	O
overtook	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
turned	O
about	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
it	O
again	O
behind	O
her	O
;	O
Mr	O
Thorn	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
confused	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Is	O
this	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
piece	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
woman	O
there	O
buying	O
of	O
buttons	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
dropp	O
'd	O
the	O
piece	O
and	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
another	O
woman	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
none	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
serving	O
a	O
boy	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Green	O
.	O
Did	O
another	O
woman	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
speaks	O
of	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
another	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
but	O
a	O
fortnight	O
in	O
this	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
82	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Laws	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
26	O
.	O
||	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Grub-street	B-place
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Victualler	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
about	O
eleven	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
much	O
above	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
maid	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
woman	O
's	O
shoe	O
in	O
the	O
Club-room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
missed	O
a	O
sheet	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
her	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
shoe	O
and	O
say	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
see	O
about	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
;	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
thought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
customer	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
she	O
?	O
Martin	O
.	O
Her	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
for	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
at	O
her	O
foot	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
and	O
saw	O
she	O
had	O
one	O
shoe	O
with	O
a	O
string	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
a	O
buckle	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
can	O
match	O
the	O
shoe	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
buckle	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
buckle	O
in	O
the	O
shoe	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
Club-room	O
,	O
matched	O
the	O
buckle	O
she	O
had	O
on	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
sho	O
es	O
matched	O
also	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
;	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
not	O
money	O
enough	O
to	O
fetch	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
I	O
kept	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
kitchen	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
her	O
husband	O
and	O
sister	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
very	O
sorry	O
this	O
should	O
happen	O
;	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
shilling	O
towards	O
fetching	O
the	O
sheet	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
them	O
no	O
promise	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
fetch	O
it	O
again	O
they	O
might	O
;	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
never	O
knew	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
she	O
sent	O
another	O
woman	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
her	O
husband	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
sheet	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
down	O
our	O
stairs	O
that	O
night	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
use	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
use	O
to	O
visit	O
any	O
people	O
above	O
stairs	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Martin	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
my	O
maid	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
sheet	O
taken	O
from	O
off	O
her	O
bed	O
;	O
the	O
night	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
up	O
stairs	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
a	O
shoe	O
behind	O
her	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
and	O
found	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
two	O
odd	O
shoes	O
on	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
and	O
the	O
buckle	O
,	O
were	O
fellows	O
to	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
buckle	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
our	O
Club-room	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
sheet	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
where	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
an	O
aunt	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
sheet	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Martin	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
sheet	O
that	O
was	O
brought	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
husband	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
no	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Swanston	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
kitchen	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
sheet	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
aunt	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
also	O
by	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
and	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
the	O
same	O
there	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
83	O
,	O
84	O
,	O
85	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Hailey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Lucy	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
James	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
lawn	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
2	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Martha	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
January	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Martha	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
;	O
I	O
begg	O
'd	O
leave	O
of	O
my	O
mistress	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
things	O
that	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
wear	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
a	O
lawn	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
shop	O
looking	O
at	O
some	O
flannel	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
look	O
at	O
it	O
with	O
that	O
bundle	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
afford	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
price	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
flannel	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
bundle	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
cry	O
'd	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
uneasy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
At	O
a	O
shop	B-place
in	I-place
Cranbourn-alley	I-place
;	O
soon	O
after	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
these	O
three	O
children	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
one	O
Mr	O
Dod	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
up	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
them	O
?	O
Cooper	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Hull	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
brought	O
and	O
pledg	O
'd	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
one	O
.	O
)	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
that	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
produced	O
another	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
,	O
I	O
really	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
a	O
girl	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
another	O
girl	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
where	O
all	O
produced	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
bundle	O
from	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
out	O
to	O
Holland	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
sent	O
him	O
in	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
girls	O
own	O
that	O
they	O
divided	O
the	O
money	O
they	O
made	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
amongst	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
the	O
stockings	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
Kelly	O
's	O
lodging	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Kelly	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
gave	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
and	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
kept	O
the	O
stockings	O
;	O
his	O
mother	O
says	O
he	O
is	O
ten	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Holland	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
This	O
boy	O
(	O
meaning	O
Willis	O
)	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
Poll	O
Taylor	O
to	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
would	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
pretty	O
ribbon	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
but	O
that	O
.	O
Willis	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Kelly	O
and	O
Holland	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
86	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
December	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
My	O
wife	O
let	O
a	O
room	O
ready	O
furnished	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
as	O
a	O
single	O
woman	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
your	O
wife	O
?	O
Murray	O
.	O
She	O
lyes-in	O
,	O
and	O
ca	O
n't	O
attend	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
present	O
when	O
your	O
wife	O
let	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Murray	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
'd	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
feather-bed	O
,	O
blanket	O
,	O
and	O
sheet	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
and	O
mention	O
'd	O
where	O
the	O
Justice	O
might	O
send	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
house	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
blanket	O
were	O
brought	O
;	O
she	O
own	O
'd	O
they	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
furniture	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
here	O
?	O
Murray	O
.	O
No	O
:	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
sheet	O
?	O
Murray	O
.	O
The	O
pawnbroker	O
has	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Murray	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
his	O
Herring	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Herring	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
wife	O
owned	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
for	O
her	O
after	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
husband	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
sheet	O
were	O
produced	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
landlady	O
for	O
rent	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
their	O
places	O
again	O
when	O
her	O
money	O
came	O
up	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
hearing	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
the	O
Justice	O
's	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
speaks	O
off	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
I	O
expected	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
up	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
take	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
turned	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
not	O
bring	O
the	O
Pawnbroker	O
's	O
wife	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
at	O
Hicks's-hall	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
trial	O
here	O
today	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
here	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
87	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Greenhow	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
thread	O
stocking	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Anne	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
thread	O
stocking	O
.	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
Jan.	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Anne	B-pers
Sophia	I-pers
Carter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
where	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
tell	O
that	O
?	O
who	O
was	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Cartr	O
.	O
My	O
cousin	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
asleep	O
likewise	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
tell	O
who	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
you	O
was	O
asleep	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
awake	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
the	O
boy	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
no	O
occasion	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
two	O
people	O
that	O
were	O
asleep	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
could	O
give	O
a	O
better	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
one	O
that	O
was	O
awake	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
for	O
that	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
the	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
afterwards	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
for	O
himself	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
keep	O
them	O
.	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Holding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
our	O
back-door	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
two	O
months	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
lodge	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Holding	O
.	O
We	O
live	O
at	O
Hendon	B-place
;	O
there	O
was	O
Farmer	O
Sanders	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Dowglas	I-pers
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
home	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
;	O
Dowglas	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
mistrust	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
asleep	O
or	O
awake	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Holding	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Holding	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
had	O
from	O
our	O
boy	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Who	O
has	O
play	O
'd	O
the	O
rogue	O
with	O
the	O
buckles	O
?	O
the	O
boy	O
said	O
,	O
Samuel	O
has	O
taken	O
the	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
Mistress	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Samuel	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
going	O
to	O
steal	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
you	O
and	O
your	O
mistress	O
drunk	O
or	O
sober	O
?	O
Holding	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
all	O
very	O
sober	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
both	O
to	O
fall	O
asleep	O
?	O
Holding	O
.	O
We	O
fell	O
asleep	O
being	O
tired	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
My	O
landlady	O
took	O
the	O
liberty	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Carter	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
take	O
that	O
liberty	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Carter	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
he	O
laugh	O
,	O
and	O
say	O
afterwards	O
,	O
it	O
way	O
only	O
a	O
joke	O
.	O
Carter	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
88	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Anne	B-pers
Gyles	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Friday	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
ten	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
and	O
money	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Banford	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
Dec.	O
4	O
.	O
*	O
Sarah	O
Banford	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
to	O
toast	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bacon	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
knife	O
like	O
a	O
pen-knife	O
;	O
she	O
got	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
as	O
I	O
sat	O
by	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
Half-guineas	O
,	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
half	O
her	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
I	O
presently	O
ran	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
catch	O
'd	O
her	O
'till	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
,	O
in	O
St	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
perceive	O
her	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Banford	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
doing	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
her	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
for	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
;	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
the	O
money	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
confess	O
the	O
rings	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
confessed	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
the	O
rings	O
were	O
?	O
Banford	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Western	I-pers
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
rings	O
and	O
shew	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
money	O
you	O
had	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Banford	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
distiller	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
but	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Western	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Western	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
December	O
.	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
lend	O
her	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
Western	O
.	O
I	O
lent	O
her	O
a	O
guinea	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
these	O
rings	O
?	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
lost	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
into	O
Staffordshire	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
to	O
carry	O
her	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
89	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Hopgood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
black	O
gelding	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Page	I-pers
,	O
Nov.	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
Richard	B-pers
Page	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Harrow	B-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
stable	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
November	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
lock	O
'd	O
?	O
Page	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
only	O
shut	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
night-time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
found	O
him	O
since	O
?	O
Page	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
horse	O
?	O
Page	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
do	O
you	O
charge	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Page	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
seen	O
with	O
such	O
a	O
horse	O
in	O
the	O
Broad-way	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Cuttle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Farrier	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
two	O
horses	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
break	O
of	O
day	O
,	O
one	O
them	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
shoe	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
one	O
on	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
dock	O
a	O
black	O
gelding	O
:	O
he	O
staid	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
'till	O
three	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Cuttle	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Westminster	O
;	O
after	O
this	O
,	O
Mr	O
Page	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
horse	O
?	O
and	O
according	O
to	O
his	O
description	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
horse	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
.	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
Mr	O
Cuttle	O
's	O
yard	O
with	O
two	O
horses	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
black	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
grey	O
one	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
one	O
to	O
be	O
dock	O
'd	O
;	O
he	O
staid	O
'till	O
three	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
nor	O
the	O
horses	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
?	O
Bullock	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
about	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Seymour	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr	O
Cuttle	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
speak	O
of	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
nor	O
horses	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
90	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Cornew	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
47	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
honey	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Dec.	O
16	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Holman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
Grocer	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
December	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
honey	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
it	O
weighed	O
47	O
pounds	O
4	O
ounces	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
soon	O
after	O
;	O
a	O
child	O
told	O
me	O
some	O
men	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
pursuit	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
Aldersgate-bars	O
;	O
a	O
young	O
gentleman	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Charter-house-square	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
;	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
square	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
two	O
men	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
my	O
pot	O
of	O
honey	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
come	O
to	O
them	O
they	O
shifted	O
it	O
from	O
one	O
to	O
another	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
throw	O
'd	O
the	O
pot	O
of	O
honey	O
on	O
my	O
arm	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
by	O
my	O
preventing	O
it	O
from	O
falling	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
least	O
it	O
should	O
break	O
,	O
it	O
prevented	O
me	O
from	O
securing	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
and	O
us	O
'd	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
overcame	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
him	O
pretty	O
well	O
;	O
the	O
porter	O
of	O
the	O
Charter-house	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
feasible	O
to	O
think	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
take	O
the	O
honey	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
buckle	O
my	O
shoe	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
carry	O
a	O
coat	O
to	O
the	O
scowerer	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
after	O
that	O
into	O
the	O
Square	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
a	O
shipmate	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
occasions	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
down	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
absolutely	O
befoul	O
'd	O
myself	O
in	O
abundance	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
the	O
honey	O
,	O
than	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
sacred	O
God	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
employ	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
Shoemaker	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
recommended	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
master	O
that	O
had	O
employed	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
91	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Green	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
shilling	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jos	B-pers
.	I-pers
Sanderson	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Jos	O
.	O
Sanderson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Bell	I-place
in	I-place
Poppin's-alley	I-place
,	I-place
Fleet-Street	I-place
;	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
before	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
bureau	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
having	O
another	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
money	O
every	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
once	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
In	O
about	O
a	O
week	O
after	O
my	O
key	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
I	O
also	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
shilling	O
a	O
day	O
several	O
days	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
having	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
marked	O
15	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
access	O
to	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
bureau	O
stood	O
?	O
Sanderson	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
beside	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
that	O
day	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
bed	O
as	O
usual	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
examin	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
having	O
taken	O
any	O
.	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
searching	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
her	O
things	O
from	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
presently	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
my	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
came	O
out	O
my	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
mark	O
upon	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
the	O
bureau	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
shilling	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
shilling	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
shilling	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Mr	O
Alderman	O
Gosling	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
use	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Deborah	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
prosecuter	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
the	O
maid	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
pull	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
which	O
were	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
out	O
some	O
small	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
pull	O
out	O
the	O
key	O
or	O
shilling	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
mistress	O
desired	O
the	O
pocket	O
might	O
be	O
turned	O
inside	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
key	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
constable	O
was	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
comes	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
she	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
master	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
charged	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
key	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
where	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
shilling	O
from	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
begg	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
forgiven	O
;	O
the	O
mistress	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
forgive	O
her	O
no	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
law	O
would	O
go	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
never	O
took	O
any	O
money	O
before	O
that	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
fetch	O
down	O
the	O
money	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
marked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
shilling	O
was	O
marked	O
as	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
the	O
shilling	O
to	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
here	O
yesterday	O
,	O
but	O
whether	O
by	O
pulling	O
out	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
or	O
by	O
what	O
accident	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
the	O
shilling	O
;	O
the	O
Grand	O
Jury	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
other	O
money	O
which	O
I	O
marked	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
that	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
shilling	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
sent	O
down	O
to	O
mistress	O
by	O
her	O
k	O
inswoman	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
key	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
under	O
the	O
bureau	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
same	O
beer	O
to	O
the	O
Fleet	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
directly	O
took	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
key	O
belonging	O
to	O
you	O
;	O
I	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
this	O
key	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
This	O
I	O
picked	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
sent	O
me	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
beer	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
it	O
him	O
directly	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
Counter	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Lee	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
shilling	O
under	O
the	O
bureau	O
?	O
Lee	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
above	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
away	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
readily	O
say	O
upon	O
your	O
charging	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
key	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
pull	O
out	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
from	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
she	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
two	O
sixpences	O
,	O
a	O
half-penny	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
farthings	O
.	O
She	O
utterly	O
denied	O
taking	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
key	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
but	O
her	O
own	O
key	O
and	O
her	O
own	O
money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
92	O
,	O
93	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Falkner	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Fielder	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
unlawfully	O
aiding	O
Abraham	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
committed	O
to	O
Wood-street	O
Counter	O
,	O
on	O
suspicion	O
of	O
felony	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
from	O
the	O
said	O
Counter	O
,	O
November	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Crompton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
Falkner	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
prison	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
about	O
ten	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
my	O
man	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
prisoner	O
escaped	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
tell	O
who	O
assisted	O
?	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
up	O
in	O
Falkner	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Falkner	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
at	O
first	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
cloaths	O
were	O
deposited	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
escaped	O
was	O
shaved	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
knew	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
he	O
would	O
escape	O
,	O
or	O
at	O
least	O
,	O
attempt	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
that	O
escaped	O
?	O
Crompton	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
was	O
Abraham	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
reason	O
why	O
he	O
knew	O
he	O
would	O
attempt	O
to	O
escape	O
?	O
Crompton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
cruel	O
as	O
not	O
to	O
discover	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
knew	O
I	O
