TOKEN	NE
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissioners	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
,	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
9th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
10th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
11th	O
,	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
In	O
the	O
Thirty-third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1760	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
SESSIONS	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
CHITTY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
by	O
G.	O
KEARSLY	O
(	O
Successor	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
)	O
at	O
the	O
Golden-Lion	O
,	O
in	O
Ludgate-Street	O
,	O
1760	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Four-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commissions	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
and	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
General	O
Sessions	B-pers
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
at	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
Old-Bailey	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
Sir	O
THOMAS	B-pers
CHITTY	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
PARKER	O
,	O
*	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
BATHURST	O
,	O
+	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
WILMOT	O
,	O
||	O
Sir	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
MORETON	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
++	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
His	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
Characters	O
*	O
+	O
||	O
++	O
direct	O
to	O
the	O
Judge	O
by	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
;	O
also	O
(	O
L.	O
and	O
M.	O
)	O
by	O
what	O
Jury	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
Henry	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
Robert	B-pers
Garrard	I-pers
Caleb	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
James	B-pers
Jervis	I-pers
William	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
Edward	B-pers
Mottley	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Beard	I-pers
Joseph	B-pers
Tenniswood	I-pers
Samuel	B-pers
Bignall	I-pers
Anthony	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
William	B-pers
Boozeher	I-pers
John	B-pers
Manvell	I-pers
Francis	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Gaff	I-pers
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
George	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
Richard	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
Thomas	B-pers
Burt	I-pers
James	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
James	B-pers
Sherridine	I-pers
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
210	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Carroll	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
pint	O
mugg	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Dennis	B-pers
Commins	I-pers
,	O
June	O
15	O
.	O
||	O
Mrs.	O
Commins	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Dennis	B-pers
Commins	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
King	I-place
's	I-place
head	I-place
,	I-place
the	I-place
corner	I-place
of	I-place
Prince	I-place
's	I-place
street	I-place
,	I-place
Drury	I-place
lane	I-place
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
your	O
servant	O
?	O
Commins	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
chairwoman	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
chairwoman	O
at	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Commins	O
.	O
Not	O
above	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lived	O
there	O
3	O
months	O
or	O
better	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
mugg	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
last	O
?	O
Commins	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Wailey	I-pers
,	O
my	O
maid	O
,	O
to	O
wash	O
it	O
with	O
others	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
me	O
5	O
silver	O
tankards	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
2	O
muggs	O
behind	O
,	O
presently	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
muggs	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
in	O
your	O
house	O
?	O
Commins	O
.	O
She	O
lay	O
with	O
the	O
maid	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
20	O
minutes	O
after	O
:	O
I	O
accused	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
a	O
private	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
;	O
a	O
gentleman	O
named	O
Turner	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
our	O
other	O
house	O
(	O
we	O
kept	O
two	O
houses	O
)	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
the	O
mugg	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Crown	O
and	O
Cusheon	O
,	O
Russel	O
street	O
,	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
(	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
)	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
sometimes	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
at	O
near	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
paid	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
leave	O
this	O
silver	O
mugg	O
with	O
me	O
(	O
producing	O
one	O
)	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
no	O
questions	O
,	O
haveing	O
no	O
body	O
at	O
home	O
but	O
myself	O
to	O
attend	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
busy	O
with	O
my	O
customers	O
.	O
She	O
not	O
coming	O
again	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
proposed	O
,	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
name	O
Matthews	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Angel	O
and	O
Crown	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Commins	O
's	O
former	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
immediately	O
to	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Commins	O
came	O
and	O
own	O
'd	O
the	O
mugg	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
their	O
other	O
house	O
near	O
Drury	O
lane	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Commins	O
had	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
the	O
Roundhouse	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
the	O
servant	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
?	O
Turn	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
say	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
servant	O
maid	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
words	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
particular	O
notice	O
of	O
,	O
being	O
busy	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
soon	O
call	O
again	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
maid	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
her	O
Mistress	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
had	O
a	O
dispute	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
even	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
got	O
a	O
large	O
glass	O
of	O
Brandy	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
washing	O
the	O
pots	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
shelling	O
of	O
pease	O
;	O
she	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
.	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
this	O
pint	O
mugg	O
,	O
and	O
carry	O
it	O
abroad	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
call	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Turner	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
211	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Bridget	B-pers
Callahan	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
blond	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
necklace	O
of	O
French	O
beads	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
d.	O
one	O
muslin	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
gown	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
2	O
silk	O
gown	O
linings	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linnen	O
shift	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Parnell	I-pers
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
||	O
Ann	B-pers
Parnell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
am	O
a	O
milliner	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
a	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
A.	O
Parnell	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
Michaelmas	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
first	O
?	O
A.	O
Parnell	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
January	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
another	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
mistress	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
A.	O
Parnell	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
A.	O
Parnell	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
212	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Elias	I-pers
Flanders	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
ounces	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Pattersgale	I-pers
,	O
June	O
7	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Norbury	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Hoxton	O
Market	O
place	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
for	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Pattersgale	I-pers
;	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Friday	O
street	O
in	O
the	O
City	O
,	O
I	O
hired	O
the	O
prisoner	O
out	O
of	O
Spittle	O
fields	O
market	O
,	O
at	O
3	O
s.	O
per	O
week	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
at	O
winding	O
of	O
silk	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
me	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
5	O
days	O
,	O
the	O
silk	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Pattersgale	O
's	O
silk	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
my	O
care	O
;	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
some	O
silk	O
when	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
catch	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
possible	O
,	O
I	O
weighed	O
2	O
empty	O
bobbins	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
some	O
silk	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
wind	O
upon	O
them	O
bobbins	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
silk	O
at	O
the	O
usual	O
place	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
i	O
weighed	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
ought	O
to	O
have	O
had	O
12	O
ounces	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
drams	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
an	O
ounce	O
and	O
7	O
drams	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
silk	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Cornelius	I-pers
,	O
a	O
man	O
we	O
have	O
had	O
suspicion	O
on	O
in	O
the	O
trade	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
We	O
should	O
be	O
glad	O
to	O
see	O
that	O
man	O
here	O
.	O
Magdalen	O
Sturt	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
silk	O
to	O
Cornelius	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
court	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Cornelius	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
213	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
-	I-pers
Priswell	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
did	O
unlawfully	O
,	O
knowingly	O
and	O
designedly	O
,	O
by	O
false	O
pretences	O
,	O
obtain	O
from	O
John	B-pers
Charlton	I-pers
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
bohea	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
goods	O
,	O
wares	O
and	O
merchandise	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
cheat	O
and	O
defraud	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
against	O
the	O
peace	O
of	O
our	O
Lord	O
the	O
King	O
,	O
his	O
crown	O
and	O
dignity	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
,	O
Guilty	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
214	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Frances	B-pers
Newcome	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
yards	O
and	O
half	O
of	O
white	O
linnen	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
other	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
other	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
one	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
other	O
thread	O
lace	O
,	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
other	O
lace	O
,	O
2	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
other	O
lace	O
,	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
silk	O
lace	O
,	O
9	O
yards	O
of	O
ribbon	O
,	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
black	O
sattin	O
ribbon	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Emm	B-pers
Scott	I-pers
,	O
Theodotia	B-pers
Hathway	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Cove	I-pers
,	O
June	O
4	O
++	O
Emm	O
Scott	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
milliner	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
partners	O
?	O
E.	O
Scott	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
,	O
Theodotia	O
Hathway	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Cove	I-pers
;	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Milk	B-place
street	I-place
;	O
I	O
lost	O
some	O
laces	O
and	O
ribbons	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
the	O
indictment	O
read	O
?	O
E.	O
Scott	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
our	O
servant	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
us	O
5	O
weeks	O
all	O
but	O
one	O
day	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
having	O
miss	O
'd	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
ask	O
'd	O
her	O
about	O
them	O
;	O
she	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
her	O
box	O
serached	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
owned	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
our	O
property	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
too	O
)	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
character	O
had	O
you	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
E.	O
Scott	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
taken	O
her	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Bowyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Scott	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
tell	O
Mrs.	O
Emm	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
my	O
Mistress	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Newcombe	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cove	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
partners	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
tax	O
the	O
maid	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
denied	O
having	O
any	O
thing	O
but	O
what	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
own	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
were	O
certain	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
the	O
better	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
still	O
denied	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
the	O
constable	O
below	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
must	O
search	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
up	O
and	O
open	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
.	O
She	O
opened	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
it	O
were	O
found	O
these	O
goods	O
mentioned	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Cartwright	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
too	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
years	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Kirby	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
callender	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
character	O
has	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Kirby	O
.	O
The	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
once	O
asked	O
at	O
the	O
church	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
marry	O
her	O
to-morrow	O
if	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
into	O
consideration	O
,	O
and	O
clear	O
her	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
2	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
ticket	O
porter	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
a	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
in	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Jenkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
used	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
she	O
lived	O
upwards	O
of	O
2	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
bare	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
characters	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Recommended	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
215	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Chesterfield	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
blanket	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
sheet	O
,	O
value	O
11	O
d.	O
one	O
mahogany	O
spoon	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Whipping	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
216	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jos	B-pers
Allvey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Obadiah	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
June	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Obadiah	O
Wright	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
stockings	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
some	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
concluded	O
they	O
must	O
be	O
taken	O
by	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
16	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
always	O
before	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
:	O
my	O
son	O
said	O
he	O
suspected	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
will	O
soon	O
catch	O
him	O
;	O
we	O
put	O
19	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
upon	O
a	O
shelf	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
my	O
son	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
finish	O
them	O
.	O
When	O
night	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
pair	O
;	O
my	O
son	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pair	O
missing	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
pull	O
off	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
it	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
stockings	O
put	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
hole	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
the	O
coat	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
fellow	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
fearing	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
angry	O
.	O
Then	O
in	O
searching	O
farther	O
,	O
one	O
Richard	B-pers
Slaughter	I-pers
found	O
the	O
fellow	O
stocking	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
ever	O
had	O
done	O
so	O
.	O
Rich	O
.	O
Slaughter	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wright	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
stockings	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pair	O
then	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
they	O
call	O
'd	O
him	O
back	O
;	O
they	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
pair	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
came	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
nobody	O
here	O
but	O
you	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
stand	O
search	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
search	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
(	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
deny	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
stockings	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
cut	O
off	O
the	O
tops	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
21	O
years	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
people	O
here	O
to	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
company	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
belongs	O
to	O
about	O
17	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
folder	O
in	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
inlisted	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
abroad	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
last	O
war	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Megriger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
suspected	O
of	O
any	O
theft	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
ever	O
hear	O
the	O
least	O
complaint	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
217	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
womens	O
stays	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
black	O
flower	O
'd	O
bonnet	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Fra	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
+	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
is	O
Fra	O
.	O
Roberts	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
,	O
to	O
sell	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
occasion	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
to	O
sell	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
at	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
getting	O
supper	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
sick	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
child	O
out	O
at	O
nurse	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
stripp	O
'd	O
my	O
children	O
to	O
wash	O
their	O
little	O
things	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wou	O
'd	O
stay	O
and	O
help	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wou	O
'd	O
give	O
her	O
2	O
d.	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
childrens	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
a	O
bonnet	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
old	O
stays	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
and	O
white	O
cheque	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
copper	O
saucepan	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
stays	O
in	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
drinking	O
in	O
an	O
alehouse	O
with	O
my	O
bonnet	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
(	O
pro	O
duc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
depos	O
'd	O
to	O
)	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
E.	O
Roberts	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
these	O
stays	O
in	O
Rag	O
fair	O
for	O
9	O
d.	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
as	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
218	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
brown	O
and	O
white	O
sattin	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
crape	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
black	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
linen	O
aprons	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Fitzhew	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Fitshew	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
breeches-maker	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
these	O
things	O
mentioned	O
between	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Dec.	O
last	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
5th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Bartholomew	I-place
the	I-place
Great	I-place
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
they	O
taken	O
from	O
?	O
Fitzhew	O
.	O
From	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
things	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodg	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
elop	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
After	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Welch	O
;	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
John	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
find	O
them	O
till	O
Monday	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
John	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
?	O
Fitzbew	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
such	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
stood	O
at	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
came	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Sam	B-pers
Slayter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Dec.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
this	O
gown	O
and	O
cardinal	O
to	O
me	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Bristow	I-pers
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Broad	O
way	O
,	O
Black	O
Fryers	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
find	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
those	O
he	O
produced	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
brought	O
me	O
from	O
a	O
sick	O
bed	O
in	O
the	O
workhouse	O
;	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
last	O
Monday	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
him	O
any	O
such	O
proposal	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
loth	O
to	O
take	O
away	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
say	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
have	O
that	O
money	O
paid	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
meddle	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
did	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
219	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Myford	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Currel	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
July	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Currel	I-pers
.	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
up	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
let	O
with	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
,	O
almost	O
half	O
a	O
year	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
confess	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
at	O
2	O
pawnbrokers	O
that	O
are	O
here	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
15th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
this	O
sheet	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
3	O
shillings	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
I	O
attended	O
justice	O
Welch	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Summer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawn	O
'd	O
this	O
sheet	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
defence	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
first	O
sheet	O
,	O
having	O
no	O
work	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
my	O
landlady	O
knew	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
forgive	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
fetching	O
it	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
quit	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
intended	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
again	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
out	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
before	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
I	O
give	O
her	O
liberty	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
220	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
blew	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Price	B-pers
Swancott	I-pers
,	O
June	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
Price	O
Swancott	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
imployed	O
to	O
do	O
bussiness	O
for	O
my	O
wife	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
a	O
blew	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
shirt	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
intelligence	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
round	O
house	O
for	O
a	O
quarrel	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
my	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
shirt	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pell	O
,	O
the	O
shirt	O
in	O
Russel	O
street	O
Covent	O
Garden	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
accordingly	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
knew	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
the	O
like	O
before	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
before	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
waistcoat	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
(	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
she	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
take	O
things	O
of	O
people	O
in	O
liquor	O
?	O
Harrison	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
one	O
William	B-pers
Rounds	I-pers
sent	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
took	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
alehouse	O
in	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
things	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Donwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
13	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
I	O
always	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
till	O
now	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Lambeth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
8	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
school	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
sober	O
girl	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
trusted	O
her	O
with	O
a	O
thousand	O
pounds	O
;	O
she	O
has	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
had	O
she	O
been	O
so	O
minded	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
.	O
Whether	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
221	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
4	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
cotton	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
,	O
July	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
Robert	B-pers
Copeland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
stocking	O
shop	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Prince	O
's	O
street	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
Haymarket	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
sister	O
lives	O
at	O
Islington	O
;	O
she	O
sent	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
send	O
up	O
some	O
stockings	O
for	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
child	O
of	O
her	O
's	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
6	O
pair	O
by	O
my	O
2	O
children	O
,	O
they	O
having	O
frequently	O
gone	O
that	O
walk	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
2	O
children	O
were	O
,	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
they	O
?	O
Copeland	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
is	O
upwards	O
of	O
8	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
boy	O
turn	O
'd	O
of	O
6	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
11	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
last	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
witnesses	O
can	O
inform	O
the	O
court	O
better	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Crump	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
last	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
12	O
and	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	B-place
White	I-place
Conduit	I-place
,	I-place
by	I-place
Islington	I-place
;	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
large	O
pond	O
wall	O
'd	O
in	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
west	O
side	O
of	O
that	O
wall	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
little	O
boy	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
had	O
a	O
parcel	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
was	O
about	O
20	O
yards	O
behind	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
parcel	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
brown	O
paper	O
;	O
the	O
little	O
girl	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Jackey	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
the	O
way	O
;	O
the	O
boy	O
answered	O
,	O
this	O
will	O
take	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
new	O
road	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
come	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
show	O
you	O
the	O
road	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
I	O
came	O
about	O
half	O
way	O
down	O
the	O
next	O
field	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
something	O
bubbling	O
in	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
I	O
stopp	O
'd	O
by	O
the	O
pond	O
side	O
;	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
standing	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
distinguished	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
crying	O
of	O
children	O
;	O
I	O
look	O
'd	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
first	O
saw	O
nobody	O
;	O
presently	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
running	O
under	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
first	O
met	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
wall	O
he	O
jump	O
'd	O
over	O
the	O
rails	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
down	O
the	O
grass	O
,	O
making	O
towards	O
Sadlers	O
Wells	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
of	O
the	O
children	O
,	O
increased	O
my	O
suspicion	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
as	O
near	O
me	O
as	O
he	O
chose	O
to	O
come	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Hollow	O
,	O
you	O
sir	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
children	O
,	O
very	O
loud	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
short	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
made	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
wall	O
of	O
the	O
reservoir	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
fouth	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
kept	O
so	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
get	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Hollow	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
you	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
wall	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
this	O
bundle	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
paper	O
)	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
throw	O
it	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
into	O
the	O
water	O
,	O
it	O
hit	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
throwed	O
it	O
over	O
,	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
convinced	O
he	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
the	O
children	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
now	O
road	O
.	O
Mr.	O
King	O
was	O
amongst	O
his	O
sheep	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
children	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
man	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
him	O
)	O
had	O
robb	O
'd	O
them	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
there	O
justice	O
Wright	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
stockings	O
which	O
I	O
sent	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
by	O
my	O
children	O
,	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
King	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
field	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
Mr.	O
Crump	O
pursuing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
sling	O
the	O
bundle	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Crump	O
say	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
have	O
you	O
presently	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
assistance	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
secured	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
overtook	O
the	O
girl	O
about	O
30	O
yards	O
behind	O
the	O
boy	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
I	O
overtook	O
the	O
boy	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
new	O
road	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
show	O
you	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
straight	O
forward	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
field	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
ease	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
run	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
sister	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
to	O
Noble	O
street	O
,	O
by	O
Goswell	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
bundle	O
in	O
the	O
grass	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
presently	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
sound	O
of	O
crying	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
that	O
gentleman	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Crump	O
;	O
he	O
turned	O
and	O
made	O
towards	O
me	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
.	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
as	O
I	O
understood	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
nothing	O
of	O
your	O
's	O
,	O
nor	O
no	O
body	O
's	O
else	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
I	O
'll	O
have	O
you	O
;	O
so	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
an	O
attempt	O
to	O
throw	O
the	O
parcel	O
over	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
throw	O
'd	O
it	O
over	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
the	O
larceny	O
only	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
222	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Hand	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Varthe	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
linnen	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
,	O
August	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Rob	B-pers
Austin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
ready	O
furnished	O
lodging	O
of	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
but	O
one	O
week	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
3	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
gowns	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
;	O
the	O
drawer	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
let	O
to	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
lodging	O
.	O
After	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
the	O
gowns	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
drawer	O
left	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bunch	O
of	O
keys	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
which	O
would	O
open	O
many	O
locks	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Austin	O
.	O
These	O
3	O
gowns	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
hired	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
R.	O
Austin	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
these	O
gowns	O
found	O
again	O
?	O
R.	O
Austin	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
overseers	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Clements	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
R.	O
Austin	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
.	O
Jos	B-pers
Burnthwite	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
past	O
to	O
our	O
parish	O
St.	O
Clements	O
from	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
,	O
Shropshire	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Varthe	O
,	O
last	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
overseer	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
us	O
by	O
a	O
vagrant	O
pass	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
my	O
partner	O
and	O
I	O
she	O
belong	O
'd	O
to	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
family	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
brother	O
that	O
had	O
an	O
estate	O
of	O
five	O
hundred	O
Pounds	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
a	O
counseller	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
very	O
good	O
things	O
in	O
pawn	O
,	O
but	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
money	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
redeem	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
write	O
to	O
her	O
brother	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
her	O
money	O
up	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
upon	O
this	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
redeem	O
'd	O
them	O
,	O
among	O
which	O
were	O
those	O
three	O
gowns	O
;	O
we	O
kept	O
them	O
some	O
months	O
expecting	O
the	O
money	O
from	O
her	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
allow	O
'd	O
her	O
2	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
sent	O
us	O
word	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
we	O
would	O
some	O
of	O
us	O
appear	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
messenger	O
come	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
many	O
things	O
:	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
perticularly	O
these	O
3	O
gowns	O
.	O
She	O
describ	O
'd	O
one	O
a	O
white	O
gown	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
string	O
sowed	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
the	O
pattern	O
of	O
another	O
gown	O
,	O
it	O
match	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
describ	O
'd	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
no	O
doubt	O
of	O
the	O
three	O
gowns	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
vestry	O
room	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
some	O
goods	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
show	O
'd	O
the	O
pieces	O
belonging	O
to	O
my	O
gown	O
to	O
prove	O
them	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
kept	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
parish	O
officers	O
,	O
and	O
described	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
own	O
gowns	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
223	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Messenger	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
privately	O
and	O
secretly	O
,	O
June	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Daniel	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
a	O
brewers	O
in	O
Clare	B-place
market	I-place
;	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
head	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Dixon	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
as	O
sober	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
now	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
awaked	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
my	O
friend	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
me	O
by	O
my	O
arm	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
have	O
you	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wants	O
you	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
Dixon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
only	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
held	O
me	O
fast	O
by	O
the	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
arm	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
observed	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
again	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
have	O
you	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
your	O
money	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
when	O
you	O
laid	O
your	O
head	O
down	O
to	O
sleep	O
?	O
Dixon	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
silver	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
give	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
will	O
tear	O
your	O
arm	O
off	O
She	O
immediately	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
she	O
had	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
metal	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
before	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
counter	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
set	O
down	O
by	O
you	O
?	O
Dixon	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
not	O
except	O
she	O
did	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
sware	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
224	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Susanna	B-pers
Cottell	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Samuel	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
20	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
call	O
'd	O
corded	O
tabby	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
l.	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Miles	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
,	O
Benj	B-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
second	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
May	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
Benj	O
.	O
Lucas	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
green	O
corded	O
tabby	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
20	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
partners	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
,	O
Miles	O
Mason	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
we	O
are	O
mercers	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Catherine	B-place
street	I-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
often	O
lost	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
could	O
fix	O
them	O
on	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
advertis	O
'd	O
this	O
at	O
20	O
guineas	O
reward	O
on	O
the	O
conviction	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
stole	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
advertisement	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Pell	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
4	O
yards	O
of	O
corded	O
tabby	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
the	O
mark	O
being	O
cut	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
cut	O
into	O
small	O
pieces	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
my	O
weaver	O
from	O
Spittle	O
fields	O
,	O
who	O
weav	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
fellow	O
piece	O
to	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
;	O
the	O
4	O
yards	O
tally	O
'd	O
with	O
that	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
brought	O
2	O
yards	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
sort	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pell	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
person	O
particularly	O
well	O
that	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
4	O
yards	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
for	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
It	O
happen	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pell	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
May	O
to	O
take	O
a	O
coat	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
secur	O
'd	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Bradford	O
.	O
We	O
detain	O
'd	O
him	O
till	O
we	O
got	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
at	O
the	O
black	O
horse	O
in	O
Bedford	O
bury	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
red	O
lion	O
in	O
Russel	O
street	O
in	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
something	O
privately	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
go	O
and	O
call	O
for	O
something	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
unhappy	O
in	O
a	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
given	O
much	O
to	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
spent	O
him	O
3	O
or	O
400	O
l.	O
at	O
Bristol	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
certainly	O
be	O
the	O
ruin	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
order	O
'd	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
the	O
woman	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
He	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
4	O
yards	O
of	O
this	O
silk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pell	O
.	O
2	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
,	O
4	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
St.	O
Martin	O
's	O
lane	O
,	O
4	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
names	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
places	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
but	O
2	O
yards	O
at	O
that	O
house	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
6	O
yards	O
we	O
found	O
put	O
up	O
his	O
chimney	O
where	O
he	O
lodg	O
'd	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
found	O
all	O
but	O
2	O
yards	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
his	O
wife	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
piece	O
;	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
in	O
Russel	O
street	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
acknowledg	O
'd	O
she	O
carry	O
'd	O
the	O
2	O
yards	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bibby	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
made	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
any	O
promises	O
?	O
Lucas	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
any	O
discovery	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
go	O
home	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
directly	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
4	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
in	O
pawn	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
named	O
John	B-pers
Bradford	I-pers
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
speak	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
to	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
declared	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
she	O
took	O
the	O
piece	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
if	O
they	O
sold	O
printed	O
linnen	O
;	O
the	O
answer	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
deal	O
in	O
linnen	O
,	O
but	O
only	O
silks	O
and	O
stuffs	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
she	O
saw	O
this	O
piece	O
of	O
silk	O
lying	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
cardinal	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
not	O
being	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Sydenham	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
there	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
there	O
any	O
promises	O
made	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Pell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
none	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gunsten	I-pers
.	O
The	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Saunders	I-pers
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
sware	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
impossible	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
as	O
I	O
lost	O
.	O
Gunston	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
confess	O
at	O
the	O
Blakeney	O
's	O
head	O
in	O
Bow	O
street	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
Mr.	O
Lucas	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
if	O
they	O
sold	O
linnen	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
saw	O
this	O
rowl	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
her	O
husband	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Demark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
the	O
produced	O
4	O
yards	O
of	O
)	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
that	O
pawn	O
'd	O
this	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
sware	O
positively	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Abraham	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
6	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
up	O
the	O
prisoners	O
chimney	O
in	O
that	O
lodging	O
room	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Lamater	I-pers
.	O
He	O
looks	O
at	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
and	O
produc	O
'd	O
some	O
other	O
silk	O
;	O
this	O
I	O
cut	O
from	O
the	O
same	O
piece	O
which	O
I	O
sold	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
;	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
upon	O
comparing	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
these	O
pieces	O
are	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
I	O
sware	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
sold	O
him	O
.	O
Susannah	B-pers
Cottell	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Cottell	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
goods	O
of	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
promis	O
'd	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
confess	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
bought	O
before	O
the	O
face	O
of	O
a	O
justice	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Sturt	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoners	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
they	O
kept	O
a	O
house	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
years	O
ago	O
when	O
I	O
knew	O
them	O
at	O
Bristol	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Perriwig	O
maker	O
;	O
about	O
4	O
months	O
ago	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
;	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
distress	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
could	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
furniture	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
do	O
pretty	O
well	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
upholster	O
in	O
Fleet	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
let	O
them	O
have	O
26	O
l.	O
worth	O
of	O
goods	O
upon	O
my	O
credit	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
that	O
confidence	O
in	O
their	O
characters	O
;	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
at	O
5	O
l.	O
a	O
quarter	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
some	O
dependance	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
them	O
good	O
people	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Lowrey	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
lodg	O
'd	O
4	O
months	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
they	O
behav	O
'd	O
very	O
decently	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
soberly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Lowrey	O
.	O
In	O
Round	O
court	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
Vine	O
street	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Mason	O
's	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
sale	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
lost	O
nothing	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
Susannah	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Samuel	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
225	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Moses	B-pers
Birch	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
wooden	O
barrels	O
fill	O
'd	O
with	O
flour	O
,	O
value	O
38	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
Wm	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bethnal	O
green	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
knowledge	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
can	O
inform	O
the	O
court	O
as	O
to	O
particulars	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Burnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
corn	O
dealer	O
and	O
lighterman	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
barge	O
down	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
flour	O
from	O
a	O
mill	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
we	O
brought	O
the	O
barge	O
to	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
work	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
there	O
;	O
he	O
return	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
miss	O
'd	O
6	O
barrels	O
of	O
meal	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
a	O
washing	O
his	O
boat	O
(	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
waterman	O
)	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
sunk	O
her	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
wash	O
her	O
;	O
yet	O
there	O
were	O
some	O
stains	O
of	O
flour	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
are	O
a	O
villain	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
6	O
barrels	O
of	O
flour	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
weigh	O
'd	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
900	O
and	O
odd	O
weight	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
meal	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Burnett	O
.	O
The	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Slade	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
as	O
his	O
waterman	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
particular	O
order	O
,	O
only	O
3	O
bushels	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
in	O
a	O
barrel	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
the	O
heads	O
of	O
the	O
barrels	O
that	O
had	O
the	O
brand	O
marks	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
barrels	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hays	I-pers
.	O
I	O
loaded	O
this	O
vessel	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
with	O
them	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
were	O
6	O
barrels	O
missing	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
master	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
enquire	O
of	O
people	O
about	O
Ratcliff	O
Cross	O
;	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
washing	O
his	O
boat	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
stains	O
of	O
flour	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
charg	O
'd	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
6	O
barrels	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
barge	O
;	O
he	O
own	O
'd	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
vessels	O
heads	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
W.	O
Slade	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
vessels	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
we	O
lost	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
On	O
that	O
Sunday	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Greenwich	O
with	O
a	O
fair	O
;	O
staying	O
there	O
some	O
time	O
we	O
drank	O
pretty	O
plentifully	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
lay	O
down	O
instead	O
of	O
stowing	O
my	O
boat	O
;	O
3	O
men	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
me	O
to	O
carry	O
them	O
on	O
board	O
that	O
barge	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
jump	O
'd	O
into	O
the	O
lighter	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
one	O
drew	B-pers
a	O
cutlass	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
out	O
6	O
casks	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
be	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
they	O
might	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
lighterman	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
dead	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
witnesses	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Anthony	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
block-maker	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
A.	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
this	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
evening	O
before	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
stay	O
?	O
A.	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
stay	O
above	O
20	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
away	O
?	O
A.	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
About	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Nicholls	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
brother	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
A.	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
river	O
pilot	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
E.	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
that	O
Sunday	O
night	O
?	O
E.	O
Nicholls	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Grimes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
been	O
his	O
behaviour	O
?	O
Grimes	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
bad	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
fact	O
happened	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
Sunday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
June	O
?	O
Grimes	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
226	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Perry	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
purse	O
;	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
30	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
right	O
honourable	O
George	B-pers
Earle	I-pers
of	I-pers
Pomfret	I-pers
,	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Tebay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Mount	O
street	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
my	O
Lord	O
Pomfret	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Tebay	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stable	O
keeper	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
was	O
desired	O
by	O
my	O
Lord	O
Pomfret	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
capacity	O
?	O
Tebay	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
purse	O
of	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
my	O
Lord	O
present	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
?	O
Tebay	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
mention	O
'd	O
what	O
the	O
sum	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
to	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Tebay	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
it	O
at	O
first	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
own	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
conceal	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
little	O
place	O
where	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
horses	O
stand	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
a	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
an	O
old	O
ceiling	O
he	O
look	O
'd	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
up	O
to	O
within	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
tyles	O
of	O
the	O
ridge	O
tyle	O
into	O
a	O
little	O
hole	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
a	O
purse	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
;	O
my	O
Lord	O
told	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
near	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
there	O
were	O
29	O
or	O
30	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
30	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
when	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tyling	O
?	O
Tebay	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
till	O
my	O
Lord	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
room	O
from	O
off	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
?	O
Tebay	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
possession	O
?	O
Tebay	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
my	O
Lord	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Tebay	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
boy	O
with	O
you	O
when	O
you	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
?	O
Tebay	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
my	O
Lord	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
questions	O
?	O
Tebay	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
repeat	O
the	O
words	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
boy	O
say	O
?	O
Tebay	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
sorry	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
intend	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
my	O
Lord	O
again	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Pomfret	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
show	O
him	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
capacity	O
are	O
you	O
servant	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
?	O
Barnes	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
groom	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Barnes	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
on	O
errands	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
been	O
there	O
?	O
Barnes	O
.	O
About	O
3	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
he	O
to	O
be	O
suspected	O
?	O
Barnes	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
because	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
servants	O
had	O
been	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
that	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
after	O
my	O
Lord	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
away	O
,	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
room	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Barnes	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
dressing	O
room	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
down	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chair	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
Lordship	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
home	O
again	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
my	O
Lord	O
came	O
home	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
water	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
forgot	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bradshaw	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
14	O
or	O
15	O
years	O
,	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
he	O
comes	O
from	O
Tositer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Bradshaw	O
.	O
He	O
his	O
about	O
15	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
my	O
Lord	O
?	O
Bradshaw	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Davis	O
at	O
Tositer	O
better	O
than	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
nephew	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
character	O
?	O
Bradshaw	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Reeve	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
been	O
his	O
character	O
?	O
Reeve	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
otherwise	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
for	O
whatever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
verdict	O
my	O
Lord	O
Pomfret	O
spoke	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
In	O
consideration	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
youth	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
has	O
committed	O
a	O
crime	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
parents	O
people	O
of	O
very	O
honest	O
character	O
,	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
court	O
will	O
think	O
well	O
to	O
inflict	O
a	O
light	O
punishment	O
on	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
him	O
to	O
sea	O
,	O
his	O
uncle	O
is	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
received	O
sentence	O
to	O
be	O
branded	O
in	O
the	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
branded	O
immediately	O
.	O
227	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Whiteman	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
quart	O
mugg	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Chant	I-pers
,	O
May	O
28	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Chant	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	B-place
Jane	I-place
Shore	I-place
in	I-place
Shoreditch	I-place
,	I-place
a	I-place
public	I-place
house	I-place
;	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
drinking	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
before	O
?	O
Chant	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
her	O
backward	O
and	O
forward	O
for	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
2	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
people	O
drinking	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
company	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Men	O
or	O
women	O
?	O
Chant	O
.	O
Some	O
men	O
and	O
some	O
women	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
about	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
they	O
drink	O
out	O
of	O
?	O
Chant	O
.	O
They	O
drank	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
silver	O
quart	O
mugg	O
;	O
I	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
mugg	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
let	O
people	O
drink	O
out	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
not	O
look	O
about	O
to	O
see	O
whether	O
all	O
are	O
safe	O
before	O
they	O
go	O
?	O
Chant	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
busy	O
in	O
shutting	O
up	O
the	O
windows	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
all	O
go	O
away	O
together	O
?	O
Chant	O
.	O
They	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
searched	O
about	O
that	O
night	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
those	O
people	O
that	O
were	O
drinking	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
they	O
all	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
neighbours	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
lived	O
in	O
Newin	O
yard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
liv	O
'd	O
?	O
Chant	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
send	O
for	O
them	O
all	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
'll	O
examine	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
will	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
confess	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
accident	O
;	O
he	O
can	O
give	O
a	O
farther	O
account	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Nichols	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
facing	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Nichols	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
for	O
a	O
penyworth	O
of	O
beer	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
spouse	O
was	O
saying	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
silver	O
mugg	O
,	O
mentioning	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
where	O
the	O
lived	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
drink	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Buckmaster	O
,	O
ker	O
.	O
She	O
there	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
vault	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
heard	O
something	O
drop	O
into	O
the	O
vault	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
silver	O
mugg	O
there	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Nichols	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
upon	O
its	O
being	O
found	O
?	O
Nichols	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
her	O
say	O
a	O
word	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Boss	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
almost	O
a	O
year	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
May	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
we	O
asked	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
tankard	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
made	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
baker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
worth	O
of	O
bread	O
;	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
drink	O
without	O
eating	O
first	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
to	O
the	O
vault	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
and	O
I	O
both	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
afraid	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
us	O
the	O
slip	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
out	O
backwards	O
;	O
the	O
maid	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
running	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
something	O
dropp	O
'd	O
from	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
mugg	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
vault	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
her	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
mugg	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
confess	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
asked	O
her	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
mugg	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
with	O
some	O
beer	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
George	B-pers
Buckmaster	I-pers
,	O
a	O
baker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
last	O
witnesses	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
bread	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
2	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
the	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
ketchen	O
,	O
joining	O
almost	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
a	O
halfpenny	O
worth	O
of	O
bread	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
serv	O
'd	O
her	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
asked	O
to	O
go	O
backwards	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
answered	O
,	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
little	O
water	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
she	O
wanted	O
some	O
water	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
ask	O
the	O
maid	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
call	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
go	O
backwards	O
with	O
this	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
for	O
what	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
more	O
places	O
to	O
make	O
water	O
in	O
than	O
coming	O
just	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
necessary	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
her	O
go	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
turn	O
'd	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
entry	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
turned	O
again	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
shut	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
odd	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
must	O
not	O
shut	O
it	O
,	O
because	O
it	O
would	O
kill	O
the	O
chickens	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
standing	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
face	O
towards	O
the	O
vault	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
in	O
great	O
distress	O
,	O
something	O
fell	O
from	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
nothing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
put	O
something	O
down	O
the	O
vault	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
?	O
and	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
for	O
some	O
help	O
;	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Nichols	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
here	O
is	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
has	O
put	O
something	O
down	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
I	O
fear	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
and	O
will	O
be	O
smothered	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
away	O
backwards	O
;	O
they	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
silver	O
mugg	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
something	O
tied	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Linnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Spread	O
Eagle	O
court	O
,	O
Shoreditch	O
,	O
I	O
wind	O
silk	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
liv	O
'd	O
there	O
?	O
M.	O
Linnet	O
.	O
20	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
12	O
months	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
my	O
husba	O
nd	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
hospital	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
things	O
from	O
him	O
home	O
very	O
honestly	O
,	O
and	O
very	O
just	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoreditch	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
by	O
trade	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
11	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
An	O
honest	O
,	O
poor	O
,	O
industrious	O
woman	O
;	O
she	O
sometimes	O
winds	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
works	O
in	O
the	O
loom	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
12	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
has	O
been	O
her	O
behaviour	O
;	O
M.	O
Cook	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
by	O
her	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
day	O
and	O
night	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Rowley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
otherwise	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Elizabeth	O
Hill	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
3	O
months	O
before	O
christmas	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
work	O
'd	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
living	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Bovine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
months	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
with	O
me	O
as	O
a	O
stranger	O
about	O
10	O
weeks	O
ago	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Bovine	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
;	O
she	O
behav	O
'd	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
soberly	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
left	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
our	O
absence	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
miss	O
'd	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
228	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Carver	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
before	O
Dr.	O
Ducarrel	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prerogative	O
court	O
of	O
Canterbury	O
;	O
swearing	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
half	O
brother	O
to	O
Wm	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
deceas	O
'd	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
died	O
without	O
any	O
nearer	O
relations	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
,	O
by	O
means	O
of	O
an	O
administration	O
,	O
to	O
obtain	O
money	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Salisbury	O
,	O
Feb.	O
29	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Moxey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Navy	O
office	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
capacity	O
?	O
Moxey	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
messenger	O
;	O
in	O
Feb.	O
last	O
,	O
towards	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Walter	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
along	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Holding	O
,	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Holding	O
would	O
be	O
much	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
put	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
readiest	O
way	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
wages	O
,	O
and	O
Prize	O
money	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
dead	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Salisbury	O
in	O
the	O
East	O
Indies	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
Wm	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
acquainting	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
brother	O
's	O
death	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
of	O
any	O
service	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
by	O
enquiring	O
what	O
wages	O
and	O
prize	O
money	O
was	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
administer	O
accordingly	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
agent	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
prize	O
money	O
for	O
that	O
ship	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
kind	O
enough	O
to	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
what	O
prize	O
money	O
might	O
be	O
due	O
to	O
Wm	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
of	O
the	O
Salisbury	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
3	O
different	O
sums	O
,	O
which	O
amounted	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
to	O
54	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
then	O
for	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
the	O
wages	O
and	O
prize	O
money	O
would	O
amount	O
to	O
upwards	O
of	O
60	O
l.	O
I	O
then	O
told	O
them	O
they	O
must	O
administer	O
for	O
upper	O
value	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
to	O
exceed	O
60	O
l.	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
after	O
this	O
for	O
some	O
days	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
an	O
administration	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
apply	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
to	O
receive	O
this	O
prize	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
agent	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
prize	O
money	O
only	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
was	O
but	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
before	O
the	O
day	O
to	O
pay	O
the	O
prize	O
money	O
came	O
on	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
public	O
advertisement	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
of	O
payment	O
they	O
both	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
mob	O
about	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
they	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
come	O
near	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
at	O
the	O
Navy	O
office	O
by	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
be	O
of	O
any	O
service	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
knowing	O
some	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
's	O
clerks	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
endeavour	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
money	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
of	O
them	O
spoke	O
to	O
you	O
about	O
it	O
?	O
Moxey	O
.	O
They	O
both	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
Walter	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
said	O
the	O
most	O
,	O
this	O
seem	O
'd	O
very	O
ignorant	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
understood	O
,	O
and	O
seem	O
'd	O
to	O
conduct	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
Navy	O
office	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
waiting	O
for	O
me	O
there	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
throng	O
about	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
so	O
that	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
come	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
took	O
the	O
administration	O
from	O
his	O
bosom	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
desir	O
'd	O
I	O
would	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
gratuity	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
receiv	O
'd	O
54	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
sign	O
'd	O
my	O
name	O
Richard	B-pers
Moxey	I-pers
for	O
John	B-pers
Carver	I-pers
,	O
administrator	O
to	O
his	O
book	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
I	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
receipt	O
for	O
the	O
same	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
it	O
is	O
read	O
.	O
Receiv	O
'd	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
1760	O
,	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Moxey	I-pers
,	O
54	O
l	O
9	O
s.	O
being	O
the	O
prize	O
money	O
he	O
received	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
's	O
of	O
the	O
Salisbury	O
,	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Carver	I-pers
,	O
I	O
say	O
received	O
by	O
me	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Carver	I-pers
.	O
I	O
wrote	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
administration	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
administrator	O
in	O
the	O
administration	O
to	O
Wm	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
?	O
Moxey	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Carver	I-pers
was	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
warrant	O
upon	O
which	O
the	O
administration	O
was	O
granted	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
dropp	O
'd	O
a	O
guinea	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
will	O
that	O
satisfy	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
yes	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
been	O
of	O
great	O
service	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
another	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
the	O
administration	O
?	O
Moxey	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
or	O
was	O
it	O
Walter	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
?	O
Moxey	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
Walter	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
sole	O
transactor	O
of	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
guided	O
by	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
every	O
respect	O
behaved	O
as	O
much	O
like	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
it	O
as	O
any	O
body	O
could	O
do	O
,	O
and	O
Walter	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
quite	O
otherwise	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
till	O
last	O
Sessions	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
application	O
made	O
to	O
you	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
money	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Moxey	O
?	O
Dixon	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
3	O
payments	O
for	O
John	B-pers
Carver	I-pers
,	O
administrator	O
for	O
Wm	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
.	O
	O
.	O
s.	O
d.	O
One	O
for	O
the	O
taking	O
Shandanagore	O
,	O
9	O
3	O
6	O
Another	O
for	O
taking	O
Goree	O
,	O
1	O
16	O
6	O
And	O
the	O
Nabob	O
of	O
Bengall	O
's	O
gift	O
,	O
43	O
9	O
0	O
The	O
lotal	O
54	O
9	O
0	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
the	O
death	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
?	O
Dixon	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
books	O
come	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
have	O
them	O
examin	O
'd	O
at	O
the	O
Navy	O
office	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
men	O
are	O
dead	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
dead	O
men	O
are	O
paid	O
by	O
administration	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
living	O
by	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
make	O
any	O
difficulty	O
of	O
paying	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Dixon	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
I	O
remember	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
days	O
after	O
,	O
when	O
Mr.	O
Moxey	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
take	O
care	O
how	O
he	O
brought	O
himself	O
into	O
a	O
scrape	O
;	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
more	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Jol	O
.	O
Robins	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Farrer	O
's	O
clerk	O
,	O
named	O
Jones	O
,	O
to	O
attend	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Farrer	O
as	O
proctor	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
attended	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
at	O
Doctors	O
Commons	O
before	O
Dr.	O
Ducarrel	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
?	O
Robins	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
certain	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
only	O
last	O
sessions	O
and	O
now	O
;	O
since	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
a	O
person	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
swore	O
himself	O
brother	O
by	O
the	O
half	O
blood	O
to	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
that	O
means	O
obtained	O
letters	O
of	O
administration	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
attested	O
it	O
as	O
a	O
notary	O
public	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
upon	O
this	O
.	O
Robins	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
takes	O
a	O
writing	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
my	O
attestation	O
,	O
and	O
here	O
is	O
Dr.	O
Ducarrel	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
(	O
pointing	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
)	O
Wm	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Farrer	O
,	O
a	O
Proctor	O
in	O
the	O
Commons	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
with	O
2	O
women	O
to	O
the	O
office	O
;	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
if	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
Will	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
how	O
near	O
a	O
kin	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
brother	O
by	O
the	O
half	O
blood	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
any	O
other	O
kin	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
paper	O
(	O
the	O
warrant	O
)	O
Wm	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
Here	O
is	O
Dr.	O
Ducarrel	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
obtain	O
'd	O
the	O
administration	O
of	O
the	O
Doctor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Doctor	O
administred	O
the	O
usual	O
oath	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
subscribing	O
witness	O
to	O
the	O
Execution	O
of	O
the	O
bond	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
apply	O
'd	O
for	O
the	O
administration	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
?	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
parties	O
that	O
executed	O
the	O
bond	O
;	O
I	O
fill	O
'd	O
up	O
the	O
bond	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
executed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
by	O
whom	O
executed	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
the	O
parties	O
sign	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
about	O
the	O
court	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
here	O
that	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
?	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
court	O
that	O
I	O
can	O
say	O
sign	O
'd	O
it	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
impossible	O
to	O
remember	O
who	O
signs	O
these	O
,	O
there	O
comes	O
may	O
be	O
half	O
a	O
score	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Goodwin	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Jones	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
take	O
upon	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Fuller	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
proctor	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
was	O
absent	O
;	O
on	O
my	O
return	O
I	O
received	O
a	O
note	O
wrote	O
by	O
Wm	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
just	O
now	O
examin	O
'd	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
apply	O
'd	O
for	O
an	O
administration	O
,	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Carver	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
effects	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
deceas	O
'd	O
,	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Salisbury	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
that	O
man	O
?	O
Fuller	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
till	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Farrer	O
?	O
Fuller	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
person	O
.	O
The	O
.	O
Haywood	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
April	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Haywood	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
clerk	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Callaghan	O
,	O
attorney	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
there	O
charg	O
'd	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
that	O
receiving	O
54	O
l.	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
proper	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
Barry	I-pers
,	O
he	O
said	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
:	O
my	O
lord	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
taking	O
out	O
this	O
false	O
administration	O
;	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
hop	O
'd	O
his	O
lordship	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
offence	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
ignorant	O
man	O
.	O
His	O
lordship	O
answer	O
'd	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
oblig	O
'd	O
to	O
commit	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
charge	O
was	O
for	O
taking	O
a	O
false	O
oath	O
,	O
to	O
obtain	O
a	O
letter	O
of	O
administration	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
obtain	O
the	O
prize	O
money	O
,	O
due	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
but	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
sufficient	O
proof	O
of	O
his	O
taking	O
that	O
oath	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
229	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
making	O
an	O
assault	O
upon	O
William	B-pers
Linton	I-pers
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling	O
house	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
3	O
guineas	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
,	O
June	O
9	O
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Linton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
little	O
house	O
in	O
Long	B-place
lane	I-place
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
Knights	O
bridge	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
Broad	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
into	O
Holborn	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
walking	O
along	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
is	O
my	O
way	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
that	O
way	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
we	O
walk	O
together	O
let	O
's	O
drink	O
together	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
no	O
way	O
unserviceable	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
near	O
Middle	O
Row	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
push	O
'd	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
here	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
and	O
pushed	O
me	O
cross	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
flung	O
her	O
petticoats	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
feel	O
upon	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
5	O
guineas	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
having	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
down	O
again	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
robb	O
'd	O
me	O
of	O
3	O
guineas	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
felt	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
miss	O
'd	O
them	O
)	O
I	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
arm	O
;	O
she	O
kept	O
pulling	O
till	O
she	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
pay	O
my	O
rent	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
landlord	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
since	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
several	O
people	O
have	O
come	O
in	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
offer	O
'd	O
me	O
my	O
money	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
she	O
spoke	O
to	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
did	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
spoke	O
first	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
positive	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
her	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
in	O
Holborn	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
just	O
before	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
Middle	O
Row	O
,	O
she	O
turn	O
'd	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
was	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
robb	O
'd	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
Magpye	O
alley	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
there	O
before	O
,	O
nor	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
had	O
you	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
5	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
the	O
silver	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gold	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
room	O
was	O
this	O
bed	O
in	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
we	O
entered	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
on	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
here	O
;	O
no	O
sooner	O
was	O
the	O
word	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
push	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
fell	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
over	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
ask	O
me	O
to	O
lie	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
bed	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
oath	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
not	O
you	O
push	O
her	O
down	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
touched	O
her	O
,	O
till	O
I	O
catch	O
'd	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
made	O
any	O
overtures	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
money	O
.	O
Linton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
cardinal	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
her	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
motherly	O
woman	O
than	O
one	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Were	O
all	O
the	O
5	O
guineas	O
wrapp	O
'd	O
up	O
together	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
it	O
possible	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
out	O
of	O
5	O
guineas	O
,	O
wrapt	O
in	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
take	O
3	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
She	O
broke	O
the	O
paper	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
I	O
produced	O
the	O
2	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
broke	O
through	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
Knights	O
bridge	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
from	O
thence	O
at	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
that	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Grigg	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
on	O
a	O
friend	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
this	O
woman	O
all	O
you	O
met	O
with	O
in	O
your	O
way	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
several	O
people	O
before	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
conversation	O
with	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
before	O
you	O
charg	O
'd	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
after	O
you	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
in	O
Magpye	O
alley	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
possible	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
took	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
Not	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
good	O
not	O
bad	O
,	O
but	O
pushed	O
me	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Linton	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
some	O
rum	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
no	O
way	O
at	O
all	O
disguised	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
paper	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
that	O
was	O
torne	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Belamy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
the	O
clock	O
was	O
ready	O
to	O
strike	O
one	O
when	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
call	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Castle	O
yard	O
;	O
Magpye	O
alley	O
is	O
infested	O
with	O
such	O
people	O
as	O
this	O
is	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
her	O
frequently	O
about	O
on	O
nights	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
Castle	O
door	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
charg	O
'd	O
her	O
with	O
picking	O
his	O
pocket	O
of	O
3	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
show	O
'd	O
us	O
the	O
torne	O
paper	O
and	O
the	O
2	O
guineas	O
at	O
the	O
watchhouse	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
woman	O
say	O
?	O
Belamy	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
Long	O
acre	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
pushed	O
against	O
me	O
2	O
or	O
3	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Betty	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
come	O
and	O
lie	O
down	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
you	O
a	O
shilling	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
go	O
along	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
call	O
the	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
call	O
'd	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
did	O
;	O
when	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
this	O
woman	O
has	O
pick	O
'd	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
3	O
guineas	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
searched	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
watchman	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
woman	O
run	O
down	O
Magpye	O
alley	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
another	O
woman	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
mine	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
no	O
house	O
upon	O
my	O
word	O
and	O
honour	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
day	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
watchman	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
give	O
you	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
Watchman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
watchman	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
from	O
her	O
own	O
house	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
her	O
into	O
custody	O
?	O
Watchman	O
.	O
The	O
very	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
her	O
own	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
Connely	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
7	O
or	O
8	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
market	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
shared	O
fish	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
character	O
?	O
E.	O
Connely	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
her	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
honest	O
woman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
she	O
get	O
her	O
living	O
by	O
that	O
now	O
?	O
E.	O
Connel	O
.	O
She	O
does	O
,	O
and	O
works	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
living	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Salmon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
7	O
years	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
by	O
selling	O
fish	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
by	O
selling	O
of	O
fruit	O
,	O
according	O
as	O
fruit	O
was	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
very	O
hard	O
working	O
woman	O
for	O
her	O
family	O
,	O
always	O
just	O
and	O
honest	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stunt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
sold	O
fish	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
went	O
to	O
Leadenhall	O
market	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
industrious	O
,	O
and	O
has	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
honest	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
paid	O
her	O
way	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Stuberfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
betwixt	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
gets	O
her	O
living	O
by	O
selling	O
of	O
fish	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
do	O
I	O
;	O
she	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
knew	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Shoen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
2	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
her	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
52	O
shillings	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
come	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
2	O
months	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
her	O
with	O
fish	O
in	O
the	O
winter	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
fruit	O
in	O
the	O
summer	O
;	O
she	O
bera	O
s	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
or	O
saw	O
;	O
she	O
always	O
bid	O
me	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
in	O
good	O
hours	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
M.	I-pers
Coone	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
going	O
on	O
7	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
her	O
character	O
?	O
M.	O
M.	O
Coone	O
.	O
Her	O
character	O
is	O
selling	O
fruit	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
market	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
look	O
'd	O
upon	O
to	O
be	O
honest	O
or	O
dishonest	O
?	O
M.	O
M.	O
Coone	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
always	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
;	O
I	O
liv	O
'd	O
with	O
her	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
as	O
this	O
happened	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
230	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Wm	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
He	O
stood	O
also	O
charg	O
'd	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquisition	O
for	O
manslaughter	O
,	O
May	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
John	B-pers
Dav	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
,	O
I	O
Windsor	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
May	O
last	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Davidson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Windsor	O
?	O
Davidson	O
.	O
My	O
partner	O
Wm	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
for	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
installation	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
coming	O
from	O
Windsor	O
on	O
the	O
7	O
th	O
of	O
May	O
,	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
hundred	O
yards	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
10	O
mile	O
stone	O
on	O
Hounslow	B-place
heath	I-place
,	O
we	O
overtook	O
a	O
waggon	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
leather	O
to	O
Eaton	O
they	O
were	O
returning	O
empty	O
,	O
we	O
ask	O
'd	O
them	O
to	O
give	O
us	O
a	O
lift	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
may	O
were	O
there	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Davidson	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
4	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
David	B-pers
Tooth	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lomas	I-pers
,	O
the	O
Deceased	O
and	O
I.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
happened	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Davidson	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
waggon	O
,	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
merry	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
overtook	O
us	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
chaise	O
marine	O
,	O
the	O
chaise	O
marine	O
went	O
by	O
us	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
high	O
as	O
I	O
can	O
guess	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
left	O
hand	O
side	O
on	O
horseback	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
nor	O
we	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
again	O
and	O
whipp	O
'd	O
our	O
horses	O
;	O
the	O
waggoner	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
?	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
again	O
a	O
2	O
d	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
whipp	O
'd	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
horses	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
turn	O
'd	O
back	O
and	O
whipp	O
'd	O
your	O
horses	O
,	O
the	O
chaise	O
marine	O
was	O
nearer	O
to	O
Hounslow	O
than	O
your	O
waggon	O
was	O
?	O
Davidson	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
chaise	O
marine	O
was	O
pretty	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
for	O
they	O
ran	O
a	O
full	O
trot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
distance	O
from	O
you	O
?	O
Davidson	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
account	O
within	O
a	O
few	O
yards	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
near	O
the	O
10	O
mile	O
stone	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
near	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
;	O
the	O
10	O
mile	O
stone	O
stands	O
about	O
a	O
100	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
exact	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
his	O
coming	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
striking	O
the	O
other	O
2	O
horses	O
,	O
what	O
happened	O
then	O
?	O
Davidson	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
ask	O
'd	O
him	O
what	O
that	O
was	O
for	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
whipp	O
'd	O
us	O
with	O
his	O
horsewhip	O
in	O
the	O
waggon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
in	O
particular	O
that	O
he	O
whipp	O
'd	O
the	O
deceased	O
?	O
Davidson	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
not	O
strike	O
at	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
particular	O
,	O
but	O
whipp	O
'd	O
who	O
he	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
he	O
whip	O
?	O
Davidson	O
.	O
He	O
whipp	O
'd	O
me	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
blow	O
to	O
light	O
upon	O
the	O
deceased	O
?	O
Davidson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
had	O
a	O
little	O
willow	O
stick	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
he	O
shook	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
deserv	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
beat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
keep	O
your	O
eye	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Davidson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
receive	O
any	O
blow	O
?	O
Davidson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
within	O
that	O
distance	O
to	O
receive	O
a	O
blow	O
?	O
Davidson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
could	O
not	O
reach	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
struck	O
him	O
.	O
Counsel	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
right	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
could	O
reach	O
the	O
deceased	O
with	O
his	O
whip	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
deceased	O
could	O
not	O
reach	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
his	O
stick	O
.	O
Davidson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
could	O
not	O
reach	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
stick	O
was	O
about	O
3	O
feet	O
long	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
whip	O
with	O
a	O
lash	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
desire	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
my	O
whip	O
(	O
a	O
messenger	O
goes	O
for	O
it	O
)	O
Davidson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
immediately	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
like	O
that	O
take	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
pull	O
'd	O
out	O
his	O
hanger	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
become	O
of	O
the	O
willow	O
