TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
21st	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
22d	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
APRIL	O
,	O
1762	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
Fourth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
FLUDYER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
IV	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1762	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
JOHN	B-pers
RYALL	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX	O
PENCE	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
whole	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
FLUDYER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
these	O
Proceedings	O
for	O
each	O
Session	O
will	O
be	O
only	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
FLUDYER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
Mansfield	O
*	O
,	O
Sir	O
Edward	B-pers
Clive	I-pers
+	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
Sidney	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
Smythe	O
||	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
++	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
~	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Woodcock	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Wynn	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Milner	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Power	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Emerton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Shelton	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Charties	I-pers
,	O
Gyles	B-pers
Turner	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Norman	I-pers
,	O
Edmund	B-pers
Mason	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Wilde	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Woodin	I-pers
,	O
a	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
a	O
Samuel	B-pers
Lane	I-pers
served	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
of	O
William	O
Ward	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Jason	I-pers
,	O
Jason	B-pers
Lofton	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Fraswell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Walter	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Whitacre	I-pers
,	O
Peter	B-pers
Hurlston	I-pers
.	O
116	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Frances	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Flood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pound	O
weight	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
April	O
12	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Penn	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
:	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
grocer	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
Monday	O
was	O
sevennight	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
ounce	O
of	O
bohea	O
tea	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
we	O
missed	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
green	O
tea	O
which	O
was	O
weighed	O
,	O
and	O
done	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
customer	O
with	O
other	O
goods	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
our	O
servant	O
after	O
her	O
,	O
who	O
brought	O
her	O
and	O
the	O
tea	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
.	O
After	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
missing	O
the	O
pound	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
sent	O
me	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
overtook	O
her	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
hundred	O
yards	O
from	O
our	O
shop	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
tea	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
got	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
and	O
mistress	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
She	O
then	O
fell	O
down	O
on	O
her	O
knees	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
pardon	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
picked	O
the	O
parcel	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
apron	O
:	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
making	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Hughes	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
not	O
making	O
a	O
hole	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
lying	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
From	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
to	O
Penn	O
:	O
Was	O
there	O
not	O
another	O
person	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Penn	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
117	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Jewen	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Chambers	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Gordon	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
soup	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
six	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Currie	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
October	O
25	O
,	O
1759.	O
Robert	B-pers
Currie	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin's-street	I-place
,	I-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
October	O
1759	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bureau	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
the	O
tankard	O
,	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
large	O
soup	O
spoon	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
kept	O
locked	O
.	O
The	O
six	O
table	O
spoons	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
case	O
with	O
some	O
knives	O
on	O
a	O
shelf	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
let	O
the	O
room	O
ready	O
furnished	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Currie	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
only	O
paid	O
for	O
the	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
these	O
things	O
there	O
last	O
?	O
Currie	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
bureau	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
time	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
1759	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
honest	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
night	O
I	O
double	O
locked	O
the	O
street	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
key	O
up	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
window	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
open	O
that	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
lamp	O
iron	O
just	O
by	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
bent	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
holding	O
by	O
it	O
to	O
let	O
himself	O
down	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
bureau	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
found	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
searched	O
for	O
him	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
described	O
in	O
the	O
Public	O
Advertiser	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
about	O
the	O
26th	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
after	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
,	O
``	O
That	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
``	O
send	O
for	O
him	O
from	O
Doncaster	O
gaol	O
,	O
and	O
secure	O
him	O
``	O
in	O
any	O
other	O
gaol	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
satisfaction	O
``	O
for	O
the	O
injury	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
``	O
sooner	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
better	O
.	O
''	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
sentenced	O
to	O
be	O
shot	O
as	O
a	O
deserter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
writing	O
?	O
Currie	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
,	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
can	O
speak	O
to	O
that	O
.	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
has	O
the	O
letter	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
who	O
could	O
direct	O
such	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
me	O
but	O
himself	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Savoy	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
last	O
fast	O
day	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
here	O
mentioned	O
:	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Currie	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
October	O
1759	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
candle	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
the	O
bureau	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
lock	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
mug	O
,	O
and	O
soup	O
spoon	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
together	O
:	O
the	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
case	O
on	O
a	O
shelf	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
saw	O
me	O
examine	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
locked	O
up	O
the	O
case	O
which	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
the	O
key	O
which	O
used	O
to	O
hang	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Our	O
dwelling-house	O
door	O
was	O
double	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
other	O
way	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
that	O
door	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
was	O
up	O
first	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
irons	O
ready	O
against	O
the	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
(	O
the	O
room	O
above	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
)	O
he	O
laid	O
up	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
,	O
his	O
door	O
stood	O
a	O
jar	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
bureau	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
window	O
open	O
over	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lamp	O
iron	O
pulled	O
down	O
.	O
He	O
might	O
go	O
from	O
that	O
window	O
upon	O
the	O
leads	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
lamp	O
iron	O
get	O
down	O
easy	O
;	O
there	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
a	O
living	O
soul	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
but	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
letter	O
your	O
husband	O
speaks	O
of	O
?	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Currie	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
own	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
heard	O
him	O
dispute	O
with	O
another	O
man	O
who	O
could	O
write	O
best	O
.	O
The	O
contents	O
of	O
the	O
letter	O
were	O
,	O
if	O
my	O
husband	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
from	O
that	O
gaol	O
to	O
any	O
other	O
of	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
prisons	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
the	O
things	O
again	O
,	O
or	O
else	O
satisfaction	O
for	O
the	O
injury	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
us	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
acknowledge	O
I	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
when	O
before	O
justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
they	O
speak	O
of	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
118	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
glass	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Anthony	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
and	O
secretly	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
April	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
Anthony	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
a	O
lecture	O
:	O
as	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
from	O
St.	B-place
Dunstan	I-place
's	I-place
church	I-place
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
four	O
men	O
hustled	O
me	O
in	O
betwixt	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
watch	O
jerk	O
'd	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
gone	O
.	O
Who	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
upon	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
move	O
off	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
four	O
that	O
you	O
mention	O
?	O
Andrews	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
:	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
dodged	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
between	O
the	O
coaches	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
ran	O
down	O
Fleet-street	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
calling	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Fetter-lane	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
him	O
two	O
men	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
immediately	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
]	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
lecture	O
at	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
that	O
evening	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
cry	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
running	O
.	O
I	O
stopped	O
him	O
near	O
Fetter-lane	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Andrews	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
yours	O
,	O
sir	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
immediately	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
and	O
another	O
person	O
held	O
him	O
till	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
fetched	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
he	O
said	O
necessity	O
drove	O
him	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bodington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
taken	O
into	O
custody	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
strange	O
thing	O
you	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
honest	O
;	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
watch	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
he	O
had	O
ever	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
St.	O
Dunstan	O
's	O
Church	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
people	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
church	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
past	O
;	O
I	O
turned	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
mob	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
hanging	O
by	O
my	O
button	O
;	O
it	O
knocked	O
against	O
my	O
thigh	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
coaches	O
,	O
and	O
run	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
watch	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
yours	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
immediately	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
119	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
the	O
wife	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Denman	I-pers
,	O
February	O
20	O
.	O
*	O
Sarah	B-pers
Denman	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
last	O
,	O
near	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
pots	O
(	O
he	O
keeps	O
an	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
served	O
us	O
with	O
beer	O
)	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
my	O
husband	O
was	O
come	O
home	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
expect	O
him	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
or	O
day	O
after	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
particular	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
and	O
tore	O
me	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
from	O
one	O
place	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
he	O
forced	O
me	O
upon	O
a	O
chair	O
by	O
clapping	O
his	O
knee	O
upon	O
my	O
belly	O
;	O
he	O
confined	O
both	O
my	O
hands	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
got	O
his	O
ends	O
of	O
me	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
concerned	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
by	O
force	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
had	O
four	O
children	O
.	O
Council	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
be	O
more	O
particular	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
carnal	O
knowledge	O
of	O
my	O
body	O
to	O
all	O
intents	O
and	O
purposes	O
.	O
I	O
come	O
here	O
to	O
say	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
resist	O
him	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
all	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
resist	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
all	O
in	O
his	O
power	O
to	O
keep	O
his	O
mouth	O
over	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
prevent	O
my	O
speaking	O
or	O
crying	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
stay	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
He	O
staid	O
but	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
while	O
after	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
three	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
application	O
made	O
to	O
you	O
afterwards	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
would	O
acquaint	O
my	O
husband	O
with	O
it	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
sent	O
three	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
they	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
make	O
this	O
affair	O
up	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
last	O
two	O
,	O
one	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Gofton	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
Doctor	O
Bare	B-pers
in	O
Nightingale	O
lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
them	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
th	O
e	O
prisoner	O
himself	O
make	O
application	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
spoke	O
to	O
him	O
since	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
with	O
you	O
when	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
came	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
Two	O
women	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
White	I-pers
and	O
Isabella	O
Bowling	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
cross	O
examination	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
19	O
years	O
-	O
she	O
cried	O
out	O
as	O
loud	O
as	O
possible	O
for	O
help	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
-	O
that	O
she	O
told	O
her	O
husband	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
-	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Plunket	O
the	O
attorney	O
came	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
made	O
affidavit	O
of	O
it	O
-	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
indictment	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
-	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
apply	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
other	O
person	O
,	O
to	O
propose	O
if	O
a	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
were	O
paid	O
there	O
should	O
be	O
no	O
prosecution	O
-	O
that	O
she	O
never	O
consented	O
to	O
take	O
any	O
sum	O
of	O
money	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
stop	O
the	O
prosecution	O
-	O
that	O
the	O
court	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
is	O
no	O
thoroughfare	O
-	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
keeps	O
an	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Norris's-court	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Baldwin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
made	O
application	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
account	O
to	O
Sarah	B-pers
Denman	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
send	O
you	O
?	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
discourse	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
his	O
brother	O
and	O
one	O
Mr.	O
Baker	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
his	O
brother	O
live	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Baldwin	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
intirely	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
charge	O
against	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
is	O
done	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
extort	O
money	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
otherwise	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
S.	O
Denman	O
.	O
Explain	O
the	O
situation	O
of	O
the	O
chair	O
on	O
which	O
you	O
say	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
done	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
chairs	O
standing	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
hardly	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
partly	O
in	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
an	O
elbow	O
or	O
a	O
common	O
chair	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
A	O
common	O
chair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
your	O
husband	O
owe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
any	O
money	O
?	O
Denman	O
.	O
He	O
does	O
,	O
a	O
trifle	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Waite	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
they	O
are	O
wainscot	O
houses	O
;	O
we	O
can	O
very	O
well	O
hear	O
common	O
conversation	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
as	O
we	O
sit	O
in	O
our	O
own	O
,	O
partly	O
any	O
thing	O
they	O
say	O
.	O
My	O
mother	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
this	O
same	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
it	O
by	O
my	O
child	O
being	O
christened	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
the	O
least	O
crying	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
we	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
heard	O
none	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Macone	I-pers
her	O
mother	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purport	O
.	O
Sarah	O
Hall	O
,	O
her	O
nurse	O
,	O
deposed	O
she	O
was	O
absent	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mother	O
supplied	O
her	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
easy	O
to	O
hear	O
common	O
talk	O
or	O
walking	O
about	O
in	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
when	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Waite	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
crying	O
out	O
,	O
which	O
might	O
easily	O
be	O
heard	O
had	O
it	O
been	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
married	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
well	O
with	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
industrious	O
man	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Powell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
any	O
calling	O
out	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
heard	O
none	O
:	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
told	O
her	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
used	O
her	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
up	O
her	O
body	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
answered	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
at	O
all	O
:	O
She	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
did	O
not	O
tell	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
ravished	O
her	O
?	O
she	O
answered	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
no	O
man	O
can	O
force	O
a	O
woman	O
without	O
she	O
be	O
willing	O
:	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
kiss	O
and	O
play	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
no	O
farther	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Howell	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
in	O
Norris's-court	O
within	O
four	O
doors	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
plate	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
is	O
heard	O
from	O
one	O
house	O
to	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
if	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
had	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
.	O
Susanna	B-pers
Titcome	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
lived	O
within	O
one	O
door	O
of	O
being	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
;	O
that	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
called	O
out	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
heard	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
heard	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Bare	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
apothecary	O
and	O
surgeon	O
;	O
upon	O
hearing	O
this	O
charge	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
this	O
affair	O
stood	O
between	O
her	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
meeting	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
the	O
officer	O
's	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
the	O
meeting	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
your	O
consent	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
Mr.	O
Plunket	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
would	O
pay	O
forty	O
pounds	O
,	O
you	O
would	O
stop	O
all	O
prosecution	O
;	O
is	O
that	O
true	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gofton	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
to	O
,	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Plunket	O
your	O
attorney	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
paid	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gofton	O
said	O
,	O
suppose	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
that	O
money	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
prosecute	O
him	O
hereafter	O
?	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
it	O
shall	O
be	O
all	O
void	O
for	O
ever	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
called	O
down	O
a	O
woman	O
:	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
without	O
your	O
husband	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Bare	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	O
,	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
send	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
Bare	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
nobedy	O
had	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
asked	O
this	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
a	O
newborn	O
babe	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Gofton	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Bare	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
go	O
?	O
Gofton	O
.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
beckon	O
to	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Clark	O
had	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
lay	O
in	O
his	O
way	O
to	O
get	O
somebody	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
her	O
consent	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
for	O
forty	O
pounds	O
:	O
she	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
her	O
attorney	O
power	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
mention	O
this	O
to	O
Bare	O
?	O
Gofton	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bare	O
asked	O
her	O
at	O
going	O
in	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
did	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
pretty	O
well	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
how	O
does	O
this	O
affair	O
stand	O
between	O
you	O
and	O
Clark	O
?	O
Said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
meeting	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Hill	O
's	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
by	O
your	O
consent	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
Mr.	O
Plunket	O
was	O
her	O
attorney	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
made	O
a	O
demand	O
of	O
forty	O
pounds	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
by	O
your	O
consent	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
made	O
any	O
other	O
proposal	O
since	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
stand	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
paid	O
to	O
you	O
or	O
your	O
attorney	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
money	O
enough	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
it	O
be	O
paid	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
mean	O
to	O
prosecute	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
then	O
there	O
will	O
be	O
an	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
.	O
Then	O
a	O
woman	O
called	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
without	O
the	O
consent	O
of	O
your	O
husband	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Plunket	O
had	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
talked	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
give	O
her	O
a	O
farthing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Rogers	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Clark	O
's	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bare	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
;	O
he	O
joked	O
about	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
made	O
up	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
care	O
to	O
hurt	O
a	O
hair	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
sad	O
thing	O
a	O
man	O
should	O
be	O
kept	O
from	O
his	O
family	O
so	O
.	O
She	O
replied	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
family	O
many	O
days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
mention	O
any	O
terms	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
say	O
what	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
?	O
Rogers	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Booth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
with	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
of	O
my	O
shopmates	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
ten	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
about	O
as	O
usual	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
him	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
February	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
pay	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
about	O
20	O
minutes	O
after	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
till	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
11	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
very	O
busy	O
with	O
his	O
customers	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
seem	O
in	O
any	O
confusion	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
struggling	O
with	O
any	O
body	O
?	O
Wm	B-pers
Stapleton	I-pers
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
20	O
years	O
;	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stoaks	I-pers
,	O
14	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Lakehorn	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
his	O
son	O
in-law	O
apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Anderson	O
,	O
11	O
;	O
William	B-pers
Warren	I-pers
,	O
20	O
;	O
and	O
Martin	B-pers
Long	I-pers
about	O
six	O
years	O
;	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
,	O
well-behaved	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
120.	O
Mace	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
chain	O
for	O
a	O
coral	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
the	O
younger	O
,	O
Sept.	O
27	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Upon	O
an	O
affidavit	O
being	O
read	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
that	O
proper	O
notice	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
of	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
surrender	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
circumstances	O
appearing	O
relating	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
behaviour	O
,	O
a	O
copy	O
of	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
granted	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
121	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nailer	I-pers
.	O
+	O
Thomas	B-pers
Nailer	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
about	O
nine	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
honest	O
by	O
being	O
out	O
one	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
laying	O
out	O
about	O
12	O
l.	O
in	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
received	O
any	O
wages	O
of	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Lincoln's-Inn-Fields	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
Mr.	O
Adams	O
to	O
send	O
his	O
boy	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
ten	O
shilling	O
tea	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
marks	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
years	O
they	O
were	O
coined	O
,	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
the	O
boy	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
they	O
marked	O
?	O
Nailer	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
king	O
George	B-pers
the	O
First	O
's	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
with	O
SS	O
.	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
cut	O
one	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
S	O
off	O
,	O
the	O
dates	O
were	O
1723	O
:	O
a	O
king	O
Charles	B-pers
the	O
Second	O
's	O
sixpence	O
,	O
date	O
1697	O
:	O
the	O
other	O
shilling	O
was	O
a	O
a	O
plain	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
marked	O
with	O
a	O
cut	O
on	O
the	O
edge	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
went	O
and	O
bought	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
tea	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
that	O
money	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
and	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
and	O
a	O
sixpence	O
of	O
the	O
marked	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
shillings	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
said	O
nothing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
but	O
kept	O
a	O
stricter	O
eye	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
discharge	O
him	O
:	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
my	O
sister	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
strict	O
charge	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
when	O
the	O
boy	O
came	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
trembled	O
and	O
could	O
not	O
move	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
given	O
him	O
50	O
l.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
owe	O
him	O
any	O
wages	O
?	O
Nailer	O
.	O
I	O
owed	O
him	O
5	O
l.	O
14	O
s.	O
A	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
Spotted	O
Dog	O
,	O
in	O
Blackamoor-street	O
,	O
owned	O
she	O
received	O
sugar	O
of	O
him	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
.	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Welstead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
Blackamoor-street	O
,	O
Clare	O
market	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
four	O
pounds	O
of	O
sugar	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
different	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
paid	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
wipe	O
off	O
his	O
score	O
it	O
was	O
sugar	O
at	O
8	O
d.	O
a	O
pound	O
.	O
Judith	B-pers
Murphy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
.	O
I	O
washed	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
shirts	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
seven-pence	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
tea	O
and	O
a	O
quartern	O
of	O
soap	O
,	O
which	O
came	O
to	O
six-pence	O
halfpenny	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
wronged	O
my	O
master	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
:	O
I	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
for	O
the	O
tea	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
as	O
lief	O
put	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
pay	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
122	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
South	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
metal	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
2	O
seals	O
set	O
in	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
steel	O
chain	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Walter	B-pers
Vane	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
March	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
Walter	B-pers
Vane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Covent-garden	B-place
play-house	I-place
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
watch	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
seated	O
in	O
the	O
gallery	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
.	O
A	O
gentleman	O
that	O
sat	O
next	O
me	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
but	O
before	O
I	O
had	O
laid	O
the	O
affair	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
my	O
brother	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
my	O
watch	O
was	O
at	O
justice	O
Welch	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Galendine	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
produced	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
]	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
watch	O
that	O
was	O
picked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Galendine	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
going	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
gallery	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Abbot	O
,	O
have	O
an	O
eye	O
to	O
that	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
mistrust	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Abbot	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
goes	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Noaks	O
give	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
watch	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
almost	O
in	O
Hart-street	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
Noaks	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
rescued	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
gets	O
off	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
stop	O
you	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
d	O
-	O
n	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
rascal	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
stop	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
knock	O
you	O
down	O
:	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Abbot	O
came	O
up	O
;	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
put	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Abbot	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Hen	O
.	O
Abbot	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
leading	O
to	O
the	O
crown	O
gallery	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Galendine	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
would	O
give	O
an	O
eye	O
to	O
those	O
men	O
,	O
meaning	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
one	O
Noaks	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
both	O
come	O
down	O
;	O
they	O
passed	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Galendine	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
goes	O
the	O
two	O
men	O
;	O
he	O
ran	O
after	O
them	O
and	O
secured	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
South	O
run	O
up	O
towards	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
scuffle	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Before	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
got	O
off	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
people	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
there	O
lies	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
upon	O
a	O
bench	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
put	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
South	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Abbott	O
you	O
know	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
you	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
never	O
did	O
me	O
any	O
.	O
We	O
secured	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
an	O
order	O
about	O
some	O
holland	O
's	O
gin	O
A	O
relation	O
of	O
mine	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
oratorio	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
;	O
they	O
asked	O
a	O
crown	O
to	O
go	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
promiscuously	O
by	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
quarrel	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
pushed	O
his	O
hand	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
watch	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
Mr.	O
Galendine	O
said	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
wanted	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
and	O
went	O
contentedly	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
once	O
kept	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
in	O
covent-garden	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Wm	B-pers
Holloway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
7	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
once	O
kept	O
the	O
Globe	O
,	O
Covent-garden	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
regular	O
honest	O
man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Can	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
2	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
See	O
No	O
.	O
67.	O
in	O
Sir	O
Matthew	B-pers
Blackiston	I-pers
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
123	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Rebecca	I-pers
Matthews	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
repeating	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
yellow	O
sattin	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
pillow-case	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Jacob	B-pers
Nathan	I-pers
Moses	I-pers
,	O
April	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Jacob	B-pers
Nathan	I-pers
Moses	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
my	O
compting-house	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
servants	O
say	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
gone	O
that	O
hung	O
at	O
my	O
bed	O
's	O
head	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
of	O
opinion-that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
foolish	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
did	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
before	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
.	O
Ziphrah	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
she	O
delivered	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
watch	O
that	O
I	O
wear	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
foolish	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
a	O
shirt	O
of	O
my	O
husband	O
's	O
we	O
found	O
all	O
pinned	O
in	O
a	O
pillow	O
case	O
to	O
her	O
back	O
under	O
her	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
sattin	O
gown	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
under	O
her	O
own	O
gown	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
all	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
124	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
stone	O
seal	O
set	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
April	O
7	O
++	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
fleet-market	B-place
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
lord-mayor	O
with	O
the	O
aldermen	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
majesty	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
my	O
watch	O
stir	O
in	O
my	O
fob	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
greatly	O
surprized	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
without	O
any	O
assistance	O
of	O
mine	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
person	O
that	O
pulled	O
it	O
out	O
,	O
twisted	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
hand	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
collar	O
.	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
denied	O
it	O
with	O
very	O
bad	O
language	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
He	O
threw	O
it	O
down	O
upon	O
the	O
stones	O
.	O
While	O
I	O
stooped	O
for	O
it	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
soon	O
taken	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Orange	I-pers
assisted	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
market	O
again	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bodington	O
the	O
constable	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Pattison	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
noon	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
till	O
taken	O
again	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
lodged	O
in	O
Wood-street	O
Compter	O
till	O
next	O
day	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
aldermen	O
.	O
I	O
swore	O
there	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
now	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Orange	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
upon	O
Fleet-bridge	O
leaning	O
on	O
a	O
post	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Pattison	O
was	O
behind	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
drop	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
between	O
us	O
three	O
.	O
He	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pattison	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
first	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
him	O
not	O
fifty	O
yards	O
from	O
where	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Pattison	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bodington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
having	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
hand-cuffs	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
used	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
having	O
once	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
Newgate	O
*	O
before	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
alderman	O
,	O
the	O
watch	O
might	O
hang	O
by	O
his	O
button	O
.	O
*	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Isaac	O
Hall	O
,	O
otherwise	O
Howse	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
III	O
.	O
in	O
Sir	O
Matthew	O
Blackiston	O
's	O
mayoralty	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
carr-black	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
T.	O
Hurnall	O
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
He	O
was	O
cist	O
for	O
transportation	O
,	O
but	O
pardoned	O
on	O
condition	O
or	O
serving	O
as	O
a	O
soldier	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
125	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Uzriel	B-pers
Baruch	I-pers
,	O
of	O
Shoemaker-row	B-place
,	O
butcher	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Rockom	B-pers
Polock	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lopaz	I-pers
not	O
taken	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
two	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Lyon	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
black	O
petticoat	O
lined	O
with	O
Persian	O
silk	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
red	O
sattin	O
waistcoat	O
laced	O
with	O
silver-lace	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
one	O
damask	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
22	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
brown	O
woollen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
paper	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
four	O
iron	O
keys	O
and	O
a	O
ring	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Lyon	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
++	O
Lyon	O
Marks	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
those	O
goods	O
and	O
more	O
than	O
are	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
nobody	O
more	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
but	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
my	O
son	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
bed	O
sleeping	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
came	O
,	O
halloo	O
!	O
halloo	O
!	O
what	O
's	O
the	O
matter	O
here	O
;	O
why	O
are	O
all	O
these	O
cloathes	O
thrown	O
about	O
?	O
This	O
was	O
exactly	O
at	O
four	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
Some	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
My	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
shelves	O
almost	O
stripped	O
.	O
My	O
son	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
fasten	O
your	O
door	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Marks	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
Mrs.	O
Alexander	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
some	O
things	O
she	O
had	O
were	O
not	O
my	O
goods	O
;	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stocking	O
breeches	O
and	O
a	O
laced	O
hat	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
her	O
maid	O
had	O
seen	O
them	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lopaz	O
's	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Abraham	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
his	O
advice	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
heard	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
at	O
Monsanto	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Spencer	O
the	O
evidence	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
all	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
nothing	O
there	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
son	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
master	O
butcher	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
over	O
against	O
us	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
coats	O
and	O
waistcoats	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
had	O
just	O
begun	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
breeches	O
.	O
The	O
pin	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
is	O
lost	O
;	O
to	O
this	O
minute	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
;	O
the	O
lock	O
was	O
not	O
broke	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
make	O
every	O
thing	O
right	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
could	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
do	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
helped	O
.	O
Aaron	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
can	O
give	O
the	O
best	O
account	O
how	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
.	O
Last-Saturday	O
was	O
three	O
weeks	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lopaz	I-pers
's	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
-	O
[	O
At	O
the	O
desire	O
of	O
the	O
jury	O
all	O
the	O
evidences	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
were	O
put	O
out	O
of	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
in	O
by	O
one	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
]	O
Spencer	O
.	O
We	O
met	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
he	O
spoke	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
earn	O
any	O
money	O
to	O
night	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
in	O
what	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
at	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
by	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
'll	O
tell	O
you	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Rose	O
and	O
Crown	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
Rockom	O
Polock	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
was	O
eleven	O
we	O
all	O
three	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
.	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
He	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
or	O
at	O
his	O
door	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
the	O
pin	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
key	O
dropped	O
out	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
shutter	O
down	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
sash	O
of	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
back	O
and	O
opened	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
bundles	O
and	O
bundles	O
of	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
them	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
shop	O
all	O
scattered	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
bed	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
and	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
and	O
bundled	O
all	O
up	O
in	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
all	O
of	O
us	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
Moses	B-pers
Baruch	I-pers
's	O
:	O
He	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
married	O
to	O
his	O
daughter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
does	O
Moses	B-pers
Baruch	I-pers
live	O
from	O
his	O
shop	O
?	O
Spencer	O
.	O
About	O
four	O
minutes	O
walk	O
.	O
Moses	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
them	O
be	O
there	O
till	O
after	O
day	O
light	O
;	O
if	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
before	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
turn	O
them	O
all	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
left	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
a	O
worse	O
hobble	O
than	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
Philip	B-pers
Abraham	I-pers
's	O
,	O
perhaps	O
he	O
will	O
buy	O
them	O
or	O
keep	O
them	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
there	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
for	O
him	O
which	O
he	O
believed	O
would	O
do	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
who	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
butcher	O
name	O
Baruch	O
.	O
Rockom	O
Polock	O
had	O
one	O
bundle	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
carried	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
Abrahams	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
perfectly	O
guess	O
where	O
they	O
came	O
from	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
lend	O
you	O
money	O
to	O
buy	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
have	O
no	O
concern	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
Then	O
coming	O
along	O
Houndsditch	O
he	O
pitched	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
steps	O
,	O
till	O
we	O
went	O
back	O
for	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
Bundles	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Duke's-place	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
to	O
Moses	B-pers
Caravallo	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
wanted	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
room	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
Goodman's-fields	O
;	O
Caravallo	O
gave	O
him	O
no	O
answer	O
When	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
we	O
may	O
as	O
well	O
drop	O
them	O
,	O
for	O
we	O
can	O
not	O
go	O
lugging	O
them	O
about	O
the	O
streets	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
open	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
throw	O
them	O
in	O
again	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
three	O
bundles	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
in	O
the	O
hurry	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
left	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
the	O
watchman	O
being	O
coming	O
his	O
beat	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
blankets	O
away	O
;	O
we	O
also	O
left	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
Breeches	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
upon	O
Lopaz	O
's	O
stairs	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
now	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Lopaz	O
and	O
Polock	O
took	O
two	O
coats	O
,	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
a	O
velvet	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
sheets	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
[	O
Here	O
is	O
that	O
sheet	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
]	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Monsanto	I-pers
;	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
threw	O
them	O
in	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
from	O
work	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Spencer	O
,	O
what	O
must	O
I	O
do	O
in	O
this	O
affair	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
than	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
whole	O
affair	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
We	O
were	O
examined	O
before	O
my	O
lord-mayor	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
lord	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
sheet	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
My	O
lord	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
lay	O
with	O
one	O
sheet	O
or	O
two	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
with	O
one	O
because	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
Rhumatism	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sweated	O
pretty	O
much	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
servant	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
a	O
boy	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
where	O
he	O
lay	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
and	O
bed	O
with	O
his	O
Master	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
laid	O
with	O
one	O
sheet	O
or	O
two	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
two	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
sheets	O
were	O
produced	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
fellows	O
.	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Monsanto	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
it	O
than	O
that	O
two	O
coats	O
,	O
two	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
velvet	O
cloth	O
were	O
thrown	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
by	O
Aaron	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
and	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lopaz	I-pers
.	O
Spencer	O
worked	O
at	O
the	O
passover-cakes	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
work	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
flung	O
them	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
are	O
they	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
?	O
Spencer	O
said	O
let	O
them	O
alone	O
;	O
I	O
'll	O
warrant	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
come	O
to	O
no	O
harm	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Spencer	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
drowsy	O
,	O
go	O
and	O
make	O
my	O
dough	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
looked	O
over	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
on	O
my	O
bed	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
work	O
,	O
at	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
Spencer	O
said	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
ruined	O
and	O
am	O
afraid	O
to	O
confess	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
to	O
confess	O
.	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
say	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
those	O
things	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
belonged	O
to	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Marks	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
of	O
his	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
my	O
key	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
staff	O
and	O
broke	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
brought	O
out	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
Marks	O
,	O
owned	O
them	O
immediately	O
.	O
Coleman	B-pers
Solomon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Marks	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Abrahams	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
and	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
Abraham	B-pers
Lopaz	I-pers
and	O
Spencer	O
.	O
Lopaz	O
is	O
a	O
shoe	O
blacker	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
immediately	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
to	O
several	O
houses	O
:	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Gabriel	B-pers
Monsanto	I-pers
's	O
house	O
we	O
met	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
we	O
had	O
intelligence	O
that	O
some	O
goods	O
were	O
lodged	O
there	O
;	O
let	O
us	O
know	O
and	O
no	O
harm	O
can	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
seemed	O
a	O
little	O
concerned	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
take	O
me	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
shall	O
certainly	O
be	O
murdered	O
by	O
the	O
gang	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
very	O
bad	O
people	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
Spencer	O
and	O
Lopaz	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
:	O
we	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
backwards	O
;	O
he	O
opened	O
the	O
casement	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
us	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
owned	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Solomon	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
a	O
bad	O
character	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
now	O
he	O
is	O
innocent	O
.	O
Spencer	O
at	O
first	O
said	O
,	O
Lopaz	O
and	O
Polock	O
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
breaking	O
open	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
lent	O
them	O
a	O
knife	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
concerned	O
in	O
breaking	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
son	O
say	O
there	O
would	O
be	O
40	O
l.	O
reward	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
ticket	O
on	O
their	O
conviction	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
.	O
This	O
constable	O
threatened	O
to	O
get	O
me	O
committed	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
rigour	O
of	O
the	O
law	O
.	O
Spencer	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
call	O
Abraham	B-pers
Baruch	I-pers
;	O
he	O
can	O
explain	O
this	O
matter	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Baruch	I-pers
.	O
When	O
Spencer	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
word	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Abrahams	I-pers
.	O
The	O
morning	O
after	O
this	O
thing	O
happened	O
Mr.	O
Marks	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
a	O
considerable	O
quantity	O
of	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
Spencer	O
and	O
Lopaz	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
people	O
that	O
did	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
at	O
Lopaz	O
's	O
steps	O
were	O
found	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watchman	O
thought	O
Spencer	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
Lopaz	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
several	O
houses	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
Monsanto	O
:	O
we	O
told	O
him	O
we	O
mistrusted	O
some	O
things	O
being	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
some	O
things	O
put	O
in	O
by	O
Spencer	O
and	O
Lopaz	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
they	O
would	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
being	O
afraid	O
of	O
being	O
killed	O
by	O
the	O
gang	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
had	O
given	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
seeing	O
three	O
men	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Spencer	O
said	O
Lopass	O
and	O
Polock	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
knife	O
to	O
break	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
carried	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Spencer	O
.	O
This	O
evidence	O
is	O
brother-in-law	O
to	O
Moses	B-pers
Baruch	I-pers
;	O
I	O
told	O
this	O
man	O
,	O
Baruch	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Abrahams	O
.	O
When	O
Spencer	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
absented	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
breaking	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
the	O
candle	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
say	O
this	O
at	O
first	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
Spencer	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
kept	O
company	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
or	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
him	O
no	O
other	O
way	O
than	O
by	O
living	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
I	O
disdain	O
such	O
company	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
witnesses	O
here	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
hundreds	O
of	O
pounds	O
to	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Orwood	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
quarters	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Martin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ten	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
sober	O
young	O
fellow	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
deserves	O
that	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
paid	O
his	O
father	O
through	O
his	O
hands	O
many	O
hundreds	O
of	O
pounds	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Till	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
pretty	O
near	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
sober	O
,	O
hard-working	O
young	O
fellow	O
:	O
he	O
has	O
dealt	O
with	O
me	O
for	O
pounds	O
and	O
pounds	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
10	O
or	O
14	O
l.	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Marks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
of	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Robert	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
dealt	O
with	O
him	O
for	O
pounds	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wrench	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
dealings	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
Abraham	B-pers
Riatie	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
industrious	O
,	O
sober	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
butcher	O
to	O
me	O
16	O
years	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Rickaby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
two	O
years	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Fonseca	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
15	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
hard-working	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
lives	O
near	O
me	O
.	O
Solomon	B-pers
Cordosa	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
his	O
master	O
to	O
teach	O
him	O
Hebrew	O
;	O
he	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
two	O
days	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
in	O
comparison	O
;	O
he	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
set	O
up	O
for	O
himself	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Devall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
years	O
;	O
his	O
character	O
is	O
as	O
good	O
as	O
any	O
man	O
's	O
can	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
months	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Moses	B-pers
Ebeau	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
sober	O
honest	O
young	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
126	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Treadway	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
April	O
7	O
||	O
.	O
Eliz	B-pers
Treadway	I-pers
the	O
elder	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Treadway	I-pers
is	O
my	O
daughter	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
.	O
My	O
child	O
complained	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
this	O
month	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
sore	O
.	O
I	O
examined	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
running	O
,	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
venereal	O
disease	O
.	O
The	O
parts	O
were	O
swelled	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Could	O
you	O
judge	O
that	O
her	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
entered	O
?	O
E.	O
Treadway	O
.	O
The	O
midwife	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
entered	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
think	O
within	O
myself	O
,	O
some	O
man	O
had	O
entered	O
her	O
body	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
London	O
when	O
it	O
happened	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
one	O
door	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
child	O
used	O
sometimes	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
My	O
child	O
is	O
five	O
years	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
old	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Treadway	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
father	O
to	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gardener	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Benedict	B-pers
Duddle	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
brought	O
the	O
child	O
to	O
me	O
last	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'ennight	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
venereal	O
shankers	O
on	O
the	O
labia	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
swelling	O
upon	O
each	O
groin	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
ulcer	O
of	O
matter	O
issuing	O
through	O
the	O
virginale	O
:	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
all	O
circumstances	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
entered	O
her	O
body	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
talked	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
how	O
could	O
shankers	O
come	O
since	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
?	O
I	O
apprehend	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
venereal	O
disease	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
the	O
venereal	O
disorder	O
about	O
his	O
private	O
parts	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
only	O
to	O
attempt	O
it	O
,	O
would	O
not	O
there	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
symptoms	O
?	O
Duddle	O
.	O
Certainly	O
he	O
entered	O
her	O
,	O
for	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
laceration	O
on	O
the	O
parts	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
think	O
shankers	O
could	O
come	O
between	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
and	O
the	O
Sunday	O
?	O
Duddle	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
think	O
they	O
could	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
examine	O
me	O
,	O
whether	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
venereal	O
disorder	O
or	O
not	O
?	O
Duddle	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
examine	O
him	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
to	O
examine	O
those	O
things	O
,	O
except	O
we	O
take	O
a	O
proper	O
catheter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
infected	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
have	O
given	O
her	O
shankers	O
in	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
would	O
there	O
not	O
have	O
been	O
a	O
running	O
on	O
him	O
?	O
Duddle	O
.	O
I	O
might	O
not	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
,	O
except	O
I	O
had	O
pressed	O
the	O
instrument	O
along	O
the	O
said	O
tube	O
.	O
The	O
Child	O
examined	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
sworn	O
.	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
carry	O
my	O
grandmother	O
's	O
shoe	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
He	O
put	O
me	O
upon	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
shop	O
below	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
do	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
not	O
tell	O
my	O
mamma	O
.	O
He	O
laid	O
me	O
down	O
on	O
my	O
back	O
and	O
hurt	O
my	O
groin	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
cock	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
he	O
doing	O
this	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
put	O
any	O
thing	O
into	O
you	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
cry	O
out	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
not	O
generally	O
cry	O
out	O
when	O
you	O
are	O
hurt	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
shed	O
tears	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
not	O
frighted	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
after	O
this	O
did	O
you	O
complain	O
and	O
tell	O
your	O
mother	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
my	O
mamma	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
long	O
that	O
was	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
do	O
any	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
your	O
cloaths	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
He	O
pulled	O
up	O
my	O
petticoats	O
when	O
he	O
laid	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
table	O
.	O
But	O
he	O
laid	O
me	O
cross	O
his	O
lap	O
after	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
he	O
put	O
something	O
into	O
your	O
body	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
sure	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Was	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Child	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
Mrs.	O
Barnard	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
grand-mother	O
in	O
another	O
room	O
,	O
not	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Mother	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
girl	O
complain	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
The	O
Mother	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
way	O
she	O
does	O
now	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
complain	O
before	O
you	O
asked	O
her	O
?	O
Mother	O
.	O
She	O
complained	O
of	O
her	O
groin	O
being	O
sore	O
first	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
out	O
of	O
spite	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
deliver	O
the	O
shoes	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
them	O
without	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Barnard	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
over	O
head	O
when	O
the	O
child	O
came	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
shoes	O
to	O
be	O
mended	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
or	O
heard	O
any	O
disturbance	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
detained	O
to	O
be	O
tried	O
at	O
Hicks's-hall	O
for	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
with	O
an	O
intent	O
to	O
commit	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
the	O
child	O
.	O
127	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Isabella	B-pers
Denston	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sallsbury	B-pers
Purrier	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sallsbury	O
,	O
March	O
13	O
||	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Kelmer	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Purrier	O
is	O
a	O
linen	O
draper	O
,	O
in	O
Castle-street	B-place
,	I-place
Leicester-fields	I-place
:	O
I	O
am	O
journeyman	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
some	O
lawns	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
from	O
a	O
customer	O
of	O
ours	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Broomfield	O
,	O
that	O
lives	O
about	O
five	O
doors	O
from	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
come	O
herself	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
.	O
As	O
she	O
was	O
looking	O
over	O
the	O
pieces	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
fearful	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
please	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
her	O
carry	O
it	O
to	O
shew	O
her	O
.	O
In	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
another	O
piece	O
.	O
I	O
acquainted	O
my	O
master	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sent	O
me	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Broomfield	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
she	O
never	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
justice	O
Cox	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
lawn	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
[	O
He	O
produced	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
lawn	O
.	O
]	O
One	O
she	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
have	O
to	O
carry	O
to	O
shew	O
Mrs.	O
Broomfield	O
.	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Morris	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
house-keeper	O
to	O
George	B-pers
Drummond	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
Palace-yard	O
,	O
Westminster	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
lawn	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
our	O
house-maid	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Skilton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
house-maid	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Drummond	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
lawn	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
it	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
but	O
very	O
little	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
when	O
I	O
first	O
knew	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
your	O
lordship	O
will	O
consider	O
my	O
condition	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
down	O
lying	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
an	O
hour	O
to	O
reckon	O
.	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
her	O
for	O
a	O
single	O
felony	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
128	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Dick	I-pers
Rice	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
yards	O
of	O
duffel	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
Manchester	O
velvet	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
fustian	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Cameron	I-pers
,	O
April	O
10	O
+	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Cameron	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holywell-street	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Clements	I-place
:	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
taylor	O
,	O
and	O
deal	O
in	O
remnants	O
of	O
cloth	O
.	O
On	O
Saturday	O
was	O
se'ennight	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
goods	O
tumbled	O
about	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
my	O
maid	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
blue	O
duffil	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
named	O
Isabella	O
Bullock	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
saw	O
Dick	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
go	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
another	O
neighbour	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
go	O
by	O
with	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
blue	O
stuff	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
a	O
cook	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Swan-alley	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
blue	O
huffily	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
six	O
yards	O
;	O
and	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
Manchester	O
velvet	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
yards	O
of	O
fustian	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
Thistle	O
and	O
Crown	O
,	O
an	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Russel-court	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
stealing	O
some	O
duffil	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
that	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
The	O
landlord	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
courted	O
him	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
days	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
Manchester	O
velvet	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
said	O
was	O
in	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
piece	O
torn	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
remnant	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
duffil	O
I	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
fustian	O
at	O
a	O
piece-broker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
named	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
in	O
White-horse-yard	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
confirmed	O
in	O
his	O
evidence	O
by	O
Rachel	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
the	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Leonard	B-pers
Holyday	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
request	O
redeemed	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Manchester	O
velvet	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
fustian	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
goods	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
]	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
,	O
who	O
came	O
from	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
in	O
Covent	O
garden	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
among	O
some	O
whores	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
spent	O
all	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
these	O
things	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Reynolds	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
for	O
14	O
s.	O
He	O
gave	O
me	O
some	O
beer	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
fustian	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
pawned	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
fetch	O
these	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
them	O
for	O
myself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
129	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joyce	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Edward	I-pers
Topping	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
linen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ockleford	I-pers
.	O
April	O
6	O
.~	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
takes	O
in	O
washing	O
.	O
The	O
handkerchiefs	O
mentioned	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
her	O
to	O
wash	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
taking	O
one	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
linen	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
employed	O
to	O
carry	O
home	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
found	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
pawned	O
by	O
her	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
.	O
Guilty	O
9	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
130	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Birk	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ralph	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
March	O
2	O
.~	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
keeps	O
the	O
White	O
Swan	O
alehouse	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
there	O
pretending	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
old	O
cloaths	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
amongst	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
an	O
opportunity	O
to	O
convey	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
in	O
her	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
131	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charlton	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
April	O
17	O
.~	O
Thomas	B-pers
Charlton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shoemaker-row	O
,	O
Black	O
friers	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
night	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
Nightingale-lane	B-place
.	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
company	O
till	O
the	O
gentleman	O
I	O
wanted	O
came	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
of	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
;	O
we	O
sat	O
and	O
drank	O
till	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
twelve	O
;	O
after	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
this	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
;	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
country	O
girl	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
apartment	O
;	O
through	O
persuasions	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
house	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
something	O
to	O
drink	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
drink	O
any	O
more	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
this	O
is	O
only	O
my	O
lower	O
apartment	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
see	O
that	O
above	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
stay	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
through	O
persuasions	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
give	O
her	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Charlton	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
stay	O
with	O
her	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
another	O
girl	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
partner	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
gave	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
the	O
shilling	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
then	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
about	O
17	O
or	O
18	O
shillings	O
.	O
She	O
saw	O
it	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
;	O
we	O
put	O
off	O
our	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
breeches	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
not	O
quite	O
under	O
the	O
pillow	O
;	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
laid	O
above	O
twenty	O
minutes	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
snatched	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
the	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
,	O
who	O
ran	O
down	O
stairs	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
not	O
having	O
any	O
thing	O
on	O
did	O
not	O
follow	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Charlton	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
come	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
care	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
and	O
then	O
took	O
a	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
under	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
pillow	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
whether	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
it	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
no	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
secured	O
and	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
justice	O
Scott	B-pers
the	O
next	O
morning	O
about	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
justice	O
saw	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
called	O
her	O
by	O
her	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
come	O
again	O
?	O
I	O
missed	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
silver	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
left	O
me	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
condition	O
was	O
you	O
in	O
for	O
liquor	O
?	O
Charlton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
drunk	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
as	O
well	O
all	O
about	O
it	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
.	O
She	O
threatened	O
to	O
cut	O
my	O
throat	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
opportunity	O
,	O
and	O
cut	O
my	O
nose	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
been	O
asleep	O
?	O
Charlton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
Charlton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
money	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
?	O
Charlton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
hand	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
woman	O
's	O
hand	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
between	O
eleven	O
and	O
twelve	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
gin	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
the	O
girl	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
sleep	O
with	O
me	O
all	O
night	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
excessively	O
immodest	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
chuse	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
him	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
down	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
the	O
constable	O
searched	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
of	O
his	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
sent	O
the	O
other	O
girl	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
for	O
six	O
weeks	O
to	O
hard	O
labour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
?	O
Charlton	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
in	O
Swan-alley	O
,	O
St.	O
Catharine	O
's	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
132	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
seat	O
and	O
five	O
curtains	O
to	O
a	O
sedan	O
chair	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Darby	B-pers
Goff	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cole	I-pers
,	O
March	O
10	O
.~	O
The	O
prosecutors	O
are	O
chairmen	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
waiting	O
in	O
Brewer	B-place
street	I-place
for	O
their	O
fare	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
March	O
;	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
to	O
screen	O
themselves	O
from	O
the	O
inclemency	O
of	O
the	O
weather	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
John's-street	O
sitting	O
together	O
at	O
the	O
step	O
of	O
a	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
behind	O
or	O
partly	O
under	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
Wilkinson	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
coachman	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
with	O
a	O
brother	O
coachman	O
;	O
was	O
got	O
a	O
little	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
As	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
saw	O
Clark	O
sitting	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
what	O
she	O
sat	O
there	O
for	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
well	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
drink	O
part	O
of	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
:	O
then	O
he	O
sat	O
down	O
by	O
her	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
or	O
six	O
minutes	O
came	O
the	O
chairmen	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
things	O
?	O
That	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
them	O
till	O
the	O
woman	O
got	O
up	O
.	O
William	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
the	O
year	O
1747	O
;	O
Francis	B-pers
Boarer	I-pers
,	O
13	O
or	O
14	O
years	O
;	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
above	O
20	O
,	O
all	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Clark	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
things	O
came	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
except	O
Wilkinson	O
brought	O
them	O
.	O
Wilkinson	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Clark	O
guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
133	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
M'Koy	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
tea	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
brass	O
candlestick	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
diaper	O
table	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Stanley	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
March	O
5	O
.	O
+	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
134	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Tims	I-pers
and	O
Alice	B-pers
Rockham	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
check	O
aprons	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
cotton	O
slip	O
for	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Alice	B-pers
Shergold	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
March	O
19	O
.	O
*	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
135	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
Zachariah	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
;	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
against	O
his	O
will	O
March	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Zachariah	O
Stevens	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
March	O
last	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wogin	O
and	O
I	O
set	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
post	O
chaise	O
from	O
Princes-street	B-place
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Ealing	B-place
that	O
evening	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
were	O
about	O
four	O
miles	O
upon	O
the	O
road	O
about	O
20	O
minutes	O
before	O
seven	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
rode	O
very	O
swiftly	O
by	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
crossed	O
the	O
head	O
of	O
the	O
horses	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
round	O
again	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wogin	O
's	O
side	O
,	O
he	O
presented	O
a	O
pistol	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wogin	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
pistol	O
aside	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
my	O
purse	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
more	O
,	O
Sir	O
?	O
-	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
upon	O
my	O
honour	O
.	O
-	O
Sir	O
,	O
you	O
have	O
more	O
(	O
swearing	O
)	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
have	O
more	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
imposed	O
upon	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
all	O
you	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
more	O
.	O
He	O
stopped	O
us	O
matter	O
of	O
four	O
minutes	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
is	O
nothing	O
but	O
silver	O
in	O
the	O
purse	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
little	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
all	O
that	O
you	O
have	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
make	O
you	O
get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
more	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
silver	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
shillings	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
said	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wogin	O
,	O
give	O
me	O
your	O
watch	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wogin	O
slipped	O
his	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
fob	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
towards	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
watch	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
my	O
watch	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
chaise	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
search	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
carrying	O
it	O
too	O
far	O
;	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
be	O
satisfied	O
with	O
what	O
you	O
have	O
got	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wogin	O
got	O
the	O
chaise	O
open	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
man	O
said	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
gentlemen	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
take	O
your	O
words	O
;	O
I	O
wish	O
you	O
a	O
good	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
rode	O
off	O
towards	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
we	O
had	O
been	O
telling	O
the	O
story	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
circumstances	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
servants	O
waiting	O
at	O
the	O
table	O
listened	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
Presently	O
came	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
bill	O
upon	O
Mr.	O
Wogin	O
for	O
post	O
chaises	O
;	O
this	O
man	O
was	O
informed	O
by	O
the	O
servants	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Wogin	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
the	O
evening	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
inquisitive	O
what	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
horse	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
hanged	O
if	O
that	O
very	O
man	O
and	O
horse	O
are	O
not	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
three	O
pidgeons	O
,	O
at	O
Brentford	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
interrogated	O
the	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
just	O
such	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
and	O
horse	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
We	O
walked	O
down	O
to	O
Brentford	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
a	O
man	O
answering	O
that	O
description	O
had	O
come	O
in	O
there	O
at	O
10	O
o'clock	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
ordered	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
at	O
six	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
laid	O
in	O
bed	O
till	O
10	O
or	O
11	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
before	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
suspected	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
highwayman	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
stable	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
horse	O
.	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
stable	O
door	O
to	O
be	O
locked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
horse	O
to	O
be	O
secured	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
his	O
boots	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
coffee-room	O
in	O
his	O
slippers	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wogin	O
being	O
dressed	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
pulled	O
off	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
proposed	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
coffee	O
room	O
without	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Wogin	O
desired	O
me	O
not	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
till	O
we	O
were	O
sure	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
and	O
entered	O
into	O
conversation	O
with	O
the	O
people	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
talking	O
about	O
highway	O
robberies	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
him	O
by	O
his	O
face	O
;	O
but	O
was	O
certain	O
if	O
I	O
heard	O
his	O
voice	O
I	O
should	O
recollect	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
the	O
same	O
hat	O
and	O
coat	O
on	O
(	O
when	O
he	O
robbed	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
his	O
coat	O
buttoned	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
mouth	O
)	O
;	O
something	O
was	O
said	O
which	O
provoked	O
him	O
to	O
speak	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wogin	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
Tyburn	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
graced	O
with	O
any	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wogin	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
will	O
be	O
very	O
soon	O
graced	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
They	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
on	O
what	O
account	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
was	O
it	O
between	O
this	O
and	O
London	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
road	O
within	O
a	O
mile	O
of	O
Acton	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
looked	O
confused	O
.	O
While	O
the	O
other	O
people	O
were	O
talking	O
about	O
the	O
particulars	O
of	O
robberies	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
,	O
but	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
our	O
duty	O
to	O
apprehend	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
will	O
follow	O
him	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
will	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
will	O
take	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
.	O
Then	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
had	O
better	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
one	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
better	O
and	O
safer	O
to	O
wait	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
garden	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
point	O
him	O
out	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
take	O
him	O
.	O
We	O
stood	O
together	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
of	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
we	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
conducted	O
into	O
a	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
as	O
little	O
fear	O
as	O
possible	O
a	O
man	O
could	O
have	O
upon	O
such	O
an	O
occasion	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
we	O
meant	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
we	O
suspected	O
to	O
have	O
robbed	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
any	O
body	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
great	O
service	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
write	O
to	O
somebody	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
people	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
search	O
his	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
garden	O
.	O
While	O
he	O
was	O
writing	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
was	O
wanted	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
:	O
they	O
brought	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
necessary-house	O
,	O
and	O
pointed	O
to	O
a	O
horse	O
pistol	O
which	O
lay	O
concealed	O
[	O
producing	O
one	O
]	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
very	O
same	O
pistol	O
that	O
was	O
presented	O
to	O
us	O
.	O
We	O
both	O
had	O
described	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
with	O
balls	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
them	O
now	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
produced	O
the	O
pistol	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
proceed	O
with	O
his	O
letter	O
,	O
or	O
tell	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
or	O
give	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
himself	O
.	O
He	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
half	O
guinea	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
little	O
bill	O
.	O
I	O
apprehend	O
that	O
half	O
guinea	O
he	O
had	O
from	O
me	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
new	O
King	O
George	B-pers
II	I-pers
's	O
.	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
turned	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
before	O
she	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
master	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
committed	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
pistol	O
was	O
it	O
he	O
presented	O
to	O
you	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
common	O
size	O
horse-pistol	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
a	O
gentleman	O
's	O
pistol	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
arms	O
upon	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
brass	O
mounted	O
pistol	O
,	O
very	O
bright	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
so	O
at	O
the	O
muzzle	O
;	O
it	O
looked	O
as	O
this	O
,	O
appearing	O
dull	O
at	O
muzzle	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
it	O
had	O
got	O
some	O
rust	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
not	O
the	O
garden	O
at	O
the	O
three	O
pidgeons	O
a	O
place	O
where	O
a	O
person	O
could	O
easily	O
escape	O
over	O
the	O
pales	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
they	O
could	O
very	O
easily	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
he	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
About	O
ten	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
that	O
was	O
your	O
half	O
guinea	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
If	O
a	O
person	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
such	O
a	O
one	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
of	O
voice	O
,	O
hat	O
,	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
have	O
raised	O
a	O
suspicion	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
half	O
guinea	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
say	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
doubt	O
but	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
wish	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
have	O
none	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
horse	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Banks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Grosvenor-square	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
be	O
at	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
pistols	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
kept	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
a	O
pistol	O
till	O
we	O
heard	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
found	O
upon	O
a	O
highwayman	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
a	O
gunsmith	O
to	O
see	O
who	O
owned	O
it	O
:	O
then	O
upon	O
searching	O
we	O
missed	O
No	O
.	O
2	O
.	O
This	O
pistol	O
here	O
produced	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
before	O
the	O
second	O
of	O
March	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
your	O
pistols	O
were	O
?	O
Banks	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
Christmas	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
How	O
was	O
the	O
pistol	O
hid	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
lay	O
the	O
paper	O
in	O
the	O
necessary-house	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noaks	I-pers
the	O
post-boy	O
found	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
over	O
it	O
till	O
I	O
came	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
Mr.	O
Wogin	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
bad	O
state	O
of	O
health	O
in	O
Pembrokeshire	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Cotheroy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stable-keeper	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
a	O
mare	O
of	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
seen	O
her	O
since	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
brown	O
mare	O
;	O
he	O
hired	O
her	O
I	O
think	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
to	O
return	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
following	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
about	O
14	O
hands	O
two	O
inches	O
high	O
;	O
and	O
is	O
hurt	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
the	O
hock	O
;	O
and	O
has	O
a	O
little	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
star	O
on	O
her	O
forehead	O
;	O
a	O
genteel	O
mare	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Is	O
the	O
mare	O
this	O
evidence	O
describes	O
like	O
her	O
the	O
man	O
rode	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
She	O
answers	O
exactly	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
you	O
I	O
believed	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
?	O
Cotheroy	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
I	O
found	O
some	O
crape	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
bills	O
of	O
fare	O
from	O
the	O
houses	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
,	O
and	O
turnpike	O
tickets	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
bills	O
shew	O
a	O
journey	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
Brentford	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
just	O
going	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wogin	O
was	O
frighted	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
for	O
five	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
;	O
and	O
described	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
in	O
a	O
different	O
dress	O
than	O
what	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
has	O
:	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
so	O
dark	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
describe	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
says	O
the	O
horse	O
was	O
very	O
swift	O
;	O
as	O
for	O
that	O
horse	O
I	O
rode	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
very	O
lame	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
going	O
to	O
Kingston	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
that	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Allam	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Three	O
Pidgeons	O
at	O
Brentford	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
twice	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
over	O
night	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
came	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
nine	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
public	O
coffee-room	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
noon	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
.	O
Allam	O
.	O
The	O
mare	O
he	O
rode	O
on	O
was	O
very	O
lame	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
on	O
her	O
both	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
he	O
have	O
made	O
his	O
escape	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
garden	O
with	O
ease	O
had	O
he	O
a	O
mind	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
Allam	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
little	O
rivulet	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
;	O
sometimes	O
the	O
water	O
is	O
hardly	O
over	O
the	O
shoes	O
.	O
There	O
is	O
a	O
wall	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
pales	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
;	O
the	O
latter	O
a	O
child	O
of	O
six	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
may	O
get	O
over	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
farrier	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
Highgate	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
putting	O
a	O
bar-shoe	O
on	O
a	O
brown	O
mare	O
for	O
a	O
chance	O
customer	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
lame	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
came	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
you	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
and	O
a	O
glass	O
of	O
wine	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
hostler	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Pidgeons	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
.	O
The	O
mare	O
he	O
rode	O
was	O
very	O
lame	O
:	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
foot	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
bar	O
shoe	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Chapter	O
coffee-house	O
,	O
Pater-noster-row	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
five	O
months	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
spend	O
his	O
evenings	O
mostly	O
there	O
;	O
and	O
kept	O
very	O
good	O
company	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Olton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
rope	O
ground	O
just	O
by	O
where	O
his	O
mother	O
lives	O
.	O
She	O
keeps	O
milch	O
asses	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
leashold	O
estate	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
is	O
gone	O
.	O
He	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
