TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
24th	O
and	O
Thursday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
,	O
1762	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
FLUDYER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1762	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
JOHN	B-pers
RYALL	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
SIX	O
PENCE	O
.	O
]	O
WHERE	O
MAY	O
BE	O
HAD	O
,	O
All	O
Sorts	O
of	O
English	O
and	O
Foreign	O
PRINTS	O
and	O
MAPS	O
,	O
BOOKS	O
in	O
all	O
Languages	O
,	O
Arts	O
,	O
and	O
Sciences	O
,	O
STATIONARY	O
WARES	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
DRAWINGS	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Fram	O
'd	O
and	O
Glaz	O
'd	O
in	O
the	O
most	O
Elegant	O
Taste	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
During	O
the	O
whole	O
Mayoralty	O
of	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
FLUDYER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
the	O
Price	O
of	O
these	O
Proceedings	O
for	O
each	O
Session	O
will	O
be	O
only	O
Six-Pence	O
.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
FLUDYER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Baron	O
Gould	O
*	O
,	O
Sir	O
Wm	O
.	O
Moreton	O
,	O
+	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
James	O
Eyre	O
,	O
++	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Christopher	B-pers
Stedman	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Biffen	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Eastman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Collierigg	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Merriman	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Harris	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haslehurst	I-pers
,	O
Geo	B-pers
Snowball	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Budley	I-pers
,	O
Jos	B-pers
Cooper	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Hurst	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tressler	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Geo	B-pers
Dale	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Longdale	I-pers
,	O
Ishmael	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Long	I-pers
,	O
Edward	B-pers
Crease	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Powson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pickering	I-pers
.	O
88	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Jaques	I-pers
of	O
London	B-place
,	O
labourer	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
coachman	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
at	O
Deptford	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Jan.	O
21	O
,	O
1762	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
drive	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
's	O
in	O
Leadenhall	B-place
street	I-place
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gloves	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
great	O
coat	O
upon	O
the	O
coach-box	O
;	O
upon	O
my	O
return	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
coat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
again	O
?	O
Hewitt	O
.	O
At	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
's	O
Shop	O
[	O
Coat	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
sworn	O
to	O
]	O
.	O
Morgan	O
Bennet	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
's	O
in	O
Leaden-hall-street	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
take	O
a	O
coat	O
off	O
the	O
coach-box	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
then	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
likewise	O
observed	O
by	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
ladies	O
who	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
who	O
immediately	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
that	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
coat	O
off	O
the	O
coach-box	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
inquired	O
something	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
about	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Axe	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
do	O
then	O
?	O
Bennet	O
.	O
Sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
?	O
Bennet	O
.	O
That	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
done	O
any	O
such	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
.	O
The	O
21st	O
of	O
January	O
two	O
ladies	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
chariot	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
first	O
witness	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Hewitt	I-pers
,	O
was	O
the	O
coachman	O
;	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
absent	O
for	O
some	O
purpose	O
or	O
other	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
ladies	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
took	O
the	O
coachman	O
's	O
great	O
coat	O
from	O
the	O
coach-box	O
:	O
Upon	O
inquiry	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
pursued	O
and	O
overtook	O
him	O
in	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Axe	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
great	O
coat	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
great	O
coat	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
off	O
a	O
coach	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Morgan	O
Bennet	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Kennedy	O
.	O
Only	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
then	O
but	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
the	O
lady	O
that	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
information	O
,	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
persuaded	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Said	O
,	O
That	O
the	O
coat	O
lay	O
a	O
good	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
from	O
thence	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
there	O
for	O
a	O
good	O
while	O
without	O
attempting	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
89	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Henning	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
Holland	O
shirt	O
,	O
one	O
crape	O
and	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Best	I-pers
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Best	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
lodging	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Calley	O
's	O
in	O
Catherine-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
plain	O
work	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
shirts	O
to	O
ruffle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
day	O
leaving	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
upon	O
the	O
dresser	O
.	O
I	O
returned	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
the	O
shirt	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
I	O
looked	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
of	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
often	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
any	O
body	O
else	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
,	O
finding	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
the	O
shirt	O
.	O
She	O
at	O
first	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
afterwards	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
shirt	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Brooks	O
's	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
Where	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
shirt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
means	O
did	O
you	O
use	O
to	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
it	O
?	O
E.	O
Best	O
.	O
I	O
promised	O
to	O
be	O
as	O
favourable	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
shirt	O
by	O
particularly	O
?	O
E.	O
Best	O
.	O
By	O
this	O
lace	O
at	O
the	O
bosom	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
,	O
Pawn-broker	O
,	O
examined	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
that	O
shirt	O
?	O
Brooks	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
January	O
,	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
.	O
She	O
pledged	O
it	O
as	O
her	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Henning	I-pers
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Calley	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
C.	O
You	O
are	O
to	O
given	O
an	O
Account	O
of	O
the	O
crape	O
gown	O
with	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
charged	O
.	O
A.	O
Calley	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
gown	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
that	O
the	O
shirt	O
was	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
afterwards	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
it	O
there	O
?	O
A.	O
Calley	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
sleevestaken	O
off	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Best	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
gown	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
lodging	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Best	I-pers
called	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
gown	O
?	O
E.	O
Best	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
at	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
lodging	O
?	O
E.	O
Best	O
.	O
By	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
say	O
where	O
her	O
lodging	O
was	O
?	O
E.	O
Best	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
she	O
first	O
directed	O
us	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
when	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
a	O
constable	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
gown	O
with	O
the	O
sleeves	O
off	O
.	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
any	O
thing	O
?	O
D.	O
Rogers	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
;	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
and	O
where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
them	O
again	O
?	O
D.	O
Rogers	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
back	O
,	O
altered	O
to	O
sit	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
in	O
her	O
lodging	O
at	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
positive	O
?	O
The	O
pattern	O
of	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
may	O
be	O
the	O
same	O
as	O
many	O
others	O
?	O
D.	O
Rogers	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
one	O
of	O
this	O
pattern	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
it	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
are	O
many	O
marks	O
that	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
gown	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
marks	O
shown	O
.	O
]	O
Frances	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
with	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
charged	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Frederic	I-pers
Willis	O
?	O
Willis	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
this	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
lodging	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
box	O
not	O
locked	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
handkerchief	O
?	O
[	O
Frances	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
opened	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
showed	O
a	O
particular	O
mark	O
near	O
the	O
selvage	O
by	O
which	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
hers	O
]	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
?	O
F.	O
Willis	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
husband	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
F.	O
Willis	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Charles	I-pers
Frederic	I-pers
Willis	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
wronged	O
any	O
body	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
gowns	O
of	O
an	O
old	O
cloaths	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
altered	O
one	O
to	O
fit	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
before	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
last	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
kept	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
box	O
till	O
I	O
could	O
find	O
time	O
to	O
mend	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
you	O
are	O
charged	O
with	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
your	O
character	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
90	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Morris	B-pers
Delaney	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Combe	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
scollop	O
waiter	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
waiter	O
stand	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
sauce	O
boats	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
gold	O
studs	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
pint	O
mug	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
sauce	O
pan	O
,	O
three	O
shirts	O
,	O
three	O
dimity	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Thomas	B-pers
Combe	I-pers
+	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Combe	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Tottenham	B-place
Cross	I-place
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
12th	O
and	O
13th	O
instant	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
When	O
my	O
maid	O
got	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
and	O
window	O
shutter	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
drawers	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
things	O
all	O
about	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Upon	O
that	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
acquaint	O
me	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
my	O
wife	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
plate	O
principally	O
was	O
,	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
the	O
locks	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
forced	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
almost	O
all	O
the	O
locks	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
opened	O
,	O
by	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
instrument	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
carpenter	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
any	O
picklock	O
keys	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
of	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
if	O
any-body	O
had	O
been	O
seen	O
about	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
been	O
lurking	O
about	O
the	O
street	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
believing	O
I	O
had	O
reasons	O
sufficient	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
to	O
get	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
returned	O
from	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
lodgings	O
with	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
instrument	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
which	O
we	O
apprehend	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
very	O
instrument	O
that	O
had	O
forced	O
or	O
broke	O
open	O
the	O
locks	O
;	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
bringing	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
trying	O
how	O
it	O
fitted	O
the	O
holes	O
,	O
we	O
concluded	O
it	O
must	O
be	O
done	O
by	O
that	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
other	O
such-like	O
instrument	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
afterwards	O
took	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
had	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
there	O
?	O
Combes	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
searched	O
at	O
the	O
constable	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Combes	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
your	O
property	O
upon	O
him	O
?	O
Combes	O
.	O
Nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
charge	O
him	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
only	O
?	O
Combes	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
found	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
your	O
goods	O
?	O
Combes	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Combes	I-pers
,	O
When	O
Mr.	O
Combes	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
informed	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
some	O
suspicion	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
very	O
little	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
a	O
hammock	O
put	O
up	O
in	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
instrument	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
[	O
holding	O
it	O
up	O
]	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
very	O
thing	O
broke	O
open	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
return	O
home	O
,	O
we	O
fitted	O
it	O
to	O
several	O
holes	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
drawers	O
and	O
cupboard	O
doors	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
other	O
reason	O
have	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
that	O
instrument	O
?	O
M.	O
Combes	O
.	O
Any-body	O
might	O
see	O
it	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
such	O
an	O
instrument	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
fitted	O
the	O
places	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Mr.	O
Combes	O
,	O
in	O
your	O
presence	O
,	O
ask	O
him	O
any	O
questions	O
about	O
that	O
instrument	O
?	O
M.	O
Combes	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Combes	O
asked	O
him	O
about	O
it	O
afterwards	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
that	O
and	O
another	O
screw	O
and	O
staple	O
to	O
fasten	O
up	O
his	O
hammock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
hammock	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
screwed	O
up	O
by	O
such	O
an	O
instrument	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Combes	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Waters	I-pers
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
M.	O
Waters	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lives	O
at	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
this	O
matter	O
?	O
M.	O
Waters	O
.	O
Only	O
this	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
very	O
bad	O
hours	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
I	O
saw	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
or	O
they	O
,	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
M.	O
Waters	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
;	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
both	O
just	O
got	O
up	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Melling	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
watch	O
about	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
H.	O
Melling	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
watch	O
near	O
Mr.	O
Combes	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Melling	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
stand	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
way	O
from	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
my	O
rounds	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
about	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
met	O
this	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
you	O
met	O
?	O
Melling	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
?	O
Melling	O
.	O
After	O
one	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any-body	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Melling	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Melling	O
.	O
None	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
all	O
fast	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Combes	O
's	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Melling	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Rose	I-pers
,	O
Watchman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
your	O
round	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
twelve	O
,	O
two	O
,	O
and	O
four	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
all	O
fast	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Combes	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
meet	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
him	O
when	O
you	O
met	O
him	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
your	O
rounds	O
after	O
four	O
?	O
Rose	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
carpenter	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Combes	O
's	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
kind	O
of	O
instrument	O
had	O
opened	O
the	O
shutter	O
,	O
cupboard-door	O
,	O
and	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
forced	O
by	O
some	O
other	O
instrument	O
than	O
common	O
pick-lock	O
tools	O
;	O
that	O
I	O
imagined	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
a	O
screw	O
like	O
what	O
is	O
called	O
a	O
cooper	O
's	O
vice	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
what	O
is	O
called	O
so	O
[	O
holding	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
]	O
When	O
this	O
instrument	O
had	O
been	O
found	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
tried	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
went	O
in	O
very	O
easy	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
instrument	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
other	O
like	O
it	O
,	O
must	O
have	O
opened	O
the	O
desk	O
,	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
cupboard	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
they	O
were	O
forced	O
by	O
a	O
screw	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
The	O
desk	O
was	O
forced	O
in	O
the	O
joint	O
opposite	O
to	O
the	O
lock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
leaf	O
of	O
the	O
desk	O
much	O
torn	O
or	O
not	O
,	O
or	O
the	O
drawers	O
?	O
Edwards	O
.	O
The	O
holes	O
made	O
in	O
the	O
flap	O
of	O
the	O
desk	O
were	O
pretty	O
much	O
torn	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
drawers	O
were	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
all	O
we	O
know	O
from	O
your	O
evidence	O
is	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
by	O
that	O
or	O
some	O
other	O
instrument	O
like	O
it	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
They	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Upon	O
searching	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
this	O
screw	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
afterwards	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
asked	O
for	O
my	O
authority	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
with	O
his	O
fist	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
better	O
be	O
easy	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
then	O
took	O
his	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
rip	O
me	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
got	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
afterwards	O
took	O
him	O
.	O
Court	O
to	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
questions	O
to	O
ask	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Detained	O
upon	O
another	O
indictment	O
.	O
91.	O
Mary	B-pers
Sherman	I-pers
,	O
Spinster	O
,	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cap	O
and	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
seven	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr.	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
*	O
Mr.	O
Barnard	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
a	O
servant	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
February	O
my	O
wife	O
turned	O
her	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
wife	O
insisted	O
upon	O
seeing	O
what	O
it	O
contained	O
.	O
She	O
at	O
first	O
refused	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
her	O
setting	O
down	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
were	O
the	O
seven	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
viz	O
,	O
two	O
bottles	O
of	O
Sherry	O
,	O
three	O
of	O
Malaga	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
of	O
Madeira	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
indictment	O
mentions	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
your	O
property	O
:	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
in	O
my	O
cellar	O
to	O
see	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
vacancies	O
where	O
those	O
bottles	O
had	O
stood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
keep	O
those	O
different	O
sorts	O
of	O
wine	O
in	O
different	O
places	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
wine	O
before	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
hours	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
this	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
unfortunately	O
left	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
in	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
take	O
any	O
notice	O
whether	O
the	O
wine	O
was	O
all	O
there	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
I	O
observed	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
situation	O
as	O
I	O
had	O
placed	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
Madeira	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
Sherry	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
only	O
two	O
bottles	O
of	O
each	O
in	O
that	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
opened	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
you	O
saw	O
the	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
at	O
the	O
top	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
as	O
soap	O
,	O
starch	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
not	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
his	O
searching	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
night-cap	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
there	O
when	O
he	O
searched	O
her	O
pockets	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
then	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
the	O
cap	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
taken	O
from	O
her	O
were	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
maid	O
will	O
prove	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
particular	O
mark	O
upon	O
the	O
corks	O
or	O
the	O
bottles	O
?	O
Barnard	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
her	O
taking	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
cellar	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Ledger	I-pers
,	O
constable	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Barnard	O
's	O
,	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
some	O
bottles	O
of	O
wine	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
that	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
box	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Ledger	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
being	O
desired	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
search	O
her	O
pockets	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
prevented	O
me	O
by	O
putting	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
pulling	O
out	O
this	O
cap	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
dropping	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
coats	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
immediately	O
took	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
kept	O
ever	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
with	O
her	O
?	O
what	O
did	O
she	O
say	O
there	O
?	O
Ledger	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
asked	O
where	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
wine	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
.	O
This	O
cap	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
are	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
particular	O
knowledge	O
have	O
you	O
of	O
the	O
cap	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
whereby	O
you	O
can	O
be	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
E.	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
hands	O
often	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
washed	O
and	O
ironed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
cap	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
were	O
my	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
box	O
would	O
be	O
cumbersome	O
to	O
carry	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
box	O
locked	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
unlocked	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
or	O
taken	O
out	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
?	O
Catherine	B-pers
Grey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
is	O
a	O
neighbour	O
's	O
child	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
sober	O
family	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
at	O
service	O
at	O
Mile-end	O
,	O
and	O
elsewhere	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
always	O
thought	O
her	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
before	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Wilcox	I-pers
and	O
Mercy	B-pers
Halibank	I-pers
were	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
both	O
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
purpose	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
92	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Teeling	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
and	O
a	O
Gloucester	O
cheese	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hickman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cheesemonger	O
at	O
East	O
Smith-field	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
Christmas-day	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
cask	O
of	O
west	O
country	O
butter	O
,	O
about	O
56	O
lb	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
it	O
?	O
Hickman	O
.	O
The	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
down	O
at	O
my	O
warehouse	O
at	O
Woolwich	B-place
;	O
there	O
were	O
10	O
firkins	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
,	O
and	O
20	O
of	O
another	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
looking	O
it	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
ten	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
it	O
you	O
first	O
missed	O
your	O
cheese	O
?	O
Hickman	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
and	O
place	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
this	O
butter	O
and	O
cheese	O
again	O
?	O
Hickman	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Trumbell	O
,	O
constable	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
case	O
produced	O
,	O
the	O
hoops	O
were	O
stripped	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
begun	O
to	O
be	O
cut	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
this	O
firkin	O
to	O
be	O
yours	O
?	O
Hickman	O
.	O
The	O
dairyman	O
cuts	O
the	O
letters	O
I	O
H	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cooper	O
likewise	O
marks	O
them	O
with	O
this	O
mark	O
.	O
[	O
Showing	O
it	O
.	O
]	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
,	O
from	O
these	O
marks	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
is	O
your	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
?	O
Hickman	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
like	O
marks	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
cheese	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
15	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
sort	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
goods	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Hickman	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
justice	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
man	O
so	O
capable	O
of	O
getting	O
his	O
bread	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
thing	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
what	O
he	O
thought	O
a	O
fault	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
none	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
sent	O
me	O
a	O
letter	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
innocent	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
attend	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
surrender	O
himself	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
in	O
time	O
,	O
or	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Trumbell	I-pers
,	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
butter	O
and	O
cheese	O
mentioned	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
by	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
they	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
concealed	O
when	O
you	O
found	O
them	O
?	O
Trumbell	O
.	O
The	O
cask	O
of	O
butter	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
cheese	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Trumbell	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
surrendered	O
himself	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
acquaint	O
his	O
wife	O
that	O
you	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
him	O
?	O
Trumbell	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
surrendered	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
18th	O
day	O
of	O
January	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
justice	O
Scot	O
,	O
after	O
acquainting	O
Mr	O
Hickman	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
passed	O
before	O
justice	O
Scot	O
?	O
Trumbell	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
found	O
the	O
goods	O
in	O
the	O
stern-sheet	O
of	O
a	O
lighter	O
at	O
Bull	O
Wharf	O
stairs	O
,	O
above	O
bridge	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Berry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
left	O
my	O
boat	O
at	O
Dier	O
's	O
Wharf	O
,	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Bull	O
Wharf	O
,	O
under	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
there	O
in	O
your	O
boat	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
Ten	O
firkins	O
of	O
butter	O
,	O
and	O
forty-eight	O
cheese	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whose	O
property	O
were	O
they	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hickman	O
's	O
,	O
delivered	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Hickman	O
's	O
waterman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
20	O
firkins	O
more	O
at	O
the	O
Three	O
Cranes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
staid	O
all	O
night	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
;	O
when	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
20	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
it	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Woolwich	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
before	O
Christmas-day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
this	O
firkin	O
of	O
butter	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
took	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
20	O
,	O
and	O
likewise	O
the	O
cheese	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
Mr.	O
Hickman	O
notice	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
servant	O
down	O
to	O
Woolwich	O
,	O
and	O
mean	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
for	O
to	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
before-mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
acquaint	O
Mr.	O
Hickman	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
does	O
the	O
prisoner	O
live	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
At	O
Red-maid	O
Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
might	O
that	O
be	O
from	O
the	O
wharf	O
where	O
the	O
goods	O
lay	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
mile	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
latest	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
when	O
you	O
saw	O
those	O
goods	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
About	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
boat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
when	O
you	O
left	O
the	O
boat	O
yourself	O
,	O
all	O
the	O
butter	O
and	O
cheese	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
boat	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
the	O
marks	O
on	O
the	O
butter	O
tub	O
and	O
the	O
cheese	O
when	O
you	O
took	O
them	O
into	O
your	O
boat	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
pray	O
,	O
what	O
induced	O
you	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
?	O
Berry	O
.	O
The	O
watchman	O
at	O
the	O
Red	O
Bull	O
wharf	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
that	O
wharf	O
about	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighterman	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
business	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
all	O
hours	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
Red	O
Bull	O
wharf	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
the	O
lighters	O
were	O
safe	O
or	O
in	O
any	O
danger	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
partner	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
one	O
lighter	O
that	O
was	O
headmost	O
in	O
some	O
danger	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
wanting	O
a	O
rope	O
to	O
secure	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
lighter	O
that	O
lay	O
sternmost	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
rope	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
observed	O
a	O
bag	O
containing	O
these	O
things	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
fellow	O
servant	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
something	O
of	O
a	O
prize	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
handed	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
the	O
lighter	O
's	O
storn	O
sheet	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
carry	O
it	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
for	O
safety	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
inquiry	O
was	O
made	O
,	O
the	O
right	O
owner	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
there	O
it	O
should	O
be	O
ready	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
away	O
again	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
;	O
and	O
before	O
I	O
returned	O
home	O
again	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
such	O
things	O
found	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
innocent	O
as	O
to	O
any	O
theft	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
such	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
home	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
owner	O
,	O
upon	O
inquiry	O
,	O
might	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
again	O
,	O
as	O
my	O
business	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
till	O
such	O
time	O
as	O
they	O
began	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
bills	O
at	O
Hicks	O
's	O
Hall	O
the	O
last	O
session	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
was	O
less	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hickman	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
know	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
thro	O
'	O
any	O
fear	O
of	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
myself	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
might	O
depend	O
upon	O
it	O
I	O
would	O
appear	O
at	O
the	O
proper	O
time	O
to	O
answer	O
for	O
myself	O
at	O
the	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
not	O
go	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
and	O
spoke	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Akerman	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
surrender	O
myself	O
;	O
but	O
Mr.	O
Akerman	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
bail	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
he	O
could	O
take	O
no	O
surrender	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
my	O
business	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
afterwards	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
surrender	O
myself	O
to	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
with	O
bail	O
for	O
my	O
appearance	O
.	O
At	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
any	O
bail	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
unwilling	O
to	O
injure	O
my	O
family	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
avail	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
produce	O
in	O
favour	O
of	O
you	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
My	O
fellow-servant	O
,	O
who	O
knows	O
that	O
I	O
only	O
carried	O
the	O
things	O
home	O
till	O
a	O
right	O
owner	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
lighterman	O
;	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Hermitage	O
,	O
servant	O
to	O
one	O
Mr	O
.	O
Staples	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
fellow-servant	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
is	O
our	O
business	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
our	O
craft	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
do	O
what	O
business	O
offers	O
,	O
and	O
look	O
out	O
for	O
more	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
preceding	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
December	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
lighter	O
at	O
Red	O
Bull	O
wharf	O
,	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
fast	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
lighter	O
by	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
partner	O
went	O
into	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
rope	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
going	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
stern	O
sheet	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
bag	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
a	O
prize	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Hand	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
skiff	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
Somebody	O
may	O
inquire	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
do	O
,	O
they	O
may	O
have	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
his	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
searched	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
So	O
you	O
heard	O
him	O
say	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
any-body	O
inquired	O
after	O
it	O
they	O
might	O
have	O
it	O
?	O
Woodward	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
look	O
to	O
see	O
what	O
prize	O
this	O
was	O
?	O
Woodward	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
inspect	O
it	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
your	O
lighter	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
your	O
return	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
searched	O
.	O
-	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
by	O
whom	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
whose	O
behalf	O
?	O
Woodward	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
not	O
till	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
acquainted	O
with	O
this	O
affair	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
ever	O
go	O
to	O
acquaint	O
Mr.	O
Hickman	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
or	O
of	O
his	O
character	O
?	O
Woodward	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
troubled	O
myself	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hickman	O
had	O
his	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
follow	O
'd	O
his	O
business	O
as	O
usual	O
,	O
and	O
continued	O
so	O
to	O
do	O
for	O
two	O
months	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
thought	O
nothing	O
more	O
would	O
come	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hickman	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
the	O
constable	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
?	O
Mr.	O
Hickman	O
said	O
the	O
constable	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
had	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Trumbell	I-pers
,	O
constable	O
,	O
called	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
endeavour	O
to	O
take	O
this	O
man	O
?	O
Trumbell	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
times	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
ever	O
I	O
enquired	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
lighter	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Jones	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
these	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
August	O
last	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
my	O
business	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
intrusted	O
with	O
lighters	O
loaded	O
with	O
linen	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
goods	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
whatever	O
I	O
know	O
,	O
or	O
ever	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
93	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Steward	I-pers
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
day	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
I	O
lost	O
two	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
cupboard	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
had	O
put	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
crown	O
piece	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
reason	O
had	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
her	O
stealing	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Hicks	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
was	O
there	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
and	O
between	O
that	O
time	O
and	O
Monday	O
my	O
wife	O
miss	O
'd	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
left	O
my	O
house	O
unknown	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
Star	O
alley	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
charging	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
out	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
deliver	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
from	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
induce	O
her	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
promise	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
her	O
?	O
Hicks	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
get	O
the	O
crown	O
again	O
?	O
Hicks	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
changed	O
that	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Poor	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
candle	O
left	O
burning	O
;	O
I	O
supposed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
might	O
be	O
gone	O
out	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
dram	O
.	O
I	O
opened	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
there	O
till	O
my	O
mistress	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
knew	O
not	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
;	O
and	O
afterwards	O
my	O
mistress	O
miss	O
'd	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
master	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
That	O
she	O
saw	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
cupboard	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
left	O
any-body	O
else	O
should	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
94	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Davenporte	I-pers
,	O
spinsters	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seventeen	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
twelve	O
pillow	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
14	O
s.	O
three	O
round	O
towels	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
holland	O
shirts	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stocking	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
coffee	O
,	O
4	O
damask	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
2	O
napkins	O
,	O
and	O
sundry	O
other	O
goods	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
E.	B-pers
of	I-pers
March	I-pers
and	I-pers
Rutland	I-pers
.	O
+	O
Malcomb	B-pers
Black	I-pers
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
latter	O
end	O
of	O
March	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
honour	O
to	O
enter	O
into	O
my	O
Lord	O
March	O
's	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Davenporte	I-pers
,	O
were	O
intrusted	O
with	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
linen	O
,	O
grocery	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
housekeeper	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
Mary	B-pers
Davenporte	I-pers
's	O
conduct	O
was	O
not	O
approved	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
warning	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
accordingly	O
did	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
Ann	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
express	O
'd	O
her	O
dissatisfaction	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
be	O
discharg	O
'd	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
complied	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
paid	O
them	O
their	O
wages	O
;	O
upon	O
my	O
taking	O
an	O
inventory	O
of	O
the	O
linen	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
extremely	O
thin	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
very	O
bad	O
order	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
mean	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
that	O
quantity	O
of	O
linen	O
you	O
expected	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
merely	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
inventory	O
they	O
gave	O
me	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
the	O
inventory	O
we	O
had	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
seeing	O
no	O
date	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
some	O
doubt	O
whether	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
right	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
they	O
pretended	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
inventory	O
given	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
the	O
linen	O
which	O
they	O
then	O
delivered	O
was	O
in	O
great	O
confusion	O
,	O
and	O
hardly	O
sorted	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
they	O
delivered	O
up	O
the	O
linen	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
check	O
the	O
inventory	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
several	O
articles	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
nearly	O
agreed	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
exactly	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
late	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
least	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
examine	O
this	O
inventory	O
,	O
great	O
doubts	O
arose	O
,	O
how	O
such	O
a	O
family	O
could	O
be	O
so	O
extremely	O
destitute	O
of	O
linen	O
.	O
About	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
days	O
after	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
considerable	O
bill	O
was	O
presented	O
by	O
the	O
linen-draper	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
surprised	O
that	O
all	O
those	O
goods	O
should	O
be	O
charged	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
few	O
or	O
scarcely	O
any	O
of	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
might	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
be	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
including	O
a	O
former	O
bill	O
,	O
above	O
a	O
hundred	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
in	O
consequence	O
of	O
this	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
I	O
inquired	O
if	O
any-body	O
knew	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
that	O
inventory	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
any	O
satisfactory	O
account	O
;	O
whereupon	O
my	O
suspicions	O
increased	O
,	O
and	O
accordingly	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
I	O
determined	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
search	O
their	O
lodgings	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
with	O
some	O
difficulty	O
I	O
found	O
out	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
but	O
at	O
length	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
at	O
one	O
Anderson	O
's	O
in	O
Blenheim-street	O
:	O
soon	O
after	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
I	O
acquainted	O
Ann	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Davenporte	I-pers
,	O
that	O
I	O
was	O
come	O
there	O
to	O
search	O
their	O
lodging	O
.	O
They	O
expressed	O
great	O
displeasure	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
lived	O
so	O
long	O
with	O
Lord	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
at	O
length	O
it	O
should	O
come	O
to	O
this	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
constable	O
accompanied	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
must	O
submit	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
They	O
opened	O
several	O
boxes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
things	O
,	O
viz	O
.	O
some	O
sheets	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
too	O
fine	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
their	O
property	O
:	O
turning	O
round	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
contents	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
opening	O
it	O
there	O
were	O
thirty	O
or	O
forty	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
candles	O
.	O
This	O
increased	O
my	O
suspicion	O
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Davenporte	I-pers
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
.	O
-	O
Looking	O
round	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
door	O
with	O
a	O
brass	O
lock	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
leading	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
things	O
standing	O
against	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
whether	O
that	O
room	O
belonged	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
it	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
who	O
it	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
to	O
a	O
carpenter	O
,	O
who	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
till	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
wait	O
so	O
long	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
be	O
sent	O
for	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
at	O
home	O
between	O
one	O
and	O
two	O
o'clock	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
my	O
suspicion	O
rather	O
increased	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
landlord	O
's	O
daughter	O
whose	O
room	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
the	O
room	O
belongs	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
pay	O
rent	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
Mary	B-pers
Davenporte	I-pers
to	O
see	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
key	O
to	O
open	O
this	O
door	O
.	O
She	O
brought	O
some	O
keys	O
,	O
but	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
would	O
open	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
I	O
ordered	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
lock	O
was	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
of	O
their	O
lodging	O
-	O
the	O
constable	O
therefore	O
unscrewed	O
the	O
lock	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
theirs	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
a	O
box	O
or	O
two	O
.	O
Upon	O
my	O
entering	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
perfect	O
ware-room	O
,	O
and	O
contained	O
such	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
things	O
as	O
one	O
could	O
scarce	O
expect	O
to	O
be	O
collected	O
together	O
.	O
Pointing	O
to	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
that	O
appeared	O
to	O
have	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
if	O
that	O
was	O
theirs	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
desired	O
them	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
,	O
taking	O
up	O
one	O
sheet	O
,	O
tore	O
off	O
one	O
corner	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
look	O
on	O
the	O
corner	O
that	O
was	O
tore	O
off	O
,	O
whether	O
there	O
was	O
any	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
mark	O
was	O
there	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
Several	O
dots	O
in	O
dark-coloured	O
silk	O
;	O
that	O
are	O
known	O
to	O
the	O
laundress	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
fie	O
,	O
Ann	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
?	O
She	O
then	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
napkins	O
,	O
marked	O
with	O
M.	O
R	O
..	O
and	O
a	O
coroner	O
,	O
for	O
E.	O
of	O
March	O
and	O
Rutland	O
.	O
I	O
pulled	O
them	O
from	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
the	O
constable	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
sheet	O
which	O
the	O
corner	O
was	O
tore	O
from	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
intend	O
to	O
make	O
any	O
farther	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
a	O
coach	O
to	O
be	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
bundle	O
,	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
the	O
napkins	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
went	O
with	O
you	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
After	O
you	O
left	O
the	O
lodging	O
,	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
keys	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
The	O
keys	O
were	O
lock	O
'd	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
we	O
had	O
found	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
upon	O
looking	O
for	O
the	O
napkins	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
-	O
and	O
Sir	O
John	O
told	O
us	O
,	O
laughing	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
very	O
bad	O
searchers	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
again	O
with	O
Mary	B-pers
Davenporte	I-pers
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Mary	B-pers
Davenporte	I-pers
she	O
had	O
better	O
have	O
been	O
quiet	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
I	O
had	O
already	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
than	O
give	O
me	O
farther	O
trouble	O
,	O
and	O
have	O
more	O
things	O
found	O
against	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
upon	O
her	O
finding	O
those	O
napkins	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
not	O
here	O
.	O
Will	O
you	O
then	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
another	O
truth	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
are	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
thrown	O
them	O
away	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
linen	O
sheets	O
there	O
with	O
particular	O
marks	O
upon	O
them	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
there	O
are	O
ten	O
or	O
twelve	O
of	O
them	O
that	O
are	O
properly	O
marked	O
with	O
M.	O
R.	O
and	O
a	O
coronet	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
otherwise	O
,	O
and	O
known	O
be	O
my	O
lord	O
March	O
's	O
laundress	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
also	O
half	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
coffee	O
unroasted	O
,	O
directed	O
for	O
my	O
Lord	O
March	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
find	O
any	O
keys	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
in	O
different	O
places	O
sixty-five	O
keys	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
try	O
any	O
of	O
those	O
keys	O
upon	O
the	O
locks	O
belonging	O
to	O
Lord	O
March	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
five	O
keys	O
that	O
will	O
open	O
eleven	O
locks	O
;	O
four	O
locks	O
to	O
rooms	O
,	O
and	O
seven	O
other	O
doors	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
the	O
linen	O
press	O
,	O
a	O
library	O
table	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
places	O
wherein	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
are	O
deposited	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
you	O
examined	O
the	O
linen	O
by	O
the	O
inventory	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
very	O
nearly	O
but	O
not	O
exactly	O
agreed	O
-	O
Was	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
housekeeper	O
at	O
my	O
lord	O
's	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
were	O
severally	O
intrusted	O
with	O
keys	O
,	O
and	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Stubbs	I-pers
had	O
been	O
in	O
my	O
lord	O
's	O
house	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
bore	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Davenporte	I-pers
had	O
been	O
there	O
but	O
about	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
character	O
unsuspected	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
it	O
was	O
with	O
difficulty	O
you	O
found	O
her	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
informed	O
you	O
had	O
been	O
there	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
dined	O
there	O
.	O
Black	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
amazed	O
!	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Black	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
lodgings	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
telling	O
them	O
what	O
business	O
I	O
came	O
upon	O
,	O
they	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
out	O
of	O
humour	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Black	O
soon	O
discovered	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
opened	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
contained	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
candles	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Black	O
supposed	O
might	O
belong	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Black	O
asked	O
who	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
,	O
pointing	O
to	O
a	O
door	O
that	O
was	O
locked	O
?	O
One	O
of	O
them	O
said	O
it	O
belonged	O
to	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
to	O
see	O
it	O
opened	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
no	O
key	O
that	O
would	O
open	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
Mr.	O
Black	O
's	O
order	O
I	O
unscrewed	O
the	O
lock	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
which	O
Mr.	O
Black	O
said	O
belonged	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
;	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Black	O
and	O
the	O
prisoners	O
?	O
Thomas	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
asked	O
for	O
two	O
napkins	O
which	O
had	O
been	O
found	O
in	O
that	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
upon	O
their	O
being	O
missing	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Black	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Davenporte	I-pers
went	O
back	O
to	O
find	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
flung	O
them	O
away	O
.	O
We	O
went	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
and	O
found	O
keys	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Black	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
paper	O
containing	O
coffee	O
there	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
Yes	O
;	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
the	O
earl	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
laundress	O
being	O
called	O
,	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
produced	O
and	O
shown	O
article	O
by	O
article	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
deposed	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Black	O
.	O
Were	O
any	O
of	O
these	O
things	O
so	O
old	O
and	O
out	O
of	O
repair	O
as	O
to	O
be	O
usually	O
given	O
to	O
servants	O
?	O
Black	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
many	O
of	O
them	O
so	O
fine	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
such	O
good	O
condition	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
suppose	O
that	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
case	O
.	O
Counsel	O
for	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
,	O
Observed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
marks	O
to	O
the	O
linen	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
to	O
be	O
unquestionable	O
,	O
but	O
such	O
as	O
might	O
be	O
mistaken	O
.	O
[	O
A	O
shirt	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
March	O
's	O
produced	O
.	O
]	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Laundress	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
shirt	O
?	O
Laundress	O
.	O
By	O
an	O
M	O
R	O
,	O
that	O
it	O
came	O
from	O
Scotland	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
made	O
by	O
a	O
person	O
who	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
the	O
coronet	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
positively	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
Lord	O
March	O
's	O
shirt	O
.	O
Ann	O
Stubb	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
things	O
that	O
are	O
not	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
have	O
done	O
us	O
great	O
injustice	O
in	O
charging	O
us	O
with	O
stealing	O
them	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Davenport	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
Lord	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
opened	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
mine	O
that	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
opened	O
these	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
belonged	O
to	O
my	O
mother	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
your	O
mother	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Davenporte	O
.	O
Her	O
name	O
was	O
Mary	B-pers
Davenporte	I-pers
,	O
and	O
always	O
marked	O
with	O
an	O
M.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Willis	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoners	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
servants	O
to	O
Madam	O
Cartes	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
intrusted	O
with	O
very	O
considerable	O
property	O
;	O
they	O
always	O
bore	O
an	O
unexceptionable	O
character	O
;	O
they	O
have	O
been	O
frequently	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
there	O
have	O
been	O
bank-notes	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
lay	O
open	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
had	O
any	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
their	O
honesty	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Postern	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoners	O
these	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
they	O
lived	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Bloomsbury	O
opposite	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
intrusted	O
to	O
a	O
considerable	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
person	O
question	O
their	O
honesty	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Postern	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
they	O
were	O
never	O
before	O
charged	O
with	O
any	O
dishonesty	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Anderson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
about	O
twelve	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
always	O
looked	O
upon	O
them	O
as	O
persons	O
of	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Alloway	I-pers
,	O
Catharine	B-pers
Davidson	I-pers
,	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Oates	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Thompson	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ferry	I-pers
,	O
Martha	B-pers
Henry	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Hester	B-pers
Stephenson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
had	O
known	O
them	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
believed	O
they	O
deserved	O
it	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Willis	I-pers
said	O
she	O
knew	O
them	O
many	O
years	O
servants	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cartes	O
,	O
and	O
intrusted	O
with	O
great	O
property	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
did	O
every	O
thing	O
with	O
great	O
care	O
and	O
probity	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Cartes	O
,	O
junior	O
,	O
told	O
her	O
that	O
Mary	B-pers
Davenporte	I-pers
had	O
many	O
things	O
left	O
her	O
of	O
value	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
95	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Walter	B-pers
Randall	I-pers
,	O
Indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
++	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Black-Friars	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopped	O
at	O
a	O
picture-shop	O
in	O
Cheapside	B-place
;	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
a	O
haberdasher	O
,	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
little	O
crooked	O
fellow	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gilbody	I-pers
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
and	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
;	O
the	O
people	O
persuaded	O
me	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
about	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
Lordship	O
committed	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
96	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Welch	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
fifteen	O
iron	O
screen	O
cases	O
japaned	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
,	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
1762	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Thawley	I-pers
.	O
++	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Thawley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	B-place
Poultry	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
shop	O
of	O
ironmongery	O
and	O
hardware	O
goods	O
;	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
pound	O
of	O
honey	O
(	O
which	O
I	O
also	O
sell	O
)	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
in	O
a	O
pound	O
weight	O
,	O
and	O
turning	O
round	O
to	O
get	O
some	O
other	O
weights	O
,	O
to	O
balance	O
the	O
pot	O
more	O
exactly	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
again	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
weight	O
in	O
the	O
scale	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
making	O
towards	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
being	O
shut	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
before	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
seizing	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
of	O
his	O
great	O
coat	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
till	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
me	O
my	O
weight	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
spring	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
both	O
fell	O
down	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
fall	O
there	O
fell	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bosom	O
sixteen	O
iron	O
spring	O
cases	O
,	O
made	O
for	O
screens	O
for	O
the	O
eyes	O
;	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
struggling	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
coming	O
by	O
took	O
them	O
up	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
;	O
a	O
constable	O
happening	O
to	O
come	O
by	O
at	O
that	O
juncture	O
,	O
I	O
charged	O
the	O
constable	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
Matthew	B-pers
Blackiston	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
who	O
committed	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
they	O
are	O
your	O
cases	O
?	O
Thawley	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
two	O
dozen	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
sold	O
three	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
dozen	O
and	O
five	O
out	O
of	O
another	O
:	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
they	O
dropt	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bosom	O
in	O
the	O
struggle	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Gravesend	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
my	O
captain	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
see	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
acquaintances	O
and	O
staid	O
with	O
them	O
till	O
near	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
passing	O
by	O
this	O
gentleman	O
's	O
door	O
he	O
caught	O
hold	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
committed	O
to	O
the	O
compter	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Am	O
I	O
to	O
understand	O
by	O
your	O
account	O
,	O
that	O
you	O
never	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
they	O
had	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
any	O
witnesses	O
to	O
call	O
?	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
97	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Rebecca	B-pers
,	I-pers
the	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Houghton	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pewter	O
pint	O
pots	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
21	O
,	O
1762	O
.	O
++	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
last	O
Sunday	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
for	O
some	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
Mrs.	O
Houghton	O
had	O
got	O
two	O
pint	O
pots	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
and	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
found	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
if	O
there	O
is	O
it	O
is	O
none	O
of	O
yours	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
sending	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
on	O
a	O
form	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
my	O
husband	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
took	O
another	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
fault	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
denied	O
the	O
pots	O
were	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
proved	O
to	O
be	O
ours	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
wronged	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Thomas	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
always	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
her	O
before	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Parsons	I-pers
,	O
Humphry	O
Parsons	O
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Kettel	I-pers
,	O
Jane	B-pers
Kettel	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
intrusted	O
by	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
98	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Morring	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
16	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
laced	O
ruffles	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
.	O
February	O
8	O
,	O
1762	O
.	O
++	O
Stephen	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
behind	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
fore	O
room	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
apron	O
that	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
;	O
she	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
returning	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
Lord	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
this	O
apron	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawers	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
take	O
more	O
care	O
of	O
your	O
things	O
.	O
The	O
maid	O
(	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
)	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
heard	O
her	O
talk	O
something	O
about	O
fire	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
casting	O
my	O
eye	O
to	O
the	O
bed	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bed	O
cloaths	O
a	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
wife	O
turned	O
about	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
O	O
!	O
Lord	O
,	O
Sall	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
!	O
I	O
turned	O
about	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
kicks	O
as	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
;	O
she	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
immediately	O
to	O
put	O
the	O
fire	O
out	O
,	O
not	O
seeking	O
at	O
all	O
after	O
her	O
.	O
Some	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
seeing	O
a	O
smoke	O
,	O
came	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
seeing	O
smoke	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
room	O
,	O
we	O
opened	O
the	O
drawers	O
and	O
found	O
some	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
with	O
some	O
things	O
in	O
them	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
extinguished	O
,	O
we	O
began	O
to	O
examine	O
what	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
.	O
About	O
this	O
time	O
a	O
girl	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
picked	O
up	O
a	O
muslin	O
double	O
ruffle	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
maid	O
had	O
dropped	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
saw	O
her	O
drop	O
it	O
?	O
S.	O
Dalton	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Abram	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
be	O
burnt	O
?	O
S.	O
Dalton	O
.	O
No	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
silver	O
spoons	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lived	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
S.	O
Dalton	O
.	O
Three	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
you	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
?	O
S.	O
Dalton	O
.	O
Because	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
found	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
a	O
suspicion	O
of	O
her	O
dishonesty	O
when	O
you	O
kicked	O
her	O
down	O
stairs	O
?	O
S.	O
Dalton	O
.	O
Only	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
carelessly	O
set	O
the	O
bed	O
on	O
fire	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
.	O
As	O
I	O
and	O
my	O
husband	O
were	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
room	O
,	O
some	O
person	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Dalton	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
and	O
with	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
them	O
and	O
found	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
apron	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
next	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
Lord	O
have	O
mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
came	O
this	O
apron	O
here	O
?	O
And	O
my	O
husband	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
is	O
carelessness	O
in	O
you	O
not	O
to	O
keep	O
your	O
drawers	O
fast	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
latch	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
readily	O
get	O
it	O
open	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
the	O
candle	O
was	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
;	O
Who	O
is	O
there	O
?	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
And	O
the	O
maid	O
answered	O
,	O
Nobody	O
but	O
me	O
,	O
Madam	O
.	O
Then	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
What	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
?	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
there	O
is	O
fire	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
,	O
go	O
down	O
and	O
light	O
the	O
candle	O
as	O
quick	O
as	O
possible	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
she	O
staying	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
for	O
somebody	O
to	O
come	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
which	O
they	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bed	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bed	O
was	O
tucked	O
in	O
very	O
close	O
;	O
and	O
we	O
pulled	O
off	O
the	O
sheets	O
and	O
blankets	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
all	O
on	O
fire	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
they	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
smoke	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
out	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
on	O
fire	O
;	O
here	O
are	O
the	O
remains	O
of	O
several	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
on	O
fire	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
drawers	O
before	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
double	O
ruffles	O
,	O
a	O
gauze	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
black	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
flowered	O
linen	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
large	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
;	O
so	O
looking	O
over	O
the	O
things	O
that	O
were	O
left	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Lord	O
have	O
mercy	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
signifies	O
what	O
is	O
left	O
,	O
so	O
many	O
things	O
are	O
lost	O
!	O
At	O
this	O
juncture	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Bradfield	O
,	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
here	O
is	O
something	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
since	O
you	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
and	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
plain	O
muslin	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
upon	O
this	O
?	O
A.	O
Dalton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
quite	O
unhappy	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
finding	O
my	O
sheets	O
and	O
linen	O
burnt	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
things	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
hear	O
where	O
the	O
girl	O
was	O
,	O
till	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
by	O
much	O
inquiry	O
,	O
found	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
for	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
course	O
of	O
that	O
examination	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
find	O
out	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
you	O
lost	O
?	O
A.	O
Dalton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
told	O
you	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
had	O
picked	O
up	O
some	O
things	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
?	O
A.	O
Dalton	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bradfield	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
father	O
lived	O
?	O
A.	O
Dalton	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
upon	O
her	O
uncle	O
's	O
account	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Kelley	O
's	O
to	O
inquire	O
for	O
her	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
A.	O
Dalton	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
now	O
,	O
good	O
woman	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
heard	O
where	O
the	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
,	O
why	O
did	O
not	O
you	O
search	O
his	O
house	O
next	O
morning	O
?	O
A.	O
Dalton	O
.	O
I	O
really	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
father	O
's	O
house	O
was	O
searched	O
some	O
time	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Abram	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
H.	O
Abram	O
.	O
Turned	O
of	O
fourteen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
an	O
oath	O
?	O
H.	O
Abram	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
shall	O
be	O
punished	O
in	O
another	O
world	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
speak	O
the	O
truth	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
of	O
an	O
errand	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
girl	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Dalton	O
's	O
,	O
who	O
dropt	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
new	O
muslin	O
and	O
a	O
plain	O
double	O
ruffle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
dropt	O
it	O
?	O
H.	O
Abram	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
she	O
coming	O
out	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
,	O
or	O
leisurely	O
.	O
H.	O
Abram	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
out	O
hastily	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
offer	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
ask	O
her	O
any	O
questions	O
?	O
H.	O
Abram	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
dropt	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
?	O
H.	O
Abram	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Bradfield	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
Mr.	O
Dalton	O
?	O
H.	O
Abram	O
.	O
Very	O
lately	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bradfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dalton	O
's	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
February	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
tumult	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
girl	O
,	O
coming	O
in	O
,	O
asked	O
for	O
the	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
had	O
dropt	O
some	O
things	O
.	O
Q.	O
Pray	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Dalton	O
,	O
when	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
,	O
the	O
last	O
time	O
before	O
that	O
?	O
A.	O
Dalton	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
upper	O
drawer	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bradfield	I-pers
cross-examined	O
.	O
When	O
Hannah	B-pers
Abram	I-pers
asked	O
for	O
the	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
went	O
out	O
had	O
dropt	O
some	O
things	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
go	O
out	O
?	O
Bradfield	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
?	O
Bradfield	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
.	O
-	O
Brenton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Dalton	O
's	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
,	O
sitting	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
heard	O
an	O
uncommon	O
noise	O
of	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
running	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
ran	O
through	O
the	O
tap-room	O
with	O
something	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
.	O
Brenton	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
running	O
by	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
and	O
just	O
after	O
she	O
had	O
ran	O
by	O
me	O
a	O
man	O
pick	O
'd	O
up	O
a	O
black	O
silk	O
apron	O
;	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Dalton	O
cry	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
house	O
was	O
on	O
fire	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
three	O
upper	O
drawers	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Dalton	O
putting	O
it	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
bedcloaths	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
witnesses	O
ran	O
and	O
fetched	O
some	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawers	O
,	O
and	O
dipt	O
them	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
put	O
out	O
the	O
fire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Brenton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
about	O
three	O
minutes	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
came	O
back	O
any	O
more	O
till	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
it	O
the	O
black	O
silk	O
apron	O
was	O
found	O
?	O
Was	O
it	O
before	O
or	O
after	O
the	O
girl	O
came	O
running	O
down	O
?	O
Brenton	O
.	O
Upon	O
her	O
running	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
dropt	O
it	O
going	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
black	O
silk	O
apron	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
before	O
she	O
came	O
running	O
down	O
stairs	O
?	O
Brenton	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
any	O
thing	O
being	O
said	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dalton	O
about	O
the	O
apron	O
?	O
Brenton	O
.	O
Not	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
girl	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Upon	O
what	O
occasion	O
did	O
Mrs.	O
Dalton	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
?	O
Brenton	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Dalton	O
called	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
room	O
on	O
fire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Just	O
after	O
the	O
girl	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
apron	O
found	O
,	O
did	O
any-body	O
call	O
in	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
ruffle	O
drop	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pick	O
'd	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Brenton	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
delivered	O
?	O
Brenton	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Brenton	O
.	O
As	O
sober	O
as	O
a	O
judge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Brenton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
assisted	O
at	O
putting	O
the	O
fire	O
out	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
discovery	O
made	O
by	O
the	O
girl	O
after	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
put	O
out	O
or	O
before	O
?	O
Brenton	O
.	O
The	O
apron	O
was	O
before	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
whether	O
the	O
ruffle	O
was	O
found	O
before	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
alarm	O
?	O
Brenton	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
's	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
hurry	O
,	O
and	O
dropping	O
something	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
this	O
apron	O
;	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
a	O
girl	O
brought	O
in	O
the	O
muslin	O
ruffle	O
and	O
some	O
muslin	O
.	O
[	O
Court	O
observed	O
this	O
witness	O
plainly	O
mistook	O
in	O
giving	O
his	O
evidence	O
]	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Belton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
apron	O
dropt	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
tap-room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
found	O
a	O
black	O
apron	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
any	O
alarm	O
of	O
fire	O
just	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Belton	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
master	O
shoved	O
the	O
girl	O
down	O
stairs	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
understand	O
you	O
right	O
,	O
you	O
found	O
the	O
black	O
apron	O
dropt	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
stairs	O
before	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
being	O
shoved	O
by	O
the	O
master	O
,	O
came	O
running	O
down	O
stairs	O
and	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
doors	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
stole	O
any	O
thing	O
from	O
them	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Osborn	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
eight	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
girl	O
,	O
for	O
any	O
thing	O
I	O
knew	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
take	O
her	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
as	O
a	O
servant	O
to-morrow	O
if	O
I	O
wanted	O
one	O
.	O
Rowland	B-pers
Wenfleet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
know	O
her	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
intrusted	O
with	O
every	O
thing	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
her	O
dishonest	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Cowlin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
ever	O
since	O
she	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
very	O
honest	O
parents	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
always	O
bore	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Mering	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
the	O
same	O
effect	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Kelley	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
resided	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
when	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
the	O
least	O
doubt	O
of	O
her	O
honesty	O
.	O
-	O
Kelly	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
his	O
house	O
was	O
searched	O
and	O
she	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
surrendered	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
readily	O
went	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cowlin	I-pers
also	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
these	O
ten	O
years	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
girl	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
knowledge	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
inquired	O
after	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
charge	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
averse	O
to	O
going	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Kegin	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Hayden	I-pers
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Peachy	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Skiers	I-pers
,	O
likewise	O
appeared	O
on	O
her	O
behalf	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
farther	O
arraigned	O
for	O
setting	O
fire	O
to	O
a	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
neither	O
Mr.	O
Dalton	O
,	O
nor	O
any	O
other	O
evidence	O
,	O
gave	O
any	O
proof	O
of	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
being	O
burned	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
was	O
of	O
opinion	O
that	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
acquitted	O
of	O
that	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
thereupon	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
Judge	O
reprehended	O
her	O
conduct	O
,	O
and	O
recommended	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
relations	O
to	O
take	O
better	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
99	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Izack	I-pers
,	O
late	O
of	O
the	B-place
Parish	I-place
of	I-place
Feltham	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
chimney	O
glasses	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
six	O
brass	O
locks	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
galley	O
tiles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Fawkener	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
Nov.	O
1761	O
.	O
+	O
Mr.	O
Payne	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
carpenter	O
at	O
Hammersmith	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
intrusted	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
belonging	O
to	O
'Squire	O
Fawkener	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
do	O
something	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
chimney	O
glasses	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
locks	O
upon	O
the	O
doors	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
in	O
November	O
my	O
servant	O
informed	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
locks	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
yourself	O
?	O
Payne	O
.	O
The	O
26th	O
of	O
November	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
six	O
locks	O
,	O
two	O
chimney	O
glasses	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
galley	O
tiles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
then	O
?	O
Payne	O
.	O
I	O
acquainted	O
Mr.	O
Fawkener	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
consulted	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
Some	O
time	O
in	O
November	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
House	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Fawkener	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
away	O
from	O
thence	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
brass	O
locks	O
and	O
some	O
galley	O
tiles	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
locks	O
off	O
,	O
we	O
concluded	O
to	O
sell	O
the	O
tiles	O
first	O
;	O
but	O
not	O
meeting	O
with	O
a	O
purchaser	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
endeavoured	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
lock	O
.	O
As	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
any-body	O
immediately	O
to	O
buy	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
carried	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hilton	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
Two	O
shillings	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
We	O
got	O
leave	O
for	O
the	O
tiles	O
to	O
remain	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
till	O
we	O
called	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
locks	O
we	O
took	O
home	O
to	O
Izack	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
insides	O
of	O
the	O
locks	O
out	O
;	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
best	O
way	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
.	O
A	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
sell	O
or	O
pawn	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Swithin's-alley	O
,	O
Le	O
cester	O
fields	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Watson	O
's	O
.	O
Then	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
we	O
parted	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
he	O
sold	O
one	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
sold	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
tiles	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
divide	O
the	O
rest	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
lock	O
that	O
he	O
sold	O
he	O
kept	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
that	O
I	O
sold	O
I	O
kept	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
know	O
not	O
what	O
became	O
of	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
chimney	O
glasses	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
We	O
saw	O
none	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
only	O
took	O
brass	O
locks	O
and	O
the	O
galley	O
tiles	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
had	O
you	O
of	O
the	O
first	O
lot	O
that	O
was	O
pawn	O
'd	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
One	O
shilling	O
,	O
my	O
lord	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Gee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
person	O
who	O
first	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
Michealmas	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
chimney	O
glass	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
in	O
the	O
housekeeper	O
's	O
room	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
besides	O
a	O
lookingglass	O
in	O
another	O
chamber	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
brass	O
locks	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
a	O
gentleman	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
there	O
were	O
locks	O
to	O
the	O
doors	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
brass	O
locks	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
of	O
the	O
locks	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
to	O
shew	O
him	O
that	O
the	O
locks	O
had	O
been	O
taken	O
off	O
;	O
and	O
observed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
person	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
off	O
,	O
had	O
broke	O
the	O
boxes	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
false	O
ones	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
acquainting	O
my	O
master	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
ordered	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
in	O
January	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
us	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
doors	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
to	O
get	O
at	O
the	O
things	O
up	O
stairs	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
November	O
Samuel	B-pers
Izack	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
lock	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
pledge	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
2	O
s.	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Hilton	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
after	O
he	O
brought	O
another	O
lock	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
Richard	O
Smith	O
came	O
with	O
one	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
refused	O
taking	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
After	O
this	O
I	O
saw	O
an	O
advertisement	O
of	O
some	O
locks	O
being	O
stole	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
and	O
gave	O
a	O
description	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
they	O
knew	O
them	O
both	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
November	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
and	O
pledged	O
this	O
lock	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
forenoon	O
,	O
as	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
any-body	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
,	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
knew	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
him	O
.	O
Watson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
offer	O
to	O
pledge	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
?	O
Watson	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
tiles	O
;	O
but	O
some	O
were	O
broken	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
refused	O
taking	O
them	O
in	O
pledge	O
.	O
He	O
desired	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
leave	O
them	O
till	O
he	O
called	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
permitted	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
fetched	O
away	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Izack	O
a	O
good	O
many	O
years	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
taken	O
in	O
shoes	O
of	O
him	O
that	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
making	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
lock	O
,	O
saying	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
helping	O
his	O
sister	O
to	O
move	O
household	O
goods	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
or	O
pawn	O
it	O
;	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
[	O
The	O
Court	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
ask	O
Mr.	O
Payne	O
if	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
did	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
charge	O
Smith	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
not	O
concerned	O
in	O
the	O
theft	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Payne	O
answered	O
in	O
the	O
negative	O
]	O
.	O
Constable	O
sworn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
were	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
when	O
Izack	O
and	O
Smith	O
were	O
brought	O
before	O
him	O
-	O
Who	O
was	O
first	O
examined	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
he	O
then	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
,	O
or	O
not	O
till	O
Isaac	O
was	O
examined	O
.	O
Constable	O
.	O
Before	O
his	O
examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
done	O
now	O
?	O
Constable	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Clarke	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
at	O
Kensington	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
he	O
hath	O
wrote	O
for	O
me	O
and	O
kept	O
my	O
books	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
often	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
to	O
write	O
?	O
Clarke	O
.	O
Two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
Christmas	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
weeks	O
together	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
intrusted	O
him	O
to	O
receive	O
money	O
several	O
times	O
by	O
drafts	O
on	O
bankers	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
always	O
behaved	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
intrusted	O
him	O
any	O
time	O
these	O
two	O
years	O
?	O
Clarke	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
parted	O
from	O
him	O
upon	O
account	O
of	O
some	O
charge	O
laid	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
rather	O
have	O
lost	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
than	O
it	O
should	O
have	O
happened	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Walter	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
100	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Bloor	I-pers
.	O
of	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	B-place
George	I-place
,	I-place
Middlesex	I-place
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
quartern	O
loaf	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
d.	O
and	O
three	O
shillings	O
numbered	O
in	O
half	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Matthew	B-pers
Scarrolt	I-pers
.	O
Feb.	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
Matthew	B-pers
Scarrolt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Gravel-lane	B-place
in	I-place
St.	I-place
George	I-place
's	I-place
parish	I-place
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
chandler	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
often	O
lost	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
reason	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
suspect	O
him	O
?	O
Scarrolt	O
.	O
Because	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
faster	O
than	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
could	O
afford	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
would	O
mark	O
me	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
half-pence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
carried	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
who	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
was	O
locked	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
quartern	O
loaf	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
5	O
d.	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
called	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
lodger	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
quartern	O
loaf	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
mentioned	O
the	O
loaf	O
,	O
the	O
officer	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
swear	O
to	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
half	O
pence	O
which	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
under	O
his	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
lay	O
the	O
key	O
also	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
?	O
was	O
he	O
awake	O
?	O
Scarrolt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
stockings	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
to	O
him	O
?	O
Scarrolt	O
.	O
Asked	O
him	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
do	O
so	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
made	O
us	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
shop	O
door	O
locked	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
?	O
Scarrolt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
;	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
key	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
opens	O
the	O
lock	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
door	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
my	O
own	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
his	O
room	O
?	O
Scarrolt	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
let	O
him	O
the	O
room	O
?	O
Scarrolt	O
.	O
For	O
aught	O
I	O
know	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Scarrolt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
put	O
any	O
marked	O
money	O
into	O
your	O
till	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Scarrolt	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
15	O
d.	O
in	O
marked	O
halfpence	O
into	O
my	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
s.	O
9	O
d.	O
of	O
other	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
Q	O
.	O
Of	O
whom	O
did	O
you	O
receive	O
the	O
marked	O
halfpence	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Scarrolt	O
.	O
From	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
there	O
was	O
3	O
s.	O
5	O
d	O
,	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
upon	O
finding	O
you	O
were	O
robbed	O
of	O
the	O
marked	O
money	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Scarrolt	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
had	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
ready	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
went	O
for	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
his	O
room	O
together	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
go	O
up	O
with	O
them	O
?	O
Mrs.	O
Scarrolt	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nor	O
sawer	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
passed	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
went	O
thro	O
'	O
my	O
room	O
below	O
stairs	O
to	O
have	O
him	O
to	O
prison	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Blare	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
headborough-man	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
application	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
I	O
marked	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
halfpence	O
;	O
I	O
marked	O
some	O
with	O
a	O
punch	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
with	O
a	O
file	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Scarrolt	O
,	O
by	O
virtue	O
of	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
to	O
search	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodging	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
I	O
immediately	O
saw	O
a	O
good	O
quantity	O
of	O
half-pence	O
lying	O
in	O
the	O
chair	O
under	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
looking	O
them	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
of	O
the	O
half-pence	O
I	O
had	O
marked	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
for	O
his	O
wages	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
his	O
mistake	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
gave	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Scarrolt	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
that	O
day	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
,	O
when	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
acknowledge	O
the	O
fact	O
?	O
Blare	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
absolutely	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
101	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
feather-bed	O
and	O
bolster	O
,	O
a	O
saucepan	O
,	O
tin	O
boiler	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
February	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Turnmill-street	B-place
,	I-place
Clerkenwell	I-place
,	O
and	O
the	O
latter-end	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
a	O
lodging	O
at	O
2	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
per	O
week	O
ready	O
furnished	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
bed	O
,	O
blankets	O
,	O
sheets	O
drawers	O
,	O
saucepan	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
between	O
the	O
12th	O
and	O
13th	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
carried	O
off	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
when	O
you	O
missed	O
your	O
goods	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
Chick-lane	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Jolly	O
Sailor	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
I	O
secured	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
robbing	O
her	O
lodgings	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
she	O
denied	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
owned	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
directions	O
where	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
things	O
you	O
had	O
lost	O
?	O
Dean	O
.	O
Not	O
directly	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
mention	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Nichols	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
had	O
a	O
lodging	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
and	O
one	O
night	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
after	O
my	O
husband	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
out	O
before	O
we	O
were	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
only	O
the	O
steddle	O
and	O
drawers	O
,	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
particular	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
Eliz	O
.	O
Cox	O
,	O
taken	O
up	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
was	O
no-way	O
concerned	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
any	O
farther	O
than	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
sheets	O
at	O
my	O
desire	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
102	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bladin	I-pers
,	I-pers
alias	I-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
and	O
a	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
lodging	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
13	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
This	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
and	O
flat	O
iron	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Gumber	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gumber	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
and	O
flat	O
iron	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
received	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	B-pers
Price	I-pers
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
to	O
pay	O
a	O
debt	O
she	O
owed	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
103	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Butson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
val	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
September	O
last	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Magdalen	B-pers
Masquerier	I-pers
.	O
++	O
Magdalen	O
Masquerier	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Coventry-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
after	O
the	O
coronation	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
gold	O
ring	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
several	O
;	O
she	O
looked	O
them	O
over	O
and	O
over	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
them	O
strong	O
enough	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
in	O
particular	O
stronger	O
than	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
missed	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
have	O
seen	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
it	O
?	O
M.	O
Masquerier	O
.	O
Before	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
bespoke	O
two	O
very	O
strong	O
ones	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
to	O
call	O
for	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
any	O
more	O
till	O
I	O
saw	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
having	O
taken	O
it	O
at	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
M.	O
Masquerier	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
surprize	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
presence	O
of	O
mind	O
to	O
speak	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Afterwards	O
,	O
upon	O
hearing	O
that	O
some	O
such	O
lost	O
goods	O
were	O
advertised	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
?	O
M.	O
Masquerier	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
but	O
one	O
such	O
strong	O
ring	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
it	O
before	O
her	O
among	O
several	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
saw	O
it	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
exact	O
number	O
of	O
rings	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
M.	O
Masquerier	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
particular	O
strong	O
one	O
I	O
knew	O
from	O
the	O
rest	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
that	O
ring	O
with	O
several	O
others	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
let	O
her	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
without	O
saying	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
M.	O
Masquerier	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
were	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
did	O
you	O
charge	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
the	O
ring	O
?	O
M.	O
Masquerier	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
nor	O
was	O
ever	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
never	O
heard	O
of	O
your	O
ring	O
,	O
you	O
say	O
?	O
M.	O
Masquerier	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Might	O
not	O
the	O
ring	O
have	O
fallen	O
down	O
in	O
your	O
shop	O
?	O
M.	O
Masquerier	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
but	O
she	O
and	O
I.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
search	O
for	O
it	O
narrowly	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
