TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
,	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
;	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
16th	O
and	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
of	O
JULY	O
,	O
1762	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Second	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
;	O
Being	O
the	O
Sixth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honble	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
FLUDYER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
LORD	B-pers
MAYOR	I-pers
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VI	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1762	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
JOHN	B-pers
RYALL	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Fleet-street	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
SAMUEL	B-pers
FLUDYER	I-pers
,	O
Bart	O
.	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Hon	O
.	O
Sir	O
Thomas	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Baron	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
*	O
,	O
the	O
honourable	O
Mr.	O
Justice	O
Bathurst	O
+	O
,	O
Sir	O
Eardley	O
Wilmot	O
,	O
||	O
Knt	O
.	O
Sir	O
William	O
Moreton	O
++	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
,	O
James	O
Eyre	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol	O
Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gibbs	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Gates	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Reading	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Hilton	I-pers
,	O
Philip	B-pers
Neat	I-pers
,	O
Jos	B-pers
Rollo	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Peast	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Ward	I-pers
,	O
Percival	B-pers
Philips	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lee	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Boorshire	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gaff	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Sutton	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Sheridine	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Gaff	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Lake	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Groome	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
176	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Elgar	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
purse	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
pence	O
,	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
foreign	O
silver	O
coin	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
Spanish	O
dollar	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
||	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Keene	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
last	O
June	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Cornhill	B-place
.	O
A	O
woman	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
of	O
a	O
purse	O
with	O
the	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
money	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
;	O
on	O
which	O
she	O
gave	O
my	O
purse	O
into	O
the	O
hand	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bidicey	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
standing	O
at	O
his	O
shop	O
door	O
,	O
came	O
out	O
and	O
pursued	O
him	O
:	O
he	O
took	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
never	O
got	O
my	O
money	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
attempted	O
to	O
push	O
me	O
down	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bidicey	O
This	O
lady	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
her	O
pocket	O
picked	O
.	O
I	O
offered	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
woman	O
which	O
she	O
had	O
hold	O
of	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
woman	O
has	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
that	O
man	O
[	O
pointing	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
]	O
.	O
He	O
directly	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
after	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
down	O
Pope's-Head	O
Alley	O
,	O
and	O
Swithen's-Lane	O
,	O
down	O
Lombard	O
Street	O
,	O
round	O
St.	O
Mary	O
Woolnoth	O
's	O
Church	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
blind	O
alley	O
that	O
leads	O
into	O
Sherborne-Lane	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
never	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sight	O
,	O
but	O
just	O
as	O
he	O
turned	O
the	O
corners	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
frighted	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
several	O
people	O
pursued	O
him	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
myself	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
thing	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
that	O
she	O
could	O
own	O
.	O
We	O
found	O
about	O
seven	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
bank	O
note	O
of	O
ten	O
pounds	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
upwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Dawson	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
an	O
officer	O
in	O
the	O
Marshal	O
's	O
Court	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
done	O
business	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
do	O
any	O
thing	O
bad	O
in	O
my	O
days	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
goes	O
to	O
horse	O
races	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
horses	O
.	O
I	O
suppose	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
sporting	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Dawson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
salesman	O
in	O
Monmouth-Street	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
made	O
him	O
cloaths	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
supply	O
him	O
with	O
laced	O
cloaths	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
these	O
places	O
?	O
Dawson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
.	O
Caleb	O
Dawson	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
had	O
things	O
of	O
me	O
and	O
my	O
brother	O
:	O
he	O
always	O
paid	O
very	O
honestly	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wooley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
livery	O
stables	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
horses	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
horses	O
to	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Always	O
industrious	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
shoe	O
and	O
farrier	O
his	O
horses	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
live	O
?	O
Murray	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
lodge	O
in	O
Gray	O
's	O
Inn-Lane	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Hogen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
upwards	O
of	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
bore	O
always	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
three	O
horses	O
stood	O
with	O
me	O
upwards	O
of	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Hogen	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Horse	O
and	O
Groom	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn-Lane	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
use	O
to	O
let	O
these	O
horses	O
out	O
.	O
Hogen	O
.	O
Not	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
use	O
did	O
he	O
put	O
them	O
to	O
?	O
Hogen	O
.	O
He	O
never	O
sold	O
one	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
177	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jer	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
boots	O
,	O
value	O
five	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
iron	O
wedge	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Harvey	I-pers
,	O
June	O
19	O
||	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
178	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
flock	O
bed	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
two	O
linen	O
sheets	O
,	O
one	O
tin	O
kettle	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
bellows	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Frances	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
179	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Frances	B-pers
Rawlins	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
seven	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
May	O
28	O
.~	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Brownlow-street	B-place
by	I-place
Drury-lane	I-place
.	O
I	O
understood	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
watchman	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
for	O
her	O
husband	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
.	O
I	O
paid	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
out	O
of	O
which	O
she	O
spent	O
a	O
penny	O
.	O
The	O
constable	O
pays	O
the	O
watchmen	O
quarterly	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
but	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
wife	O
of	O
one	O
Newman	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
some	O
more	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
till	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
her	O
;	O
they	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
some	O
money	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
we	O
opened	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
three	O
shillings	O
.	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
that	O
money	O
?	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
certainly	O
was	O
mine	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
Soon	O
after	O
he	O
called	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
seven	O
shillings	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
May	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gay	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
charge	O
.	O
They	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
some	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
seven	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
till	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
three	O
shillings	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
before	O
justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
never	O
did	O
such	O
a	O
thing	O
before	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Branding	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
[	O
Imprisonment	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
180	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Carey	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
saw	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
one	O
spade	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
one	O
hammer	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
pence	O
,	O
five	O
pictures	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
trowel	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Lewis	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1	O
.~	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
181	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ashford	I-pers
and	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cock	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Rumbold	I-pers
;	O
two	O
hens	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Baringarious	B-pers
Chadwick	I-pers
,	O
June	O
9	O
.~	O
Both	O
guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
182	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Ring	I-pers
.	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
walnut	O
tree	O
tea	O
chest	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
linen	O
apron	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Laurence	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
.	O
July	O
12	O
++	O
.	O
Laurence	B-pers
Crow	I-pers
.	O
I	O
once	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
reduced	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
promiscuously	O
.	O
Being	O
destitute	O
of	O
a	O
servant	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
for	O
her	O
victuals	O
and	O
drink	O
,	O
She	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
Saturday	O
,	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
Monday	O
.	O
She	O
never	O
lay	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
among	O
the	O
people	O
in	O
the	O
tap	O
room	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchiefs	O
on	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
by	O
the	O
mark	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
justice	O
Welch	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
:	O
she	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
upon	O
being	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
the	O
other	O
handkerchief	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
apron	O
on	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
183	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
,	O
June	O
28	O
+	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Partridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
James's-street	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
a	O
box	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
pumps	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Mouth	O
Inn	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
eight	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
pumps	O
.	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
boots	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
at	O
Birmingham	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
offered	O
for	O
sale	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
stopped	O
,	O
and	O
were	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
mark	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
your	O
property	O
?	O
Partridge	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
make	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
of	O
those	O
I	O
sent	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
the	O
box	O
and	O
all	O
were	O
lost	O
together	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Maning	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Bull	O
and	O
Mouth	O
Inn	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
box	O
directed	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Taylor	O
of	O
Birmingham	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
booked	O
with	O
the	O
goods	O
that	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
house	O
to	O
Birmingham	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
November	O
,	O
1761	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Alsworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cordwainer	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
,	O
on	O
Monday	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
this	O
pair	O
of	O
pumps	O
[	O
producing	O
one	O
]	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
for	O
sale	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
her	O
brother	O
made	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
her	O
brother	O
was	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
brother	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
proved	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
deliver	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
no	O
more	O
of	O
her	O
till	O
July	O
the	O
7th	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
her	O
brother	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
never	O
a	O
brother	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
,	O
a	O
journey	O
man	O
shoemaker	O
of	O
Wolverhampton	O
,	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
to	O
bring	O
her	O
up	O
to	O
London	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
same	O
she	O
said	O
before	O
Mr.	O
Welch	O
when	O
he	O
committed	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
184	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
six	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
muslin	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
sixpence	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
linen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
three	O
linen	O
napkins	O
,	O
value	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
,	O
two	O
laced	O
caps	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
one	O
laced	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Cooley	I-pers
,	O
December	O
21st	O
+	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Cooley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Henry	B-pers
Cooley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
goods	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
December	O
last	O
:	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
shirts	O
(	O
and	O
caps	O
I	O
lost	O
before	O
)	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
muslin	O
neckloius	O
,	O
three	O
napkins	O
,	O
two	O
laced	O
caps	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
laced	O
handkerchief	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
warning	O
when	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
little	O
box	O
.	O
She	O
made	O
an	O
excuse	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
for	O
water	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
there	O
was	O
none	O
wanted	O
.	O
She	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
catch	O
her	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
lighter	O
pair	O
of	O
heels	O
than	O
her	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
two	O
shirts	O
and	O
laced	O
caps	O
:	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
rightly	O
tell	O
then	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
Robert	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
brought	O
a	O
shirt	O
about	O
this	O
time	O
twelve	O
months	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sent	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
her	O
mistress	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
name	O
was	O
Cooley	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
neckcloths	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeves	O
brought	O
I	O
believe	O
in	O
August	O
.	O
A	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
widow	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
Mrs.	O
Cooley	O
's	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
maid	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
words	O
about	O
the	O
linen	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
going	O
for	O
a	O
pail	O
of	O
water	O
.	O
Her	O
mistress	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
need	O
of	O
any	O
.	O
She	O
run	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cooley	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Cooley	O
should	O
have	O
a	O
lighter	O
pair	O
of	O
heels	O
than	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
catched	O
her	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
My	O
mistress	O
had	O
set	O
me	O
to	O
clean	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
pail	O
to	O
fetch	O
some	O
water	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
serve	O
me	O
as	O
she	O
did	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
better	O
pay	O
me	O
my	O
wages	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
six	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
whole	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
the	O
goods	O
for	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
redeemed	O
them	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
expence	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Cooley	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
send	O
her	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
pawn	O
?	O
Ann	B-pers
Cooley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
cap	O
,	O
and	O
apron	O
,	O
two	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
and	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
constable	O
that	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
fir	O
st	O
time	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
they	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
charged	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
with	O
two	O
caps	O
and	O
some	O
shirts	O
:	O
she	O
stood	O
it	O
out	O
that	O
Mrs.	O
Cooley	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
for	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
that	O
they	O
made	O
it	O
up	O
;	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Cooley	O
fetched	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
at	O
her	O
own	O
expence	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
servant	O
with	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
turned	O
her	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
finding	O
more	O
things	O
missing	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
was	O
two	O
months	O
afterwards	O
.	O
She	O
insisted	O
that	O
her	O
mistress	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
;	O
but	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
much	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
said	O
her	O
mistress	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
these	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
said	O
the	O
reason	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
these	O
before	O
was	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
her	O
fright	O
she	O
had	O
forgot	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
but	O
by	O
her	O
mistress	O
's	O
consent	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
me	O
there	O
was	O
due	O
forty	O
shillings	O
for	O
wages	O
:	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
it	O
before	O
Mrs.	O
Cooley	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
185	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
books	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Cefas	B-pers
Salter	I-pers
,	O
July	O
1st	O
+	O
.	O
Cefas	O
Salter	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
bookseller	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Gray's-Inn	O
passage	O
,	O
Red-lyon	O
Square	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
three	O
books	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Wade	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
sold	O
to	O
him	O
again	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
.	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
them	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
following	O
:	O
having	O
more	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
that	O
these	O
were	O
the	O
same	O
I	O
had	O
sold	O
when	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ask	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
got	O
them	O
?	O
Wade	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
brother	O
that	O
lived	O
at	O
Chatham	O
,	O
that	O
had	O
bought	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
bought	O
odd	O
volumes	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
months	O
,	O
one	O
a	O
week	O
or	O
so	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
through	O
Queen-Street	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
two	O
story	O
books	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
me	O
and	O
brought	O
me	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
told	O
his	O
wife	O
to	O
search	O
me	O
.	O
He	O
brought	O
in	O
a	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
conveyed	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
my	O
petticoat	O
.	O
He	O
carried	O
me	O
before	O
justice	O
Welch	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
me	O
to	O
Bridewell	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Pearson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
know	O
her	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
she	O
always	O
behaved	O
honest	O
and	O
well	O
;	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
her	O
father	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
his	O
houshold	O
work	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Has	O
she	O
a	O
brother	O
?	O
Pearson	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
a	O
brother	O
in	O
the	O
army	O
,	O
but	O
where	O
he	O
is	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gardner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
:	O
she	O
and	O
her	O
father	O
lived	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
girl	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
father	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
afflicted	O
for	O
two	O
years	O
with	O
fits	O
;	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
school	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
these	O
fits	O
by	O
a	O
fall	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
her	O
ever	O
since	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
.	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Aspridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
her	O
and	O
her	O
parents	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
people	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
to	O
the	O
contrary	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Mowland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
birth	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Wade	I-pers
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Wade	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
but	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
she	O
lives	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
books	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
186	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Rustid	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
++	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
eleventh	O
of	O
June	O
between	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
o'clock	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
up	O
the	O
Poultry	B-place
,	O
near	O
the	O
compter	O
:	O
I	O
felt	O
a	O
violent	O
twitch	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
wherein	O
this	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
was	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
lady	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
that	O
my	O
pocket	O
was	O
picked	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
stood	O
by	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
pickpocket	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
word	O
pickpocket	O
:	O
he	O
ran	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
pickpocket	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
;	O
and	O
a	O
young	O
lad	O
run	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
also	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
perceived	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
short	O
into	O
a	O
court	O
.	O
Just	O
as	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
upper	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
he	O
was	O
stopped	O
:	O
the	O
young	O
fellow	O
and	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
people	O
followed	O
us	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
picked	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
We	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
Poultry	O
compter	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
appeared	O
before	O
my	O
lord	O
mayor	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
picked	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
when	O
I	O
felt	O
the	O
twitch	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
time	O
I	O
cried	O
stop	O
thief	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
same	O
man	O
as	O
run	O
.	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
and	O
pointed	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
pickpocket	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
from	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
cried	O
out	O
stop	O
thief	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
?	O
Simpson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
sight	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
:	O
the	O
gentleman	O
came	O
one	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
I	O
run	O
to	O
apprehend	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
among	O
the	O
people	O
;	O
the	O
gentleman	O
said	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
searched	O
there	O
was	O
nothing	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
187	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Moses	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hempen	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
two	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
ninety	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
pimento	O
,	O
value	O
sixty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
,	O
July	O
the	O
2	O
d	O
++	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Plain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
sight	O
.	O
I	O
belong	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
My	O
master	O
has	O
lost	O
pimento	O
three	O
different	O
times	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
warehouse	O
,	O
but	O
by	O
whom	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
up	O
several	O
nights	O
to	O
watch	O
the	O
thief	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
home	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Whitehead	I-pers
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
warehouse	O
,	O
concealed	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
lives	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
on	O
both	O
sides	O
the	O
court	O
.	O
About	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
four	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
the	O
court	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
under	O
a	O
gateway	O
in	O
a	O
posture	O
to	O
ease	O
himself	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
up	O
the	O
court	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
any	O
thing	O
was	O
stirring	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
we	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
:	O
the	O
place	O
he	O
got	O
over	O
is	O
upwards	O
of	O
seven	O
foot	O
high	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
there	O
.	O
His	O
excuse	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
a	O
pidgeon	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Branham	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
warehouse	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
put	O
the	O
bags	O
and	O
things	O
to	O
rights	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
that	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
bag	O
removed	O
from	O
the	O
warehouse	O
into	O
the	O
yard	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
ladder	O
set	O
at	O
the	O
gate	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
high	O
is	O
the	O
warehouse	O
?	O
Branham	O
.	O
Three	O
story	O
high	O
.	O
He	O
offered	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
baker	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
till	O
five	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
mackerel	O
at	O
Billingsgate	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
came	O
past	O
Mincing-lane	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
pidgeon	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
flew	O
away	O
;	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
drawn	O
sword	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
jumped	O
over	O
to	O
save	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
run	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
hide	O
myself	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
of	O
you	O
see	O
me	O
move	O
the	O
bag	O
to	O
the	O
first	O
floor	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Jonas	B-pers
Nathan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
intrusted	O
him	O
with	O
things	O
of	O
value	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
through	O
him	O
.	O
First	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
sober	O
,	O
honest	O
,	O
hardworking	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
employed	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
goods	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
bills	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
lost	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Second	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
bring	O
bread	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
merchant	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
missed	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
Third	O
Witness	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
12	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
supplied	O
him	O
with	O
money	O
.	O
I	O
take	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
honest	O
boy	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
188	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Thorne	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
jack	O
plane	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
oil	O
stone	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Bowdler	I-pers
,	O
June	O
7th	O
++	O
.	O
William	O
Bowdler	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
acarpenter	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
jack	O
plane	O
and	O
an	O
oil	O
stone	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
at	O
noon	O
.	O
My	O
next	O
door	O
neighbour	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shop	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	O
the	O
Cock	O
in	O
the	O
Corner	O
.	O
I	O
ran	O
after	O
him	O
up	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
Surgeons	O
Hall	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
both	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
asked	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
for	O
them	O
as	O
he	O
knew	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
man	O
at	O
home	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
met	O
a	O
carpenter	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
lend	O
me	O
a	O
plane	O
and	O
oil	O
stone	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
bring	O
them	O
home	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
that	O
I	O
met	O
is	O
William	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
:	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
there	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
189	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Orput	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
nine	O
ounces	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
forty-five	O
shillings	O
,	O
nine	O
ounces	O
of	O
silk	O
covered	O
with	O
silver	O
,	O
value	O
forty-five	O
shillings	O
,	O
nine	O
ounces	O
of	O
silver	O
gilt	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
value	O
forty-five	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
and	I-pers
Co	I-pers
.	I-pers
and	O
Co.	O
And	O
Susan	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
July	O
12	O
*	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
This	O
here	O
Jemmet	O
is	O
a	O
workman	O
to	O
us	O
;	O
he	O
is	O
employed	O
to	O
make	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
brocades	O
,	O
Orput	O
is	O
his	O
apprentice	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
found	O
great	O
deficiencies	O
of	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
wanting	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
what	O
was	O
given	O
him	O
to	O
make	O
his	O
work	O
.	O
We	O
sent	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
he	O
could	O
account	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
himself	O
was	O
innocent	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
mistrusted	O
Orput	O
his	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
which	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
it	O
most	O
adviseable	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
Orput	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
boy	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
warehouse	O
,	O
my	O
partner	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
now	O
going	O
before	O
a	O
magistrate	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
the	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
you	O
have	O
taken	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
seemed	O
much	O
confused	O
;	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
on	O
the	O
12th	O
of	O
June	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
got	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
only	O
way	O
to	O
have	O
any	O
favour	O
shewn	O
him	O
,	O
was	O
to	O
confess	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
or	O
otherwise	O
he	O
would	O
be	O
hanged	O
.	O
The	O
boy	O
immediately	O
confessed	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
officer	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
as	O
we	O
went	O
along	O
to	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
an	O
aunt	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
who	O
sold	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
at	O
sundry	O
times	O
;	O
for	O
which	O
she	O
sometimes	O
gave	O
him	O
eighteen	O
pence	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
sometimes	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
very	O
rarely	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
not	O
above	O
once	O
;	O
this	O
he	O
confessed	O
again	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
On	O
which	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
his	O
aunt	O
,	O
who	O
strongly	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
or	O
that	O
she	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
her	O
coming	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
:	O
but	O
on	O
confronting	O
them	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
the	O
boy	O
taxed	O
her	O
so	O
close	O
,	O
that	O
by	O
degrees	O
she	O
confessed	O
almost	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
he	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
confession	O
taken	O
in	O
writing	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
whether	O
it	O
was	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
confess	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
to	O
have	O
received	O
the	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
burnt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
,	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
under	O
pretence	O
of	O
being	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
lace	O
burnt	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
received	O
more	O
money	O
than	O
she	O
gave	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
At	O
first	O
,	O
when	O
Orput	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
brought	O
to	O
your	O
house	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
deny	O
it	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
totally	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
lad	O
had	O
made	O
an	O
confession	O
,	O
promise	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
expected	O
any	O
favour	O
he	O
must	O
confess	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
On	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Orput	O
thought	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
confess	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
receive	O
favour	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
intend	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
confessed	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
shewn	O
him	O
favour	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
exempt	O
from	O
any	O
punishment	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Jemmet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
.	O
I	O
work	O
in	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bad	O
opinion	O
lately	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
by	O
keeping	O
disorderly	O
hours	O
;	O
and	O
missing	O
the	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
the	O
masters	O
I	O
was	O
employed	O
by	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
complaint	O
of	O
the	O
gentlemen	O
I	O
work	O
for	O
on	O
carrying	O
home	O
the	O
last	O
piece	O
that	O
I	O
made	O
during	O
the	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
me	O
:	O
they	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deficiency	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
tenth	O
of	O
June	O
I	O
carried	O
it	O
home	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
warehouse	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
books	O
that	O
there	O
were	O
36	O
ounces	O
deficient	O
in	O
the	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
:	O
on	O
that	O
they	O
agreed	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nobody	O
else	O
about	O
that	O
was	O
intrusted	O
that	O
could	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
so	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
warrant	O
of	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
upon	O
suspicion	O
;	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
:	O
he	O
at	O
last	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
there	O
no	O
promise	O
made	O
of	O
favour	O
?	O
Jemmet	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Charles	B-pers
Piquet	I-pers
said	O
,	O
that	O
if	O
he	O
confessed	O
who	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
received	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
if	O
not	O
,	O
he	O
must	O
expect	O
no	O
mercy	O
.	O
He	O
made	O
many	O
hesitations	O
of	O
wanting	O
his	O
parents	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
deal	O
of	O
sorrow	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
he	O
confess	O
this	O
?	O
Jemmet	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
this	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
make	O
that	O
confession	O
in	O
the	O
coach	O
?	O
Jemmet	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
who	O
he	O
disposed	O
of	O
it	O
to	O
?	O
Jemmet	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
his	O
aunt	O
burnt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
.	O
Upon	O
this	O
,	O
a	O
warrant	O
was	O
granted	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
:	O
she	O
has	O
been	O
at	O
my	O
shop	O
several	O
times	O
:	O
she	O
brought	O
burnt	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
it	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Orput	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
wronged	O
my	O
master	O
,	O
nor	O
nobody	O
else	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Creed	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
,	O
and	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoners	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Jordan	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
William	B-pers
Orput	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
asked	O
several	O
acquaintance	O
that	O
knew	O
his	O
master	O
and	O
him	O
;	O
and	O
they	O
said	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
very	O
well	O
.	O
John	O
Hills	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Aller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
birth	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
bore	O
an	O
honest	O
character	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Susan	B-pers
Creed	I-pers
fifteen	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
lived	O
with	O
the	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
of	O
this	O
Orput	O
.	O
Daniel	B-pers
Stilwell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
lad	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Cane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
seven	O
or	O
eight	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Webster	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
from	O
his	O
birth	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
woman	O
many	O
years	O
:	O
I	O
live	O
very	O
near	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
she	O
get	O
her	O
living	O
?	O
Webster	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
a	O
charing	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Bocock	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Orput	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
very	O
honest	O
,	O
and	O
sober	O
,	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Gilman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
amiss	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Benson	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Creed	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
always	O
an	O
honest	O
woman	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
her	O
living	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Linnet	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
twenty-five	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
always	O
bore	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
an	O
honest	O
,	O
industrious	O
and	O
just	O
woman	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Lefose	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
her	O
from	O
her	O
infancy	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
dishonest	O
of	O
her	O
.	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
190	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Alice	B-pers
Wadington	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
gown	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
calimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
holland	O
shift	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gadsby	I-pers
++	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gadsby	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
black	O
callimanco	O
petticoat	O
,	O
and	O
shift	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
own	O
room	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
a	O
husband	O
?	O
Gadsby	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
a	O
husband	O
,	O
but	O
know	O
not	O
whether	O
he	O
is	O
alive	O
or	O
no	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
left	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
work	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
.	O
She	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
;	O
we	O
slept	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
bed	O
.	O
She	O
confessed	O
that	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
gentlewoman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
sold	O
my	O
gown	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
,	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
to	O
who	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
pawned	O
the	O
petticoat	O
and	O
shift	O
.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Freer	I-pers
.	O
My	O
brother	O
is	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
in	O
this	O
petticoat	O
and	O
shift	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
]	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Grave	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
brought	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
gown	O
in	O
Rag	O
Fair	O
for	O
seven	O
shillings	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
believed	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
the	O
petticoat	O
for	O
five	O
shillings	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
shift	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
at	O
Mr	O
.	O
Freer	O
's	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
great	O
necessity	O
;	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
make	O
them	O
good	O
again	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
191	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
on	O
James	B-pers
Kettle	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
him	O
one	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
four	O
shillings	O
,	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
numbered	O
,	O
three	O
razors	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
pence	O
,	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
twelve	O
pence	O
,	O
one	O
clasp	O
knife	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
May	O
23	O
+	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Kettle	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
foot	O
,	O
coming	O
from	O
Wapping	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
friends	O
to	O
Rumford	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
stopped	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
prisoners	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
Hunter	O
the	O
Evidence	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
not	O
yet	O
taken	O
;	O
they	O
stopped	O
me	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
three	O
o'clock	O
between	B-place
the	I-place
Turnpike	I-place
and	I-place
New	I-place
Vauxhall	I-place
;	O
they	O
swore	O
a	O
great	O
oath	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
they	O
wanted	O
;	O
they	O
held	O
me	O
up	O
against	O
the	O
pails	O
,	O
and	O
threatened	O
to	O
knock	O
my	O
brains	O
out	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
resistance	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
from	O
my	O
pocket	O
with	O
a	O
linen	O
waistcoat	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
two	O
shillings	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
a	O
clasp	O
knife	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
breeches	O
pocket	O
,	O
three	O
razors	O
in	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
coat	O
pocket	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
razors	O
?	O
Kettle	O
.	O
I	O
shave	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
any	O
noise	O
or	O
resistance	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
press-gang	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
should	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
willing	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
strip	O
me	O
of	O
my	O
stockings	O
and	O
shirt	O
.	O
The	O
evidence	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
make	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
his	O
way	O
off	O
.	O
I	O
discovered	O
it	O
to	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Monday	O
and	O
described	O
all	O
four	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
were	O
they	O
first	O
taken	O
?	O
Kettle	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
last	O
Friday	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
that	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
him	O
since	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
your	O
things	O
again	O
?	O
Kettle	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
them	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
positive	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
are	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
robbed	O
you	O
?	O
Kettle	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
positive	O
:	O
three	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
water	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
took	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
your	O
pocket	O
?	O
Kettle	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
all	O
four	O
round	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
who	O
took	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
drawn	O
in	O
by	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
that	O
morning	O
:	O
they	O
happened	O
of	O
nobody	O
:	O
they	O
stopped	O
this	O
man	O
between	O
three	O
and	O
four	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
Mitchell	O
and	O
Hardy	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
stood	O
before	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
from	O
him	O
three	O
razors	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
are	O
the	O
others	O
?	O
Hunter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
-	O
Waklin	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
Waklin	O
that	O
is	O
dead	O
;	O
he	O
died	O
last	O
week	O
or	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
them	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
it	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
to	O
a	O
young	O
fellow	O
that	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
sea	O
:	O
Mitchell	O
took	O
two	O
shillings	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
that	O
we	O
never	O
saw	O
a	O
farthing	O
of	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
napkin	O
with	O
some	O
boiled	O
pork	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
man	O
the	O
pork	O
.	O
Mitchell	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
some	O
stockings	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
have	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
a	O
good	O
pair	O
on	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
let	O
the	O
man	O
go	O
;	O
and	O
he	O
wanted	O
his	O
shirt	O
;	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
not	O
to	O
take	O
it	O
.	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fielding	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
king	O
's	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
admitted	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Clifton	I-pers
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
are	O
not	O
taken	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
my	O
information	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
were	O
taken	O
by	O
my	O
information	O
.	O
Mitchell	O
has	O
been	O
down	O
to	O
Yarmouth	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
my	O
information	O
on	O
Friday	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
were	O
taken	O
on	O
Saturday	O
.	O
Oliver	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
clock	O
and	O
watch	O
maker	O
,	O
but	O
keep	O
a	O
publick	O
house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
for	O
or	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Three	O
Tuns	O
in	O
Cable	O
street	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
Hunter	O
first	O
;	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
him	O
told	O
me	O
a	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
lane	O
was	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
used	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
they	O
never	O
behaved	O
ill	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
Hunter	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
at	O
four	O
of	O
the	O
clock	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
hours	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
.	O
Mitchell	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
a	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
Hardy	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
ever	O
since	O
I	O
was	O
eleven	O
years	O
old	O
;	O
my	O
friends	O
are	O
130	O
miles	O
off	O
Hyde-Park	O
Corner	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
about	O
this	O
affair	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
For	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Collins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
Richard	B-pers
Mitchell	I-pers
ever	O
since	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
first	O
married	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
eighteen	O
years	O
ago	O
to-morrow	O
morning	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
Hunter	O
?	O
Collins	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Mitchell	O
's	O
mother	O
lived	O
near	O
me	O
in	O
New	O
Gravel	O
Lane	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
Mitchell	O
's	O
mother	O
and	O
him	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
192	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Sullingwood	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
James	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
,	O
one	O
quart	O
silver	O
mug	O
,	O
value	O
seven	O
pounds	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Webb	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Charles	O
,	O
September	O
25	O
,	O
1760	O
.	O
For	O
want	O
of	O
room	O
in	O
this	O
paper	O
,	O
see	O
the	O
trial	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hicks	I-pers
his	O
accomplice	O
,	O
No	O
.	O
17	O
in	O
Sir	O
Matthew	B-pers
Blackiston	I-pers
's	O
mayoralty	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
193	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Rock	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Clare	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
194	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
M'Gee	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Rose	B-pers
his	I-pers
wife	I-pers
:	O
he	O
likewise	O
stood	O
charged	O
on	O
the	O
coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
for	O
manslaughter	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Blane	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Rosemary	O
Lane	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
Sparrow	O
's	O
Corner	O
,	O
Little	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
ninth	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
:	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
bacon	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
His	O
wife	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
a	O
crowd	O
of	O
people	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
liver	O
to	O
eat	O
with	O
the	O
bacon	O
for	O
supper	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
very	O
drunk	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
was	O
he	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
fell	O
down	O
several	O
times	O
.	O
She	O
cursed	O
and	O
swore	O
most	O
prodigiously	O
.	O
A	O
cart	O
loaded	O
with	O
green	O
beans	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Tower	O
Hill	O
to	O
cross	O
the	O
kennel	O
;	O
as	O
the	O
cart	O
was	O
come	O
near	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
blow	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
fell	O
;	O
the	O
wheel	O
run	O
over	O
her	O
he	O
stooped	O
as	O
though	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
catch	O
her	O
up	O
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
wheel	O
was	O
gone	O
over	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
to	O
lay	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
driver	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Manslaughter	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
195	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Avery	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
canvas	O
bag	O
,	O
value	O
one	O
penny	O
,	O
2	O
guineas	O
,	O
one	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
and	O
six	O
pence	O
,	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
,	O
June	O
29	O
*	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Parker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
look	O
after	O
my	O
door	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
about	O
eight	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
bake-house	O
to	O
fetch	O
a	O
two	O
penny	O
loaf	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
was	O
you	O
gone	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
above	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
her	O
on	O
the	O
bench	O
where	O
I	O
left	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
money	O
to	O
pay	O
away	O
that	O
day	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
upon	O
the	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
fearing	O
I	O
should	O
forget	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
money	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
nineteen	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
that	O
made	O
twenty	O
pounds	O
,	O
four	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
half	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
five	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
,	O
which	O
made	O
twenty	O
five	O
pounds	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
blame	O
,	O
not	O
the	O
girl	O
.	O
The	O
chamber	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
so	O
she	O
opened	O
no	O
lock	O
.	O
It	O
had	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
called	O
that	O
day	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
a	O
great	O
while	O
so	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
that	O
day	O
.	O
I	O
intended	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
look	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
hear	O
a	O
sermon	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
miss	O
it	O
till	O
Thursday	O
night	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
hunted	O
every	O
where	O
.	O
I	O
rummmaged	O
up	O
stairs	O
and	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
to	O
speak	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
;	O
and	O
on	O
Monday	O
morning	O
I	O
taxed	O
her	O
about	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
did	O
nobody	O
come	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
that	O
took	O
something	O
out	O
?	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
somebody	O
had	O
taken	O
something	O
that	O
did	O
not	O
belong	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
me	O
neither	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
took	O
something	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
forgive	O
you	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
talk	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
tell	O
;	O
you	O
had	O
as	O
good	O
tell	O
;	O
for	O
if	O
you	O
have	O
broke	O
into	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
forgive	O
you	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
hear	O
me	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
she	O
heard	O
you	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
She	O
heard	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
laughed	O
at	O
me	O
.	O
She	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
house	O
.	O
A	O
person	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
warrant	O
on	O
suspicion	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
the	O
Providence	O
of	O
God	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
warrant	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Bell	O
saw	O
her	O
buying	O
a	O
cardinal	O
.	O
She	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
.	O
Said	O
I	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
fault	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
forgive	O
her	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
will	O
deliver	O
the	O
rest	O
.	O
She	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
near	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
from	O
justice	O
Berry	O
:	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
suspicion	O
:	O
for	O
several	O
days	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
her	O
;	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
surrendered	O
.	O
On	O
Friday	O
morning	O
following	O
she	O
sent	O
word	O
she	O
would	O
surrender	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
sorry	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
done	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
told	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
;	O
then	O
Mr.	O
Cragg	O
brought	O
me	O
that	O
message	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
Friday	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
the	O
justice	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
contented	O
with	O
what	O
was	O
left	O
,	O
be	O
it	O
what	O
it	O
will	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
said	O
I	O
must	O
have	O
a	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
headborough	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
came	O
there	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
need	O
not	O
part	O
with	O
any	O
thing	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
hard	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
return	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
about	O
sixteen	O
pounds	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
how	O
she	O
laid	O
the	O
money	O
out	O
?	O
Parker	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
bought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
them	O
I	O
gave	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
so	O
kind	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
God	O
bless	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
m	O
of	O
you	O
before	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
jury	O
and	O
my	O
lord	O
will	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
consideration	O
to	O
do	O
you	O
no	O
hurt	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
my	O
fault	O
in	O
laying	O
that	O
temptation	O
in	O
her	O
way	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
the	O
court	O
will	O
it	O
take	O
into	O
consideration	O
;	O
for	O
God	O
Almighty	O
will	O
provide	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
surrendered	O
herself	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
was	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
she	O
had	O
bought	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
Three	O
witnesses	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
from	O
her	O
infancy	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
196	O
.	O
(	O
L	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
deal	O
box	O
,	O
value	O
three	O
pence	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
German	O
flute	O
,	O
value	O
ten	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
++	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
abook	O
keeper	O
to	O
the	O
Winchester	O
stage	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
took	O
an	O
outside	O
place	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Winchester	O
.	O
The	O
box	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
Bristol	O
by	O
the	O
Bristol	O
machine	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
sat	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
hours	O
with	O
two	O
others	O
.	O
The	O
box	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
where	O
he	O
sat	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
when	O
the	O
other	O
men	O
left	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
just	O
stepped	O
from	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
gone	O
in	O
the	O
yard	O
among	O
the	O
people	O
.	O
I	O
caused	O
the	O
Winchester	O
and	O
Bath	O
coaches	O
to	O
be	O
unloaded	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
found	O
;	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
hurry	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
put	O
in	O
through	O
mistake	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
into	O
the	O
other	O
yard	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
must	O
know	O
something	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
Before	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
he	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
said	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
tell	O
where	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
lanthorn	O
and	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boot	O
of	O
the	O
Winchester	O
coach	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
besides	O
?	O
Richard	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
several	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
the	O
box-up	O
in	O
the	O
boot	O
of	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
I	O
lighted	O
him	O
up	O
with	O
it	O
to	O
the	O
Winchester	O
coach	O
with	O
a	O
candle	O
and	O
lanthorn	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Whether	O
the	O
coach	O
was	O
unloaded	O
at	O
all	O
?	O
Richards	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
loaded	O
and	O
unloaded	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
it	O
was	O
loaded	O
again	O
the	O
prisoner	O
put	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Walter	B-pers
Lesley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
.	O
The	O
box	O
was	O
missing	O
before	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
.	O
The	O
gentleman	O
and	O
his	O
wife	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
but	O
that	O
two	O
ladies	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Gray	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
take	O
me	O
into	O
another	O
room	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
confess	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
the	O
ruin	O
of	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
was	O
convicted	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
coach	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
boot	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bodington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
They	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
prisoner	O
into	O
custody	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
hoped	O
they	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
lace	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
on	O
breaking	O
it	O
open	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
alderman	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
German	O
flute	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
ordered	O
down	O
to	O
Winchester	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
captain	O
's	O
clerks	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
with	O
a	O
friend	O
to	O
the	O
gravel	O
pits	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
in	O
liquor	O
;	O
from	O
thence	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
and	O
got	O
worse	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
what	O
happened	O
afterwards	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Hamilton	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
child	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
both	O
his	O
father	O
and	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
thing	O
to	O
his	O
discredit	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Mitchell	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
since	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
two	O
years	O
old	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
of	O
honest	O
creditable	O
parents	O
:	O
and	O
his	O
character	O
was	O
always	O
a	O
good	O
one	O
.	O
A	O
witness	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
school	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
person	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Watts	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
twenty	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
very	O
honest	O
and	O
well	O
behaved	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
has	O
been	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
.	O
Mark	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
above	O
five	O
years	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
that	O
this	O
happened	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
very	O
plentifully	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
when	O
this	O
affair	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
five	O
and	O
six	O
years	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
heard	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Light	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
but	O
a	O
little	O
time	O
.	O
He	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
as	O
an	O
honest	O
seafa	O
ring	O
gentleman	O
.	O
He	O
always	O
behaved	O
as	O
such	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cummins	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
twelve	O
months	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
him	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
W	O
.	O
197	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckle	O
,	O
value	O
eight	O
shillings	O
,	O
one	O
metal	O
watch	O
with	O
two	O
cases	O
,	O
value	O
thirty	O
shillings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Roe	I-pers
,	O
July	O
6	O
++	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
?	O
Roe	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
whether	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
or	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
happened	O
to	O
take	O
up	O
a	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
town	O
:	O
I	O
carried	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
chambers	O
in	O
Staple	O
's	O
Inn	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
pretend	O
to	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
but	O
as	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
able	O
to	O
judge	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
witnesses	O
here	O
to	O
prove	O
my	O
finding	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Slater	I-pers
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
sixth	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
this	O
watch	O
to	O
pledge	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
eleven	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
lose	O
your	O
watch	O
?	O
Roe	O
.	O
I	O
lost	O
my	O
watch	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
about	O
eight	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
chambers	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
sixth	O
.	O
Slater	O
.	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
.	O
She	O
offered	O
it	O
to	O
pledge	O
.	O
She	O
seemed	O
willing	O
to	O
be	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
her	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
buckles	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
to	O
the	O
compter	O
[	O
The	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutor	O
]	O
.	O
I	O
stopt	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
suspecting	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Dodington	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
evidence	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
search	O
me	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
in	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
her	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
buckle	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
where	O
the	O
fellow	O
of	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
shoe	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
steal	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
advertised	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
as	O
directed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
swore	O
to	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
money	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
Middle	O
Row	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
stopped	O
.	O
I	O
drank	O
a	O
dram	O
and	O
was	O
foolish	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
said	O
.	O
As	O
to	O
the	O
buckle	O
,	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
fellow	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
three	O
shillings	O
and	O
sixpence	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
is	O
now	O
gone	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
.	O
Her	O
name	O
is	O
Carrotty	O
Bess	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
198	O
,	O
199	O
,	O
200	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cayton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Shakespeare	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
June	O
23	O
++	O
.	O
John	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
ataylor	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Black	O
Friers	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cayton	I-pers
's	O
in	O
Black	B-place
Boy	I-place
Alley	I-place
;	O
they	O
were	O
drinking	O
of	O
tea	O
.	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
some	O
tea	O
along	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
contribute	O
something	O
to	O
the	O
tea	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
sixpence	O
to	O
Ann	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
out	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
pocket	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
to	O
buy	O
tea	O
or	O
sugar	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
my	O
groat	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
to	O
be	O
two	O
pence	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
poured	O
out	O
the	O
liquor	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
a	O
cup	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
it	O
for	O
tea	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
it	O
very	O
nauseous	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
either	O
gin	O
or	O
annifeed	O
.	O
Drink	O
it	O
,	O
Jemmy	O
,	O
says	O
she	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
do	O
you	O
good	O
.	O
Then	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
walk	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
but	O
found	O
myself	O
very	O
giddy	O
and	O
stupid	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
partly	O
lost	O
my	O
senses	O
:	O
I	O
wish	O
'd	O
myself	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
lie	O
down	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
,	O
and	O
immediately	O
fell	O
fast	O
asleep	O
;	O
and	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
I	O
felt	O
somebody	O
about	O
my	O
left-hand	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
asleep	O
or	O
awake	O
,	O
but	O
stupid	O
;	O
I	O
lay	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
side	O
where	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
rolled	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
.	O
The	O
money	O
that	O
I	O
lost	O
was	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
bound	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
white	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
ribbon	O
bound	O
over	O
it	O
and	O
pinn	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
that	O
you	O
was	O
turn	O
'd	O
from	O
your	O
left	O
side	O
to	O
your	O
right	O
side	O
;	O
can	O
you	O
tell	O
who	O
turn	O
'd	O
you	O
?	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
observe	O
any	O
particular	O
person	O
turn	O
me	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
together	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cayton	I-pers
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
waked	O
I	O
saw	O
Ann	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
;	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
before	O
I	O
could	O
recover	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
then	O
look	O
'd	O
much	O
confused	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
again	O
;	O
Cayton	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
Ann	B-pers
Christian	I-pers
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
a	O
constable	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Shakespeare	O
sat	O
in	O
one	O
place	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
acquitted	O
.	O
199	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Plackett	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
open	O
field	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Jacob	B-pers
Faye	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve-buttons	O
set	O
with	O
precious	O
stones	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
15	O
s.	O
one	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
black	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
breeches	O
buckle	O
,	O
one	O
shirt	O
and	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
one	O
27	O
shilling	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
one	O
6	O
s.	O
and	O
9	O
d.	O
piece	O
of	O
gold	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
June	O
17	O
.	O
||	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
not	O
understanding	O
English	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
Jacob	B-pers
Faye	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
between	O
the	O
hours	O
of	O
eight	O
and	O
nine	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
my	O
lodgings	O
at	O
Shadwell	O
dock	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Osmond	B-pers
Osmondson	I-pers
,	O
to	O
the	O
Danish	O
coffeehouse	O
in	O
Wellclose-square	O
to	O
see	O
for	O
a	O
countryman	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
him	O
;	O
returning	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
my	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
rambled	O
about	O
till	O
near	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
hackney	O
coaches	O
standing	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
one	O
;	O
the	O
man	O
refused	O
to	O
carry	O
me	O
on	O
account	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
him	O
understand	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
drive	O
me	O
to	O
Limehouse	O
;	O
the	O
last	O
word	O
he	O
understood	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
to	O
pay	O
him	O
before	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
coach	O
.	O
Then	O
came	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
to	O
the	O
best	O
of	O
my	O
knowledge	O
it	O
was	O
he	O
,	O
by	O
his	O
size	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
could	O
observe	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
star-light	O
)	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
me	O
to	O
Limehouse	O
;	O
he	O
spoke	O
English	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
I	O
understood	O
all	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
understood	O
him	O
that	O
he	O
lived	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
through	O
several	O
street	O
till	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
open	O
fields	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
walked	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
in	O
the	O
fields	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
I	O
was	O
wrong	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
said	O
so	O
he	O
struck	O
me	O
down	O
by	O
a	O
blow	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
remember	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
one	O
blow	O
more	O
;	O
what	O
happened	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
recovered	O
my	O
senses	O
I	O
found	O
myself	O
stripped	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
as	O
naked	O
as	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
,	O
only	O
my	O
stockings	O
:	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
knocked	O
me	O
down	O
standing	O
by	O
me	O
with	O
my	O
pocket	O
book	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
My	O
book	O
,	O
my	O
book	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
lying	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
not	O
able	O
to	O
rise	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
over	O
the	O
papers	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
[	O
he	O
produced	O
three	O
pieces	O
of	O
paper	O
sprinkled	O
with	O
blood	O
]	O
these	O
were	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
remained	O
still	O
on	O
the	O
spot	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
got	O
down	O
into	O
a	O
dry	O
ditch	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
remained	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
long	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
got	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
a	O
light	O
I	O
ventured	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
new	O
turnpike	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
road	O
from	O
Moorfields	O
to	O
Islington	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
man	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
talk	O
English	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
let	O
him	O
understand	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lay	O
down	O
on	O
his	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
covered	O
me	O
up	O
:	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
surgeon	O
to	O
dress	O
my	O
wounds	O
,	O
name	O
Goodman	O
;	O
he	O
procured	O
a	O
lodging	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
lay	O
till	O
I	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
go	O
abroad	O
again	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
in	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
days	O
.	O
Part	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
swear	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Faye	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
my	O
senses	O
would	O
allow	O
me	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
of	O
it	O
since	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
not	O
say	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
was	O
the	O
man	O
?	O
Faye	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
that	O
man	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
laid	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
that	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
but	O
one	O
man	O
with	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
coach	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Priscilla	B-pers
Ketchin	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
six	O
weeks	O
to	O
day	O
;	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
where	O
he	O
did	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
M'Cullough	O
's	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
apartment	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
before	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
work	O
'd	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
bloody	O
shirt	O
in	O
a	O
tub	O
of	O
water	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
:	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
two	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
gone	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
fustian	O
waistcoat	O
without	O
sleeves	O
,	O
without	O
a	O
coat	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
mark	O
on	O
the	O
shirt	O
in	O
the	O
tub	O
;	O
it	O
had	O
ruffles	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wristband	O
stitched	O
to	O
imitate	O
work	O
:	O
[	O
a	O
shirt	O
produced	O
]	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
shirt	O
;	O
I	O
wash	O
'd	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
beat	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
went	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
home	O
from	O
Sadlers	O
Wells	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
wash	O
'd	O
and	O
iron	O
'd	O
that	O
shirt	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
After	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
and	O
seen	O
several	O
things	O
,	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
affrighted	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
landlady	O
up	O
:	O
she	O
saw	O
that	O
bloody	O
shirt	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
buckle	O
behind	O
mark	O
'd	O
J	O
G	O
F	O
;	O
they	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pistol	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
some	O
other	O
things	O
of	O
his	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
his	O
fustian	O
waistcoat	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
On	O
this	O
I	O
gave	O
information	O
to	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
being	O
committed	O
;	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
and	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
in	O
his	O
sleeves	O
with	O
green	O
stones	O
;	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
socket	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
were	O
diamonds	O
set	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
they	O
cost	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
aunt	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
that	O
ever	O
wore	O
diamond	O
buttons	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
lose	O
such	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeve	O
buttons	O
as	O
she	O
has	O
described	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Melling	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
landlady	O
's	O
daughter	O
of	O
that	O
house	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
his	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
box	O
was	O
opened	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
with	O
a	O
silver	O
buckle	O
,	O
a	O
blue	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
scarlet	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
his	O
fustian	O
waistcoat	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
on	O
was	O
bloody	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
fighting	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
sleeve-buttons	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
as	O
the	O
other	O
witness	O
described	O
,	O
(	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
velvet	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
buckle	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
a	O
stock	O
buckle	O
marked	O
J	O
G	O
F	O
,	O
a	O
half-crown	O
piece	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
a	O
shirt	O
marked	O
H	O
F	O
4	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hat	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
hat	O
I	O
believe	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
has	O
been	O
altered	O
;	O
all	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
are	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
I	O
had	O
on	O
and	O
about	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
;	O
the	O
half	O
crown	O
is	O
a	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
of	O
1707	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
by	O
a	O
crack	O
in	O
the	O
silver	O
just	O
over	O
the	O
head	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
eleven	O
at	O
the	O
Barley-mow	O
and	O
Magpye	O
in	O
Gray's-inn-lane	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
there	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
a	O
shilling	O
;	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
George	O
by	O
Holborn-bars	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
Holborn	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
Fleet-market	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
Holborn-bridge	O
;	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
Bricklayers	O
Arms	O
in	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
,	O
about	O
twelve	O
at	O
noon	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
my	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
gold	O
and	O
silver	O
plenty	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
he	O
was	O
saying	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buttons	O
that	O
cost	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
green	O
stones	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
diamond	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
evening	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
Black	O
Lion	O
in	O
Jockey	O
's	O
Fields	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Bedford	O
row	O
.	O
Matthew	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
.	O
I	O
found	O
this	O
pocket-book	O
and	O
papers	O
in	O
the	O
new	O
road	O
on	O
the	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
about	O
four	O
o'clock	O
;	O
they	O
were	O
near	O
the	O
turnpike	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
in	O
gold	O
under	O
the	O
pocket	O
book	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
found	O
two	O
wigs	O
,	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
wigs	O
before	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
[	O
producing	O
them	O
]	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
book	O
and	O
wig	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Williams	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
also	O
by	O
them	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
wood	O
[	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
]	O
;	O
they	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
pale	O
.	O
about	O
three	O
inches	O
broad	O
,	O
broke	O
in	O
two	O
pieces	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
lent	O
that	O
wig	O
to	O
Day	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
constable	O
:	O
I	O
searched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
this	O
shirt	O
and	O
breeches	O
buckle	O
in	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
pocket	O
belonging	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
another	O
bloody	O
shirt	O
and	O
a	O
bloody	O
fustian	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
also	O
this	O
pistol	O
[	O
producing	O
one	O
]	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Drury-lane	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Newtoner	O
's	O
lane	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
in	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
William	B-pers
Price	I-pers
;	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
things	O
with	O
me	O
before	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
seven	O
shillings	O
on	O
these	O
breeches	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
June	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Ferry	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
kneebuckles	O
,	O
silver	O
seal	O
and	O
stock	O
buckle	O
,	O
on	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dawson	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
used	O
to	O
sell	O
butter	O
about	O
in	O
our	O
neighbourhood	O
;	O
on	O
Thursday	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
June	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
two	O
women	O
and	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
brought	O
me	O
a	O
coat	O
to	O
sell	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
brought	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
man	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
me	O
six-pence	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
six-pence	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
half	O
guinea	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
that	O
man	O
Day	O
?	O
Dawson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Justice	O
Welch	O
deposed	O
.	O
That	O
the	O
prisoner	O
much	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
Day	O
and	O
he	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
by	O
a	O
coach	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
between	O
Leather-lane	O
and	O
Hatton-garden	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
gentleman	O
was	O
desiring	O
the	O
coachman	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
Limehouse	O
;	O
that	O
Day	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
went	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
in	O
Wood's-close	O
they	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
pale	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
fields	O
by	O
the	O
city	O
road	O
,	O
he	O
staid	O
at	O
a	O
little	O
distance	O
behind	O
;	O
that	O
Day	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
went	O
on	O
.	O
Immediately	O
after	O
their	O
parting	O
he	O
heard	O
a	O
violent	O
blow	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
after	O
two	O
other	O
blows	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
Day	O
brought	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
several	O
things	O
mentioned	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
Day	O
pawned	O
the	O
breeches	O
in	O
Holborn	O
near	O
the	O
French	O
Horn	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Day	O
pawned	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
upon	O
inquiring	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
swore	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
bringing	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
Day	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
carried	O
Day	O
to	O
them	O
;	O
and	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
his	O
worship	O
that	O
Day	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brebrook	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Bridewell	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
admitted	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
discovery	O
of	O
this	O
robbery	O
;	O
he	O
mentioned	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Jack	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Haynes	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
they	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
divers	O
robberies	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Jack	B-pers
Lamb	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
were	O
concerned	O
in	O
this	O
:	O
he	O
never	O
mentioned	O
Day	O
till	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
days	O
after	O
this	O
;	O
and	O
after	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
Day	O
was	O
likely	O
to	O
be	O
set	O
at	O
liberty	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
five	O
guineas	O
to	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
would	O
swear	O
Day	O
brought	O
the	O
cloaths	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
to	O
sell	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Over	O
night	O
,	O
when	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
and	O
I	O
parted	O
from	O
the	O
Barley-mow	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
was	O
bald-headed	O
;	O
I	O
lent	O
him	O
my	O
own	O
brown	O
wig	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
he	O
came	O
with	O
the	O
things	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
do	O
a	O
favour	O
for	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Do	O
n't	O
bring	O
me	O
into	O
trouble	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
Will	O
you	O
pawn	O
me	O
a	O
few	O
things	O
?	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
Can	O
not	O
you	O
pawn	O
them	O
your-self	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
Pawn	O
me	O
these	O
breeches	O
and	O
this	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
this	O
hat	O
turn	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
pay	O
you	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Jack	O
,	O
where	O
is	O
my	O
wig	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
lost	O
it	O
last	O
night	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
paid	O
for	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
shillings	O
for	O
turning	O
the	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
six	O
shillings	O
for	O
pawning	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
his	O
shirt	O
was	O
bloody	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
by	O
fighting	O
the	O
other	O
day	O
,	O
and	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
he	O
wiped	O
his	O
face	O
with	O
his	O
shirt	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
of	O
him	O
and	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
suffer	O
for	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
do	O
suffer	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
between	O
God	O
Almighty	O
and	O
myself	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
that	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
knows	O
what	O
time	O
I	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
almost	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
when	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
Barley-mow	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Wood	O
's	O
Close	O
:	O
if	O
I	O
die	O
for	O
it	O
I	O
will	O
say	O
the	O
same	O
words	O
as	O
I	O
do	O
now	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Parton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
home	O
that	O
morning	O
at	O
past	O
twelve	O
o'clock	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
how	O
much	O
past	O
,	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
after	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
came	O
John	B-pers
Day	I-pers
with	O
the	O
cloaths	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
hanged	O
if	O
I	O
know	O
what	O
day	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Thursday	O
morning	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Plackett	I-pers
,	O
will	O
you	O
do	O
a	O
favour	O
for	O
me	O
?	O
Do	O
take	O
them	O
things	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
he	O
ask	O
'd	O
Day	O
how	O
his	O
shirt	O
came	O
so	O
bloody	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
fighting	O
with	O
a	O
man	O
.	O
Plackett	O
ask	O
'd	O
,	O
where	O
was	O
his	O
wig	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
He	O
had	O
lost	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
Queen	O
Ann	O
's	O
half	O
crown	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
six	O
shillings	O
for	O
pawning	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Guilty	O
,	O
Death	O
.	O
201	O
,	O
202	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Neal	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Willson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
Wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Edward	I-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
July	O
4	O
.	O
||	O
Neal	O
,	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
Williams	O
,	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
203	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Simon	B-pers
Mayne	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
hammer	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
nine	O
iron	O
hoops	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Chase	I-pers
,	O
July	O
5	O
.~	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
204	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
walking-cane	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
linen	O
bag	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Adam	B-pers
Edmund	I-pers
Clauson	I-pers
,	O
May	O
31	O
.~	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
205	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Anger	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Hanger	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
books	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Stephens	I-pers
,	O
June	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
206	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Graham	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
162	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
ribbon	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Willion	I-pers
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Willion	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
their	O
warehouse	O
,	O
June	O
2	O
.~	O
It	O
appeared	O
by	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
that	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
lunatick	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
207	O
,	O
208	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Metyard	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
Sarah	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
Metyard	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Nailor	I-pers
,	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
thirteen	O
years	O
,	O
by	O
shutting	O
up	O
and	O
confining	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
32	O
d	O
year	O
of	O
king	O
George	O
II	O
.	O
to	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
and	O
starving	O
her	O
to	O
death	O
*	O
.	O
Philadelphia	B-pers
Dowley	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
bound	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Tottenham	O
High	O
Cross	O
to	O
the	O
mother	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
about	O
Michaelmas	O
,	O
1758	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Nailor	I-pers
went	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Why	O
did	O
she	O
do	O
that	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
Because	O
she	O
was	O
used	O
so	O
ill.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
be	O
beat	O
by	O
the	O
mother	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
without	O
her	O
victuals	O
.	O
We	O
used	O
to	O
have	O
bread	O
,	O
and	O
bread	O
and	O
butter	O
given	O
us	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
she	O
use	O
to	O
beat	O
her	O
with	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
With	O
a	O
walking	O
stick	O
and	O
hearth	O
brooms	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
not	O
victuals	O
given	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
we	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
had	O
she	O
never	O
any	O
victuals	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
;	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
as	O
much	O
as	O
we	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
not	O
so	O
often	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
occasion	O
she	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Brown	B-pers
the	O
milkman	O
stopped	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
and	O
saw	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
this	O
been	O
for	O
any	O
considerable	O
time	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
been	O
kept	O
without	O
victuals	O
,	O
before	O
she	O
attempted	O
to	O
run	O
away	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
condition	O
was	O
she	O
in	O
for	O
health	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
very	O
weak	O
condition	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
victuals	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
she	O
come	O
to	O
be	O
stopped	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
The	O
daughter	O
and	O
the	O
mother	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Brown	B-pers
the	O
milkman	O
to	O
stop	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
told	O
the	O
milkman	O
she	O
should	O
be	O
starved	O
if	O
she	O
was	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
she	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
word	O
starved	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
.	O
The	O
daughter	O
received	O
her	O
from	O
the	O
milkman	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
her	O
up	O
stairs	O
:	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
they	O
lay	O
,	O
and	O
beat	O
with	O
a	O
broomstick	O
(	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
)	O
;	O
the	O
mother	O
was	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
held	O
the	O
girl	O
by	O
the	O
head	O
while	O
the	O
daughter	O
beat	O
her	O
;	O
the	O
mother	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
girl	O
upon	O
it	O
:	O
then	O
she	O
was	O
carried	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
to	O
a	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
back	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
daughter	O
,	O
the	O
string	O
went	O
round	O
her	O
waist	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
hands	O
were	O
tied	O
behind	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
could	O
neither	O
sit	O
nor	O
lie	O
down	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
did	O
she	O
continue	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
She	O
continued	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
three	O
days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
mother	O
know	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
daughter	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
one	O
day	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
help	O
her	O
tie	O
that	O
girl	O
up	O
.	O
The	O
mother	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
have	O
your	O
crotches	O
,	O
you	O
may	O
do	O
them	O
yourself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
the	O
girl	O
do	O
on	O
nights	O
.	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
The	O
daughter	O
came	O
and	O
untied	O
her	O
at	O
nights	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
might	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
had	O
she	O
her	O
food	O
or	O
victuals	O
during	O
that	O
time	O
she	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
meals	O
all	O
the	O
three	O
days	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
your	O
meals	O
yourself	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
kitchen	O
in	O
the	O
summer	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
victuals	O
with	O
us	O
;	O
and	O
when	O
we	O
had	O
done	O
we	O
used	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
to	O
her	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
work	O
by	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
none	O
she	O
had	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
girl	O
speak	O
to	O
you	O
at	O
them	O
times	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
She	O
used	O
to	O
stand	O
and	O
groan	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
three	O
days	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
move	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
life	O
in	O
her	O
:	O
when	O
we	O
told	O
the	O
daughter	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
move	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
go	O
and	O
make	O
her	O
move	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
the	O
mother	O
see	O
this	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
She	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
when	O
I	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
daughter	O
about	O
it	O
;	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
down	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
posture	O
was	O
the	O
girl	O
in	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
She	O
hung	O
double	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
when	O
you	O
called	O
to	O
her	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
Miss	O
Salley	O
!	O
Miss	O
Salley	O
!	O
come	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
Nanny	O
does	O
not	O
move	O
;	O
we	O
called	O
out	O
aloud	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
apprentices	O
were	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
daughter	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
beat	O
the	O
girl	O
with	O
her	O
shoe	O
on	O
her	O
backside	O
;	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
move	O
then	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
make	O
her	O
move	O
;	O
she	O
beat	O
her	O
hand	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
beating	O
was	O
over	O
the	O
mother	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
The	O
mother	O
laid	O
the	O
girl	O
cross	O
her	O
lap	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
Sall	O
,	O
my	O
fellow	O
apprentice	O
,	O
to	O
bring	O
up	O
some	O
drops	O
:	O
they	O
were	O
brought	O
:	O
the	O
girl	O
seemed	O
dead	O
to	O
me	O
:	O
then	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
sent	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
immediately	O
;	O
that	O
is	O
me	O
,	O
my	O
fellow	O
apprentice	O
Mary	B-pers
Nailor	I-pers
,	O
sister	O
to	O
the	O
girl	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
that	O
is	O
not	O
living	O
,	O
named	O
Ann	B-pers
Paul	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
sent	O
you	O
down	O
,	O
the	O
mother	O
or	O
daughter	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
remember	O
which	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
usual	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
sent	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
mother	O
and	O
daughter	O
were	O
up	O
stairs	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
we	O
were	O
sent	O
down	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Ann	B-pers
Nailor	I-pers
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
never	O
any	O
account	O
given	O
you	O
of	O
her	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
No	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
Sall	O
,	O
my	O
fellow	O
apprentice	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
up	O
to	O
fetch	O
her	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
garret	O
;	O
we	O
usually	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
the	O
garret	O
every	O
day	O
before	O
this	O
to	O
wash	O
our	O
hands	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
there	O
for	O
two	O
days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
bid	O
you	O
not	O
go	O
there	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
The	O
mother	O
bid	O
us	O
wash	O
our	O
hands	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
;	O
sometimes	O
we	O
had	O
a	O
bason	O
of	O
water	O
brought	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
,	O
but	O
this	O
was	O
not	O
usual	O
before	O
.	O
About	O
two-days	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
to	O
dinner	O
.	O
Sall	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
garret	O
door	O
was	O
open	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
there	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
mother	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
ran	O
away	O
when	O
we	O
were	O
at	O
dinner	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
said	O
.	O
They	O
said	O
there	O
is	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
heard	O
no	O
noise	O
.	O
Sall	O
Hinchman	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
is	O
run	O
away	O
,	O
she	O
has	O
left	O
her	O
shoes	O
behind	O
her	O
.	O
The	O
mother	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
for	O
her	O
shoes	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
number	O
of	O
shifts	O
this	O
child	O
had	O
allowed	O
her	O
.	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
us	O
three	O
;	O
her	O
three	O
were	O
pretty	O
newish	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
had	O
you	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
only	O
one	O
pair	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
after	O
that	O
time	O
see	O
the	O
three	O
shifts	O
that	O
were	O
Ann	B-pers
Nailor	I-pers
's	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
the	O
biggest	O
girl	O
Sally	O
had	O
them	O
afterward	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
do	O
to	O
know	O
that	O
?	O
P.	O
Dowley	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
marked	O
;	O
mine	O
were	O
number	O
1	O
;	O
another	O
's	O
were	O
number	O
2	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
were	O
number	O
3	O
;	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Nailor	I-pers
's	O
were	O
number	O
4	O
;	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
of	O
each	O
number	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
Cross	O
Examination	O
,	O
She	O
said	O
the	O
girls	O
did	O
not	O
use	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
so	O
often	O
as	O
once	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Sunday	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
never	O
by	O
themselves	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
once	O
to	O
the	O
committee	O
of	O
the	O
workhouse	O
,	O
and	O
declared	O
that	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
were	O
used	O
ill	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
mother	O
and	O
daughter	O
frequently	O
quarrelled	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
mother	O
frequently	O
beat	O
the	O
daughter	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
