TOKEN	NE
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
Justice-Hall	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
14th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
15th	O
,	O
Friday	O
the	O
16th	O
,	O
Saturday	O
the	O
17th	O
,	O
Monday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
and	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
SEPTEMBER	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Seventh	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VII	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1763	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
JOHN	B-pers
RYALL	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six	O
Pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BECKFORD	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
*	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Please	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Perrott	I-pers
+	O
,	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
++	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Verges	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Rait	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Mirehouse	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Hillar	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Simpson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
Naboth	B-pers
Tarrington	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harrington	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Ontwisle	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Bullock	I-pers
,	O
Roger	B-pers
Paxton	I-pers
,	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Simmonds	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Houghton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Bennett	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
Jeremiah	B-pers
Oliver	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Barber	I-pers
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Kirby	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Wingfield	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Grindley	I-pers
.	O
352	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
-	I-pers
Chamberlain	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
child	O
's	O
frock	O
,	O
called	O
a	O
slip	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Dorrington	I-pers
.	O
July	O
14	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
keeps	O
the	O
Castle	B-place
alehouse	I-place
near	I-place
Guildhall	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
in	O
and	O
sat	O
some	O
time	O
by	O
the	O
maid	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
ironing	O
;	O
her	O
mistress	O
sent	O
the	O
maid	O
,	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
snuff	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
her	O
return	O
the	O
frock	O
was	O
missing	O
from	O
a	O
bundle	O
that	O
lay	O
damp	O
for	O
ironing	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
then	O
being	O
gone	O
,	O
information	O
was	O
brought	O
in	O
soon	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
Swan	O
alehouse	O
in	O
St.	O
Ann	O
's	O
Lane	O
,	O
where	O
she	O
was	O
found	O
with	O
the	O
frock	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
,	O
who	O
first	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
at	O
the	O
outside	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
W	O
.	O
353	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Hattersley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
25	O
s.	O
one	O
other	O
yard	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
half	O
a	O
yard	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
ditto	O
,	O
val	O
15	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
ditto	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
36	O
s.	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
ditto	O
,	O
val	O
42	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
of	O
alopene	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
three	O
yards	O
of	O
alopene	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
two	O
other	O
yards	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
s.	O
two	O
yards	O
of	O
ditto	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
and	O
diverse	O
other	O
cloths	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
to	O
about	O
20	O
l.	O
and	O
10	O
l.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Wharton	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
24	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
be	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
354	O
,	O
355	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Cornelius	B-pers
Donnolly	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Philip	B-pers
Tobin	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
2	O
d.	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Aug.	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
I	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
Victualling	O
Office	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
along	O
Lemon-street	B-place
,	I-place
Goodman's-fields	I-place
,	O
a	O
little	O
past	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
just	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
chemonger	O
,	O
three	O
men	O
stopped	O
me	O
,	O
Donnolly	O
collared	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
left-side	O
,	O
and	O
Tobin	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
stood	O
before	O
me	O
,	O
they	O
had	O
each	O
of	O
them	O
a	O
asked	O
knife	O
in	O
their	O
hands	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
your	O
money	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
poor	O
labouring	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
but	O
a	O
trifle	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
they	O
must	O
have	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
delivered	O
to	O
them	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
d.	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
left	O
hand	O
pocket	O
;	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
has	O
got	O
more	O
in	O
his	O
other	O
pockets	O
,	O
we	O
will	O
chip	O
him	O
down	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
and	O
slit	O
my	O
breeches	O
open	O
from	O
top	O
to	O
bottom	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
them	O
)	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
more	O
money	O
about	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
bye	O
watch	O
.	O
or	O
what	O
is	O
called	O
the	O
private	O
watch	O
,	O
was	O
coming	O
very	O
near	O
,	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
private	O
watch	O
what	O
they	O
had	O
done	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
corner	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
standing	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lesever	O
's	O
brew-house	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
gone	O
farther	O
on	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
watch-man	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
coming	O
along	O
the	O
street	O
just	O
by	O
me	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
shewed	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
he	O
seized	O
Donnolly	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
into	O
an	O
alley	O
;	O
the	O
bye	O
watch	O
struck	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
fell	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
seized	O
him	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
.	O
The	O
corner	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
standing	O
is	O
not	O
above	O
fifteen	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
I	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
in	O
less	O
than	O
five	O
miactes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
soul	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
but	O
themselves	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
lamp	O
near	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
robbed	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
at	O
the	O
brew-house	O
where	O
they	O
stood	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
had	O
you	O
been	O
so	O
late	O
?	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
with	O
an	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
and	O
staid	O
at	O
the	O
public-house	O
about	O
three	O
hours	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
liquor	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Donnolly	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
house	O
open	O
in	O
Rosemary-lane	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
That	O
is	O
false	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
either	O
of	O
the	O
prisoners	O
before	O
to	O
my	O
knowledge	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
spoke	O
to	O
either	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Crocker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
private	O
watchman	O
in	O
Lemon-street	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
twelve	O
on	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
I	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
door	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
come	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
just	O
been	O
robbed	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
of	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
they	O
have	O
got	O
three	O
naked	O
knives	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Wood	O
's	O
corner	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
standing	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Lesever	O
's	O
brew-house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
close	O
up	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
,	O
Tobin	O
had	O
a	O
naked	O
clasp	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
turned	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
sleeve	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
he	O
turned	O
it	O
up	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
blade	O
plainly	O
;	O
we	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
again	O
into	O
Lemon-street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
followed	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
and	O
got	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
4	O
watch-men	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
Donnolly	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
the	O
other	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
an	O
alley	O
very	O
soon	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
resolute	O
,	O
they	O
dragged	O
him	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
alley	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
searched	O
them	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
clasp	O
knife	O
found	O
upon	O
Tobin	O
,	O
and	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
only	O
some	O
halfpence	O
found	O
upon	O
Donnolly	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
clasp	O
knife	O
found	O
under	O
the	O
bench	O
were	O
Donnolly	O
sat	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Bennet	I-pers
.	O
The	O
last	O
witness	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
some	O
watchmen	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
He	O
confirmed	O
the	O
evidence	O
of	O
Crocker	O
;	O
and	O
Peter	B-pers
Pardock	I-pers
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Bennet	O
being	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
had	O
observed	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
breeches	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
saw	O
them	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
on	O
to	O
be	O
slit	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
manner	O
as	O
they	O
appeared	O
when	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
Donnolly	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Wapping	O
drinking	O
with	O
a	O
ship-mate	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
White	O
Hart	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
away	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
ten	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
up	O
Lemon-street	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
in	O
Spittlefields	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
man	O
and	O
watchman	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
gone	O
close	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Tobin	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
If	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
guilty	O
of	O
a	O
robbery	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
gone	O
by	O
the	O
watch-house	O
to	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
Crocket	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
this	O
was	O
truth	O
,	O
declared	O
they	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoners	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
drink	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
356	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
36	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Crane	I-pers
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
wash	O
and	O
scour	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
,	O
the	O
six	O
shirts	O
were	O
found	O
pawned	O
at	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
1762	O
,	O
another	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
1762	O
,	O
another	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
1762	O
,	O
another	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
1762	O
,	O
another	O
the	O
4th	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
June	O
1763	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
one	O
pawned	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
June	O
1763	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Nov.	O
1762	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
carried	O
by	O
herself	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
357	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Langley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Badington	I-pers
,	O
and	O
two	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
12	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Badington	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
8	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Betts	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
the	O
linnen	O
to	O
wash	O
,	O
deposed	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
from	O
her	O
lines	O
in	O
her	O
garden	O
in	O
Kingsland	B-place
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
in	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
an	O
hour	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Gerrard	O
Hussey	O
,	O
who	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
deposed	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Betts	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
linnen	O
,	O
and	O
wished	O
he	O
had	O
broke	O
his	O
neck	O
before	O
he	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
garden	O
.	O
Martha	B-pers
Ayres	I-pers
deposed	O
she	O
lives	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Betts	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
garden	O
with	O
the	O
linnen	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
she	O
alarmed	O
the	O
people	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
linnen	O
brought	O
back	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
358	O
,	O
359	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Shields	I-pers
and	O
Sebastian	B-pers
Hogan	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Joseph	B-pers
Alston	I-pers
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
July	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
Joseph	B-pers
Alston	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
past	O
11	O
o'clock	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
I	O
was	O
lock	O
'd	O
out	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
in	O
Houndsditch	O
,	O
name	O
Jacob	B-pers
Rothereges	I-pers
,	O
a	O
jeweller	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
attack	O
'd	O
on	O
Tower-hill	B-place
by	O
four	O
men	O
which	O
came	O
from	O
towards	O
Iron-gate	O
.	O
Shields	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
patted	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
left	O
shoulder	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
something	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
understand	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
I	O
continued	O
walking	O
on	O
very	O
briskly	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
No	O
,	O
friend	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
what	O
o'clock	O
it	O
is	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
felt	O
at	O
my	O
right	O
side	O
breeches-pocket	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
any	O
money	O
for	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
no	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
and	O
deliver	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
collar	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
stand	O
,	O
and	O
began	O
to	O
shake	O
myself	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
one	O
said	O
hold	O
on	O
collar	O
behind	O
and	O
the	O
others	O
held	O
me	O
by	O
each	O
arm	O
;	O
then	O
Shields	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
and	O
went	O
behind	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
presently	O
came	O
before	O
me	O
again	O
with	O
a	O
clasp-knife	O
open	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
calling	O
out	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
collar	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
swore	O
if	O
I	O
made	O
the	O
least	O
noise	O
he	O
would	O
kill	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
mind	O
his	O
threatening	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
out	O
murder	O
;	O
they	O
held	O
me	O
some	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
swear	O
who	O
cut	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
three	O
cuts	O
in	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
pretty	O
dark	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
were	O
under	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
lamp	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
his	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
breeches-pocket	O
they	O
were	O
afraid	O
of	O
somebody	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
Hogan	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
struck	O
me	O
on	O
my	O
nose	O
,	O
then	O
they	O
all	O
ran	O
away	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
nothing	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
and	O
catch	O
'd	O
hold	O
of	O
Shields	O
by	O
the	O
coat	O
,	O
but	O
running	O
against	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
posts	O
going	O
off	O
the	O
hill	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
any	O
body	O
come	O
to	O
your	O
assistance	O
?	O
Alston	O
.	O
I	O
neither	O
saw	O
nor	O
heard	O
anybody	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
three	O
ran	O
towards	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
towards	O
the	O
Victualling	O
Office	O
;	O
running	O
by	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
a	O
watchman	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
and	O
pursued	O
the	O
other	O
three	O
.	O
The	O
two	O
that	O
escaped	O
,	O
ran	O
up	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
and	O
Hogan	O
ran	O
up	O
King-street	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
,	O
and	O
knocked	O
a	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
off	O
,	O
which	O
hat	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
recovered	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
up	O
and	O
ran	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
pursued	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
arms	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shake	O
,	O
and	O
shoved	O
me	O
against	O
a	O
post	O
;	O
I	O
let	O
my	O
hold	O
go	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
ran	O
back	O
again	O
the	O
way	O
he	O
had	O
came	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
saw	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
clasp	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
ran	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
collar	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
loose	O
from	O
me	O
again	O
and	O
turned	O
and	O
ran	O
up	O
the	O
street	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
still	O
pursued	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
his	O
escape	O
he	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
a	O
leather-cutter	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
stopping	O
with	O
his	O
knife	O
ready	O
for	O
a	O
stab	O
at	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
You	O
dog	O
,	O
what	O
did	O
you	O
strike	O
me	O
for	O
?	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
let	O
you	O
know	O
presently	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
watch	O
,	O
watch	O
,	O
make	O
haste	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
thinking	O
somebody	O
was	O
coming	O
,	O
looked	O
back	O
at	O
which	O
time	O
I	O
jumped	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
seized	O
hold	O
on	O
both	O
his	O
arms	O
;	O
he	O
put	O
his	O
hand	O
down	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
knife	O
against	O
his	O
thigh	O
,	O
and	O
dropped	O
it	O
against	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
leg	O
behind	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
fall	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
got	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
leading	O
him	O
down	O
(	O
this	O
was	O
all	O
in	O
King-street	O
)	O
to	O
get	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
there	O
came	O
an	O
old	O
woman	O
that	O
had	O
heard	O
the	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
thief	O
:	O
she	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
nobody	O
to	O
assist	O
me	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
where	O
are	O
the	O
watchmen	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
believed	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
dead	O
:	O
said	O
she	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
fetch	O
you	O
a	O
watchman	O
presently	O
:	O
presently	O
she	O
sent	O
two	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
carried	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
at	O
Tower-hill	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
him	O
there	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
watchmen	O
with	O
his	O
lanthorn	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
first	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
they	O
stopt	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
they	O
had	O
dropt	O
any	O
knives	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
none	O
,	O
then	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
King-street	O
,	O
where	O
Queen-street	O
begins	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
case	O
knife	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
dropped	O
by	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
King-street	O
,	O
where	O
I	O
knocked	O
him	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
own	O
hat	O
in	O
the	O
kennel	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
again	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
10	O
minutes	O
time	O
two	O
watchmen	O
came	O
from	O
another	O
watch-house	O
,	O
to	O
know	O
if	O
any	O
body	O
was	O
there	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
watch-house	O
in	O
St.	O
Catherine	O
's	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
Shields	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
sent	O
for	O
Hogan	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
drawing	O
a	O
knife	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
rob	O
me	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
day	O
they	O
were	O
carried	O
before	O
the	O
sitting	O
Justices	O
,	O
Shields	O
confessed	O
every	O
thing	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
before	O
Justice	O
Scott	O
.	O
The	O
knife	O
which	O
Hogan	O
dropped	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
I	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
about	O
4	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Cooley	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
being	O
the	O
officer	O
,	O
there	O
Shields	O
confessed	O
he	O
was	O
in	O
this	O
robbery	O
,	O
with	O
one	O
Welch	O
,	O
Ryan	O
,	O
and	O
Hogan	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
concerned	O
in	O
other	O
robberies	O
with	O
one	O
Wilson	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
a	O
means	O
of	O
saving	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
some	O
watchmen	O
of	O
a	O
notorious	O
house	O
on	O
Salt-petre-bank	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
directed	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
them	O
.	O
John	O
Hall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
watchman	O
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
cry	O
out	O
murder	O
,	O
and	O
thieves	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
Victualling	O
office	O
,	O
Shields	O
came	O
running	O
,	O
I	O
catched	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
secured	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
past	O
11	O
o'clock	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
watch-house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
,	O
when	O
Shield	O
's	O
saw	O
them	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
be	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Grugen	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
(	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
case	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
clasp	O
knife	O
)	O
these	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
and	O
watchman	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
charged	O
Shields	O
with	O
being	O
one	O
that	O
robbed	O
him	O
of	O
his	O
hat	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
quite	O
consistent	O
in	O
his	O
charge	O
.	O
Shields	O
offered	O
to	O
turn	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
knife	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
at	O
the	O
leather-cutter	O
's	O
door	O
was	O
Hogan	O
's	O
property	O
.	O
Shield	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
drinking	O
that	O
night	O
at	O
the	O
Ship-and-Shovel	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
Guy	O
's	O
Hospital	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
lodgings	O
in	O
Catherine-wheel-alley	O
,	O
White-chapel	O
,	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
in	O
custody	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Hogan	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
about	O
my	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
gentleman	O
opposed	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
struggle	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
soul	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
gentleman	O
may	O
say	O
what	O
he	O
pleases	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
stop	O
his	O
mouth	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
360	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
David	B-pers
Crosby	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Jasper	B-pers
Child	I-pers
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
of	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
brass	O
tobacco-box	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
clasp	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buck-skin	O
gloves	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Aug.	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
Jasper	B-pers
Child	I-pers
.	O
Five	O
weeks	O
ago	O
last	O
Sunday	O
night	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
from	B-place
White-chapel	I-place
to	I-place
Sun-tavern-fields	I-place
,	O
I	O
was	O
met	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
o'clock	O
,	O
about	O
eight	O
or	O
nine	O
yards	O
from	O
a	O
place	O
called	O
Tom-turd-man's-hole	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
one	O
came	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
man	O
,	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
collar	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
stirred	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
a	O
knife	O
open	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
searched	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
(	O
not	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
I	O
having	O
no	O
money	O
the	O
little	O
man	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
from	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
his	O
on	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
made	O
my	O
way	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
for	O
the	O
turnpike	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
into	O
the	O
cross	O
road	O
and	O
met	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
bid	O
me	O
stand	O
,	O
or	O
I	O
should	O
die	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
a	O
knife	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
star	O
light	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
took	O
my	O
coat	O
from	O
my	O
back	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
pockets	O
were	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
tobacco-box	O
,	O
gloves	O
,	O
and	O
knife	O
;	O
they	O
had	O
struck	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
at	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
broke	O
my	O
stick	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
took	O
that	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
on	O
towards	O
the	O
turnpike	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
towards	O
White-chapel	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
another	O
man	O
at	O
the	O
turnpike	O
that	O
had	O
just	O
been	O
robbed	O
of	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
by	O
three	O
men	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
described	O
like	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
turnpike-man	O
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Stedman	I-pers
the	O
description	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
I	O
was	O
fetched	O
to	O
Spring-gardens	O
,	O
at	O
Stepney	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
much	O
like	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
others	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
White-chapel	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
upon	O
him	O
belonging	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
found	O
any	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
again	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Stedman	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
other	O
men	O
used	O
,	O
frequently	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
Stepney	O
fields	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
watched	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
to	O
Spring-garden	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
decoyed	O
them	O
down	O
to	O
Rosemary-lane	O
,	O
pretending	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
game	O
at	O
Skettles	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
supper	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
should	O
partake	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
there	O
they	O
secured	O
them	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
one	O
Andrews	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
dangerous	O
to	O
attempt	O
it	O
at	O
Spring-garden	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
many	O
resolute	O
people	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
taken	O
that	O
same	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
to	O
New-prison	O
,	O
by	O
Brebrook	O
and	O
Murray	O
.	O
They	O
could	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
how	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
being	O
asked	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
?	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
coal-beaver	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
a	O
constable	O
came	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
As	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
could	O
give	O
any	O
reason	O
why	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
were	O
not	O
indicted	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
secured	O
them	O
appeared	O
on	O
the	O
trial	O
to	O
be	O
examined	O
,	O
the	O
Court	O
suspected	O
it	O
was	O
conducted	O
by	O
those	O
who	O
had	O
an	O
eye	O
to	O
the	O
reward	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
361	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Wheatland	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
yard	O
of	O
green	O
silk	O
damask	O
;	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
yard	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
stuff	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
and	O
seventeen	O
yards	O
of	O
velvet	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
34	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Amery	I-pers
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
silk-dyer	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
Coleman-street	O
;	O
a	O
lady	O
brought	O
several	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
to	O
be	O
dyed	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
delivering	O
it	O
again	O
to	O
her	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
green	O
damask	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
the	O
lady	O
,	O
in	O
attempting	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
piece	O
to	O
match	O
it	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
piece	O
missing	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Gray	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
milliner	O
and	O
baberdasher	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
back	O
of	O
St.	O
Clements	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
upon	O
that	O
,	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
his	O
shop-woman	O
,	O
with	O
stealing	O
,	O
and	O
getting	O
it	O
there	O
;	O
she	O
confessed	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
sworn	O
to	O
by	O
Mrs.	O
Green	O
.	O
The	O
other	O
things	O
were	O
found	O
sold	O
by	O
her	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
acknowledged	O
she	O
had	O
stolen	O
from	O
her	O
master	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
362	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
5	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Parry	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
keeps	O
the	O
Salutation	O
tavern	O
in	O
Budge-row	B-place
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
sixpennyworth	O
of	O
brandy	O
and	O
water	O
,	O
and	O
ordered	O
some	O
mutton	O
shops	O
for	O
dinner	O
;	O
after	O
the	O
cook	O
was	O
ordered	O
to	O
do	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
them	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
an	O
hour	O
's	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
he	O
missed	O
the	O
silver	O
spoon	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
with	O
the	O
liquor	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
after	O
him	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
saw	O
him	O
he	O
ran	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
stopped	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
of	O
Dowgate-hill	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
spoon	O
between	O
the	O
waistband	O
of	O
his	O
breeches	O
and	O
his	O
shirt	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
363	O
,	O
364	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jacob	B-pers
Sidenden	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
worsted	O
hose	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Peter	B-pers
Cavallier	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
20	O
.	O
++	O
Peter	B-pers
Cavallier	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
kept	O
a	O
hatter	O
and	O
hosier	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Leadenhall-street	B-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoners	O
came	O
on	O
the	O
20th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
about	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
black	O
ribbed	O
stockings	O
;	O
that	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
there	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
removed	O
in	O
the	O
window	O
,	O
but	O
knew	O
not	O
by	O
who	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
locked	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
upon	O
searching	O
,	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
lining	O
of	O
Morgan	O
's	O
coat	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
stockings	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Morgan	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
Sidenden	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
365	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Cobbey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Frederick	B-pers
Heaton	I-pers
,	O
July	O
25	O
.	O
++	O
Frederick	B-pers
Heaton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
shoe-maker	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
Fleet-street	B-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
;	O
that	O
his	O
silver	O
buckles	O
were	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
that	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
pursued	O
by	O
his	O
apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Coleby	I-pers
,	O
the	O
apprentice	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
overtook	O
her	O
near	O
Salisbury-court	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
delivered	O
the	O
buckles	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
brought	O
her	O
and	O
them	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
366	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Bunyard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
man	O
's	O
hat	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
September	O
1	O
.	O
++	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
in	O
a	B-place
night-house	I-place
on	I-place
the	I-place
outside	I-place
of	I-place
Temple-bar	I-place
,	O
when	O
every	O
body	O
were	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
turned	O
out	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
awaked	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
proposed	O
to	O
treat	O
him	O
for	O
his	O
civility	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
missing	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
finding	O
he	O
had	O
an	O
old	O
hat	O
on	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
owned	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
got	O
his	O
new	O
one	O
on	O
,	O
he	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
taking	O
him	O
down	O
Fleet-street	O
,	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
away	O
up	O
Shoe-lane	O
;	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
in	O
charge	O
of	O
a	O
constable	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
hat	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Sumpter	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
stealing	O
10	O
s.	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
half	O
crown	O
among	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Birmingham	O
shilling	O
;	O
that	O
in	O
searching	O
he	O
found	O
such	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
watch	O
graver	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
hard	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
asleep	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
his	O
hat	O
had	O
fallen	O
from	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
by	O
mistake	O
,	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
instead	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
him	O
up	O
from	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
months	O
old	O
till	O
he	O
was	O
fit	O
to	O
go	O
apprentice	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
then	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Francis	B-pers
Stedman	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Clerkenwell	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
367	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Medows	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Meads	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
committing	O
a	O
rape	O
on	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Mary	B-pers
Heather	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
May	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
Heather	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lived	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
a	O
year	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Islip	B-place
,	O
about	O
two	O
miles	O
from	O
West-side-bottom	O
;	O
that	O
her	O
family	O
consisted	O
of	O
her	O
master	O
and	O
his	O
brother	O
,	O
a	O
maid-servant	O
,	O
and	O
herself	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
made	O
frequent	O
attempts	O
on	O
her	O
chastity	O
,	O
generally	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
in	O
a	O
week	O
;	O
that	O
once	O
he	O
had	O
almost	O
stripped	O
her	O
naked	O
in	O
pulling	O
her	O
about	O
;	O
that	O
once	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
he	O
threw	O
the	O
chair	O
back	O
against	O
the	O
wall	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
chair	O
was	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
struggle	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
the	O
ceremony	O
,	O
but	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
commit	O
the	O
crime	O
charged	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
kissed	O
her	O
in	O
his	O
life	O
.	O
Being	O
asked	O
how	O
many	O
children	O
she	O
had	O
had	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
begotten	O
by	O
one	O
Newbury	O
,	O
when	O
be	O
ravished	O
her	O
.	O
On	O
her	O
cross	O
examination	O
she	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
before	O
this	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
cry	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
continued	O
in	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
servant	O
some	O
time	O
afterwards	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
observed	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
satisfactory	O
kind	O
of	O
proof	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
a	O
conviction	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
368	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
in	O
a	O
certain	O
open	O
place	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
of	O
a	O
linnen	O
counterpane	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
six	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Sarah	O
,	O
Aug.	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Chambers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Castle-yard	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
it	O
wanted	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
between	B-place
Newington	I-place
and	I-place
Canbury-house	I-place
,	I-place
just	I-place
by	I-place
the	I-place
New-river	I-place
,	O
Mrs.	O
Jane	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
was	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
met	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
first	O
stopt	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
held	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
from	O
under	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
2	O
waistcoats	O
on	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
a	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
made	O
all	O
the	O
haste	O
I	O
could	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
being	O
frightened	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
her	O
silver	O
buckles	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
shoes	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
and	O
demanded	O
her	O
money	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
purse	O
,	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
open	O
my	O
pocket	O
that	O
he	O
might	O
feel	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
and	O
demanded	O
her	O
purse	O
,	O
she	O
told	O
him	O
she	O
had	O
none	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
demanded	O
my	O
bundle	O
which	O
I	O
had	O
in	O
my	O
hand	O
,	O
in	O
which	O
were	O
a	O
counterpane	O
,	O
a	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Then	O
he	O
made	O
towards	O
Newington	O
Green	O
,	O
I	O
seemed	O
to	O
follow	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
displeased	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
go	O
towards	O
Newington	O
Green	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
shall	O
go	O
the	O
other	O
way	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
towards	O
Canbury-house	O
,	O
I	O
stood	O
about	O
a	O
minute	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
follow	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
another	O
or	O
two	O
of	O
my	O
comrades	O
that	O
will	O
meet	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
turned	O
and	O
saw	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
up	O
what	O
I	O
took	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
turned	O
myself	O
as	O
if	O
going	O
towards	O
Newington	O
Green	O
,	O
he	O
ran	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
he	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
followed	O
him	O
at	O
a	O
distance	O
,	O
thinking	O
some	O
body	O
or	O
other	O
might	O
come	O
to	O
my	O
assistance	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
near	O
Canbury-house	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
last	O
field	O
towards	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
as	O
hard	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
a	O
soldier	O
and	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
men	O
ran	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
pointed	O
which	O
way	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
just	O
turned	O
the	O
corner	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
dropped	O
the	O
bundle	O
before	O
they	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Mrs.	O
Cook	O
's	O
buckles	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
the	O
men	O
brought	O
back	O
the	O
bundle	O
with	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
knife	O
upon	O
him	O
which	O
he	O
delivered	O
after	O
taken	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Cook	I-pers
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
in	O
almost	O
the	O
same	O
wards	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Ricks	I-pers
,	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
heard	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
ran	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
drop	O
the	O
bundle	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
score	O
yards	O
before	O
he	O
had	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
produced	O
the	O
knife	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bundle	O
(	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
prosecutrix	O
)	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
Thomas	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
a	O
carver	O
in	O
Aldersgate-street	O
,	O
with	O
whom	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
served	O
his	O
apprenticeship	O
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
,	O
who	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
Death	O
.	O
Recommended	O
to	O
mercy	O
by	O
the	O
Jury	O
and	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
369	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Grace	B-pers
Allen	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
July	O
23	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Hungerford-market	O
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
quarter	O
after	O
11	O
o'clock	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
room	O
;	O
that	O
,	O
by	O
inquiring	O
among	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
watch	O
again	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Kates	O
's	O
in	O
Chandois-street	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Kates	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
between	O
4	O
and	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
he	O
suspecting	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
stopt	O
them	O
;	O
that	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
given	O
to	O
her	O
by	O
one	O
Rawlins	O
,	O
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
one	O
Swiney	O
Rawlins	O
,	O
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
absconded	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
370	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
mahogany	O
chairs	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
July	O
11	O
.	O
+	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Nightingale-lane	B-place
.	O
The	O
morning	O
that	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
,	O
in	O
removing	O
my	O
goods	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
four	O
mahogany	O
chairs	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
absent	O
,	O
so	O
can	O
give	O
no	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Buttery	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
my	O
daughter	O
.	O
The	O
chairs	O
were	O
handed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
by	O
some	O
people	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
by	O
who	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
again	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Woolger	O
,	O
in	O
St.	O
George	O
's	O
parish	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Berry	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
New-prison	O
,	O
to	O
hear	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
woman	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
daughter	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
two	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
they	O
exactly	O
correspond	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bottoms	O
are	O
numbered	O
,	O
and	O
agree	O
with	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Woolger	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
burnt	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
while	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
book-case	O
and	O
desired	O
leave	O
to	O
set	O
it	O
in	O
there	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
book-case	O
.	O
My	O
brother	O
lives	O
in	O
the	O
Highway	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
brazier	O
and	O
broker	O
.	O
I	O
three	O
times	O
asked	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
if	O
that	O
book-case	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
?	O
he	O
answered	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
also	O
owned	O
the	O
four	O
chairs	O
mentioned	O
in	O
this	O
indictment	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
brought	O
there	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
working	O
hard	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
should	O
loose	O
his	O
all	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
more	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
liberty	O
to	O
bring	O
his	O
goods	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
might	O
detect	O
him	O
.	O
At	O
last	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
an	O
officer	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
chairs	O
they	O
were	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
on	O
his	O
knees	O
and	O
begged	O
for	O
mercy	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
brother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
about	O
half	O
a	O
mile	O
from	O
where	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
.	O
Alexander	B-pers
Goodey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
parish	O
.	O
A	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
occasion	O
to	O
trouble	O
myself	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
chairs	O
and	O
carry	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
delivered	O
to	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
delivered	O
the	O
chairs	O
to	O
him	O
and	O
the	O
bottoms	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
not	O
certain	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
away	O
together	O
.	O
Isaac	B-pers
Newton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Shadwell	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
chairs	O
handed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
go	O
up	O
the	O
walk	O
with	O
some	O
chairs	O
on	O
his	O
back	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
handed	O
four	O
chairs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
street-door	O
and	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Goodey	O
.	O
Keasey	O
Woolger	O
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
a	O
brazier	O
and	O
broker	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
four	O
chairs	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
I	O
received	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
book-case	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
worked	O
very	O
hard	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
very	O
loath	O
to	O
loose	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
begged	O
he	O
might	O
ease	O
his	O
burden	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
welcome	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
times	O
over	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
afterwards	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
away	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
.	O
Job	O
Biffin	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
an	O
officer	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Woolger	O
sent	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
clapped	O
his	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
book-case	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
is	O
this	O
yours	O
?	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
case	O
is	O
my	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
me	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
begged	O
leave	O
to	O
leave	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
till	O
the	O
owners	O
came	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
elevated	O
with	O
liquor	O
,	O
but	O
know	O
what	O
I	O
di	O
d.	O
He	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Emanuel	B-pers
Compton	I-pers
,	O
John	O
Benson	O
,	O
Matthew	B-pers
Fibbs	I-pers
,	O
Patrick	B-pers
Reynolds	I-pers
,	O
James	O
Theron	O
,	O
and	O
-	O
Sweney	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
an	O
honest	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
371	O
,	O
372	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Robert	B-pers
Hill	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Carlow	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
ten	O
silk	O
neck-cloths	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Rainforth	I-pers
privately	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
,	O
Aug.	O
21	O
.	O
++	O
Nicholas	B-pers
Rainforth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
near	B-place
the	I-place
Hermitage	I-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
slop	O
shop	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Aug.	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
sailor	O
's	O
cloaths	O
,	O
but	O
seemed	O
not	O
to	O
settle	O
to	O
any	O
thing	O
;	O
they	O
agreed	O
for	O
a	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
but	O
when	O
they	O
came	O
to	O
pay	O
,	O
they	O
neither	O
of	O
them	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
they	O
left	O
me	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buttons	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
them	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
the	O
25th	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
come	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
and	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
buttons	O
;	O
then	O
Hill	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
some	O
more	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
down	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
neck-cloths	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
had	O
missed	O
something	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
neck-cloths	O
were	O
soon	O
missing	O
,	O
I	O
seized	O
Hill	O
,	O
my	O
servant	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
bolted	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
a	O
porter	O
for	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
Hill	O
was	O
very	O
saucy	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
beer	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
stay	O
,	O
he	O
swore	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
confined	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
case	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
water	O
against	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
counters	O
;	O
then	O
they	O
josteled	O
up	O
together	O
to	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
the	O
neck-cloths	O
were	O
immediately	O
cast	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
black	O
silk	O
,	O
part	O
sell	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
part	O
behind	O
,	O
and	O
withall	O
an	O
old	O
handkerchief	O
stuck	O
to	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
Hill	O
afterwards	O
said	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
from	O
which	O
they	O
came	O
.	O
(	O
Ten	O
neck-cloths	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Bevan	I-pers
,	O
the	O
maid-servant	O
,	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
gave	O
.	O
Hill	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
man	O
missed	O
his	O
neck-cloths	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
them	O
behind	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
supposed	O
one	O
of	O
us	O
had	O
put	O
them	O
there	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
made	O
no	O
resistance	O
.	O
Carlow	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Hill	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
with	O
a	O
design	O
to	O
buy	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
keep	O
Hill	O
company	O
.	O
Hill	O
called	O
William	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bartholomew	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
about	O
six	O
months	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
behaved	O
well	O
,	O
only	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
little	O
extravagant	O
,	O
he	O
being	O
one	O
that	O
had	O
received	O
prize-money	O
for	O
taking	O
the	O
clermione	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
spent	O
the	O
money	O
.	O
Clements	O
called	O
Martha	B-pers
Seal	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
between	O
six	O
and	O
seven	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
know	O
any	O
harm	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
373	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Whiting	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
,	O
May	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
watch-maker	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
missed	O
money	O
at	O
diverse	O
times	O
;	O
he	O
marked	O
10	O
guineas	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
prisoner	O
absconded	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
guineas	O
was	O
missing	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Grub-street	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
home	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
at	O
Hicks's-hall	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
confessed	O
be	O
used	O
to	O
take	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
keys	O
from	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
shift	O
his	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
for	O
five	O
years	O
in	O
that	O
sort	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
account	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
120	O
l.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
his	O
confession	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
his	O
taking	O
this	O
single	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
many	O
others	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
374	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Wilkins	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
leather	O
saddle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
and	O
five	O
other	O
saddles	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Rowland	I-pers
,	O
the	O
head	O
hostler	O
at	O
the	B-place
Lemon-tree	I-place
,	I-place
at	I-place
the	I-place
top	I-place
of	I-place
the	I-place
Hay-market	I-place
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Jennings	O
left	O
a	O
saddle	O
in	O
his	O
care	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
missing	O
with	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
others	O
,	O
the	O
owners	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
by	O
enquiring	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Mill	I-pers
,	O
a	O
sadler	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
that	O
belonging	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jennings	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
bought	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
(	O
who	O
was	O
a	O
helper	O
in	O
the	O
stable	O
)	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
crown	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
worth	O
18	O
or	O
20	O
s.	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
other	O
saddles	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
,	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Mill	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
of	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Dawson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
since	O
made	O
off	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
375	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Jourdan	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pint	O
tin	O
jack	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
August	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
keeps	O
the	O
Horse-and-groom	O
in	O
Portland-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
observed	O
by	O
John	B-pers
Nesbit	I-pers
,	O
who	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
the	O
knife	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pint	O
tin	O
jack	O
afterwards	O
,	O
and	O
conceal	O
them	O
under	O
her	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
stopped	O
after	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
found	O
upon	O
her	O
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
knowing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
often	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
mind	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
376	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Dennis	B-pers
Gahagan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Yarrow	I-pers
.	O
+	O
William	B-pers
Yarrow	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
lives	O
at	O
Endfield	B-place
Wash	I-place
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
him	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
standing	O
by	O
his	O
chaff-house	O
,	O
there	O
lay	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
only	O
a	O
few	O
damsons	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
a	O
little	O
wallet	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
found	O
a	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
plates	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
before	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
377	O
,	O
378	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Smart	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
a	O
silver	O
watch-chain	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
privately	O
from	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Simner	I-pers
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Kirklin	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
knowing	O
it	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Aug.	O
17	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
waterman	O
,	O
and	O
lives	O
in	O
Wapping	O
;	O
he	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
met	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
their	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
bed	O
with	O
Smart	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
before	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
he	O
awaked	O
about	O
3	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
his	O
mistress	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
fastened	O
the	O
door	O
with	O
his	O
garter	O
over	O
two	O
nails	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
confessed	O
their	O
being	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
several	O
charges	O
.	O
Thomas	O
Green	O
,	O
a	O
publican	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
soldier	O
and	O
a	O
German	O
woman	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
honestly	O
come	O
by	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
stopt	O
it	O
,	O
soon	O
after	O
came	O
in	O
Kirklin	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
it	O
as	O
her	O
property	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
found	O
out	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
that	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
Smart	O
said	O
she	O
took	O
all	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
the	O
watch	O
to	O
Kirklin	O
;	O
that	O
Kirklin	O
owned	O
she	O
did	O
receive	O
the	O
watch	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Smart	O
.	O
Smart	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
.	O
T.	O
Kirklin	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
14	O
years	O
.	O
379	O
,	O
380	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Barnes	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Barrett	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
coat	O
button	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
18	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Lewis	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
keeps	O
a	O
silversmiths	O
shop	O
in	O
the	O
Borough	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee	O
buckles	O
,	O
they	O
could	O
not	O
agree	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
;	O
that	O
a	O
silver	O
button	O
was	O
missing	O
from	O
among	O
a	O
dozen	O
that	O
lay	O
on	O
the	O
counter	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
followed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
Radcliff-highway	O
charged	O
them	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
;	O
that	O
Barrett	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
,	O
and	O
hoped	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Barret	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
button	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
coming	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
381	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
linnen	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
Margaret	O
,	O
wife	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
gown	O
of	O
hers	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
she	O
ran	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
with	O
the	O
gown	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
M.	O
Wilson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
baker	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
gown	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
;	O
my	O
child	O
described	O
her	O
to	O
me	O
when	O
I	O
returned	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
such	O
a	O
woman	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
and	O
taken	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
for	O
some	O
money	O
due	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
she	O
bid	O
me	O
take	O
the	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
redeem	O
it	O
in	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hours	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
382	O
,	O
383	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Robert	B-pers
Radford	I-pers
,	O
not	O
taken	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
bushels	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
George	B-pers
Lasiene	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wyburd	I-pers
,	O
July	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	B-pers
Wybard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Tottenham	O
,	O
I	O
deal	O
in	O
coals	O
and	O
corn	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
information	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
boy	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
Wood	O
and	O
another	O
had	O
taken	O
two	O
sacks	O
of	O
malt	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
barge	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Wood	O
had	O
taken	O
out	O
coals	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
coals	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
barges	O
,	O
about	O
four	O
bushels	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
declare	O
that	O
Lassene	O
,	O
who	O
lives	O
at	O
Humerton	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
river	O
,	O
did	O
buy	O
coals	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
he	O
did	O
declare	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
set	O
the	O
coals	O
down	O
by	O
Lassene	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Eliment	I-pers
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Wood	O
and	O
Radford	O
leave	O
about	O
three	O
bushels	O
of	O
coals	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
barge	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
.	O
Wood	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T.	O
Lassene	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
384	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joshua	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
our	O
lord	O
the	B-pers
King	I-pers
,	O
July	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
Robert	B-pers
Pantany	I-pers
,	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
drinking	O
together	O
at	O
diverse	O
houses	O
,	O
they	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
yard	O
in	O
the	O
Hay-market	O
to	O
sleep	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
awaked	O
between	O
6	O
and	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
regimental	O
hat	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
and	O
made	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
tell	O
where	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
385	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Upwood	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
deal	O
chest	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
three	O
iron	O
saws	O
,	O
twenty-one	O
planes	O
,	O
eight	O
wooden	O
ganges	O
,	O
an	O
oyl	O
stone	O
,	O
a	O
hatchet	O
,	O
two	O
wooden	O
squares	O
,	O
two	O
hammers	O
,	O
three	O
rasps	O
,	O
six	O
files	O
,	O
six	O
chissels	O
,	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
pinchers	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
wooden	O
mallet	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Perkins	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
employed	O
one	O
Robert	B-pers
Row	I-pers
to	O
carry	O
the	O
chest	O
of	O
tools	O
for	O
him	O
to	O
White-chapel	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
the	O
wrong	O
way	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
hands	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Nortonfallgate	O
.	O
Robert	O
Row	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
was	O
to	O
direct	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
into	O
Nortonfallgate	B-place
he	O
pitched	O
the	O
chest	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
,	O
about	O
9	O
o'clock	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
two	O
ale-houses	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
might	O
leave	O
it	O
in	O
their	O
houses	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
denied	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
liberty	O
at	O
another	O
house	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
absent	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
;	O
that	O
upon	O
going	O
for	O
the	O
chest	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
informed	O
where	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
gone	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
shoulder	O
,	O
going	O
up	O
into	O
his	O
own	O
room	O
,	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
:	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
it	O
to	O
preserve	O
it	O
for	O
the	O
owner	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
386	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Hardimore	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cotton	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
two	O
teaspoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
a	O
cardinal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
two	O
aprons	O
,	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
a	O
shift	O
,	O
a	O
cap	O
.	O
and	O
two	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Olivia	B-pers
Milford	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Jan.	O
28	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
lives	O
in	O
Narrow-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
a	O
lodger	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
about	O
11	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
care	O
of	O
all	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
returned	O
about	O
2	O
,	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
found	O
her	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
with	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
shift	O
on	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
afterwards	O
found	O
the	O
two	O
tea-spoons	O
and	O
table-cloth	O
pawned	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
to	O
one	O
Simpson	O
,	O
a	O
neighbour	O
;	O
she	O
owned	O
pawned	O
the	O
cardinal	O
at	O
Bow	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
fact	O
I	O
ever	O
did	O
.	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
387	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Adam	B-pers
Baldwick	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mary	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
of	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
her	O
property	O
,	O
Sept.	O
2	O
.	O
+	O
Mary	B-pers
Murray	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
me	O
within	O
side	O
Privy-garden	B-place
gate	I-place
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
held	O
my	O
hands	O
while	O
the	O
prisoner	O
took	O
out	O
three	O
sixpences	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
shilling	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
;	O
he	O
pulled	O
my	O
cloaths	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
,	O
he	O
wanted	O
to	O
do	O
both	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
let	O
him	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
used	O
me	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
manner	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
private	O
part	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
me	O
very	O
ill	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
me	O
a	O
many	O
nasty	O
names	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
Poll	B-pers
Symonds	I-pers
with	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Broady	O
took	O
me	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
me	O
worse	O
than	O
before	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
about	O
100	O
yards	O
from	O
the	O
garden	O
gate	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
robbing	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
denied	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
searched	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
s.	O
4	O
d.	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
money	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
give	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
took	O
from	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
other	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
get	O
more	O
bye	O
and	O
bye	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
centinels	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Broady	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
Privy-garden	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
outcry	O
with	O
this	O
woman	O
and	O
another	O
,	O
they	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
assist	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
should	O
be	O
murdered	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
about	O
ten	O
yards	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
came	O
up	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
would	O
make	O
me	O
shew	O
my	O
authority	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
back	O
.	O
I	O
then	O
went	O
on	O
and	O
called	O
the	O
watch	O
;	O
there	O
came	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
watchmen	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
away	O
.	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
,	O
so	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
the	O
watchman	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
stood	O
to	O
talk	O
to	O
the	O
two	O
centinels	O
that	O
stood	O
at	O
Privy-garden	O
gate	O
,	O
this	O
woman	O
and	O
another	O
came	O
by	O
,	O
we	O
began	O
joking	O
,	O
they	O
seeing	O
we	O
were	O
soldiers	O
and	O
would	O
make	O
nothing	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
began	O
to	O
call	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
robbed	O
her	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
never	O
laid	O
a	O
foul	O
hand	O
upon	O
her	O
,	O
or	O
touched	O
her	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Moses	B-pers
Pale	I-pers
his	O
serjeant	O
,	O
who	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
him	O
as	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
has	O
the	O
character	O
of	O
a	O
common	O
prostitute	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Gyles	I-pers
.	O
I	O
knew	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
always	O
very	O
honest	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
388	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Christopher	B-pers
Elinor	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pewter	O
chamber-pot	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
one	O
pewter	O
bason	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Charsley	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
keeps	O
a	O
pewterer	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
Shoe-Lane	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
his	O
journeyman	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
detected	O
in	O
taking	O
the	O
chamber-pot	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
shop	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
bason	O
was	O
found	O
put	O
by	O
under	O
a	O
stair-case	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
a	O
private	O
mark	O
was	O
put	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
to	O
dinner	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
followed	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
under	O
his	O
apron	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
bason	O
in	O
change	O
for	O
a	O
quart	O
pot	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
pot	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Robert	B-pers
Norton	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
him	O
18	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
389	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Abraham	B-pers
Judah	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
forging	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
note	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	O
Hall	O
subscribed	O
thereunto	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
of	O
100	O
l.	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
20	O
.	O
1761	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
was	O
called	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
390	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Hearn	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Felstead	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
4	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
down	O
Grace-church-street	B-place
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
on	O
his	O
left	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
turned	O
his	O
hand	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
right	O
side	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
withall	O
turned	O
his	O
pocket	O
inside	O
out	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
watch	O
,	O
none	O
came	O
;	O
that	O
they	O
struggled	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
but	O
at	O
last	O
he	O
got	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
found	O
his	O
handkerchief	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
391	O
,	O
392	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
T	I-pers
-	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Tooley	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
men	O
's	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
's	O
pumps	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
stuff	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Hutton	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
James	O
,	O
August	O
23	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
lives	O
in	O
Barbican	B-place
,	O
was	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
came	O
in	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
for	O
Tooley	O
,	O
that	O
in	O
the	O
time	O
he	O
observed	O
T	O
-	O
to	O
take	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
pockets	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
took	O
one	O
pair	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
hold	O
of	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
not	O
go	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
had	O
another	O
pair	O
about	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
threw	O
down	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
then	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
kick	O
of	O
the	O
breech	O
and	O
let	O
him	O
go	O
;	O
soon	O
he	O
saw	O
they	O
were	O
not	O
the	O
shoes	O
he	O
missed	O
;	O
that	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
,	O
he	O
missed	O
three	O
pair	O
;	O
Tooley	O
was	O
taken	O
and	O
brought	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
but	O
2	O
s.	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Houton	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
felt	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
in	O
T	O
-	O
's	O
pocket-lining	O
as	O
he	O
came	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
T	O
-	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
when	O
Tooley	O
had	O
tried	O
on	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
Tooley	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
them	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
kick	O
of	O
the	O
backside	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
go	O
like	O
a	O
scoundrel	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
took	O
up	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
from	O
the	O
bench	O
and	O
threw	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
Tooley	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
trusted	O
in	O
his	O
business	O
with	O
silver	O
of	O
great	O
value	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
polisher	O
of	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
far	O
from	O
being	O
so	O
mean	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
.	O
Tooley	O
called	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hide	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cearsel	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Hearn	I-pers
,	O
Robert	B-pers
Picstersgale	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
Parnell	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
T	O
-	O
called	O
Elizabeth	O
Hill	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Goodwin	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Lankford	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Henry	B-pers
Nun	I-pers
,	O
who	O
said	O
the	O
same	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
T	O
-	O
Guilty	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
Tooley	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
[	O
Transportation	O
.	O
See	O
summary	O
.	O
]	O
393	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Palmer	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
women	O
's	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
and	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
value	O
9	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hoppy	I-pers
,	O
July	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Hoppy	I-pers
keeps	O
a	O
shoemaker	O
's	O
shop	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Paul	I-place
's	I-place
Church	I-place
yard	I-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
errand-boy	O
there	O
about	O
three	O
months	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
away	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
observed	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
new	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
on	O
,	O
on	O
asing	O
his	O
mother	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
he	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
none	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
,	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
spoiled	O
two	O
pair	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
in	O
Field	O
lane	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
the	O
man	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
brought	O
any	O
more	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
so	O
he	O
had	O
stole	O
the	O
quantity	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
old	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
's	O
son	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
but	O
about	O
teen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
boy	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
been	O
drawn	O
away	O
by	O
that	O
man	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
394	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
being	O
at	O
large	O
in	O
this	O
kingdom	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
been	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
copy	O
of	O
his	O
conviction	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
wherein	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
and	O
convicted	O
at	O
the	O
Old	O
Bailey	O
on	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
April	O
1762	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pattison	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
privately	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Bodington	I-pers
,	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
had	O
the	O
prisoner	O
twice	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
saw	O
him	O
tried	O
and	O
heard	O
sentence	O
pronounced	O
upon	O
him	O
in	O
April	O
sessions	O
1762	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
transported	O
for	O
seven	O
years	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
large	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
Cheapside	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
Tower-hill	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
this	O
last	O
year	O
,	O
particularly	O
on	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Coventry	O
gang	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
by	O
a	O
Habeas	O
to	O
London	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
pressed	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
was	O
12	O
months	O
in	O
New-York	O
town	O
in	O
Virginia	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
Jason	O
;	O
that	O
coming	O
for	O
England	O
,	O
about	O
50	O
leagues	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
the	O
gulph	O
of	O
Florida	O
,	O
he	O
and	O
a	O
Dane	O
were	O
put	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
brig	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
lost	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
hands	O
,	O
to	O
help	O
them	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
bound	O
to	O
England	O
,	O
that	O
they	O
first	O
put	O
into	O
the	O
and	O
then	O
proceeded	O
to	O
London	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
then	O
went	O
to	O
Covnery	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
395	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Hobbs	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
cloth	O
breeches	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Philip	B-pers
Barther	I-pers
.	O
June	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
lodged	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
at	O
Ponder's-end	O
;	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
after	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
being	O
charged	O
,	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
the	O
breeches	O
and	O
coat	O
for	O
12	O
s.	O
Mr.	O
Greenwood	O
and	O
Mr.	O
White	O
deposed	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
this	O
confession	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
bundle	O
together	O
near	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
door	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
396	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Death	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
waistcoat	O
with	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
,	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
++	O
Thomas	B-pers
Thornton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Tower-street	B-place
.	O
The	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
room	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
suspected	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
had	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Popard	O
in	O
Queen-street	O
,	O
Tower-hill	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
son	O
to	O
the	O
late	O
Capt	O
.	O
Death	O
,	O
who	O
commanded	O
the	O
Terrible	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
great	O
regard	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
knowing	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
family	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
ready	O
to	O
pass	O
it	O
by	O
,	O
and	O
release	O
him	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Popard	O
produced	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
4	O
s.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lived	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
till	O
the	O
14th	O
of	O
May	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
after	O
my	O
watch	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
country	O
for	O
3	O
guineas	O
;	O
he	O
begged	O
the	O
favour	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
prosecute	O
,	O
fearing	O
his	O
grandmother	O
should	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
as	O
it	O
might	O
do	O
him	O
great	O
injury	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
pass	O
it	O
by	O
,	O
but	O
hearing	O
of	O
his	O
other	O
bad	O
behaviour	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
note	O
for	O
6	O
guineas	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
.	O
Smith	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
take	O
a	O
note	O
of	O
him	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
very	O
great	O
friend	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
dated	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
March	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
The	O
Note	O
was	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Thornton	O
wrote	O
it	O
.	O
Thornton	O
.	O
I	O
drew	B-pers
this	O
Note	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
;	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
was	O
not	O
mentioned	O
;	O
what	O
was	O
between	O
Mr.	O
Smith	O
and	O
him	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Ann	B-pers
Lansescey	I-pers
,	O
with	O
whom	O
he	O
lodged	O
sometime	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
very	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
397	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Abraham	B-pers
Basset	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
ounces	O
of	O
silver	O
wire	O
and	O
cuttings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
13	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Priest	I-pers
and	O
Richard	B-pers
Passiter	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
16	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutors	O
are	O
goldsmiths	O
in	O
Wood-street	B-place
.	O
It	O
appeared	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
blacksmith	O
,	O
had	O
put	O
on	O
a	O
lock	O
to	O
a	O
back	O
shop	O
door	O
belonging	O
to	O
a	O
work-shop	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutors	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
16th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Bridges	O
a	O
silver-caster	O
in	O
Foster-lane	O
sent	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
brought	O
the	O
silver	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
cast	O
into	O
buckles	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
his	O
asking	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
,	O
suspecting	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
it	O
)	O
he	O
varied	O
in	O
his	O
account	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
taken	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Priest	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
at	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
Lad-lane	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
three	O
relations	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
,	O
exclusive	O
of	O
this	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
398	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Dixey	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
l	O
.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Cotterell	I-pers
;	O
to	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
guilty	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
told	O
the	O
Court	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
in	O
her	O
power	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
his	O
servant	O
,	O
to	O
have	O
taken	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
believed	O
it	O
her	O
first	O
offence	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
but	O
fourteen	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Her	O
father	O
promised	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
her	O
for	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
B	O
.	O
399	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Catherine	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
five	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sleeves	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
shift	O
,	O
five	O
linnen	O
caps	O
,	O
four	O
hoods	O
,	O
three	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
a	O
cambrick	O
apron	O
,	O
a	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
pockets	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
Sybilla	B-pers
Mary	I-pers
Lucas	I-pers
,	O
July	O
20	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
lives	O
in	O
Bedford-court	B-place
,	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
she	O
suspected	O
her	O
,	O
as	O
being	O
the	O
only	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
the	O
time	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
the	O
goods	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sleeves	O
in	O
her	O
hand	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
spoke	O
well	O
of	O
her	O
character	O
before	O
this	O
;	O
and	O
Mary	B-pers
Fuller	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Dorothy	B-pers
Fidler	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
employed	O
her	O
,	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
latter	O
proposed	O
to	O
employ	O
her	O
again	O
was	O
she	O
at	O
large	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
400	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Maddock	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
Aug.	O
1	O
.	O
+	O
James	B-pers
Dalton	I-pers
.	O
William	B-pers
Harrison	I-pers
is	O
a	O
lunatick	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Aug	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
a	O
silver	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
in	O
Diot-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Gyles	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
wanted	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
lodging	O
for	O
Harrison	O
,	O
Harrison	O
is	O
since	O
dead	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
take	O
it	O
publickly	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
was	O
stealing	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
Dalton	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
would	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
it	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Three	O
days	O
after	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
it	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
left	O
it	O
with	O
the	O
landlord	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
say	O
what	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
,	O
or	O
where	O
he	O
lived	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
then	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
had	O
pawned	O
it	O
at	O
one	O
Davidsons	O
's	O
at	O
Queen-hyth	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
two	O
constables	O
,	O
there	O
it	O
was	O
produced	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Davidson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
the	O
watch	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
Aug.	O
for	O
25	O
s.	O
to	O
his	O
servant	O
in	O
his	O
presence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
Harrison	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
14	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
him	O
the	O
rest	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
401	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gale	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Burton	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Sept.	O
about	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
two	O
bags	O
of	O
feathers	O
,	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
one	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
a	O
woollen	O
cloak	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
woollen	O
cloth	O
,	O
the	O
goods	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
.	O
+	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
lives	O
in	O
Lower	B-place
Holloway	I-place
.	O
He	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
missing	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
of	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Sept.	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
say	O
his	O
house	O
had	O
been	O
broke	O
open	O
,	O
there	O
being	O
several	O
panes	O
of	O
glass	O
broke	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
but	O
the	O
casement	O
might	O
be	O
left	O
open	O
;	O
he	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
house	O
which	O
his	O
brother	O
at	O
Stroud	O
Green	O
let	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
her	O
husband	O
live	O
in	O
for	O
nothing	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
,	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
said	O
she	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
two	O
men	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
;	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
them	O
when	O
first	O
asked	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
allowed	O
to	O
be	O
true	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
402	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Huff	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eleven	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Jaque	I-pers
,	O
Aug.	O
29	O
.	O
++	O
William	O
Jaque	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
linnen-draper	O
in	O
Maiden-lane	B-place
,	I-place
Covent	I-place
garden	I-place
;	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
into	O
his	O
shop	O
with	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
about	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
she	O
pretended	O
to	O
buy	O
some	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
very	O
difficult	O
,	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
,	O
mamma	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
spend	O
a	O
penny	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
the	O
prisoner	O
would	O
not	O
buy	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
followed	O
the	O
child	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
five	O
minutes	O
after	O
he	O
missed	O
some	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	O
Fielding	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
of	O
his	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Drake	I-pers
,	O
servant	O
to	O
messrs.	O
Hughes	O
and	O
Batten	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
came	O
into	O
their	O
shop	O
in	O
York-street	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
29th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
about	O
8	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
she	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
some	O
kenting	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
he	O
shewed	O
her	O
some	O
,	O
on	O
her	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
he	O
observed	O
her	O
to	O
draw	O
three	O
quantities	O
of	O
them	O
off	O
the	O
counter	O
with	O
one	O
hand	O
,	O
while	O
she	O
was	O
holding	O
a	O
piece	O
up	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
with	O
her	O
other	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
child	O
said	O
her	O
foot	O
was	O
asleep	O
,	O
and	O
her	O
garter	O
was	O
off	O
;	O
she	O
stooped	O
down	O
by	O
her	O
mother	O
,	O
as	O
if	O
to	O
tye	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
up	O
the	O
three	O
pieces	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
her	O
apron	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
woman	O
said	O
she	O
wanted	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
check	O
;	O
he	O
bid	O
her	O
walk	O
to	O
the	O
fore	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
did	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
round	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
shut	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
handkerchiefs	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
apron	O
;	O
he	O
searched	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
in	O
her	O
apron	O
many	O
silk	O
and	O
kenting	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
her	O
apron	O
was	O
full	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
her	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
swore	O
to	O
these	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
how	O
the	O
child	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Samuel	B-pers
Hoskins	I-pers
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Gray	I-pers
,	O
Margaret	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Judith	B-pers
Wright	I-pers
,	O
who	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
There	O
was	O
four	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
her	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
nature	O
.	O
403	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Francis	B-pers
Florence	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tankard	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
and	O
a	O
silver	O
cream	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Patrick	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
,	O
July	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
(	O
The	O
prisoner	O
being	O
a	O
foreigner	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
speak	O
but	O
broken	O
English	O
,	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Bourn	I-pers
keeps	O
the	O
Blue	O
Posts	O
alehouse	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Alban's-street	I-place
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
:	O
the	O
tankard	O
and	O
cream-pot	O
were	O
missing	O
about	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
from	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
bar	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
enquiring	O
about	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
pawn	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Heather	O
's	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Heather	O
deposed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pledged	O
them	O
with	O
him	O
on	O
the	O
23d	O
of	O
July	O
.	O
They	O
were	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
T.	O
404	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Pepys	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
July	O
24	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Bethall	I-pers
,	O
in	O
driving	O
Mr.	O
Pepys	O
's	O
coach	O
,	O
missed	O
the	O
great-coat	O
off	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Merchant	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Drew	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
they	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
take	O
it	O
off	O
the	O
box	O
as	O
it	O
stopt	O
in	O
Southampton-street	B-place
,	O
who	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
See	O
him	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Godson	I-pers
,	O
No	O
.	O
67	O
,	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Alderman	O
Rawlinson	O
's	O
Mayoralty	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
great-coat	O
.	O
405	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Williams	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
burglariously	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Plummer	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
April	O
,	O
about	O
12	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
castors	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
7	O
l	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
candlesticks	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
sauce-boats	O
,	O
two	O
silver	O
pint	O
mugs	O
,	O
four	O
silver	O
saltsellers	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
cup	O
,	O
a	O
large	O
silver	O
soup-spoon	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
only	O
evidence	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
Francis	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
,	O
an	O
accomplice	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
got	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
down	O
the	O
area	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
for	O
23	O
guineas	O
,	O
but	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
or	O
could	O
not	O
recollect	O
the	O
person	O
's	O
name	O
nor	O
place	O
of	O
abode	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Andrew	B-pers
Girerdot	I-pers
Lucier	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
June	O
,	O
about	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
silver	O
teaspoons	O
,	O
one	O
Japan	O
tea-chest	O
,	O
twelve	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Andrew	O
,	O
and	O
several	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Andre	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
said	O
dwelling	O
house	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
only	O
evidence	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
in	O
this	O
was	O
Wilkinson	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
406	O
,	O
407	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
third	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
John	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
2d	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
one	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Darker	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
did	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
four	O
silver	O
watches	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
watches	O
with	O
shagreen	O
cases	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
l.	O
six	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
other	O
things	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Hannah	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
only	O
evidence	O
to	O
the	O
fact	O
in	O
this	O
was	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
three	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
24	O
s.	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
Hannah	B-pers
Darker	I-pers
,	O
privately	O
,	O
Feb.	O
26	O
.	O
++	O
Hannah	B-pers
Darker	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
she	O
keeps	O
a	O
sale-shop	O
,	O
and	O
deals	O
in	O
plate	O
,	O
watches	O
,	O
&	O
c	O
.	O
in	O
Barbican	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
come	O
i	O
n	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
some	O
,	O
George	B-pers
Tucker	I-pers
came	O
in	O
and	O
asked	O
to	O
see	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
shew	O
him	O
any	O
,	O
fearing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
should	O
run	O
away	O
with	O
the	O
buckles	O
;	O
Tucker	O
stood	O
some	O
distance	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
from	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckles	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
,	O
stop	O
thief	O
!	O
Tucker	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
run	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
more	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
afterwards	O
she	O
found	O
they	O
were	O
intimate	O
acquaintance	O
,	O
but	O
Tucker	O
was	O
not	O
near	O
the	O
buckles	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
10	O
minutes	O
after	O
they	O
were	O
gone	O
she	O
missed	O
three	O
pair	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
;	O
she	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
remembered	O
coming	O
one	O
Saturday	O
night	O
to	O
her	O
shop	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
It	O
did	O
not	O
signify	O
asking	O
him	O
any	O
questions	O
then	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
remember	O
it	O
;	O
but	O
said	O
no	O
more	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
innocent	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
Joseph	B-pers
Richardson	I-pers
,	O
a	O
publican	O
in	O
Hatfield-street	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
he	O
never	O
heard	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
.	O
T.	O
408	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Tompkins	I-pers
was	O
a	O
3d	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Morgan	I-pers
a	O
2d	O
time	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
Samuel	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
other	O
silver	O
buckles	O
value	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harding	I-pers
,	O
July	O
6	O
.	O
++	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
is	O
a	O
Gold-smith	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	B-place
,	O
he	O
deposed	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
when	O
the	O
buckles	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
July	O
,	O
but	O
upon	O
returning	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
glass	O
case	O
had	O
been	O
wrenched	O
,	O
and	O
more	O
buckles	O
taken	O
away	O
than	O
had	O
been	O
laid	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
last	O
he	O
received	O
a	O
letter	O
from	O
the	O
bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
sitting	O
at	O
Hicks's-hall	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
one	O
Masters	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
saw	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
large	O
silver	O
buckles	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
lost	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
of	O
his	O
own	O
finishing	O
;	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
)	O
then	O
he	O
was	O
directed	O
to	O
New	O
Prison	O
,	O
there	O
Wilkinson	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
stole	O
them	O
and	O
others	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
glass	O
case	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
pump	O
,	O
(	O
which	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
shop	O
)	O
he	O
heard	O
Tompkins	O
,	O
on	O
his	O
reexamination	O
,	O
acknowledge	O
before	O
the	O
Justices	O
that	O
he	O
begged	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
wire	O
at	O
a	O
tin	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
crooked	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
forced	O
up	O
the	O
glass	O
so	O
as	O
to	O
hook	O
out	O
the	O
buckles	O
with	O
the	O
crooked	O
wire	O
.	O
Francis	B-pers
Wilkinson	I-pers
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
and	O
the	O
three	O
prisoners	O
did	O
the	O
fact	O
;	O
but	O
there	O
being	O
no	O
evidence	O
of	O
credit	O
to	O
support	O
him	O
against	O
Gregory	O
and	O
Morgan	O
,	O
Tomkins	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T.	O
Gregory	O
,	O
and	O
Morgan	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
409	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Isabella	B-pers
Watson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
unknown	O
,	O
did	O
put	O
George	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
dwelling-house	O
near	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
St.	O
Bride	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
two	O
guineas	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
July	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
George	B-pers
Grace	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
July	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
Bull-and-gate	O
,	O
in	O
Holborn	O
,	O
from	O
White-chapel	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
going	O
down	O
Fleet-lane	O
stood	O
two	O
women	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
see	O
her	O
lodging	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
drink	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
porter	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
afford	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
wine	O
,	O
(	O
something	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
taste	O
it	O
)	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
,	O
and	O
would	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
any	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
my	O
throat	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
me	O
backwards	O
on	O
an	O
old	O
bedstead	O
,	O
till	O
they	O
took	O
two	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
nobody	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
they	O
would	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
pay	O
for	O
the	O
wine	O
;	O
the	O
other	O
got	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
she	O
