TOKEN	NE
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
23d	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
24th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
FEBRUARY	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Third	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honurable	O
William	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
III	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1763	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
JOHN	B-pers
RYALL	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BECKFORD	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
Sir	O
Henry	B-pers
Gould	I-pers
*	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Mr.	O
Baron	B-pers
Perrott	I-pers
+	O
,	O
Sir	O
William	B-pers
Moreton	I-pers
++	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
Recorder	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
~	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Deputy	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
++	O
,	O
and	O
~	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	B-pers
,	I-pers
M	I-pers
.	I-pers
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Henry	B-pers
Connington	I-pers
,	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Keys	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Beetson	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Buckland	I-pers
,	O
Isaac	B-pers
Newman	I-pers
,	O
Jervisse	O
Schooley	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Coleman	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Herbert	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Heath	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Russell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Cobbet	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Dickins	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Townsend	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Jackson	I-pers
,	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Coates	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Carter	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
George	B-pers
Eyres	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Farmborough	I-pers
.	O
106	O
,	O
107	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Jane	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
stuff	O
pocket	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
d.	O
one	O
cloth	O
cardinal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
s.	O
four	O
linnen	O
shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
four	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
dimmity	O
stock	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
apron	O
,	O
eight	O
linnen	O
caps	O
,	O
one	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
one	O
brass	O
pepper-box	O
,	O
four	O
linnen	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
and	O
7	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Ashworth	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
13	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Ashworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bowl-yard	B-place
,	I-place
St.	I-place
Giles	I-place
's	I-place
.	I-place
About	O
9	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
January	O
last	O
,	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
fell	O
into	O
a	O
fit	O
;	O
she	O
was	O
pulling	O
off	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
struck	O
against	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
it	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
hold	O
her	O
:	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
they	O
would	O
come	O
in	O
and	O
light	O
my	O
candle	O
for	O
me	O
:	O
she	O
had	O
2	O
fits	O
,	O
which	O
continued	O
some	O
time	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
some	O
linnen	O
in	O
a	O
tub	O
that	O
day	O
,	O
which	O
my	O
wife	O
had	O
put	O
there	O
ready	O
for	O
washing	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
my	O
wife	O
first	O
missed	O
her	O
pocket	O
,	O
then	O
her	O
cardinal	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
linnen	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
gone	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
lighted	O
the	O
candle	O
for	O
you	O
?	O
Ashworth	O
.	O
Clements	O
did	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
lived	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
as	O
we	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
we	O
called	O
her	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
our	O
loss	O
.	O
My	O
wife	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
farthing	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
she	O
would	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
a	O
gown	O
for	O
her	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
would	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
in	O
.	O
Then	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
for	O
a	O
dram	O
;	O
there	O
the	O
landlord	O
informed	O
her	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
a	O
woman	O
at	O
his	O
house	O
drying	O
wet	O
linnen	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
who	O
had	O
set	O
her	O
up	O
some	O
drams	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
her	O
again	O
if	O
he	O
saw	O
her	O
.	O
Then	O
Knight	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
not	O
be	O
afraid	O
about	O
your	O
cardinal	O
,	O
for	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
room	O
:	O
she	O
delivered	O
it	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
with	O
her	O
and	O
me	O
in	O
search	O
of	O
Clements	O
;	O
and	O
at	O
Clements	O
's	O
mother	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
Coal-yard	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
found	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
pocket	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
mother	O
in	O
charge	O
till	O
we	O
found	O
the	O
daughter	O
:	O
when	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
she	O
confessed	O
she	O
had	O
sold	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
a	O
shift	O
to	O
a	O
woman	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
for	O
18	O
d.	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
accordingly	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
aprons	O
,	O
not	O
quite	O
dry	O
,	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Desalear	O
's	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
pawned	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
;	O
after	O
that	O
we	O
got	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
there	O
3	O
handkerchiefs	O
pawned	O
in	O
her	O
name	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Ashworth	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
She	O
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
her	O
husband	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
addition	O
,	O
That	O
Clements	O
owned	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
a	O
white	O
apron	O
full	O
of	O
linnen	O
,	O
which	O
she	O
lost	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
shirt	O
,	O
shift	O
,	O
and	O
apron	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
,	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
.	O
)	O
Anthony	B-pers
Desalear	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Holborn	O
.	O
Jane	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
brought	O
this	O
check	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
with	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
about	O
9	O
or	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
;	O
she	O
had	O
brought	O
2	O
handkerchiefs	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Weatherly	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
sale	O
shop	O
in	O
a	O
cellar	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
this	O
shirt	O
and	O
shift	O
,	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
;	O
it	O
was	O
some	O
time	O
since	O
Christmas	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
exact	O
time	O
.	O
Knight	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
2	O
handkerchiefs	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
all	O
dirty	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
a	O
week	O
before	O
she	O
says	O
she	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
Clements	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
washed	O
the	O
things	O
for	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
drunk	O
,	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
gin	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
drink	O
.	O
Another	O
woman	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
she	O
charged	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
She	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
home	O
with	O
her	O
gown	O
torn	O
from	O
her	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
was	O
stopt	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
:	O
she	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
shirt	O
and	O
a	O
shift	O
to	O
make	O
me	O
a	O
handkerchief	O
of	O
.	O
She	O
makes	O
it	O
her	O
practice	O
to	O
take	O
poor	O
creatures	O
lives	O
away	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
in	O
Newgate	O
herself	O
a	O
sessions	O
or	O
two	O
ago	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
was	O
discharged	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
Jane	B-pers
Knight	I-pers
;	O
I	O
believe	O
this	O
woman	O
was	O
the	O
most	O
to	O
blame	O
.	O
Knight	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
Clements	O
Guilty	O
10	O
d.	O
T	O
.	O
108	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Messenger	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
outside	O
case	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
30	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
3	O
linnen	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
George	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
George	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
opposite	O
to	O
Exeter-Change	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
fire	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
mine	O
put	O
up	O
some	O
of	O
my	O
things	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
for	O
moving	O
them	O
in	O
case	O
of	O
danger	O
;	O
these	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
put	O
into	O
a	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
they	O
lay	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
days	O
;	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
alarmed	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
with	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
we	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
let	O
them	O
abide	O
in	O
the	O
bag	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
this	O
gold	O
case	O
of	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
seen	O
it	O
between	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
put	O
into	O
that	O
bag	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
time	O
it	O
was	O
missing	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
and	O
not	O
after	O
that	O
,	O
till	O
it	O
was	O
found	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
Friday	O
the	O
18th	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
had	O
let	O
a	O
lodger	O
's	O
servant	O
see	O
the	O
watch-case	O
,	O
who	O
informed	O
us	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
upon	O
which	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
justice	O
Mombray	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
the	O
fire	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
sweeping	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
mistress	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
the	O
fire	O
?	O
Jennings	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
month	O
ago	O
last	O
Friday	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Jennings	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
servant	O
for	O
3	O
months	O
.	O
The	O
watch-case	O
was	O
missing	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
it	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
hope	O
we	O
shall	O
find	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
never	O
suspected	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scarborough	I-pers
said	O
she	O
had	O
seen	O
such	O
a	O
case	O
in	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
called	O
her	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
she	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
oblige	O
me	O
with	O
the	O
sight	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
it	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
a	O
gold	O
case	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
brother	O
3	O
months	O
ago	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
you	O
had	O
one	O
last	O
Monday	O
se'nnight	O
in	O
your	O
pocket	O
;	O
she	O
positively	O
denied	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
look	O
into	O
her	O
box	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
her	O
heart	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
her	O
box	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
could	O
accuse	O
her	O
with	O
.	O
When	O
she	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Scarborough	I-pers
were	O
together	O
,	O
I	O
began	O
about	O
it	O
again	O
:	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
equivocate	O
a	O
little	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
she	O
pulled	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
it	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
when	O
she	O
and	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
the	O
dining	O
room	O
door	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
charge	O
you	O
,	O
madam	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
say	O
that	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
into	O
her	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
hand	O
:	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
picked	O
it	O
up	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
paper	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
back	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
an	O
intention	O
to	O
give	O
it	O
me	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
told	O
it	O
to	O
some	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
some	O
table	O
linnen	O
and	O
sheets	O
at	O
her	O
brother	O
's	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
her	O
brother	O
,	O
desiring	O
him	O
to	O
bring	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
of	O
that	O
sort	O
of	O
hers	O
to	O
me	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
her	O
brother	O
and	O
sister	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
3	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
swore	O
to	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
Newgate	O
Elizabeth	O
Scarborough	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
a	O
lodger	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Jennings	O
's	O
;	O
last	O
Monday	O
was	O
fortnight	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
to	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
o'clock	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
gold	O
case	O
of	O
a	O
watch	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
whited	O
brown	O
paper	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
saw	O
some	O
cotton	O
in	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
another	O
watch	O
which	O
her	O
sister	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
her	O
sister	O
had	O
left	O
her	O
two	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
watch-case	O
wrapped	O
up	O
in	O
paper	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
sweeping	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
intend	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
.	O
Guilty	O
39	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
109	O
,	O
110	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Alice	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Dilly	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
punch	O
ladle	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
milk	O
pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
silver	O
cannister	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Scholey	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Scholey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Chamber-street	B-place
,	I-place
Goodmans-fields	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Jan	O
.	O
I	O
imagined	O
they	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
;	O
we	O
thought	O
we	O
heard	O
somebody	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
thinking	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
one	O
of	O
our	O
lodgers	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
not	O
go	O
to	O
see	O
immediately	O
;	O
but	O
,	O
in	O
about	O
time	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
parlour	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
plate	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
an	O
opposite	O
neighbour	O
saw	O
a	O
woman	O
come	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
as	O
she	O
directed	O
,	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
meet	O
with	O
her	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Poupard	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
brought	O
me	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
(	O
3	O
table	O
spoons	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
.	O
)	O
these	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
which	O
I	O
lost	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
stopt	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
is	O
here	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
court	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
,	O
only	O
Dilly	O
acknowledged	O
in	O
my	O
hearing	O
before	O
the	O
justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
spoons	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Scholey	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
another	O
man	O
gave	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Charles	B-pers
Kishire	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Poupard	O
.	O
These	O
3	O
spoons	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Feb.	O
by	O
a	O
man	O
that	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
kind	O
of	O
a	O
doctor	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Matthew	B-pers
Thorokey	I-pers
,	O
he	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Dilly	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Andrew	B-pers
Poupard	I-pers
.	O
The	O
spoons	O
were	O
brought	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
the	O
person	O
to	O
Dilly	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
the	O
spoons	O
to	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
brought	O
them	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
we	O
took	O
the	O
woman	O
also	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
Dilly	O
say	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
Poupard	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
left	O
them	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
him	O
to	O
sell	O
them	O
for	O
him	O
:	O
being	O
asked	O
who	O
that	O
man	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
sailor	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
.	O
Esther	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
came	O
into	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
a	O
silver	O
milk-pot	O
,	O
a	O
punch-ladle	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
sugar-cannister	O
.	O
She	O
offer	O
'd	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
fetch	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
price	O
they	O
were	O
pawn	O
'd	O
for	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
that	O
woman	O
?	O
E.	O
George	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
quite	O
a	O
stranger	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
her	O
.	O
Alice	B-pers
Sharp	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
the	O
prisoners	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
George	O
's	O
house	O
wrangling	O
and	O
fighting	O
and	O
making	O
a	O
disturbance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
them	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Sharp	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
them	O
a	O
little	O
while	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
harm	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
a	O
halfpenny-worth	O
of	O
ill	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
here	O
?	O
A	O
.	O
Sharp	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
;	O
because	O
I	O
said	O
a	O
woman	O
fell	O
in	O
fits	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
George	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
Poupard	O
.	O
Esther	O
George	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
woman	O
that	O
fell	O
in	O
a	O
fit	O
in	O
her	O
house	O
that	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
her	O
the	O
plate	O
she	O
has	O
mentioned	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Esther	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
Is	O
the	O
woman	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
offered	O
to	O
sell	O
you	O
the	O
plate	O
?	O
Esther	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
woman	O
that	O
fell	O
in	O
fits	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
believe	O
that	O
she	O
is	O
the	O
same	O
woman	O
that	O
offered	O
me	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Both	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
111	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Fox	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
,	O
maliciously	O
,	O
and	O
wilfully	O
setting	O
fire	O
to	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Richard	B-pers
Dymott	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
11	O
.	O
*	O
Richard	B-pers
Dymott	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
has	O
been	O
an	O
apprentice	O
to	O
me	O
a	O
little	O
better	O
than	O
12	O
months	O
,	O
she	O
is	O
about	O
16	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
Book-binder	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
opposite	O
Somerset-house	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
after	O
all	O
the	O
family	O
were	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
my	O
house	O
was	O
on	O
fire	O
;	O
it	O
began	O
among	O
some	O
paper	O
shavings	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
place	O
partitioned	O
off	O
for	O
to	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
from	O
the	O
pantry	O
door	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
quantity	O
of	O
shavings	O
might	O
there	O
be	O
?	O
Dymott	O
.	O
There	O
might	O
be	O
a	O
100	O
or	O
200	O
weight	O
of	O
them	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
boarded	O
over	O
some	O
little	O
way	O
to	O
prevent	O
accidents	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
fire	O
began	O
on	O
the	O
farther	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wainscot	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
cloaths	O
horses	O
,	O
that	O
were	O
laid	O
up	O
there	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
were	O
on	O
fire	O
,	O
the	O
ceiling	O
and	O
other	O
parts	O
were	O
on	O
fire	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
how	O
it	O
happened	O
?	O
Dymott	O
.	O
All	O
I	O
know	O
is	O
,	O
my	O
maid	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
told	O
me	O
the	O
prisoner	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
after	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
bed	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
her	O
before	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
he	O
thought	O
sit	O
to	O
bind	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
her	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Watkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
;	O
my	O
mistress	O
sent	O
the	O
prisoner	O
to	O
bed	O
almost	O
an	O
hour	O
before	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
misbehaviour	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
was	O
the	O
misbehaviour	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
offended	O
my	O
mistress	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
12	O
at	O
night	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
afterwards	O
to	O
warm	O
my	O
mistress	O
's	O
bed	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
upon	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
again	O
with	O
the	O
pan	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Hasland	I-pers
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
then	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
where	O
we	O
all	O
3	O
lay	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
one	O
pin	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
cloaths	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
why	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
undress	O
herself	O
,	O
and	O
get	O
into	O
bed	O
:	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
must	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
vault	O
.	O
As	O
Ann	B-pers
Hasland	I-pers
was	O
pulling	O
her	O
cloaths	O
off	O
,	O
she	O
put	O
the	O
candle	O
out	O
with	O
the	O
tail	O
of	O
her	O
gown	O
:	O
said	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
go	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
vault	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
take	O
the	O
candle	O
down	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
light	O
it	O
.	O
She	O
took	O
the	O
candle	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
up	O
again	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fire	O
in	O
the	O
parlour	O
;	O
she	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
lighted	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
about	O
10	O
minutes	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
violent	O
snapping	O
,	O
Ann	B-pers
Hasland	I-pers
heard	O
the	O
same	O
;	O
we	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
smelt	O
fire	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
down	O
and	O
opened	O
the	O
kitchen	O
door	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
all	O
in	O
a	O
flame	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
the	O
parlour	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
shavings	O
lay	O
?	O
Watkins	O
.	O
The	O
parlour	O
is	O
the	O
floor	O
above	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
did	O
not	O
undress	O
herself	O
,	O
nor	O
prepare	O
in	O
the	O
least	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
all	O
her	O
cloaths	O
on	O
when	O
we	O
got	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Hasland	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
E.	O
Watkins	O
,	O
with	O
this	O
little	O
difference	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
said	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
are	O
going	O
down	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
candle	O
and	O
light	O
it	O
;	O
prior	O
to	O
her	O
saying	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
light	O
it	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
112.	O
Barton	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
cloth	O
coats	O
and	O
two	O
cloth	O
waistcoats	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
50	O
s.	O
6	O
muslin	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
4	O
other	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
3	O
towels	O
,	O
a	O
5	O
guinea	O
piece	O
,	O
12	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
5	O
moidores	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wicks	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
22	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
113	O
,	O
114	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
and	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
eight	O
hogs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
9	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Bush	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
31	O
.	O
+	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Essex	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
January	O
I	O
lost	O
eight	O
hogs	O
from	O
a	O
barn	O
in	O
my	O
fields	O
;	O
I	O
pursued	O
them	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
heard	O
they	O
were	O
sold	O
;	O
I	O
afterwards	O
saw	O
them	O
in	O
Wood's-Close	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
possession	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Ambridge	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
then	O
all	O
alive	O
:	O
I	O
asked	O
Mr.	O
Ambridge	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Cockrill	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cockrill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
hogs	O
in	O
Smithfield	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
8	O
hogs	O
on	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Jan.	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
,	O
Nathaniel	O
was	O
by	O
when	O
I	O
paid	O
him	O
for	O
them	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
them	O
again	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Ambridge	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
for	O
them	O
?	O
Cockrill	O
.	O
I	O
gave	O
9	O
l.	O
5	O
s.	O
for	O
them	O
,	O
which	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
was	O
the	O
real	O
value	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Cockrill	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
dealer	O
in	O
hogs	O
I	O
saw	O
my	O
brother	O
buy	O
these	O
hogs	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Butcher	I-pers
.	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Hayward	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Waldon	O
,	O
about	O
5	O
miles	O
from	O
Rumford	O
;	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
were	O
taken	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
these	O
hogs	O
;	O
James	O
admitted	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
stealing	O
them	O
.	O
James	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Bush	O
and	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
return	O
the	O
money	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
James	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Nathaniel	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
As	O
the	O
prisoners	O
could	O
not	O
bring	O
the	O
hogs	O
out	O
of	O
Essex	O
to	O
Smithfield	O
without	O
bringing	O
them	O
through	O
part	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
had	O
a	O
right	O
to	O
have	O
them	O
tried	O
by	O
the	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
115	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bounds	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
fustian	O
frock	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
worsted	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Francis	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
18	O
.	O
+	O
Francis	B-pers
Eldridge	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lost	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
from	O
the	B-place
Nag	I-place
's	I-place
head	I-place
in	I-place
Hackney	I-place
road	I-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
used	O
to	O
lie	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
we	O
worked	O
together	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
suspect	O
him	O
,	O
till	O
Mr.	O
Woaden	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
from	O
him	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Foster	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Woaden	O
took	O
a	O
warrant	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbroker	O
's	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
pawn	O
'd	O
by	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
18th	O
of	O
Dec.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
these	O
things	O
,	O
here	O
produced	O
,	O
and	O
pledg	O
'd	O
them	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
sick	O
,	O
and	O
pawn	O
'd	O
them	O
for	O
want	O
of	O
money	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
for	O
stealing	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
buckskin	O
breeches	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Wodden	I-pers
.	O
116	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
3	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
iron	O
pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hunter	I-pers
,	O
in	O
a	O
lodging	O
room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
July	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
117	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Sarah	B-pers
Dickinson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
18	O
.	O
The	O
Prosecutor	O
did	O
not	O
appear	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
118	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Louis	B-pers
Le	I-pers
Grand	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
14	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
2	O
shirts	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Braillard	I-pers
,	O
Jan.	O
9	O
.	O
*	O
The	O
prisoner	O
not	O
speaking	O
English	O
an	O
interpreter	O
was	O
sworn	O
.	O
David	B-pers
Braillard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
on	O
the	O
9th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
he	O
left	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
for	O
a	O
fortnight	O
;	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
13	O
cantoons	O
near	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
;	O
and	O
,	O
seeing	O
him	O
have	O
my	O
silk	O
stockings	O
on	O
his	O
legs	O
,	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
:	O
he	O
confest	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
the	O
2	O
rings	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
to	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
shop	O
where	O
I	O
found	O
he	O
had	O
sold	O
them	O
.	O
Paul	B-pers
Pinard	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
New-street	O
,	O
Covent-Garden	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
2	O
rings	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
one	O
a	O
small	O
wire	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
with	O
a	O
garnet	O
and	O
2	O
small	O
diamonds	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
;	O
I	O
bought	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
following	O
.	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
The	O
rings	O
I	O
lost	O
were	O
such	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
single	O
felony	O
.	O
119	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Lucy	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Lucy	I-pers
Crane	I-pers
,	O
otherwise	O
Lucy	O
Crane	O
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
she	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
woman	O
unknown	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
on	O
Richard	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
violently	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
2	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
10	O
halfpence	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Feb.	O
8	O
.	O
++	O
Richard	B-pers
Marshall	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
Fleet-Market	O
last	O
Tuesday	O
was	O
a	O
fortnight	O
,	O
there	O
a	O
girl	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
between	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
at	O
night	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
you	O
sober	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
She	O
carried	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
the	B-place
Black	I-place
Horse	I-place
in	I-place
Fleet-lane	I-place
:	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
ever	O
I	O
got	O
in	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
wine	O
brought	O
up	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
none	O
;	O
they	O
demanded	O
18	O
d.	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
wanted	O
no	O
wine	O
,	O
nor	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
none	O
,	O
nor	O
pay	O
for	O
none	O
:	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
copper	O
pot	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
brought	O
it	O
up	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
A	O
servant	O
maid	O
:	O
the	O
girl	O
that	O
brought	O
me	O
there	O
,	O
insisted	O
upon	O
my	O
paying	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
3	O
s.	O
2	O
guineas	O
and	O
5	O
d.	O
farthing	O
,	O
I	O
laid	O
down	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
got	O
18	O
d.	O
The	O
girl	O
that	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
lent	O
me	O
a	O
sixpence	O
,	O
she	O
laid	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
upon	O
that	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
shilling	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
my	O
money	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
hat	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
be	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
my	O
situation	O
.	O
The	O
girl	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
something	O
more	O
to	O
say	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
coat	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
to	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
wanted	O
to	O
force	O
me	O
to	O
stay	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
shut	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
forced	O
one	O
of	O
her	O
hands	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
:	O
I	O
catched	O
hold	O
of	O
her	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
mean	O
to	O
pick	O
my	O
pocket	O
!	O
she	O
told	O
me	O
she	O
must	O
have	O
another	O
shilling	O
of	O
me	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
she	O
should	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
insisted	O
on	O
going	O
away	O
:	O
she	O
struggled	O
with	O
me	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
get	O
shut	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
yielded	O
to	O
give	O
her	O
another	O
shilling	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
my	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
her	O
another	O
shilling	O
;	O
I	O
then	O
saw	O
the	O
two	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
again	O
;	O
the	O
immediately	O
forced	O
her	O
hand	O
into	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
stole	O
her	O
ring	O
from	O
her	O
huger	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
in	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
would	O
have	O
it	O
out	O
:	O
I	O
immediately	O
called	O
out	O
and	O
made	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
likewise	O
:	O
immediately	O
the	O
girl	O
that	O
brought	O
the	O
wine	O
up	O
entered	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
that	O
girl	O
came	O
in	O
she	O
seemed	O
frighted	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
good	O
deal	O
frighted	O
;	O
then	O
in	O
came	O
another	O
woman	O
,	O
a	O
lusty	O
jolly	O
woman	O
,	O
(	O
such	O
as	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
bed-gown	O
on	O
,	O
no	O
hat	O
nor	O
cloak	O
,	O
she	O
asked	O
what	O
was	O
the	O
matter	O
?	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
her	O
?	O
Marshall	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
called	O
here	O
upon	O
my	O
oath	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
take	O
an	O
oath	O
that	O
she	O
was	O
the	O
woman	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
woman	O
was	O
something	O
younger	O
;	O
with	O
the	O
fright	O
I	O
was	O
pretty	O
well	O
got	O
sober	O
;	O
whoever	O
the	O
woman	O
was	O
,	O
she	O
came	O
round	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
a	O
saint	O
voice	O
said	O
,	O
Curse	O
you	O
,	O
be	O
quiet	O
!	O
She	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
slight	O
blow	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
hurt	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
got	O
from	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
they	O
intangled	O
me	O
at	O
the	O
back	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
lusty	O
woman	O
held	O
her	O
hand	O
on	O
my	O
mouth	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hands	O
with	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
while	O
the	O
girl	O
that	O
picked	O
me	O
up	O
,	O
took	O
my	O
money	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
away	O
with	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
took	O
up	O
,	O
with	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
scuffle	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
stairs	O
as	O
fast	O
as	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
women	O
stopped	O
me	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
run	O
over	O
her	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
apprehended	O
was	O
to	O
give	O
the	O
other	O
time	O
to	O
get	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
swear	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
Jonathan	B-pers
Atkins	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
constable	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
my	O
watch-night	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
person	O
was	O
robbed	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
a	O
watchman	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
with	O
the	O
man	O
he	O
sent	O
,	O
there	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
standing	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
constable	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
insist	O
upon	O
your	O
breaking	O
this	O
door	O
open	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
not	O
quite	O
clear	O
to	O
me	O
whether	O
I	O
could	O
answer	O
it	O
or	O
not	O
;	O
I	O
knocked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
it	O
fast	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
equal	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
breaking	O
a	O
stone	O
wall	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
never	O
quitted	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
believed	O
the	O
two	O
persons	O
that	O
had	O
robbed	O
him	O
were	O
both	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
lusty	O
woman	O
with	O
a	O
pale	O
face	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
in	O
what	O
manner	O
he	O
was	O
robbed	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
girl	O
picked	O
him	O
up	O
in	O
Fleet-market	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
he	O
has	O
here	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
I	O
judged	O
that	O
lusty	O
woman	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
woman	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
,	O
and	O
knew	O
her	O
before	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
a	O
bad	O
house	O
,	O
for	O
my	O
watch-night	O
before	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
person	O
robbed	O
in	O
that	O
house	O
of	O
2	O
guineas	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
hardly	O
a	O
night	O
but	O
there	O
is	O
robbery	O
or	O
murder	O
cried	O
there	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
eight	O
such	O
houses	O
in	O
that	O
same	O
Fleet-lane	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
120	O
,	O
121	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Esther	I-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
George	B-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Martin	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
Feb.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
of	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
did	O
burglariously	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
70	O
silk	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
10	O
l.	O
10	O
s.	O
20	O
handkerchiefs	O
made	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
,	O
value	O
40	O
s.	O
60	O
yards	O
of	O
long	O
lawn	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
14	O
yards	O
of	O
cotton	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
42	O
s.	O
14	O
yards	O
of	O
linnen	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
28	O
s.	O
60	O
lawn	O
handkerchiefs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
l.	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
Irish	O
cloth	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Samuel	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
shop	O
did	O
steal	O
.	O
++	O
Samuel	B-pers
Robinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
parish	O
of	O
Aldgate	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
linnendraper	O
's	O
shop	O
.	O
Last	O
Friday	O
morning	O
between	O
2	O
and	O
3	O
o'clock	O
I	O
heard	O
my	O
bell	O
ring	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
with	O
a	O
lanthorn	O
called	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
come	O
down	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
shop	O
was	O
robbed	O
.	O
I	O
put	O
on	O
my	O
cloaths	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
iron	O
bar	O
that	O
goes	O
cross	O
the	O
shutters	O
,	O
was	O
drawn	O
out	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
watchman	O
with	O
a	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
guarding	O
home	O
;	O
the	O
two	O
shutters	O
were	O
taken	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
broke	O
all	O
to	O
pieces	O
,	O
some	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
within	O
;	O
the	O
watchman	O
,	O
coming	O
over	O
the	O
hill	O
,	O
found	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
brown	O
cloth	O
with	O
6	O
of	O
my	O
handkerchiefs	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
2	O
other	O
handkerchiefs	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
lying	O
near	O
the	O
others	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
morning	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
thinking	O
he	O
could	O
give	O
me	O
some	O
directions	O
;	O
the	O
clerk	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
advertise	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
reward	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
home	O
and	O
had	O
some	O
bills	O
printed	O
and	O
dispatched	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
lawn	O
that	O
had	O
been	O
offered	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
sent	O
my	O
apprentice	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
mine	O
;	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
my	O
mark	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
could	O
swear	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
prosecutor	O
sent	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
brought	O
it	O
to	O
him	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
neighbours	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
woman	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
carry	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
had	O
given	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
an	O
officer	O
,	O
and	O
proceeded	O
six	O
of	O
us	O
to	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lyon	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
woman	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
serve	O
her	O
so	O
to	O
send	O
her	O
to	O
pawn	O
goods	O
that	O
were	O
stolen	O
?	O
Lyon	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
sent	O
her	O
with	O
no	O
stolen	O
goods	O
:	O
then	O
I	O
shewed	O
her	O
the	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
tell	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
her	O
,	O
where	O
and	O
when	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
yesterday	O
morning	O
about	O
6	O
o'clock	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
wrapt	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
:	O
I	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
could	O
say	O
she	O
found	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
when	O
it	O
was	O
quite	O
clean	O
.	O
Several	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
desired	O
her	O
to	O
confess	O
the	O
truth	O
,	O
and	O
give	O
an	O
account	O
of	O
her	O
confederates	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
no	O
accomplice	O
,	O
nor	O
she	O
would	O
discover	O
none	O
.	O
The	O
officer	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Justice	O
Berry	O
for	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
the	O
clerk	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
with	O
her	O
that	O
looked	O
like	O
a	O
sailor	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
should	O
bring	O
him	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
bring	O
him	O
and	O
all	O
the	O
people	O
you	O
find	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
and	O
urged	O
her	O
again	O
to	O
confess	O
before	O
we	O
began	O
to	O
search	O
;	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
confess	O
any	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
this	O
would	O
hang	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
would	O
be	O
hang	O
'd	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
The	O
officer	O
searched	O
under	O
the	O
bolster	O
of	O
her	O
bed	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
2	O
silk	O
and	O
cotton	O
handkerchiefs	O
;	O
between	O
the	O
feather-bed	O
and	O
the	O
matting	O
we	O
found	O
a	O
Southsea	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
here	O
was	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
silk	O
handkerchief	O
and	O
put	O
between	O
the	O
head-board	O
and	O
the	O
wall	O
,	O
when	O
the	O
board	O
was	O
taken	O
away	O
it	O
fell	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
began	O
to	O
cry	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
and	O
her	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
have	O
my	O
pencil	O
mark	O
upon	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
about	O
50	O
handkerchiefs	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
these	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
my	O
shop	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
desired	O
to	O
know	O
,	O
how	O
she	O
came	O
by	O
them	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
she	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
morning	O
about	O
6	O
o'clock	O
in	O
East-Smithfield	O
,	O
as	O
she	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
to	O
buy	O
fish	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
blamed	O
her	O
very	O
much	O
for	O
going	O
so	O
much	O
out	O
of	O
her	O
way	O
.	O
Then	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Martin	O
was	O
examined	O
.	O
The	O
Justice	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
what	O
business	O
he	O
had	O
there	O
at	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
get	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
that	O
was	O
there	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
take	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
shoes	O
of	O
his	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
a	O
little	O
girl	O
there	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
she	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
about	O
10	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
shore	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
ship	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
and	O
what	O
money	O
he	O
had	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
on	O
shore	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
6	O
guineas	O
;	O
and	O
by	O
his	O
own	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
but	O
16	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
The	O
justice	O
asked	O
,	O
how	O
long	O
ago	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
his	O
shoes	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
very	O
inconsistent	O
in	O
his	O
answers	O
:	O
the	O
justice	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
laid	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
with	O
his	O
mother	O
in	O
Spittlefields	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
tall	O
sailor	O
that	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lyon	O
,	O
one	O
James	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
.	O
The	O
justice	O
ordered	O
us	O
a	O
search	O
warrant	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
his	O
lodgings	O
at	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
;	O
the	O
mother	O
was	O
a	O
basket-woman	O
that	O
attends	O
Leadenhall	O
market	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
;	O
we	O
looked	O
in	O
at	O
a	O
hole	O
big	O
enough	O
to	O
put	O
my	O
hand	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
saw	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
ordinary	O
room	O
,	O
with	O
only	O
one	O
bed	O
in	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
view	O
the	O
room	O
all	O
over	O
;	O
we	O
were	O
informed	O
by	O
the	O
neighbours	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
lodge	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
mother	O
had	O
not	O
seen	O
him	O
for	O
some	O
time	O
,	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
find	O
where	O
he	O
lodged	O
:	O
we	O
found	O
James	B-pers
Connor	I-pers
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
answer	O
the	O
description	O
that	O
Martin	O
gave	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
shortish	O
man	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
voluntary	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
he	O
was	O
upon	O
his	O
duty	O
that	O
night	O
as	O
a	O
watchman	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
sent	O
home	O
about	O
hi	O
s	O
business	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lyon	O
apart	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
certainly	O
would	O
be	O
acquitted	O
if	O
she	O
would	O
tell	O
the	O
truth	O
:	O
at	O
last	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
discharge	O
us	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
will	O
tell	O
you	O
the	O
whole	O
story	O
;	O
this	O
the	O
justice	O
's	O
clerk	O
and	O
several	O
others	O
heard	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
discharge	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
that	O
were	O
innocent	O
:	O
when	O
she	O
found	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
discharge	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
all	O
myself	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
be	O
hanged	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
's	O
an	O
end	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
she	O
went	O
in	O
to	O
be	O
farther	O
examined	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
committed	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
bound	O
me	O
over	O
to	O
prosecute	O
.	O
It	O
went	O
very	O
hard	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
to	O
think	O
this	O
woman	O
must	O
suffer	O
,	O
for	O
what	O
I	O
know	O
she	O
could	O
not	O
of	O
herself	O
effect	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
yesterday	O
in	O
Newgate	O
,	O
there	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
own	O
so	O
far	O
as	O
she	O
had	O
before	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
all	O
in	O
my	O
power	O
to	O
save	O
her	O
life	O
;	O
she	O
says	O
she	O
is	O
but	O
18	O
years	O
old	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
think	O
she	O
is	O
above	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
and	O
20.	O
Hannah	B-pers
Burroughs	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
me	O
information	O
his	O
master	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
stop	O
any	O
thing	O
that	O
I	O
suspected	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
morning	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
10	O
,	O
Mary	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
came	O
and	O
offered	O
me	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
linnen	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
I	O
stopt	O
it	O
and	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
2	O
prisoners	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
.	O
I	O
carried	O
this	O
linnen	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Burrough	O
's	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
it	O
of	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Lyon	I-pers
,	O
Mrs.	O
Burrough	O
's	O
stopt	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
sent	O
for	O
the	O
gentleman	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lyon	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
the	O
other	O
prisoner	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
when	O
she	O
sent	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
ever	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
before	O
?	O
Horton	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
but	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
before	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
good	O
opinion	O
of	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
very	O
good	O
hours	O
.	O
Joseph	B-pers
Cox	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Lyon	O
's	O
lodging	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
found	O
this	O
bit	O
of	O
linnen	O
that	O
was	O
stopt	O
at	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
her	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
things	O
there	O
as	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
has	O
before	O
mentioned	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Prosser	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Mrs.	O
Burroughs	O
's	O
when	O
Mary	B-pers
Horton	I-pers
brought	O
in	O
the	O
lawn	O
to	O
pawn	O
;	O
Mrs.	O
Burroughs	O
said	O
she	O
had	O
an	O
order	O
to	O
stop	O
all	O
such	O
things	O
;	O
then	O
she	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
his	O
property	O
;	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
goods	O
found	O
in	O
Lyon	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
Lyon	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
Defence	O
.	O
Martin	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
get	O
my	O
shoes	O
out	O
of	O
pawn	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
Sarah	B-pers
Barker	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
carried	O
them	O
,	O
to	O
fetch	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
there	O
but	O
once	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Lyon	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
Martin	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
122	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Joshua	I-pers
Richmond	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pewter	O
dish	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
three	O
other	O
pewter	O
dishes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
s.	O
one	O
pewter	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
pewter	O
ink-stands	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
and	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
Feb.	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Gibson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pewterer	O
,	O
in	O
partnership	O
with	O
Ann	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
;	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
5	O
weeks	O
ago	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
ink-stands	O
and	O
dishes	O
,	O
about	O
a	O
fortnight	O
after	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
more	O
;	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
I	O
missed	O
some	O
,	O
I	O
advised	O
with	O
a	O
neighbour	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
he	O
advised	O
me	O
to	O
set	O
a	O
watch	O
:	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
(	O
which	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Monday	O
)	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
of	O
my	O
setting	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
I	O
missed	O
a	O
large	O
dish	O
;	O
Charles	O
Dunlop	O
,	O
whom	O
I	O
set	O
to	O
watch	O
,	O
saw	O
her	O
take	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
back	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
;	O
she	O
confest	O
she	O
had	O
robbed	O
me	O
3	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
pawn	O
'd	O
the	O
goods	O
:	O
the	O
constable	O
went	O
by	O
her	O
direction	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
the	O
goods	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
her	O
and	O
them	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Dunlop	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
set	O
to	O
watch	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
the	O
woman	O
went	O
twice	O
by	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
time	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
closet	O
,	O
and	O
looked	O
through	O
a	O
sash	O
window	O
;	O
at	O
first	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
about	O
half	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
then	O
she	O
came	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
counter	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
dish	O
,	O
and	O
clapt	O
it	O
under	O
her	O
arm	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
out	O
directly	O
;	O
I	O
followed	O
her	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
baker	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
charged	O
her	O
;	O
she	O
delivered	O
the	O
dish	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
,	O
Mr.	O
Gibson	O
's	O
apprentice	O
,	O
who	O
went	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dennis	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
last	O
witness	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Curtoice	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
22d	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
the	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
3	O
ink-stands	O
to	O
pawn	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
they	O
were	O
her	O
husband	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
maker	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
Minories	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
constable	O
came	O
and	O
demanded	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
,	O
but	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
20	O
years	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Hornby	I-pers
25	O
,	O
John	B-pers
Thorn	I-pers
,	O
as	O
long	O
as	O
he	O
has	O
known	O
any	O
body	O
,	O
Francis	B-pers
Lawley	I-pers
almost	O
4	O
,	O
Richard	B-pers
Pugh	I-pers
and	O
Mrs.	O
Keys	O
from	O
an	O
infant	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Lewis	O
7	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Ludford	O
8	O
or	O
9	O
years	O
,	O
all	O
which	O
gave	O
her	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
123	O
,	O
124	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
40	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Tailsworth	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Rebecca	B-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Joseph	I-pers
Edwards	I-pers
,	O
for	O
feloniously	O
inciting	O
,	O
procuring	O
,	O
counselling	O
,	O
and	O
commanding	O
the	O
said	O
Mary	O
to	O
commit	O
the	O
said	O
felony	O
,	O
as	O
an	O
accessary	O
before	O
the	O
fact	O
,	O
Feb.	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
Edward	O
Tailsworth	O
.	O
Mary	O
Edwards	O
is	O
between	O
13	O
and	O
14	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
servant	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Tailsworth	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Leadenhall-market	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
a	O
public-house	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
money	O
several	O
times	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawer	O
,	O
I	O
taxed	O
her	O
with	O
taking	O
it	O
,	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
between	O
3	O
and	O
4	O
l.	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
taking	O
money	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
before	O
my	O
Lord-Mayor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
against	O
the	O
mother	O
?	O
Tailsworth	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
she	O
used	O
to	O
come	O
after	O
the	O
daughter	O
,	O
I	O
used	O
to	O
bid	O
her	O
keep	O
away	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
more	O
than	O
what	O
the	O
girl	O
has	O
said	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Lobourn	I-pers
and	O
John	B-pers
Tailsworth	I-pers
deposed	O
to	O
that	O
of	O
hearing	O
the	O
girl	O
confess	O
she	O
took	O
away	O
money	O
at	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
her	O
master	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
to	O
her	O
mother	O
.	O
Mary	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Rebecca	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
125	O
,	O
126	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
James	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
,	O
were	O
indicted	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
for	O
stealing	O
85	O
wooden	O
bobbins	O
with	O
3	O
pounds	O
weight	O
of	O
silk	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
l.	O
and	O
divers	O
other	O
bobbins	O
with	O
silk	O
and	O
silk	O
and	O
worsted	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Ann	O
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
knowing	O
them	O
to	O
be	O
stolen	O
,	O
Jan.	O
24	O
.	O
*	O
Ebenezer	B-pers
Atkinson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
weaver	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Spittlefields	B-place
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Thomas	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
has	O
been	O
a	O
servant	O
with	O
me	O
4	O
or	O
5	O
months	O
,	O
to	O
do	O
my	O
business	O
that	O
we	O
have	O
to	O
do	O
:	O
about	O
the	O
middle	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
we	O
had	O
2	O
small	O
parcels	O
of	O
silk	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
weight	O
of	O
20	O
lb	O
.	O
20	O
z.	O
the	O
other	O
17	O
lb	O
.	O
5	O
oz	B-pers
this	O
silk	O
was	O
delivered	O
into	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
the	O
servant	O
that	O
has	O
the	O
care	O
of	O
raw	O
silk	O
before	O
it	O
is	O
put	O
to	O
do	O
;	O
several	O
days	O
after	O
the	O
silk	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
us	O
in	O
the	O
counting-house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
the	O
last	O
parcel	O
of	O
silk	O
weighed	O
16	O
lb	O
.	O
upon	O
which	O
I	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
tied	O
them	O
in	O
separate	O
bags	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
was	O
sure	O
had	O
been	O
untied	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
done	O
up	O
different	O
to	O
what	O
they	O
were	O
when	O
he	O
did	O
them	O
:	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
suspect	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
,	O
but	O
thought	O
that	O
(	O
it	O
being	O
evening	O
)	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
mixed	O
them	O
together	O
himself	O
,	O
so	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
let	O
it	O
alone	O
till	O
morning	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
we	O
examined	O
and	O
weighed	O
the	O
other	O
parcel	O
,	O
which	O
wanted	O
1	O
lb	O
.	O
2	O
oz	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
was	O
wanting	O
2	O
lb	O
.	O
1	O
oz	O
.	O
this	O
made	O
me	O
suspcious	O
:	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
warp	O
'd	O
one	O
parcel	O
of	O
silk	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
my	O
man	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
warp	O
another	O
cane	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
no	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
there	O
was	O
as	O
much	O
silk	O
gone	O
as	O
goes	O
to	O
the	O
warping	O
.	O
A	O
cane	O
contains	O
126	O
yards	O
of	O
silk	O
and	O
worsted	O
together	O
,	O
this	O
silk	O
is	O
only	O
a	O
part	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
more	O
suspicious	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
neighbour	O
that	O
had	O
frequently	O
been	O
in	O
things	O
of	O
this	O
sort	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
a	O
warrant	O
of	O
Justice	O
Somerville	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
desired	O
us	O
to	O
lay	O
a	O
trap	O
for	O
him	O
;	O
accordingly	O
my	O
partner	O
and	O
I	O
threw	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
bobbins	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
marked	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
found	O
them	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
condition	O
we	O
left	O
them	O
:	O
we	O
had	O
the	O
day	O
before	O
sent	O
for	O
some	O
bobbins	O
to	O
wind	O
silk	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
not	O
being	O
enough	O
,	O
we	O
put	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
drawer	O
;	O
my	O
apprentice	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
taken	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
bobbins	O
out	O
?	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
one	O
missing	O
;	O
my	O
partner	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
came	O
to	O
serve	O
the	O
warrant	O
;	O
for	O
,	O
though	O
we	O
could	O
not	O
fix	O
upon	O
any	O
one	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
time	O
to	O
search	O
:	O
he	O
was	O
obliged	O
to	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
so	O
the	O
whole	O
weight	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
fell	O
upon	O
me	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
I	O
mentioned	O
first	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
searched	O
the	O
house	O
where	O
Holden	O
lived	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
searched	O
the	O
lower	O
room	O
,	O
we	O
found	O
small	O
quantities	O
of	O
worsted	O
that	O
was	O
our	O
property	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
upon	O
the	O
second	O
floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
manner	O
did	O
it	O
lie	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
in	O
a	O
trunk	O
about	O
18	O
inches	O
broad	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
a	O
peculiar	O
sort	O
:	O
Mrs.	O
Holden	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
refused	O
,	O
I	O
insisted	O
upon	O
going	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
it	O
appeared	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
warehouse	O
than	O
any	O
thing	O
else	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
worsted	O
on	O
the	O
floor	O
to	O
a	O
great	O
amount	O
;	O
upon	O
opening	O
a	O
hat-box	O
we	O
saw	O
several	O
bobbins	O
of	O
orange-colour	O
silk	O
,	O
together	O
with	O
some	O
pink	O
,	O
we	O
had	O
missed	O
the	O
pink	O
the	O
first	O
thing	O
,	O
but	O
we	O
had	O
not	O
missed	O
the	O
orange	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
worth	O
about	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
a	O
bobbin	O
;	O
in	O
a	O
trunk	O
I	O
found	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
60	O
bobbins	O
more	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
some	O
of	O
the	O
pink	O
silk	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
box	O
a	O
large	O
painted	O
Christmass-box	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
opening	O
of	O
which	O
we	O
found	O
14	O
l.	O
2	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
that	O
these	O
things	O
you	O
found	O
were	O
your	O
goods	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
positive	O
that	O
these	O
things	O
we	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
box	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
that	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
bobbins	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
him	O
into	O
the	O
custody	O
of	O
the	O
constable	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
must	O
do	O
with	O
him	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
watch-house	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
at	O
the	O
watch-house	O
?	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
the	O
first	O
time	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
forgive	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
do	O
so	O
no	O
more	O
:	O
these	O
bobbins	O
are	O
most	O
of	O
them	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
my	O
name	O
,	O
(	O
produc	O
'd	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
besides	O
they	O
are	O
mark	O
'd	O
with	O
our	O
windster	O
's	O
mark	O
.	O
We	O
took	O
the	O
mother	O
to	O
the	O
alehouse	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
have	O
favour	O
,	O
would	O
be	O
to	O
confess	O
.	O
She	O
confess	O
'd	O
that	O
he	O
dealt	O
with	O
Abraham	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
in	O
Halfmoon	O
alley	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
employed	O
as	O
a	O
winder	O
of	O
worsted	O
with	O
us	O
.	O
He	O
confessed	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
silk	O
to	O
my	O
man	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
18	O
s	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
my	O
man	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
saw	O
42	O
bobbins	O
of	O
yellow	O
shade	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
24	O
oz	O
.	O
the	O
bobbins	O
being	O
marked	O
,	O
and	O
having	O
the	O
persons	O
names	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
to	O
all	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Cocker	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
bobbins	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
bobbins	O
,	O
being	O
marked	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
name	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
James	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
.	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
swear	O
to	O
the	O
bobbins	O
,	O
when	O
my	O
master	O
buys	O
old	O
bobbins	O
of	O
people	O
when	O
they	O
leave	O
off	O
trade	O
?	O
Cocker	O
.	O
I	O
ticketed	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
windster	O
's	O
book	O
.	O
The	O
woman	O
wanted	O
to	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
we	O
found	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
.	O
Hezekiah	O
Brace	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
search	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
the	O
bobbins	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
trunk	O
;	O
he	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
dealt	O
with	O
Stevens	O
several	O
years	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
say	O
whose	O
silk	O
he	O
sold	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
public-house	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
the	O
mother	O
the	O
same	O
question	O
;	O
she	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
upon	O
the	O
25th	O
of	O
Jan.	O
she	O
carried	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
silk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
received	O
no	O
money	O
;	O
and	O
that	O
she	O
carried	O
a	O
parcel	O
the	O
week	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
whose	O
it	O
was	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hewler	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
watchman	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Atkinson	O
sent	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
taken	O
a	O
man	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
for	O
assistance	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
an	O
officer	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
James	O
say	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
mostly	O
all	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
silk	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
innocent	O
of	O
the	O
affair	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Holden	I-pers
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
Ann	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
127	O
,	O
128	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Margaret	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
David	I-pers
Allen	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
30	O
pounds	O
wt	O
.	O
of	O
beef	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
one	O
oxe	O
's	O
tongue	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
David	B-pers
Sullivan	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Jennet	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
for	O
receiving	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
well	O
knowing	O
the	O
same	O
to	O
have	O
been	O
stolen	O
,	O
Feb.	O
14	O
.	O
~	O
Both	O
acquitted	O
.	O
129	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Wise	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
guineas	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Green	I-pers
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mallet	I-pers
,	O
Feb.	O
15	O
.	O
~	O
John	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Tottenham-Court-Road	B-place
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
spin	O
packthread	O
and	O
twine	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
whose	O
house	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Green	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mallet	I-pers
.	O
Last	O
Shrove-Tuesday	O
I	O
took	O
out	O
one	O
guinea	O
and	O
then	O
another	O
and	O
slung	O
them	O
in	O
my	O
wife	O
's	O
lap	O
;	O
she	O
took	O
them	O
both	O
,	O
and	O
wrapt	O
them	O
up	O
in	O
an	O
old	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
tied	O
them	O
in	O
a	O
knot	O
,	O
and	O
put	O
them	O
into	O
a	O
drawer	O
in	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
not	O
lock	O
the	O
drawer	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
me	O
give	O
them	O
to	O
my	O
wife	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
cold	O
,	O
coming	O
in	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
snow	O
,	O
and	O
sat	O
by	O
the	O
fire	O
;	O
there	O
being	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
hemp	O
lying	O
so	O
that	O
it	O
in	O
part	O
kept	O
me	O
from	O
seeing	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
at	O
the	O
drawer	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
my	O
wife	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
drawer	O
for	O
something	O
,	O
missed	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
knot	O
was	O
cut	O
off	O
in	O
which	O
it	O
had	O
been	O
tied	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
work	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
but	O
made	O
off	O
about	O
noon	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
over	O
the	O
water	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
between	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
at	O
his	O
own	O
home	O
in	O
Southwark	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
lost	O
2	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
have	O
it	O
but	O
you	O
.	O
We	O
walked	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
between	O
the	O
constable	O
and	O
me	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
we	O
would	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
him	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
me	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
cut	O
the	O
knot	O
off	O
the	O
rag	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
.	O
Then	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
Justice	O
was	O
:	O
we	O
took	O
one	O
guinea	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
shoe	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
2	O
shillings	O
besides	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
he	O
took	O
it	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
drawer	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
the	O
guinea	O
in	O
his	O
shoe	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Lockyer	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
own	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
2	O
guineas	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
master	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
drawer	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
take	O
it	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
twopenny	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
much	O
about	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
The	O
weather	O
being	O
bad	O
,	O
we	O
were	O
all	O
in	O
the	O
master	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
weather	O
was	O
better	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
as	O
innocent	O
as	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
.	O
That	O
last	O
witness	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
I	O
when	O
the	O
money	O
was	O
lost	O
.	O
I	O
sav	O
'd	O
that	O
money	O
up	O
that	O
they	O
found	O
upon	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
fearing	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
brought	O
into	O
trouble	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
it	O
him	O
.	O
Guilty	O
21	O
s.	O
T	O
.	O
130	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Cassandra	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
John	I-pers
Meals	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Sinclair	I-pers
,	O
Dec.	O
10	O
*	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
the	O
breeches	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
suspected	O
of	O
taking	O
them	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
and	O
charged	O
with	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
owned	O
she	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
that	O
she	O
pawned	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
begged	O
mercy	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
131	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Daniel	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
not	O
having	O
the	O
fear	O
of	O
God	O
before	O
his	O
eyes	O
,	O
but	O
being	O
moved	O
by	O
the	O
instigation	O
of	O
the	O
devil	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Feb.	O
on	O
John	B-pers
Murcott	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
and	O
with	O
malice	O
aforethought	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
knife	O
.	O
value	O
1	O
d.	O
on	O
the	O
throat	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
wilfully	O
did	O
strike	O
and	O
cut	O
,	O
giving	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
his	O
throat	O
one	O
mortal	O
wound	O
,	O
the	O
length	O
of	O
4	O
inches	O
and	O
depth	O
of	O
3	O
inches	O
,	O
of	O
which	O
mortal	O
wound	O
he	O
instantly	O
died	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Cotes	I-pers
and	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Warton	I-pers
,	O
having	O
been	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
Jury	O
,	O
desired	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
on	O
this	O
,	O
and	O
William	B-pers
Lightfoot	I-pers
and	O
Samuel	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
were	O
sworn	O
in	O
their	O
stead	O
for	O
this	O
trial	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
indictment	O
was	O
read	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Cox	O
,	O
council	O
for	O
the	O
prosecution	O
,	O
spoke	O
as	O
follows	O
:	O
May	O
it	O
please	O
your	O
Lordship	O
;	O
and	O
you	O
Gentlemen	O
of	O
the	O
Jury	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
council	O
in	O
this	O
case	O
on	O
behalf	O
of	O
the	O
prosecution	O
against	O
the	O
prisoner	O
Daniel	B-pers
Blake	I-pers
,	O
who	O
now	O
stands	O
charged	O
with	O
a	O
soul	O
murder	O
committed	O
(	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
am	O
instructed	O
to	O
say	O
)	O
on	O
the	O
person	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Murcott	I-pers
,	O
his	O
fellow-servant	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
this	O
is	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
kinds	O
of	O
murders	O
,	O
which	O
,	O
like	O
many	O
thousands	O
of	O
others	O
,	O
are	O
so	O
far	O
committed	O
in	O
secret	O
,	O
that	O
no	O
one	O
can	O
swear	O
to	O
their	O
being	O
present	O
,	O
and	O
seeing	O
the	O
fatal	O
blow	O
given	O
.	O
The	O
consequence	O
of	O
which	O
is	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
now	O
to	O
be	O
laid	O
before	O
you	O
,	O
(	O
except	O
what	O
appears	O
from	O
the	O
confession	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
)	O
will	O
depend	O
upon	O
circumstances	O
merely	O
;	O
but	O
they	O
are	O
circumstances	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
,	O
so	O
connected	O
,	O
so	O
cemented	O
together	O
,	O
and	O
so	O
explanatory	O
of	O
one	O
another	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
they	O
will	O
have	O
the	O
effect	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
as	O
hitherto	O
they	O
have	O
had	O
with	O
other	O
people	O
:	O
they	O
will	O
leave	O
no	O
doubt	O
with	O
you	O
with	O
regard	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
.	O
The	O
facts	O
are	O
so	O
strong	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
case	O
so	O
melancholly	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
shall	O
do	O
little	O
more	O
than	O
name	O
them	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
It	O
will	O
appear	O
in	O
evidence	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
person	O
called	O
John	B-pers
Murcott	I-pers
,	O
was	O
butler	O
to	O
Lord	O
Dacre	O
,	O
that	O
on	O
the	O
evening	O
of	O
Monday	O
the	O
31st	O
of	O
Jan.	O
last	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
housekeeper	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
complained	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
ill	O
;	O
that	O
the	O
housekeeper	O
made	O
him	O
some	O
small	O
tea	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
of	O
that	O
kind	O
;	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
all	O
the	O
appearance	O
of	O
calmness	O
and	O
serenity	O
,	O
and	O
no	O
other	O
complaint	O
than	O
a	O
common	O
cold	O
,	O
or	O
some	O
flight	O
disorder	O
.	O
Some	O
little	O
time	O
after	O
this	O
he	O
complained	O
of	O
being	O
hungry	O
;	O
he	O
had	O
something	O
to	O
eat	O
and	O
drink	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
sober	O
,	O
perfectly	O
so	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
was	O
found	O
dead	O
,	O
with	O
all	O
the	O
horrid	O
circumstances	O
of	O
murder	O
about	O
him	O
;	O
his	O
throat	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
violent	O
blows	O
on	O
his	O
head	O
:	O
you	O
will	O
hear	O
what	O
knives	O
and	O
things	O
were	O
there	O
to	O
induce	O
the	O
world	O
to	O
believe	O
he	O
murder	O
'd	O
himself	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
our	O
business	O
to	O
shew	O
you	O
,	O
why	O
we	O
call	O
upon	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
answer	O
for	O
his	O
offence	O
.	O
We	O
shall	O
shew	O
this	O
in	O
the	O
following	O
manner	O
:	O
that	O
prior	O
to	O
the	O
day	O
when	O
this	O
fact	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
in	O
very	O
great	O
poverty	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
drove	O
to	O
such	O
distress	O
,	O
as	O
to	O
want	O
a	O
single	O
shilling	O
;	O
but	O
upon	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
murder	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
things	O
were	O
changed	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
,	O
before	O
noon	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
some	O
small	O
sums	O
of	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
very	O
person	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
had	O
complained	O
a	O
day	O
or	O
two	O
before	O
of	O
his	O
poverty	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
his	O
silver	O
buckles	O
in	O
pawn	O
)	O
and	O
,	O
without	O
any	O
solicitation	O
,	O
paid	O
a	O
debt	O
to	O
that	O
person	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
another	O
person	O
,	O
to	O
whom	O
he	O
owed	O
some	O
money	O
for	O
washing	O
,	O
paid	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
her	O
he	O
had	O
received	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
his	O
uncle	O
,	O
and	O
though	O
this	O
was	O
done	O
on	O
the	O
day	O
the	O
poor	O
man	O
was	O
murdered	O
,	O
(	O
and	O
you	O
know	O
murder	O
occasions	O
conversation	O
in	O
every	O
family	O
in	O
the	O
neighbourhood	O
)	O
yet	O
when	O
he	O
paid	O
this	O
money	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
no	O
notice	O
of	O
this	O
man	O
's	O
death	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
mention	O
one	O
single	O
circumstance	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Upon	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
that	O
the	O
murder	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
(	O
so	O
far	O
were	O
his	O
circumstances	O
alter	O
'd	O
)	O
he	O
bought	O
linnen	O
cloth	O
to	O
the	O
value	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
he	O
gave	O
directions	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
to	O
make	O
it	O
up	O
into	O
shirts	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
then	O
(	O
sorry	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
bring	O
this	O
circumstance	O
home	O
to	O
him	O
by	O
giving	O
his	O
generosity	O
in	O
evidence	O
)	O
made	O
a	O
present	O
to	O
a	O
child	O
belonging	O
to	O
that	O
person	O
,	O
of	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
He	O
paid	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
25	O
s.	O
for	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
;	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
satisfied	O
with	O
buying	O
necessaries	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
will	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
he	O
became	O
extravagant	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
bought	O
himself	O
a	O
watch	O
.	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
it	O
will	O
appear	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
this	O
murder	O
was	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
committed	O
,	O
a	O
noise	O
was	O
heard	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
,	O
and	O
it	O
was	O
suspected	O
to	O
be	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
going	O
backwards	O
and	O
forwards	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
many	O
circumstances	O
of	O
the	O
like	O
kind	O
,	O
but	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
had	O
notice	O
that	O
all	O
the	O
witnesses	O
will	O
not	O
be	O
here	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
open	O
willingly	O
any	O
fact	O
that	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
proved	O
in	O
evidence	O
,	O
it	O
being	O
expected	O
that	O
the	O
trial	O
would	O
not	O
come	O
on	O
till	O
tomorrow	O
.	O
I	O
mention	O
these	O
circumstances	O
,	O
because	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
have	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
his	O
unhappy	O
situation	O
be	O
too	O
much	O
affected	O
by	O
what	O
comes	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
mouth	O
;	O
therefore	O
were	O
the	O
proofs	O
to	O
rest	O
on	O
what	O
I	O
have	O
opened	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
few	O
people	O
can	O
doubt	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
guilt	O
,	O
But	O
more	O
remains	O
behind	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
afterwards	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
before	O
a	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
after	O
having	O
repeated	O
warning	O
to	O
be	O
catious	O
what	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
being	O
told	O
that	O
all	O
admissions	O
might	O
be	O
used	O
as	O
evidence	O
against	O
his	O
own	O
life	O
,	O
he	O
,	O
struck	O
with	O
a	O
proper	O
contrition	O
for	O
his	O
offence	O
,	O
and	O
willing	O
to	O
deliver	O
his	O
fellow-servants	O
from	O
this	O
heavy	O
charge	O
,	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
,	O
he	O
murdered	O
this	O
man	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
it	O
in	O
so	O
deliberate	O
a	O
way	O
,	O
he	O
calls	O
for	O
pen	O
and	O
ink	O
,	O
and	O
desires	O
him	O
to	O
write	O
it	O
down	O
;	O
on	O
writing	O
the	O
word	O
murder	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
how	O
it	O
was	O
spelt	O
,	O
and	O
being	O
informed	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
the	O
pen	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
hand	O
,	O
and	O
wrote	O
these	O
four	O
words	O
,	O
I	O
MURDERED	O
THE	O
MAN	O
.	O
This	O
he	O
wrote	O
before	O
the	O
magistrate	O
,	O
who	O
then	O
was	O
enquiring	O
after	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Murcott	I-pers
,	O
and	O
therefore	O
the	O
words	O
could	O
be	O
applied	O
to	O
nothing	O
but	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
that	O
very	O
man	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
signed	O
a	O
formal	O
confession	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
,	O
he	O
wrote	O
a	O
letter	O
to	O
the	O
Noble	O
Lord	O
whom	O
he	O
served	O
,	O
acknowledging	O
he	O
was	O
guilty	O
of	O
this	O
fact	O
.	O
These	O
facts	O
,	O
Gentlemen	O
,	O
are	O
so	O
connected	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
dare	O
say	O
,	O
when	O
they	O
are	O
proved	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
I	O
have	O
opened	O
them	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
do	O
no	O
less	O
than	O
find	O
the	O
unhappy	O
prisoner	O
guilty	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barnfield	I-pers
,	O
sworn	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Barnfield	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
porter	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Dacre	O
,	O
in	O
Burton-street	B-place
,	I-place
Berkley-square	I-place
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
Feb.	O
the	O
prisoner	O
called	O
me	O
up	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'clock	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
lived	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
12	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
In	O
what	O
capacity	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
footman	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
had	O
called	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
down	O
about	O
5	O
minutes	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
lie	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
2	O
beds	O
in	O
the	O
garret	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
footman	O
lay	O
in	O
one	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
in	O
the	O
other	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
down	O
he	O
was	O
cleaning	O
the	O
plate	O
in	O
the	O
servant	O
's	O
hall	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
butler	O
's	O
pantry	O
,	O
and	O
fetched	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
which	O
I	O
cleaned	O
;	O
at	O
8	O
o'clock	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
done	O
his	O
plate	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
into	O
the	O
butler	O
's	O
pantry	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Daniel	O
,	O
call	O
Mr.	O
Murcott	O
up	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
8	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
was	O
Mr.	O
Murcott	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
butler	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
came	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
servant	O
's	O
hall	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Daniel	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
call	O
Mr.	O
Murcott	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
him	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
.	O
Then	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Daniel	O
,	O
go	O
and	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
make	O
him	O
speak	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
awake	O
him	O
;	O
at	O
which	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
had	O
done	O
my	O
plate	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
dry	O
a	O
cloth	O
,	O
and	O
wipe	O
it	O
over	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
it	O
up	O
in	O
the	O
butler	O
's	O
pantry	O
in	O
the	O
chest	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
read	O
the	O
news	O
in	O
the	O
laundry	O
;	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
bell	O
rang	O
,	O
and	O
Mrs.	O
Jones	O
called	O
me	O
to	O
call	O
Mr.	O
Murcott	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
bell	O
rang	O
:	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
call	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
called	O
5	O
or	O
6	O
times	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
spoke	O
;	O
I	O
laid	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
shook	O
him	O
pretty	O
hard	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
stirred	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
to	O
myself	O
,	O
God	O
bless	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
is	O
dead	O
sure	O
,	O
or	O
dead	O
asleep	O
;	O
the	O
cloaths	O
were	O
thrown	O
over	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
I	O
pulled	O
them	O
from	O
his	O
face	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
all	O
bloody	O
;	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
housekeeper	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
maid	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
housekeeper	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
was	O
dead	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
make	O
him	O
move	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
face	O
was	O
all	O
bloody	O
,	O
then	O
my	O
Lady	O
's	O
woman	O
,	O
named	O
Fortiscue	O
,	O
came	O
and	O
pulled	O
the	O
cloaths	O
more	O
down	O
from	O
his	O
face	O
,	O
and	O
near	O
his	O
breast	O
saw	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
knife	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
let	O
us	O
see	O
if	O
we	O
can	O
lift	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
she	O
on	O
one	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
,	O
we	O
lifted	O
him	O
up	O
;	O
then	O
his	O
head	O
dropt	O
quite	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
saw	O
his	O
was	O
cut	O
,	O
on	O
each	O
side	O
as	O
far	O
almost	O
as	O
un	O
ears	O
,	O
(	O
describing	O
it	O
with	O
his	O
own	O
fingers	O
)	O
and	O
quite	O
deep	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
prisoner	O
soon	O
after	O
this	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
mussins	O
and	O
French	O
rolls	O
,	O
for	O
breakfast	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
while	O
we	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
pantry	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
out	O
directly	O
,	O
and	O
fell	O
in	O
a	O
great	O
crying	O
and	O
ringing	O
his	O
hands	O
;	O
I	O
bid	O
him	O
not	O
make	O
a	O
noise	O
,	O
for	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
misfortune	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
Lord	O
and	O
Lady	O
would	O
hear	O
of	O
it	O
too	O
soon	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
it	O
mentioned	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
that	O
the	O
deceased	O
was	O
dead	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
directly	O
on	O
his	O
coming	O
in	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
he	O
say	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
nothing	O
further	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
of	O
any	O
thing	O
afterwards	O
that	O
relates	O
to	O
this	O
matter	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
observe	O
whether	O
there	O
were	O
any	O
other	O
marks	O
of	O
violence	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
a	O
cut	O
on	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
temple	O
that	O
morning	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
at	O
him	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
afterwards	O
,	O
it	O
seemed	O
a	O
longish	O
cut	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
temple	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
inches	O
long	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
clean	O
cut	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
or	O
whether	O
it	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bruise	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
There	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bruise	O
with-all	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
cut	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
examine	O
that	O
wound	O
,	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
deep	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whereabouts	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
did	O
the	O
deceased	O
lie	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
He	O
lay	O
in	O
the	O
pantry	O
below	O
stairs	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
down	O
stairs	O
from	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
below	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
upon	O
the	O
kitchen	O
floor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
had	O
you	O
seen	O
Mr.	O
Murcott	O
last	O
,	O
before	O
you	O
found	O
him	O
dead	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
about	O
12	O
o'clock	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
footman	O
staid	O
for	O
something	O
to	O
be	O
made	O
hot	O
for	O
his	O
cold	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
in	O
what	O
condition	O
Mr.	O
Murcott	O
was	O
for	O
liquor	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
getting	O
up	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
of	O
his	O
getting	O
up	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
nothing	O
of	O
him	O
till	O
between	O
7	O
and	O
8	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Miller	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
house-maid	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	O
Dacre	O
's	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
do	O
you	O
lie	O
in	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
I	O
lie	O
in	O
that	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
is	O
even	O
with	O
the	O
footman	O
's	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
Mr.	O
Murcott	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
8	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
disturbance	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
No	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
laundry-maid	O
and	O
the	O
kitchen-maid	O
went	O
down	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
about	O
one	O
o'clock	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
watch	O
went	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
soon	O
after	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
our	O
washing	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
looked	O
at	O
the	O
clock	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
one	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
stay	O
from	O
that	O
time	O
till	O
morning	O
light	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
into	O
the	O
laundry	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
a	O
basket	O
of	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
carried	O
them	O
into	O
the	O
wash-house	O
;	O
the	O
laundry	O
is	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
from	O
the	O
wash-house	O
;	O
the	O
laundry	O
is	O
below	O
stairs	O
down	O
from	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wash-house	O
is	O
farther	O
on	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
floor	O
where	O
the	O
pantry	O
is	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
far	O
is	O
the	O
wash-house	O
from	O
the	O
place	O
where	O
the	O
butler	O
used	O
to	O
keep	O
his	O
plate	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
The	O
wash-house	O
is	O
a	O
good	O
distance	O
from	O
the	O
pantry	O
,	O
farther	O
than	O
the	O
breadth	O
of	O
this	O
court	O
.	O
Carrying	O
the	O
basket	O
of	O
cloaths	O
,	O
I	O
met	O
the	O
kitchen-maid	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
might	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
breakfast	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
That	O
was	O
about	O
2	O
.	O
The	O
laundry	O
maid	O
went	O
to	O
light	O
the	O
fire	O
about	O
4	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
down	O
to	O
me	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
washing	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
it	O
was	O
about	O
4	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
hear	O
any	O
noise	O
or	O
any	O
disturbance	O
during	O
any	O
part	O
of	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
About	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
5	O
o'clock	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
laundry	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
looking	O
at	O
a	O
new	O
gown	O
,	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Murcott	O
's	O
pantry	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
house-keeper	O
's	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
back	O
again	O
into	O
the	O
pantry	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
rattling	O
the	O
plate	O
about	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Daniel	O
is	O
up	O
by	O
times	O
nobody	O
made	O
me	O
any	O
answer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
say	O
,	O
you	O
thought	O
you	O
heard	O
;	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
the	O
plate	O
rattle	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
sure	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
sensible	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
plate	O
rattle	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
you	O
imagine	O
you	O
heard	O
somebody	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
a	O
person	O
move	O
about	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
step	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
The	O
noise	O
you	O
heard	O
of	O
a	O
person	O
,	O
as	O
you	O
supposed	O
,	O
did	O
it	O
found	O
like	O
shoes	O
,	O
or	O
a	O
person	O
without	O
shoes	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
so	O
much	O
observe	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
pantry	O
door	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
my	O
gown	O
going	O
to	O
carry	O
it	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
knew	O
Mr.	O
Murcott	O
was	O
out	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
seeing	O
the	O
bed	O
down	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
turn-up	O
bed	O
)	O
I	O
was	O
not	O
frightened	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
snore	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
mean	O
by	O
your	O
saying	O
you	O
thought	O
,	O
you	O
were	O
in	O
any	O
doubt	O
,	O
or	O
did	O
you	O
hear	O
him	O
snore	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
stand	O
to	O
mind	O
that	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
laid	O
over	O
head	O
and	O
ears	O
,	O
the	O
cloaths	O
were	O
turned	O
over	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
coat	O
and	O
waistcoat	O
were	O
all	O
on	O
a	O
heap	O
at	O
the	O
foot	O
of	O
the	O
bed	O
,	O
the	O
bed	O
cloaths	O
lay	O
very	O
smooth	O
,	O
I	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
his	O
head	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
a	O
candle	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
to	O
call	O
my	O
fellow-servant	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
also	O
at	O
the	O
clock	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
5	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
go	O
up	O
stairs	O
before	O
me	O
without	O
shoes	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
body	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
occasioned	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
so	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
footman	O
's	O
room	O
door	O
a	O
little	O
way	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
might	O
be	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
go	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
room	O
door	O
to	O
my	O
room	O
.	O
I	O
lighted	O
the	O
candle	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
down	O
stairs	O
into	O
the	O
wash	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
to	O
the	O
laundry-maid	O
,	O
is	O
Daniel	O
here	O
?	O
she	O
said	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
here	O
he	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
kitchen	O
,	O
and	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Daniel	O
it	O
not	O
there	O
,	O
I	O
fancy	O
he	O
is	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
again	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
thought	O
I	O
heard	O
somebody	O
go	O
up	O
before	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
Daniel	O
?	O
Miller	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
get	O
up	O
to	O
clean	O
his	O
plate	O
on	O
a	O
washing	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
thought	O
he	O
was	O
got	O
up	O
too	O
soon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
bed	O
again	O
.	O
The	O
laundry	O
maid	O
said	O
,	O
Molly	O
,	O
go	O
and	O
draw	O
a	O
little	O
beer	O
.	O
I	O
thought	O
she	O
spoke	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
but	O
she	O
spoke	O
to	O
the	O
kitchen-maid	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
pantry	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
in	O
,	O
and	O
drawed	O
some	O
small	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
the	O
door	O
open	O
as	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
is	O
not	O
certain	O
of	O
my	O
going	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
for	O
I	O
went	O
up	O
stairs	O
with	O
my	O
shoes	O
on	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
chairman	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
about	O
12	O
months	O
,	O
I	O
carry	O
a	O
lady	O
that	O
he	O
did	O
serve	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
morning	O
this	O
unhappy	O
affair	O
was	O
talked	O
of	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
morning	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
hear	O
the	O
man	O
was	O
dead	O
till	O
the	O
evening	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
was	O
it	O
?	O
Bond	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
on	O
a	O
Tuesday	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
owed	O
me	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
him	O
call	O
Bond	O
;	O
I	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
up	O
the	O
sash	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
come	O
to	O
pay	O
you	O
some	O
money	O
I	O
owe	O
you	O
:	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
threw	O
me	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
(	O
it	O
was	O
for	O
lodging	O
)	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
change	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
8	O
s.	O
then	O
he	O
wanted	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
to	O
take	O
out	O
some	O
things	O
from	O
his	O
trunk	O
,	O
he	O
having	O
sent	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
while	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
this	O
place	O
,	O
for	O
some	O
things	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
the	O
key	O
in	O
my	O
other	O
coat	O
pocket	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
be	O
here	O
again	O
in	O
10	O
minutes	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
soon	O
returned	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
key	O
,	O
he	O
took	O
out	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
mind	O
to	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
home	O
;	O
and	O
about	O
10	O
or	O
15	O
minutes	O
before	O
4	O
o'clock	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
a	O
music	O
book	O
for	O
pricking	O
down	O
tunes	O
in	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
do	O
with	O
that	O
old	O
trunk	O
?	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
going	O
to	O
Monmouth-street	O
to	O
buy	O
a	O
box	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
sell	O
you	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
bought	O
one	O
of	O
me	O
for	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
changed	O
him	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
him	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
,	O
a	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pot	O
of	O
beer	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
had	O
he	O
lived	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	O
Dacre	O
's	O
?	O
Bond	O
.	O
As	O
far	O
as	O
I	O
understand	O
between	O
nine	O
and	O
ten	O
weeks	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
whether	O
he	O
was	O
worth	O
any	O
money	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
his	O
last	O
place	O
?	O
Bond	O
.	O
He	O
had	O
some	O
money	O
coming	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
was	O
but	O
a	O
trifle	O
I	O
believe	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
leave	O
any	O
thing	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
account	O
of	O
this	O
debt	O
?	O
Bond	O
.	O
He	O
owned	O
my	O
wife	O
14	O
s.	O
for	O
washing	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
left	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
buckles	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
before	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
Lord	O
Dacre	O
's	O
services	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
when	O
he	O
left	O
Mrs.	O
Clift	O
;	O
he	O
left	O
them	O
when	O
she	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
town	O
again	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
weeks	O
time	O
and	O
paid	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
buckles	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Pain	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
washer-woman	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
I	O
washed	O
for	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
you	O
any	O
conversation	O
with	O
him	O
the	O
Friday	O
or	O
Saturday	O
before	O
this	O
accident	O
happen	O
'd	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
and	O
pay	O
me	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
10	O
d.	O
which	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
4	O
s.	O
10	O
d.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
one	O
shilling	O
would	O
be	O
of	O
service	O
to	O
me	O
I	O
should	O
have	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
give	O
me	O
any	O
more	O
till	O
Sunday	O
or	O
Monday	O
.	O
This	O
money	O
had	O
been	O
running	O
up	O
three	O
weeks	O
or	O
a	O
month	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
give	O
you	O
any	O
reason	O
why	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
pay	O
you	O
any	O
more	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
grand-mother	O
was	O
dead	O
and	O
had	O
left	O
him	O
10	O
l.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
next	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Tuesday	O
evening	O
,	O
that	O
this	O
unhappy	O
affair	O
happened	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
it	O
then	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
about	O
candle	O
lighting	O
;	O
he	O
paid	O
me	O
what	O
he	O
owed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
at	O
that	O
time	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
this	O
unhappy	O
accident	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
mentioned	O
it	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
again	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
morning	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
9	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
desired	O
my	O
little	O
boy	O
to	O
carry	O
him	O
up	O
a	O
shirt	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
10	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
this	O
unhappy	O
accident	O
then	O
?	O
Pain	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
nothing	O
about	O
it	O
then	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
French	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
linnendraper	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
at	O
the	O
Sun	O
in	O
Bond-street	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Feb	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
and	O
bought	O
some	O
linnen	O
of	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
8	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
8	O
d.	O
He	O
left	O
2	O
guineas	O
with	O
my	O
servant	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
the	O
remainder	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
for	O
the	O
goods	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
evening	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
the	O
remainder	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
linnen	O
away	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
the	O
money	O
he	O
paid	O
was	O
8	O
l.	O
1	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
more	O
;	O
only	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
's	O
,	O
and	O
heard	O
him	O
confess	O
the	O
murder	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
the	O
knife	O
that	O
was	O
found	O
in	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
bed	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
day	O
after	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
all	O
bloody	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
knives	O
that	O
we	O
dine	O
with	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
handled	O
common	O
table	O
case	O
knife	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
they	O
stand	O
?	O
Barnfield	O
.	O
The	O
clean	O
and	O
foul	O
knives	O
are	O
all	O
put	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
pant	O
ry	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
plate	O
.	O
Mary	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
.	O
I	O
take	O
in	O
washing	O
and	O
needle-work	O
;	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
the	O
day	O
this	O
unhappy	O
accident	O
happened	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
between	O
11	O
and	O
12	O
o'clock	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
call	O
in	O
Hanover	O
Square	O
(	O
at	O
Sir	O
Francis	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
's	O
)	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
have	O
some	O
shirts	O
to	O
make	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
a	O
child	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
about	O
two	O
years	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
old	O
,	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
Irish	O
cloth	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
piece	O
of	O
25	O
yards	O
,	O
the	O
other	O
26	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
one	O
piece	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
muslin	O
to	O
make	O
him	O
some	O
neckcloths	O
;	O
he	O
delivered	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
pieces	O
then	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
on	O
Friday	O
morning	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
mention	O
one	O
word	O
of	O
the	O
unhappy	O
affair	O
of	O
the	O
man	O
's	O
being	O
murder	O
'd	O
;	O
but	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
an	O
unhappy	O
affair	O
in	O
their	O
house	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
the	O
butler	O
had	O
murdered	O
himself	O
,	O
and	O
added	O
,	O
if	O
his	O
lady	O
should	O
make	O
him	O
butler	O
,	O
what	O
a	O
fine	O
fellow	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
;	O
he	O
should	O
wear	O
fine	O
lac	O
'd	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
already	O
got	O
them	O
.	O
Fermer	O
Hast	O
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
Pall-Mall	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
surgeon	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
message	O
sent	O
from	O
my	O
lord	O
Dacres	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
to	O
come	O
there	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
sent	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
about	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
February	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
man	O
dead	O
;	O
I	O
returned	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
my	O
lord	O
sent	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Hawkins	O
desiring	O
he	O
would	O
let	O
me	O
be	O
there	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
to	O
attend	O
the	O
Coroner	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
between	O
ten	O
and	O
eleven	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
deceased	O
's	O
throat	O
cut	O
through	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
wind-pipe	O
and	O
the	O
large	O
blood-vessels	O
were	O
divided	O
.	O
I	O
discovered	O
a	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
temple	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
above	O
the	O
ear	O
.	O
Feeling	O
about	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
I	O
perceived	O
an	O
unevenness	O
of	O
the	O
bone	O
underneath	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
removing	O
the	O
sealp	O
round	O
the	O
wound	O
,	O
I	O
discovered	O
a	O
large	O
fracture	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
small	O
wounds	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
corner	O
of	O
the	O
lip	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
likewise	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
near	O
the	O
other	O
place	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
think	O
those	O
wounds	O
had	O
been	O
given	O
by	O
?	O
Hast	O
.	O
The	O
fracture	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
given	O
by	O
something	O
weighty	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
extent	O
of	O
that	O
and	O
the	O
wound	O
.	O
Q.	O
Cou	O
'd	O
that	O
wound	O
have	O
been	O
given	O
by	O
the	O
deceased	O
himself	O
?	O
Hast	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
suppose	O
not	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
a	O
large	O
fracture	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
say	O
you	O
as	O
to	O
the	O
cut	O
on	O
the	O
throat	O
?	O
Hast	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
a	O
very	O
large	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
throat	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
imagine	O
a	O
wound	O
in	O
the	O
manner	O
that	O
appeared	O
to	O
you	O
,	O
that	O
a	O
person	O
could	O
have	O
made	O
such	O
an	O
incision	O
upon	O
his	O
own	O
throat	O
?	O
Hast	O
.	O
I	O
should	O
not	O
have	O
thought	O
it	O
in	O
a	O
man	O
's	O
power	O
to	O
make	O
such	O
a	O
wound	O
on	O
himself	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
have	O
some	O
reason	O
for	O
forming	O
that	O
judgement	O
.	O
Hast	O
.	O
Because	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
fracture	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
also	O
no	O
man	O
could	O
be	O
able	O
to	O
cut	O
his	O
own	O
throat	O
in	O
that	O
manner	O
;	O
it	O
is	O
impossible	O
,	O
alter	O
that	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
,	O
that	O
that	O
cut	O
could	O
have	O
been	O
done	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
the	O
wound	O
on	O
the	O
head	O
was	O
mortal	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
was	O
given	O
,	O
which	O
must	O
be	O
by	O
a	O
blow	O
,	O
I	O
suppose	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
stirred	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Helt	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	O
Dacre	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
laundry-maid	O
.	O
(	O
She	O
produced	O
a	O
strong	O
kitchen	O
poker	O
very	O
much	O
bent	O
.	O
)	O
I	O
remember	O
seeing	O
this	O
poker	O
by	O
the	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
laundry-fire	O
the	O
night	O
before	O
this	O
unhappy	O
accident	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
very	O
strait	O
then	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
bent	O
in	O
this	O
condition	O
before	O
the	O
accident	O
was	O
heard	O
of	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
made	O
observation	O
of	O
its	O
being	O
thus	O
bent	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
7	O
o'clock	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
laundry-fire	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
put	O
it	O
there	O
over	O
night	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Marsden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
examined	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
my	O
Lord	O
's	O
house	O
best	O
part	O
of	O
two	O
days	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
examined	O
with	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
servants	O
,	O
then	O
no	O
guilt	O
appeared	O
on	O
him	O
any	O
more	O
than	O
the	O
rest	O
,	O
till	O
the	O
second	O
day	O
;	O
then	O
some	O
circumstances	O
appeared	O
,	O
that	O
pointed	O
with	O
some	O
suspicion	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
first	O
day	O
he	O
was	O
examined	O
upon	O
oath	O
,	O
