TOKEN	NE
THE	O
WHOLE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Goal-Delivery	O
FOR	O
THE	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
;	O
And	O
also	O
the	O
Goal-Delivery	O
for	O
the	O
County	O
of	O
MIDDLESEX	O
,	O
HELD	O
AT	O
JUSTICE-HALL	O
in	O
the	O
OLD-BAILEY	O
,	O
On	O
Wednesday	O
the	O
19th	O
,	O
Thursday	O
the	O
20th	O
,	O
and	O
Friday	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
OCTOBER	O
.	O
In	O
the	O
Third	O
Year	O
of	O
His	O
MAJESTY	O
's	O
Reign	O
.	O
Being	O
the	O
Eighth	O
SESSION	O
in	O
the	O
MAYORALTY	O
of	O
The	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Beckford	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
LORD-MAYOR	O
of	O
the	O
CITY	O
of	O
LONDON	O
.	O
NUMBER	O
VIII	O
.	O
for	O
the	O
YEAR	O
1763	O
.	O
LONDON	O
:	O
Printed	O
for	O
and	O
Sold	O
by	O
JOHN	B-pers
RYALL	I-pers
,	O
in	O
Fleet-Street	O
.	O
[	O
Price	O
Six-pence	O
.	O
]	O
THE	O
PROCEEDINGS	O
ON	O
THE	O
King	O
's	O
Commission	O
of	O
the	O
Peace	O
,	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
,	O
and	O
Gaol-Delivery	O
,	O
held	O
for	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
LONDON	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
BEFORE	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
WILLIAM	B-pers
BECKFORD	I-pers
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
;	O
the	O
Right	O
Honourable	O
William	B-pers
Lord	I-pers
Mansfield	I-pers
*	O
,	O
Lord	O
Chief	O
Justice	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
King	O
's	O
Bench	O
;	O
Sir	O
Sidney	B-pers
Stafford	I-pers
Smythe	I-pers
+	O
,	O
Knt	O
.	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Barons	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Exchequer	O
;	O
the	O
Honourable	O
Henry	B-pers
Bathurst	I-pers
||	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Judges	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Court	O
of	O
Common	O
Pleas	O
;	O
James	B-pers
Eyre	I-pers
++	O
,	O
Esquire	O
,	O
Recorder	O
;	O
and	O
others	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
Justices	O
of	O
Oyer	O
and	O
Terminer	O
of	O
the	O
City	O
of	O
London	O
,	O
and	O
Justices	O
of	O
Goal-Delivery	O
of	O
Newgate	O
,	O
holden	O
for	O
the	O
said	O
City	O
and	O
County	O
of	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
N.	O
B	O
.	O
The	O
*	O
,	O
+	O
,	O
||	O
,	O
and	O
++	O
,	O
refer	O
to	O
the	O
Judges	O
before	O
whom	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
was	O
tried	O
.	O
L.	O
London	O
,	O
M.	O
Middlesex	O
.	O
London	O
Jury	O
.	O
Peter	B-pers
Bigs	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Benning	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Marriot	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Stevenson	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elliot	I-pers
,	O
Josiah	B-pers
Dornford	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Colley	I-pers
,	O
James	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Bell	I-pers
,	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stanney	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Richards	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Howard	I-pers
.	O
Middlesex	O
Jury	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Mount	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Charles	B-pers
Mills	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Pierrepoint	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Fullingham	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Cock	I-pers
,	O
Henry	B-pers
Houling	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Dormer	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Noy	I-pers
,	O
Blagrave	B-pers
Gregory	I-pers
,	O
Thomas	B-pers
Pyke	I-pers
,	O
Samuel	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
.	O
460	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Barnard	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
2	O
yards	O
and	O
a	O
quarter	O
of	O
black	O
sattin	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
16	O
s.	O
12	O
yards	O
and	O
3	O
quarters	O
of	O
white	O
sattin	O
,	O
3	O
yards	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
flowered	O
sattin	O
,	O
23	O
yards	O
of	O
tabby	O
,	O
and	O
11	O
guineas	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Henry	B-pers
Probin	I-pers
and	O
Co	O
.	O
Oct.	O
5	O
,	O
To	O
which	O
he	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
461	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
Burch	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
neckcloth	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Hughes	I-pers
;	O
one	O
linnen	O
shirt	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Evan	B-pers
Roberts	I-pers
;	O
three	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Samuel	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
;	O
one	O
linnen	O
shift	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stays	O
,	O
four	O
linnen	O
aprons	O
,	O
2	O
yards	O
of	O
linnen	O
cloth	O
,	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
flat	O
iron	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Edward	B-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
4	O
.	O
To	O
which	O
she	O
pleaded	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
462	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Morris	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
21	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
and	O
Co	O
.	O
it	O
was	O
laid	O
also	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
and	O
Edward	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
Oct.	O
7	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Greenwood	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Messrs.	O
William	B-pers
Snell	I-pers
,	O
William	B-pers
Pardon	I-pers
,	O
and	O
John	B-pers
Lang	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
October	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
bar	O
of	O
iron	O
,	O
their	O
property	O
,	O
was	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
Steel-yard-wharf	B-place
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
the	O
taking	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Reeves	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
cooper	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
my	O
work	O
in	O
the	O
Steel-yard	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
about	O
the	O
iron	O
,	O
I	O
watched	O
and	O
saw	O
him	O
come	O
out	O
with	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
iron	O
under	O
his	O
coat	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
Stubley	O
the	O
watchman	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
pursued	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
iron	O
from	O
him	O
,	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
;	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
my	O
Lord	O
Mayor	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
committed	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
even	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
;	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Greenwood	O
on	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
property	O
;	O
that	O
it	O
was	O
Russia	O
iron	O
,	O
called	O
new	O
fable	O
,	O
taken	O
from	O
a	O
quantity	O
of	O
such	O
married	O
in	O
the	O
like	O
manner	O
.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Stubley	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
given	O
by	O
Reeves	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
463	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
four	O
pewter	O
plates	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
18	O
.	O
++	O
Nathaniel	B-pers
Crowder	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
St.	B-place
Martin's-lane	I-place
.	O
Yesterday	O
morning	O
about	O
10	O
o'clock	O
my	O
family	O
were	O
at	O
breakfast	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
asked	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
hot	O
,	O
drank	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
another	O
;	O
after	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
kitchen	O
some	O
time	O
by	O
himself	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
my	O
wife	O
took	O
notice	O
of	O
something	O
bulging	O
out	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
she	O
called	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
no	O
answer	O
;	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
four	O
pewter	O
plates	O
under	O
his	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
N.	O
C.	O
S.	O
upon	O
them	O
all	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
brought	O
them	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
might	O
do	O
what	O
I	O
would	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
a	O
cook-shop	O
for	O
some	O
victuals	O
on	O
two	O
plates	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
to	O
cover	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
464	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Hall	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
cloth	O
coat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
shoes	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stockings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Tee	I-pers
;	O
four	O
ducks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
and	O
two	O
hempen	O
sacks	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
,	O
October	O
9	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Tee	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
servant	O
with	O
Mr	O
.	O
Tipping	O
,	O
at	O
Stanmore	B-place
;	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
as	O
my	O
property	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
stable	O
last	O
Sunday	O
was	O
se'nnight	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
Monday	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
mistrusted	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
taken	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
worked	O
with	O
my	O
master	O
last	O
summer	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Harris	O
,	O
at	O
Stanmore	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
charged	O
him	O
with	O
taking	O
my	O
thing	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
fetched	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
hay-loft	O
,	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
them	O
;	O
then	O
my	O
master	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
delivered	O
him	O
the	O
ducks	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Tipping	I-pers
.	O
I	O
missed	O
four	O
ducks	O
from	O
a	O
pen	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
charged	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
them	O
from	O
the	O
hay	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
hid	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
deliver	O
him	O
the	O
ducks	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
forgive	O
me	O
.	O
Tipping	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
be	O
favourable	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
but	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
things	O
without	O
saying	O
any	O
thing	O
about	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
465	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Matthew	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
India	O
screen	O
,	O
value	O
20	O
s.	O
one	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
worsted	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Moore	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
Sept.	O
21	O
.	O
+	O
Sarah	B-pers
Count	I-pers
.	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
lodges	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
in	O
Three	B-place
Arrow-court	I-place
.	O
On	O
the	O
21st	O
of	O
the	O
last	O
month	O
,	O
betwixt	O
12	O
and	O
1	O
at	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
coming	O
down	O
stairs	O
with	O
a	O
six-leaved	O
India	O
screen	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
screen	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Count	O
(	O
my	O
husband	O
)	O
had	O
given	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
carrying	O
it	O
up	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
then	O
carry	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
,	O
and	O
set	O
it	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
place	O
it	O
stood	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
S.	O
Count	O
.	O
He	O
used	O
to	O
write	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
writes	O
for	O
stationers	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
charged	O
with	O
taking	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
that	O
were	O
missing	O
;	O
he	O
owned	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
sold	O
them	O
near	O
the	O
Seven	O
Dials	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
and	O
found	O
them	O
;	O
he	O
mentioned	O
his	O
selling	O
the	O
waistcoat	O
at	O
another	O
shop	O
,	O
where	O
Mr.	O
Moore	O
found	O
that	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
Mr	O
.	O
Moore	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
depended	O
she	O
would	O
not	O
appear	O
against	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
have	O
brought	O
no	O
witnesses	O
,	O
thinking	O
I	O
should	O
be	O
acquitted	O
.	O
Pray	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Count	O
,	O
what	O
is	O
my	O
character	O
?	O
S.	O
Count	O
.	O
He	O
has	O
worked	O
for	O
my	O
husband	O
about	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
months	O
,	O
he	O
minded	O
his	O
business	O
some	O
little	O
time	O
,	O
he	O
might	O
have	O
earned	O
30	O
s.	O
a	O
week	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
latterly	O
neglected	O
his	O
business	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
he	O
would	O
bring	O
himself	O
to	O
something	O
bad	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
466	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Mary	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
Thomas	I-pers
Dinmore	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Thungar	I-pers
,	O
September	O
27	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Thungar	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Surry-street	B-place
,	O
and	O
keep	O
the	O
Cheshire	O
Cheese	O
,	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
she	O
came	O
to	O
my	O
house	O
and	O
dined	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
had	O
tea	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
left	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
with	O
two	O
men	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
gone	O
three	O
tea-spoons	O
were	O
missing	O
,	O
I	O
followed	O
and	O
found	O
her	O
in	O
a	O
shop	O
;	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
were	O
with	O
her	O
is	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
gentleman	O
in	O
Surry-street	O
,	O
I	O
desired	O
him	O
to	O
go	O
back	O
with	O
her	O
;	O
going	O
along	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
little	O
behind	O
her	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
two	O
tea-spoons	O
drop	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
her	O
hand	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
pocket-hole	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
,	O
going	O
a	O
little	O
farther	O
John	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
picked	O
up	O
another	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Penny	I-pers
.	O
Seeing	O
a	O
mob	O
I	O
followed	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
a	O
tea-spoon	O
drop	O
from	O
under	O
her	O
gown	O
,	O
her	O
hand	O
was	O
at	O
her	O
pocket-hole	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
;	O
I	O
suppose	O
she	O
intended	O
to	O
have	O
dropt	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
dead	O
ground	O
,	O
but	O
it	O
happened	O
to	O
fall	O
on	O
a	O
stone	O
,	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
it	O
fell	O
she	O
took	O
her	O
hand	O
from	O
her	O
pocket	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
her	O
defence	O
.	O
She	O
called	O
Eleanor	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
who	O
had	O
known	O
her	O
about	O
10	O
years	O
,	O
who	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
with	O
her	O
three	O
years	O
,	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
to	O
learn	O
the	O
art	O
of	O
mantua-making	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
been	O
with	O
her	O
two	O
years	O
besides	O
;	O
that	O
she	O
had	O
behaved	O
well	O
while	O
with	O
her	O
,	O
but	O
had	O
been	O
gone	O
from	O
her	O
about	O
six	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
married	O
from	O
the	O
duke	O
of	O
Norfolk	O
's	O
service	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
her	O
husband	O
is	O
groom	O
of	O
the	O
chamber	O
to	O
the	O
dutchess	O
of	O
Norfolk	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Clements	I-pers
,	O
a	O
peruke-maker	O
,	O
deposed	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
know	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
lived	O
with	O
Mrs.	O
Bailey	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
heard	O
Mrs.	O
Bailey	O
speak	O
well	O
of	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
good	O
servant	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
467	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Anderson	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
the	O
dwelling	O
house	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
on	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
a	O
brass	O
thimble	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
and	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Grinstead	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Mary	B-pers
Grinstead	I-pers
.	O
My	O
husband	O
is	O
named	O
John	O
,	O
we	O
lodge	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
William	B-pers
Smith	I-pers
,	O
my	O
room	O
is	O
up	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
stairs	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
awaked	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
sleep	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
opening	O
my	O
drawer	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Good	O
master	O
,	O
what	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
here	O
?	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
cross	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
a	O
little	O
,	O
then	O
went	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
casement	O
which	O
then	O
was	O
open	O
;	O
I	O
missed	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
drawer	O
6	O
s.	O
in	O
silver	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
tea-spoon	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
thimble	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
the	O
prisoner	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
you	O
saw	O
in	O
your	O
room	O
?	O
M.	O
Grinstead	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
coach	O
afterwards	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
before	O
a	O
Justice	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
That	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
robbed	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
night	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
M.	O
Grinstead	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
about	O
2	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
;	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
light	O
burning	O
by	O
my	O
bed	O
side	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
came	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
bed	O
side	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Skinner	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pentilow	O
,	O
the	O
keeper	O
of	O
New-prison	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
being	O
taken	O
up	O
,	O
Justice	O
Spinage	O
sent	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Pentilow	O
to	O
fetch	O
him	O
away	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
watch-house	O
,	O
I	O
searched	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
upon	O
him	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
Dutch	O
tinder-box	O
,	O
flint	O
and	O
steel	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
smoke	O
very	O
much	O
,	O
I	O
make	O
use	O
of	O
the	O
tinder-box	O
to	O
light	O
my	O
pipe	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
I	O
am	O
charged	O
with	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Aug.	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
1	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
gold	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
l.	O
one	O
reflecting	O
telescope	O
,	O
one	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
one	O
amathist	O
gold	O
ring	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
l.	O
four	O
mourning	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
40	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
ear-rings	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
and	O
rose	O
stones	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
l.	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
knee-buckles	O
,	O
one	O
silver	O
stock-buckle	O
,	O
and	O
40	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
James	B-pers
Warner	I-pers
.	O
*	O
Barbara	B-pers
Hardy	I-pers
.	O
I	O
lodge	O
at	O
Stoke	B-place
Newington	I-place
,	O
at	O
the	O
house	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Warner	O
.	O
I	O
awaked	O
on	O
the	O
1st	O
of	O
Aug	O
about	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
my	O
window	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
gone	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
buroe	O
that	O
stood	O
by	O
the	O
window	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
buroe	O
locked	O
over	O
night	O
?	O
B.	O
Hardy	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
your	O
window	O
fast	O
?	O
B.	O
Hardy	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
answer	O
for	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
it	O
was	O
down	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dyley	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
jeweller	O
and	O
goldsmith	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
diamond	O
ear-rings	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
and	O
advertised	O
them	O
,	O
here	O
they	O
be	O
.	O
(	O
Producing	O
a	O
pair	O
.	O
)	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
These	O
are	O
my	O
property	O
which	O
were	O
taken	O
away	O
that	O
night	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
nothing	O
else	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
brought	O
these	O
ear-rings	O
from	O
the	O
Havanna	O
,	O
I	O
got	O
them	O
that	O
night	O
we	O
took	O
Graunamacoe	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutrix	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
bed	O
that	O
night	O
?	O
B.	O
Hardy	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
about	O
10	O
,	O
and	O
to	O
sleep	O
about	O
12	O
,	O
and	O
did	O
not	O
awake	O
till	O
about	O
6	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
468	O
,	O
469	O
,	O
470	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
OHarra	I-pers
,	O
John	B-pers
Barret	I-pers
,	O
and	O
Michael	B-pers
Kenedy	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
they	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
king	O
's	O
highway	O
,	O
on	O
Caspar	B-pers
Stoupson	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
,	O
putting	O
him	O
in	O
corporal	O
fear	O
and	O
danger	O
of	O
his	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
taking	O
from	O
his	O
person	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
val	O
3	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
key	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
one	O
steel	O
hook	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
1	O
d.	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
shoe-buckles	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
hat	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
peruke	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
1	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
his	O
property	O
,	O
Sept.	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
Caspar	B-pers
Stoupson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
know	O
OHarra	O
,	O
Barret	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
evidence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
an	O
order	O
from	O
my	O
master	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
hire	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
,	O
and	O
coming	O
home	O
again	O
there	O
came	O
four	O
men	O
,	O
Folliott	O
came	O
upon	O
me	O
with	O
a	O
knife	O
,	O
and	O
OHarra	O
and	O
Barret	O
stood	O
on	O
my	O
right	O
side	O
and	O
took	O
my	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
,	O
they	O
amongst	O
them	O
took	O
a	O
shilling	O
in	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
hired	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
OHarra	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
see	O
me	O
before	O
?	O
Stoupson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
never	O
before	O
that	O
time	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
OHarra	O
.	O
Then	O
how	O
came	O
you	O
by	O
my	O
nane	O
?	O
Stoupson	O
.	O
That	O
I	O
heard	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Barret	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
crime	O
,	O
but	O
neither	O
,	O
of	O
these	O
men	O
(	O
meaning	O
his	O
fellow	O
prisoners	O
)	O
and	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
robbed	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
threw	O
myself	O
upon	O
the	O
mercy	O
of	O
the	O
court	O
John	B-pers
Folliott	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
Deptford	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
at	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
I	O
met	O
OHarra	O
and	O
Kenedy	O
,	O
OHarra	O
said	O
,	O
What	O
chear	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Brave	O
and	O
hearty	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
take	O
a	O
cruise	O
?	O
With	O
all	O
my	O
heart	O
,	O
said	O
I	O
;	O
they	O
took	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
house	O
on	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
,	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
through	O
an	O
alley	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
one	O
Swinney	O
,	O
OHarra	O
asked	O
him	O
to	O
come	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
about	O
17	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
,	O
coming	O
through	O
a	O
narrow	O
passage	O
towards	O
Wellclose-Square	O
,	O
OHarra	O
stopped	O
a	O
man	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
cried	O
out	O
,	O
they	O
knocked	O
his	O
hat	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
it	O
up	O
,	O
he	O
making	O
a	O
noise	O
we	O
got	O
off	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Road	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bricklayer	O
's	O
labourer	O
,	O
OHarra	O
and	O
Kenedy	O
pulled	O
their	O
knives	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
made	O
any	O
noise	O
they	O
would	O
cut	O
his	O
throat	O
;	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
gentleman	O
coming	O
along	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
horseback	O
called	O
out	O
,	O
These	O
men	O
have	O
robbed	O
me	O
;	O
OHarra	O
and	O
Kenedy	O
left	O
the	O
man	O
on	O
horseback	O
,	O
and	O
came	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Pitfield	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
while	O
they	O
were	O
searching	O
his	O
pockets	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
watch	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
Kenedy	O
came	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Here	O
is	O
2	O
s.	O
which	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
his	O
watch	O
.	O
OHarra	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
to	O
a	O
field	O
towards	O
Stepney	O
,	O
and	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
barber	O
's	O
hone	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
halfpence	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
all	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
drank	O
in	O
East	O
Smithfield	O
,	O
from	O
thence	O
we	O
went	O
towards	O
Saltpetre-bank	O
,	O
where	O
we	O
met	O
another	O
man	O
;	O
then	O
OHarra	O
and	O
Kenedy	O
brought	O
Nonorkan	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
five	O
of	O
us	O
then	O
together	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
New	O
Road	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
came	O
past	O
was	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
man	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
Barret	O
ran	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
,	O
Kenedy	O
took	O
his	O
hat	O
and	O
wig	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
wig	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
hat	O
to	O
Barret	O
;	O
another	O
man	O
coming	O
past	O
Barret	O
immediately	O
stopped	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
his	O
money	O
with	O
his	O
knife	O
drawn	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
side	O
was	O
OHarra	O
on	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
you	O
took	O
the	O
things	O
?	O
Folliott	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
ran	O
after	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
ran	O
away	O
.	O
Q.	O
from	O
Kenedy	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
known	O
me	O
?	O
Folliott	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
Kenedy	O
before	O
that	O
evening	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
seen	O
OHarra	O
many	O
times	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
drank	O
with	O
him	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
tried	O
here	O
last	O
sessions	O
.	O
Barret	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
Folliott	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
going	O
to	O
raffle	O
for	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
we	O
stopped	O
two	O
men	O
on	O
the	O
New	O
Road	O
,	O
Folliott	O
gave	O
me	O
the	O
hat	O
;	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
say	O
that	O
I	O
ever	O
saw	O
the	O
other	O
two	O
prisoners	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
is	O
the	O
first	O
crime	O
that	O
ever	O
I	O
committed	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
the	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
certain	O
O'Harra	O
was	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
?	O
Prosecutor	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
certain	O
he	O
was	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Grief	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
turnkey	O
to	O
the	O
Tower	O
goal	O
,	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
the	O
morning	O
after	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
us	O
he	O
had	O
lost	O
his	O
watch	O
and	O
buckles	O
;	O
in	O
came	O
a	O
sailor	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
seen	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
wig	O
and	O
buckles	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
and	O
soon	O
returned	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
had	O
them	O
was	O
fast	O
asleep	O
;	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
Folliott	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
wig	O
on	O
,	O
which	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
hook	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
he	O
named	O
Barret	O
and	O
O'Harra	O
being	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
both	O
at	O
our	O
door	O
just	O
before	O
,	O
but	O
were	O
gone	O
away	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
Kenedy	O
?	O
Grief	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
then	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
did	O
before	O
the	O
Bench	O
of	O
Justices	O
,	O
and	O
two	O
more	O
that	O
are	O
not	O
taken	O
.	O
When	O
Barret	O
was	O
taken	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
hat	O
on	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
swore	O
to	O
it	O
.	O
When	O
we	O
had	O
got	O
O'Harra	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Let	O
me	O
go	O
along	O
and	O
be	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
by	O
the	O
Holy	O
Ghost	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
tuck	O
them	O
.	O
Kenedy	O
was	O
desired	O
to	O
be	O
evidence	O
,	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
admitted	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
and	O
owned	O
to	O
the	O
robbery	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Gordon	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
Monday	O
night	O
this	O
robbery	O
was	O
committed	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
noise	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
a	O
man	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
down	O
and	O
found	O
Caen	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
in	O
my	O
charge	O
.	O
The	O
next	O
morning	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
came	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
none	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
;	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
came	O
a	O
sailor	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
did	O
the	O
robbery	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
taking	O
the	O
evidence	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
asleep	O
.	O
After	O
that	O
we	O
heard	O
O'Harra	O
and	O
Barret	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
Tower-goal	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
Muckle	O
Roy	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
there	O
we	O
took	O
them	O
,	O
the	O
hat	O
was	O
found	O
on	O
Barret	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Thursday	O
following	O
they	O
were	O
ordered	O
to	O
be	O
re-examined	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
Kenedy	O
when	O
at	O
the	O
Coach	O
and	O
Horses	O
,	O
White-chapel	O
,	O
you	O
seem	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
young	O
man	O
,	O
make	O
yourself	O
an	O
evidence	O
;	O
he	O
denied	O
knowing	O
any	O
thing	O
of	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Then	O
Folliott	O
came	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
were	O
ordered	O
up	O
;	O
when	O
Kenedy	O
found	O
Folliott	O
was	O
admitted	O
evidence	O
he	O
cried	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
something	O
to	O
the	O
men	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
I	O
Barret	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
say	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
guilty	O
of	O
the	O
robbery	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
are	O
not	O
.	O
O'Harra	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
Folliot	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
.	O
Kenedy	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
stranger	O
in	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
been	O
long	O
paid	O
off	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
at	O
Chatham	O
,	O
I	O
spent	O
most	O
part	O
of	O
my	O
money	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
up	O
to	O
town	O
,	O
I	O
worked	O
upon	O
the	O
river	O
for	O
honest	O
bread	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
about	O
the	O
affair	O
than	O
the	O
child	O
unborn	O
,	O
the	O
evidence	O
brings	O
me	O
in	O
to	O
save	O
his	O
own	O
life	O
;	O
we	O
are	O
all	O
sailors	O
.	O
All	O
three	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
See	O
O'Harra	O
tried	O
No	O
.	O
452	O
in	O
the	O
last	O
Session	O
's	O
Paper	O
,	O
for	O
robbing	O
Abraham	O
Green	O
on	O
the	O
highway	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
another	O
indictment	O
against	O
O'Harra	O
and	O
Kenedy	O
for	O
robbing	O
Mr.	O
Pitfield	O
.	O
471	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Corbett	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
leather	O
breeches	O
,	O
value	O
30	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
,	O
Sept.	O
21	O
.	O
*	O
Thomas	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
my	O
journeyman	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
country	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
,	O
I	O
missed	O
two	O
pair	O
of	O
breeches	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
left	O
by	O
himself	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
Justice	O
Cox	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
he	O
sold	O
one	O
pair	O
to	O
a	O
Jew	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
and	O
another	O
pair	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
new	O
,	O
to	O
a	O
person	O
in	O
Monmouth-street	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
472	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Rossiter	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
punch-ladle	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
table-spoon	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
pap-spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
value	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
2	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
patient	O
in	O
St.	O
Bartholomew	O
's	O
Hospital	O
,	O
a	O
person	O
came	O
and	O
let	O
me	O
know	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
robbed	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
found	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
custody	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
things	O
said	O
to	O
be	O
found	O
upon	O
him	O
,	O
my	O
property	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Bird	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
about	O
three	O
weeks	O
ago	O
to	O
take	O
charge	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
;	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
's	O
wife	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
,	O
she	O
was	O
asked	O
,	O
if	O
she	O
knew	O
anything	O
of	O
a	O
punch-label	O
?	O
She	O
looked	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
her	O
property	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
backwards	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
he	O
pulled	O
out	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Shepherd	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
did	O
take	O
them	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Shepherd	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lay	O
in	O
a	O
room	O
of	O
mine	O
,	O
where	O
these	O
things	O
were	O
in	O
a	O
buffet	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
went	O
out	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
having	O
been	O
gone	O
out	O
afterwards	O
,	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
between	O
5	O
and	O
6	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
told	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
offered	O
a	O
punch-ladle	O
to	O
sale	O
,	O
I	O
knew	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
asked	O
him	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
took	O
away	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
from	O
the	O
buffet	O
?	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
a	O
back	O
room	O
and	O
took	O
out	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
and	O
delivered	O
them	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
found	O
these	O
things	O
in	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
brown	O
paper	O
on	O
the	O
stairs	O
.	O
He	O
called	O
five	O
people	O
to	O
his	O
character	O
,	O
who	O
said	O
they	O
never	O
knew	O
any	O
ill	O
of	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
473	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Patrick	B-pers
Caen	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
with	O
a	O
certain	O
knife	O
,	O
on	O
William	B-pers
McDowell	I-pers
did	O
make	O
an	O
assault	O
with	O
intent	O
the	O
money	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
William	O
to	O
steal	O
,	O
Sept.	O
26	O
.	O
*	O
William	B-pers
McDowell	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Wellclose-squary	B-place
on	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
three	O
men	O
and	O
a	O
woman	O
stood	O
in	O
the	O
Square	O
which	O
I	O
passed	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
three	O
men	O
came	O
after	O
me	O
pretty	O
fast	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
then	O
pretty	O
near	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
came	O
before	O
me	O
and	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
right	O
arm	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
my	O
left	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
third	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
had	O
a	O
knife	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
saying	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
spoke	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
dead	O
man	O
.	O
I	O
seeing	O
the	O
knife	O
,	O
called	O
out	O
murder	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
cut	O
at	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
held	O
up	O
my	O
hand	O
to	O
save	O
my	O
neck	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
cut	O
my	O
thumb	O
.	O
The	O
man	O
at	O
my	O
right	O
hand	O
felt	O
for	O
the	O
watch	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
not	O
having	O
a	O
string	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
saved	O
it	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
women	O
looked	O
out	O
at	O
a	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
out	O
to	O
the	O
person	O
that	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
man	O
,	O
directing	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Linstead	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
near	O
Justice	O
Pell	O
's	O
door	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
murder	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
upon	O
hearing	O
it	O
a	O
second	O
time	O
I	O
ran	O
very	O
hard	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
got	O
by	O
the	O
posts	O
the	O
prisoner	O
past	O
me	O
,	O
two	O
women	O
over	O
my	O
head	O
from	O
a	O
window	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
has	O
past	O
you	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
walking	O
alone	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
doing	O
?	O
he	O
answered	O
nothing	O
at	O
all	O
;	O
the	O
women	O
said	O
,	O
they	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
murdered	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
saw	O
him	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
the	O
man	O
that	O
held	O
a	O
knife	O
to	O
my	O
throat	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
said	O
nothing	O
in	O
his	O
defence	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
474	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Kelly	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
,	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
about	O
the	O
hour	O
of	O
10	O
in	O
the	O
night	O
,	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
Robert	B-pers
Sinclair	I-pers
did	O
break	O
and	O
enter	O
,	O
and	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
watch	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
l.	O
one	O
silver	O
seal	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
d.	O
six	O
linnen	O
shirts	O
,	O
value	O
36	O
s.	O
three	O
half	O
guineas	O
,	O
four	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
,	O
and	O
26	O
s.	O
in	O
money	O
numbered	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Robert	O
,	O
in	O
his	O
dwelling-house	O
.	O
*	O
Robert	B-pers
Sinclair	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
8th	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
going	O
home	O
as	O
the	O
watch	O
was	O
going	O
eleven	O
,	O
having	O
nobody	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
but	O
myself	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
next	O
morning	O
,	O
going	O
to	O
look	O
for	O
a	O
shirt	O
,	O
found	O
the	O
money	O
and	O
things	O
mentioned	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
pane	O
of	O
glass	O
out	O
and	O
the	O
casement	O
open	O
,	O
I	O
suspected	O
the	O
prisoner	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
beg	O
my	O
pardon	O
;	O
the	O
Justice	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
had	O
done	O
with	O
the	O
money	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
a	O
blue	O
surtoute	O
coat	O
that	O
morning	O
with	O
part	O
of	O
it	O
:	O
I	O
found	O
my	O
shirts	O
in	O
his	O
lodgings	O
afterwards	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
were	O
the	O
things	O
when	O
you	O
went	O
out	O
?	O
Sinclair	O
.	O
My	O
money	O
was	O
in	O
a	O
little	O
till	O
in	O
a	O
chest	O
in	O
my	O
bed-chamber	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
watch	O
hanging	O
up	O
by	O
my	O
bed-side	O
,	O
and	O
my	O
shirts	O
were	O
lying	O
dirty	O
in	O
a	O
basket	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
headborough	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
watch	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
inside	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
breeches	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
he	O
delivered	O
up	O
to	O
me	O
two	O
quarter	O
guineas	O
which	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
with	O
his	O
landlady	O
;	O
I	O
examined	O
him	O
in	O
a	O
public-house	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
a	O
bond	O
to	O
make	O
the	O
deficiency	O
of	O
what	O
was	O
lost	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
work	O
it	O
out	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Sinclair	O
declared	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
be	O
concerned	O
with	O
him	O
upon	O
any	O
score	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
produced	O
the	O
shirts	O
and	O
watch	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
John	B-pers
George	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
,	O
on	O
Saturday	O
night	O
he	O
brought	O
half	O
a	O
dozen	O
shirts	O
to	O
wash.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
near	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
to	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
?	O
George	O
.	O
Not	O
above	O
40	O
poles	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
they	O
came	O
with	O
a	O
search-warrant	O
,	O
the	O
shirts	O
appear	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
Mr.	O
Sinclair	O
's	O
property	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
initial	O
letters	O
of	O
his	O
name	O
upon	O
them	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
home	O
at	O
half	O
an	O
hour	O
after	O
8	O
from	O
Shoreditch	O
turnpike	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
man	O
standing	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
standing	O
looking	O
about	O
for	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
I	O
want	O
to	O
speak	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
in	O
distress	O
and	O
have	O
something	O
to	O
sell	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
you	O
'll	O
buy	O
them	O
I	O
'll	O
sell	O
them	O
cheap	O
:	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
wanted	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
them	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
to	O
a	O
public-house	O
;	O
he	O
would	O
not	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
said	O
you	O
have	O
not	O
come	O
honestly	O
by	O
them	O
:	O
He	O
asked	O
a	O
guinea	O
and	O
half	O
for	O
the	O
six	O
shirts	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
24	O
s.	O
that	O
was	O
4	O
s.	O
a-piece	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
would	O
buy	O
a	O
watch	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
never	O
wear	O
any	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
it	O
since	O
he	O
came	O
from	O
sea	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
no	O
money	O
left	O
;	O
he	O
asked	O
me	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
,	O
I	O
offer	O
'd	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
and	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
he	O
follow	O
'd	O
me	O
and	O
gave	O
it	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
two	O
guineas	O
;	O
I	O
immediately	O
went	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
White-hart	O
,	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
5	O
minutes	O
after	O
10	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
went	O
home	O
to	O
my	O
own	O
lodging	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
so	O
drunk	O
I	O
was	O
hardly	O
capable	O
of	O
walking	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
475	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Charles	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Woodward	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Evans	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Saunders	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Tufnail	I-pers
,	I-pers
otherwise	I-pers
Dougan	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
minionet	O
lace	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Christopher	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Christopher	O
,	O
Sept.	O
28	O
.	O
++	O
Ann	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
wife	O
to	O
Christopher	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
we	O
live	O
in	O
Bread-street	B-place
,	I-place
Golden-square	I-place
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
millener	O
's	O
shop	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
,	O
on	O
Tuesday	O
the	O
27th	O
of	O
September	O
in	O
the	O
evening	O
,	O
and	O
ask	O
'd	O
me	O
if	O
I	O
had	O
any	O
minionet	O
ruffles	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
for	O
a	O
gentleman	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
I	O
had	O
none	O
ready	O
done	O
,	O
because	O
every	O
gentleman	O
are	O
not	O
of	O
one	O
measure	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
have	O
you	O
any	O
minionet	O
lace	O
;	O
I	O
took	O
down	O
a	O
box	O
,	O
it	O
happen	O
'd	O
to	O
be	O
blond	O
lace	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
took	O
down	O
the	O
right	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
had	O
not	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
by	O
me	O
;	O
he	O
tost	O
one	O
piece	O
and	O
another	O
about	O
,	O
saying	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
fine	O
enough	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
wanted	O
for	O
three	O
or	O
four	O
pair	O
of	O
ruffles	O
;	O
he	O
clapt	O
his	O
hand	O
to	O
his	O
head	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
not	O
well	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
:	O
He	O
had	O
been	O
telling	O
me	O
of	O
his	O
buying	O
ruffles	O
in	O
Jamaica	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
perhaps	O
,	O
Sir	O
,	O
this	O
country	O
air	O
does	O
not	O
agree	O
with	O
you	O
,	O
perhaps	O
you	O
will	O
not	O
go	O
back	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
ship	O
there	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
come	O
again	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
and	O
bring	O
a	O
lady	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
sent	O
to	O
a	O
merchant	O
and	O
got	O
12	O
pieces	O
,	O
he	O
came	O
,	O
I	O
shew	O
'd	O
him	O
them	O
,	O
he	O
talk	O
'd	O
of	O
some	O
lace	O
for	O
a	O
cravat	O
,	O
I	O
sent	O
the	O
maid	O
out	O
for	O
some	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
:	O
In	O
looking	O
over	O
the	O
lace	O
,	O
the	O
only	O
piece	O
that	O
struck	O
my	O
eye	O
as	O
a	O
genteel	O
thing	O
was	O
missing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
him	O
take	O
any	O
?	O
A.	O
Dixon	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
I	O
advertised	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
a	O
friend	O
's	O
house	O
.	O
Miss	O
Day	O
brought	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
to	O
ask	O
my	O
opinion	O
of	O
it	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
Sunday	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
lost	O
it	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
she	O
here	O
?	O
A.	O
Dixon	O
.	O
She	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
Frank	B-pers
Rotchford	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Russel-court	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
brought	O
one	O
piece	O
,	O
and	O
Maria	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
another	O
,	O
of	O
minionet	O
lace	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
in	O
pledge	O
,	O
one	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
the	O
29th	O
.	O
Maria	B-pers
Rogers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Strand	O
lane	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
.	O
This	O
day	O
three	O
weeks	O
,	O
about	O
3	O
or	O
4	O
o'clock	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
and	O
desired	O
me	O
to	O
pawn	O
it	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
did	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Rotchford	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
?	O
M.	O
Rogers	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
before	O
.	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Strand-lane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
there	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
here	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
said	O
he	O
,	O
can	O
I	O
dine	O
here	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
;	O
this	O
was	O
about	O
1	O
o'clock	O
this	O
day	O
three	O
weeks	O
;	O
he	O
wanted	O
me	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
pawn	O
this	O
lace	O
,	O
after	O
the	O
other	O
was	O
gone	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
pawned	O
it	O
for	O
half	O
a	O
guinea	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
company	O
with	O
both	O
these	O
ladies	O
I	O
confess	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Hunt	I-pers
.	O
Mrs.	O
Dixon	O
applied	O
to	O
where	O
I	O
live	O
to	O
have	O
the	O
lace	O
advertised	O
,	O
to	O
be	O
brought	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
Mr.	O
Rotchford	O
brought	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
and	O
got	O
warrants	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
women	O
that	O
pawned	O
the	O
lace	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
's	O
room	O
,	O
she	O
took	O
two	O
duplicates	O
out	O
of	O
a	O
chest	O
of	O
drawers	O
,	O
which	O
is	O
what	O
the	O
pawnbrokers	O
deliver	O
to	O
persons	O
that	O
pledge	O
goods	O
,	O
by	O
which	O
means	O
we	O
found	O
another	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
pawned	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
.	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
2	O
yards	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
lace	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
the	O
Strand	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
about	O
2	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
A.	O
Davis	O
.	O
How	O
many	O
pieces	O
did	O
you	O
pawn	O
for	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
A.	O
Davis	O
.	O
I	O
pawned	O
three	O
in	O
the	O
whole	O
;	O
I	O
pawned	O
that	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
.	O
Margaret	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
Mrs.	O
Dixon	O
.	O
On	O
Tuesday	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Parlour	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
our	O
shop	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
on	O
Wednesday	O
when	O
he	O
came	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
been	O
gone	O
above	O
10	O
minutes	O
before	O
we	O
missed	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
lace	O
.	O
Q	O
to	O
A.	O
Dixon	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
day	O
did	O
you	O
miss	O
the	O
lace	O
?	O
A.	O
Dixon	O
.	O
I	O
missed	O
it	O
on	O
the	O
Wednesday	O
about	O
1	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
much	O
was	O
there	O
of	O
it	O
?	O
A.	O
Dixon	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
12	O
yards	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
pieces	O
of	O
lace	O
produced	O
and	O
measured	O
,	O
it	O
wanted	O
five	O
inches	O
in	O
length	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
nothing	O
of	O
what	O
they	O
lay	O
to	O
my	O
charge	O
,	O
I	O
gave	O
the	O
women	O
no	O
lace	O
to	O
pawn	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
great	O
way	O
from	O
home	O
,	O
the	O
nearest	O
friend	O
I	O
have	O
is	O
in	O
Bristol	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
body	O
to	O
speak	O
for	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
brother	O
,	O
was	O
he	O
here	O
there	O
is	O
no	O
difference	O
in	O
us	O
than	O
the	O
cloaths	O
,	O
we	O
are	O
so	O
much	O
alike	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
There	O
were	O
two	O
other	O
indictments	O
against	O
him	O
.	O
476	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assuming	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
character	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
.	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
receive	O
his	O
wages	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
for	O
service	O
done	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Tyger	O
,	O
Sept.	O
17	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Habbord	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
principle	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
treasurer	O
of	O
the	O
navy	O
;	O
there	O
is	O
wages	O
due	O
to	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
for	O
95	O
months	O
and	O
3	O
weeks	O
;	O
on	O
the	O
17th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
of	O
the	O
ship	O
Tyger	O
:	O
We	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
name	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
and	O
answered	O
all	O
the	O
questions	O
we	O
usually	O
ask	O
,	O
as	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
served	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
when	O
entered	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
mustered	O
before	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
,	O
very	O
exactly	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
came	O
you	O
to	O
know	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
the	O
person	O
?	O
Hubbord	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
note	O
sent	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
that	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
would	O
apply	O
for	O
the	O
wages	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
and	O
that	O
his	O
right	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
that	O
put	O
us	O
upon	O
our	O
guard	O
;	O
then	O
that	O
ship	O
was	O
call	O
'd	O
next	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
detect	O
him	O
,	O
a	O
constable	O
was	O
sent	O
for	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
apprehended	O
immediately	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
asked	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
on	O
board	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
lame	O
thumb	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
told	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
said	O
he	O
came	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
wages	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
by	O
letter	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
and	O
felt	O
in	O
his	O
pocket	O
but	O
produced	O
none	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
left	O
it	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Elizabeth	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
had	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
three	O
days	O
before	O
he	O
died	O
,	O
I	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
her	O
at	O
Madrass	O
.	O
Hubbord	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
that	O
served	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Tyger	O
,	O
which	O
appeared	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
was	O
discharged	O
the	O
same	O
day	O
Bond	O
was	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
wages	O
is	O
now	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
.	O
George	B-pers
Wilson	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
applied	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
sell	O
some	O
wages	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Drake	B-pers
Indiaman	I-pers
.	O
I	O
bought	O
it	O
of	O
him	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
apply	O
'd	O
to	O
me	O
to	O
see	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
his	O
money	O
for	O
the	O
Tyger	O
;	O
when	O
he	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
office	O
he	O
went	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
;	O
I	O
took	O
him	O
into	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
meaning	O
of	O
his	O
changing	O
his	O
name	O
to	O
Bond	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
ran	O
away	O
from	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
,	O
fearing	O
to	O
be	O
whipp	O
'd	O
from	O
ship	O
to	O
ship	O
,	O
on	O
which	O
account	O
he	O
alter	O
'd	O
his	O
name	O
:	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
all	O
the	O
advice	O
I	O
could	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
great	O
danger	O
to	O
him	O
if	O
it	O
was	O
not	O
true	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
men	O
that	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
Tyger	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
knew	O
him	O
to	O
be	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
,	O
he	O
is	O
here	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
he	O
told	O
you	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Bond	O
,	O
did	O
he	O
tell	O
you	O
what	O
he	O
intended	O
to	O
do	O
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
word	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
and	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
of	O
money	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
about	O
seven	O
years	O
wages	O
.	O
Hugh	B-pers
Carr	I-pers
.	O
I	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Tyger	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
seven	O
years	O
and	O
odd	O
months	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
Tyger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
name	O
did	O
he	O
go	O
by	O
on	O
board	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
;	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
there	O
above	O
half	O
the	O
time	O
or	O
quite	O
so	O
much	O
as	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
go	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
name	O
than	O
that	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
on	O
board	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
England	O
in	O
the	O
Tyger	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
serve	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
time	O
John	B-pers
Dean	I-pers
did	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
he	O
now	O
?	O
Carr	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
is	O
now	O
in	O
India	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
my	O
Indiaman	O
's	O
wages	O
;	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
I	O
might	O
get	O
the	O
man	O
of	O
war	O
's	O
money	O
very	O
easily	O
;	O
he	O
offered	O
me	O
an	O
hundred	O
guineas	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
comply	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
for	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
due	O
both	O
in	O
my	O
own	O
name	O
and	O
that	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
;	O
after	O
he	O
found	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
comply	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
if	O
I	O
went	O
after	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
should	O
get	O
myself	O
into	O
trouble	O
.	O
The	O
day	O
after	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
receive	O
it	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Wilson	O
came	O
there	O
and	O
swore	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
taking	O
money	O
in	O
another	O
man	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
immediately	O
apprehended	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
a	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
,	O
and	O
when	O
I	O
came	O
from	O
on	O
board	O
at	O
Madrass	O
,	O
I	O
left	O
it	O
on	O
board	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
Wilson	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
mention	O
his	O
having	O
a	O
power	O
of	O
attorney	O
from	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
?	O
Wilson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
neither	O
did	O
he	O
converse	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
wages	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
477	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Jourdan	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
8	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Oct.	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
478	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Brooks	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
14	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
6	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Oct.	O
3	O
.	O
++	O
James	B-pers
Taylor	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
3d	O
of	O
October	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
on	O
Ralph	B-place
's	I-place
Key	I-place
,	O
William	B-pers
Cramp	I-pers
came	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
our	O
warehouse	O
loaded	O
with	O
sugar	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
walking	O
up	O
the	O
gateway	O
with	O
his	O
coat	O
taken	O
off	O
his	O
back	O
and	O
wrapt	O
up	O
with	O
a	O
bundle	O
in	O
it	O
under	O
his	O
arm	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
and	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
15	O
lb	O
.	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
of	O
sugar	O
,	O
apron	O
and	O
all	O
;	O
he	O
walked	O
very	O
well	O
up	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
brought	O
him	O
down	O
again	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
liquor	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Had	O
he	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Taylor	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
not	O
that	O
day	O
;	O
he	O
occasionally	O
had	O
worked	O
there	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Cramp	I-pers
confirmed	O
the	O
account	O
he	O
had	O
given	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
479	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Alexander	B-pers
Ross	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
6	O
lb	O
.	O
weight	O
of	O
potash	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
persons	O
unknown	O
,	O
Oct.	O
7	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Andrews	I-pers
.	O
There	O
was	O
some	O
potash	O
left	O
under	O
my	O
care	O
upon	O
the	O
Key	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
porter	O
employed	O
by	O
masters	O
of	O
vessels	O
to	O
take	O
care	O
of	O
what	O
is	O
landed	O
from	O
their	O
vessels	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
them	O
home	O
to	O
the	O
merchants	O
houses	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
,	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
the	O
prisoner	O
very	O
busy	O
,	O
and	O
detected	O
him	O
with	O
his	O
two	O
pockets	O
full	O
of	O
potash	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
12	O
lb	O
.	O
there	O
was	O
a	O
hogshead	O
of	O
potash	O
open	O
,	O
and	O
upon	O
examining	O
it	O
found	O
betwixt	O
2	O
and	O
300	O
weight	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
A	O
young	O
man	O
was	O
taking	O
some	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
to	O
wash	O
dirty	O
aprons	O
in	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
being	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
took	O
some	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
good	O
for	O
.	O
For	O
the	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Elmore	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
the	O
Bedford	O
,	O
a	O
60	O
gun	O
ship	O
,	O
he	O
behaved	O
well	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
discharged	O
just	O
before	O
last	O
Christmas	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
480	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Benjamin	B-pers
Calvot	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Hardwick	B-pers
Constantine	I-pers
,	O
October	O
10	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
481	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
George	B-pers
Pawley	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
linnen	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
10	O
d.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Highfield	I-pers
,	O
October	O
4	O
.	O
+	O
John	B-pers
Highfield	I-pers
.	O
About	O
5	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
4th	O
of	O
October	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
coming	O
from	O
Somerset	O
coffee-house	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
,	O
about	O
five	O
yards	O
on	O
this	O
side	O
Temple	B-place
bar	I-place
I	O
felt	O
a	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
snatch	O
at	O
my	O
pocket	O
,	O
I	O
turned	O
round	O
,	O
and	O
laid	O
hold	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
collar	O
,	O
(	O
I	O
had	O
passed	O
by	O
him	O
about	O
three	O
yards	O
)	O
and	O
said	O
I	O
believed	O
he	O
had	O
got	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
his	O
own	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
up	O
against	O
a	O
door	O
about	O
a	O
yard	O
farther	O
;	O
I	O
called	O
my	O
acquaintance	O
back	O
,	O
and	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
dropped	O
my	O
handkerchief	O
behind	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
by	O
mistake	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Rotation-office	O
,	O
in	O
Litchfield-street	O
,	O
before	O
Justice	O
Cox	O
,	O
and	O
others	O
,	O
not	O
knowing	O
the	O
fact	O
was	O
done	O
in	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
London	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
As	O
I	O
found	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
I	O
thought	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
property	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
very	O
much	O
flurried	O
when	O
he	O
laid	O
hold	O
on	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
mob	O
gathered	O
round	O
me	O
,	O
so	O
I	O
took	O
and	O
flung	O
the	O
handkerchief	O
away	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
482	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
William	B-pers
Bobington	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
cart	O
loads	O
of	O
dung	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
4	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
Bond	I-pers
,	O
July	O
15	O
.	O
+	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
483	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Joseph	B-pers
Stride	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
six	O
silver	O
tea-spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
d.	O
and	O
two	O
silver	O
table	O
spoons	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Battey	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
;	O
two	O
pieces	O
of	O
silk	O
containing	O
two	O
yards	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
8	O
s.	O
one	O
silk	O
gown	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
snuff-box	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
two	O
sheets	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
6	O
s.	O
one	O
silver	O
table	O
spoon	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
3	O
s.	O
and	O
five	O
linnen	O
shifts	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
20	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
one	O
silk	O
cardinal	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
5	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Fethergee	I-pers
,	O
widow	O
;	O
one	O
solitaire	O
cross	O
set	O
with	O
diamonds	O
and	O
green	O
stones	O
,	O
ten	O
silk	O
mantles	O
,	O
eleven	O
linnen	O
table-cloths	O
,	O
eleven	O
linnen	O
napkins	O
,	O
two	O
linnen	O
pillowbiers	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
coat	O
laced	O
with	O
gold	O
,	O
a	O
cloath	O
coat	O
,	O
a	O
cloth	O
waistcoat	O
,	O
two	O
diamond	O
lockets	O
,	O
and	O
three	O
gold	O
rings	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
the	O
honourable	O
Henry	B-pers
Fane	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
Henry	B-pers
Fane	I-pers
,	O
Esq	O
.	O
June	O
23	O
.	O
+	O
Ann	B-pers
Clark	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
house-keeper	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fane	O
,	O
in	O
Shakespear-street	B-place
,	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
were	O
lost	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
William	B-pers
Warrey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Spencer	O
,	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
,	O
an	O
old-cloaths-man	O
,	O
name	O
Patrick	B-pers
Keney	I-pers
,	O
brought	O
two	O
table-cloths	O
and	O
two	O
napkins	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
lady	O
,	O
he	O
agreed	O
to	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
to	O
that	O
lady	O
;	O
I	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
a	O
friend	O
of	O
his	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
they	O
both	O
acknowledged	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
a	O
man	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
he	O
brought	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
to	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
bought	O
them	O
of	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
old	O
cloaths-man	O
here	O
?	O
Warren	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
not	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
confessed	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
his	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
sold	O
them	O
to	O
the	O
old	O
cloaths-man	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
A.	O
Clark	O
,	O
as	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Mr	O
.	O
Fane	O
.	O
)	O
David	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
was	O
present	O
at	O
the	O
searching	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
lodgings	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
a	O
couple	O
of	O
pocket	O
flaps	O
to	O
a	O
coat	O
,	O
which	O
I	O
made	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Fane	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
master	O
was	O
with	O
us	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
carpenter	O
.	O
(	O
A	O
trunk	O
produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
trunk	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
taken	O
out	O
of	O
it	O
two	O
table	O
cloths	O
,	O
two	O
snuff-boxes	O
,	O
six	O
napkins	O
,	O
two	O
pocket	O
flaps	O
;	O
a	O
table-cloth	O
,	O
a	O
sheet	O
,	O
a	O
key	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Fane	O
's	O
name	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
a	O
pocket-book	O
,	O
an	O
apron	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
a	O
gown	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
parcel	O
of	O
linnen	O
,	O
which	O
were	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
cockloft	O
next	O
door	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fane	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
where	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
work	O
.	O
(	O
Deposed	O
to	O
by	O
A.	O
Clark	O
,	O
mentioning	O
the	O
respective	O
owners	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
servant	O
to	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
in	O
Germain-street	O
,	O
St.	O
Giles	O
's	O
,	O
I	O
took	O
in	O
five	O
shifts	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
on	O
the	O
10th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
A.	O
Clark	O
as	O
her	O
own	O
property	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
left	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Fane	O
's	O
house	O
when	O
the	O
family	O
went	O
out	O
of	O
town	O
)	O
.	O
Dennis	B-pers
Jacob	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
silversmith	O
's	O
shop	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
coming	O
to	O
my	O
shop	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
times	O
with	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
some	O
gold	O
lace	O
,	O
what	O
he	O
brought	O
I	O
bought	O
of	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
meited	O
them	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
disposed	O
of	O
them	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
there	O
any	O
crest	O
or	O
arms	O
on	O
the	O
spoons	O
,	O
or	O
any	O
mark	O
on	O
them	O
?	O
Jacob	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
crest	O
or	O
arms	O
?	O
Jacob	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Nor	O
no	O
mark	O
?	O
Jacob	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
as	O
I	O
know	O
of	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Was	O
the	O
lace	O
burnt	O
or	O
unburnt	O
?	O
Jacob	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
unburnt	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
did	O
he	O
bring	O
them	O
?	O
Jacob	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
the	O
days	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
before	O
Jacob	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
seemed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
do	O
you	O
live	O
?	O
Jacob	O
.	O
I	O
live	O
at	O
Charing-cross	O
.	O
Q.	O
to	O
A.	O
Clark	O
.	O
How	O
were	O
your	O
master	O
's	O
spoons	O
marked	O
?	O
A.	O
Clark	O
.	O
They	O
had	O
a	O
crest	O
on	O
them	O
,	O
mine	O
was	O
marked	O
A.	O
C.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
sold	O
three	O
gold	O
rings	O
to	O
Jacob	O
.	O
Jacob	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
recollect	O
that	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
did	O
you	O
give	O
him	O
per	O
ounce	O
?	O
Jacob	O
.	O
I	O
remember	O
giving	O
him	O
5	O
s.	O
and	O
3	O
d.	O
an	O
ounce	O
.	O
William	B-pers
Covey	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
table	O
spoon	O
to	O
pawn	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Coventry-court	O
,	O
the	O
spoons	O
and	O
sheets	O
have	O
A.	O
C.	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
sheets	O
were	O
his	O
mother	O
's	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
A.	O
Clark	O
as	O
her	O
own	O
property	O
.	O
)	O
Thomas	B-pers
Harper	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
five	O
search-warrants	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
all	O
these	O
goods	O
produced	O
here	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Horton	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Coventry-court	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
a	O
shagreen	O
case	O
,	O
a	O
solitaire	O
cross	O
,	O
a	O
silver	O
spoon	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
silver	O
tea-tongs	O
,	O
a	O
gown	O
,	O
a	O
cardinal	O
,	O
two	O
table-cloaths	O
,	O
three	O
napkins	O
,	O
a	O
pillowbier	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
mantle	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
in	O
court	O
)	O
A.	O
Clark	O
.	O
The	O
solitaire	O
cross	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
christening	O
mantle	O
is	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
,	O
the	O
spoons	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Sarah	B-pers
Bailey	I-pers
,	O
she	O
has	O
lived	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Fane	O
some	O
years	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
things	O
are	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Susanna	B-pers
Fethergee	I-pers
.	O
David	B-pers
Rice	I-pers
.	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
prisoner	O
say	O
,	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
,	O
that	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Fane	O
's	O
house	O
himself	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
at	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
garret	O
window	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
they	O
were	O
Mr.	O
Fane	O
's	O
goods	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
owned	O
I	O
pawned	O
some	O
and	O
sold	O
some	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
that	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
;	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
say	O
I	O
took	O
them	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
,	O
for	O
no	O
body	O
could	O
see	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
am	O
sure	O
I	O
found	O
them	O
on	O
the	O
flat	O
at	O
the	O
next	O
door	O
.	O
To	O
his	O
Character	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Pinkney	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
was	O
apprentice	O
to	O
my	O
father	O
,	O
who	O
is	O
dead	O
,	O
he	O
now	O
serves	O
me	O
,	O
he	O
wants	O
thirteen	O
months	O
to	O
be	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
time	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
he	O
?	O
Pinkney	O
.	O
He	O
is	O
something	O
more	O
than	O
twenty	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
general	O
character	O
?	O
Pinkney	O
.	O
His	O
general	O
character	O
was	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
esteemed	O
a	O
very	O
honest	O
man	O
,	O
I	O
know	O
no	O
dishonesty	O
by	O
him	O
before	O
this	O
fact	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
484	O
.	O
(	O
M	O
)	O
Susanna	B-pers
,	I-pers
wife	I-pers
of	I-pers
William	I-pers
Tully	I-pers
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
looking-glass	O
in	O
a	O
Japan	O
frame	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
one	O
copper	O
pot	O
,	O
value	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
brass	O
pot	O
,	O
val	O
.	O
2	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
linnen	O
sheets	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
two	O
blankets	O
,	O
value	O
4	O
s.	O
one	O
bolster	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
iron	O
poker	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
iron	O
tongs	O
,	O
value	O
1	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
William	B-pers
Chaplin	I-pers
,	O
the	O
same	O
being	O
in	O
a	O
certain	O
lodging-room	O
let	O
by	O
contract	O
,	O
&	O
c.	O
Oct.	O
15	O
.	O
||	O
Mary	B-pers
Chaplin	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
at	O
my	O
house	O
before	O
I	O
married	O
my	O
husband	O
,	O
I	O
let	O
her	O
the	O
lodging	O
,	O
she	O
will	O
have	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
lodging	O
fourteen	O
months	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
;	O
she	O
came	O
as	O
a	O
married	O
woman	O
,	O
her	O
husband	O
is	O
in	O
the	O
merchants	O
service	O
at	O
sea	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
a	O
parlour	O
ready-furnished	O
.	O
Last	O
Monday	O
I	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
.	O
(	O
Mentioning	O
them	O
by	O
name	O
.	O
)	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
Saturday	O
before	O
on	O
another	O
account	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
the	O
key	O
of	O
her	O
lodging	O
,	O
my	O
husband	O
went	O
to	O
her	O
in	O
the	O
Round-house	O
and	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
into	O
her	O
room	O
and	O
missed	O
the	O
things	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
own	O
I	O
pledged	O
the	O
things	O
,	O
Mrs.	O
Chaplin	O
knew	O
of	O
part	O
of	O
them	O
being	O
pawned	O
six	O
months	O
before	O
.	O
M.	O
Chaplin	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
till	O
Monday	O
morning	O
only	O
of	O
the	O
copper	O
pot	O
,	O
that	O
I	O
believe	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
about	O
a	O
month	O
before	O
,	O
she	O
said	O
she	O
would	O
bring	O
it	O
again	O
.	O
Jos	O
.	O
Packer	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
pawnbroker	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
sheets	O
and	O
a	O
brass	O
pottage-pot	O
at	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
sheets	O
last	O
December	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
pot	O
last	O
April	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutrix	O
.	O
)	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
long	O
have	O
you	O
been	O
married	O
?	O
M.	O
Chaplin	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
been	O
married	O
four	O
months	O
the	O
26th	O
of	O
this	O
instant	O
.	O
Court	O
.	O
Then	O
these	O
could	O
not	O
be	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
your	O
husband	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
stolen	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Swinton	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
pawned	O
a	O
small	O
pottage-pot	O
,	O
a	O
pair	O
of	O
tongs	O
and	O
poker	O
,	O
with	O
me	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
When	O
?	O
Swinton	O
.	O
Not	O
above	O
a	O
fortnight	O
ago	O
.	O
(	O
Produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
deny	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
it	O
with	O
no	O
intention	O
to	O
injure	O
them	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
485	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Samuel	B-pers
Slingsby	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
pair	O
of	O
silk	O
stockings	O
,	O
value	O
7	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Charles	B-pers
Wood	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
15	O
.	O
||	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
486	O
,	O
487	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Alsop	I-pers
and	O
Charles	B-pers
Moss	I-pers
were	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
one	O
silver	O
buckle	O
set	O
with	O
paste	O
,	O
value	O
21	O
s.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
,	O
Oct.	O
13	O
.	O
||	O
John	B-pers
Holland	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
a	O
silversmith	O
,	O
and	O
live	O
in	O
Bishopsgate-street	B-place
.	O
About	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
a	O
silver	O
paste	O
buckle	O
was	O
forced	O
out	O
of	O
my	O
shew-glass	O
.	O
Robert	B-pers
Jones	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
apprentice	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Holland	O
.	O
Edward	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
the	O
evidence	O
had	O
a	O
wire	O
bent	O
at	O
both	O
ends	O
,	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
were	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
leaning	O
over	O
the	O
glass-case	O
while	O
Spencer	O
with	O
the	O
wire	O
pulled	O
out	O
a	O
paste	O
buckle	O
,	O
it	O
fell	O
down	O
to	O
the	O
ground	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
in	O
the	O
shop	O
looking	O
at	O
them	O
all	O
the	O
while	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
Spencer	O
into	O
the	O
shop	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
out	O
and	O
ran	O
off	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
again	O
in	O
Whitechappel	O
,	O
then	O
he	O
turned	O
evidence	O
,	O
and	O
his	O
friends	O
took	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
.	O
(	O
The	O
buckle	O
produced	O
in	O
Court	O
.	O
)	O
Edward	B-pers
Spencer	I-pers
.	O
On	O
the	O
13th	O
of	O
September	O
the	O
two	O
prisoners	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
Thomas	B-pers
Simonds	I-pers
,	O
set	O
out	O
together	O
,	O
Simonds	O
left	O
us	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
we	O
went	O
to	O
Bishopsgate-street	O
,	O
where	O
Moss	O
and	O
Alsop	O
agreed	O
to	O
change	O
coats	O
,	O
Alsop	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
at	O
the	O
gentleman	O
's	O
shop	O
before	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
should	O
know	O
him	O
when	O
we	O
came	O
to	O
it	O
;	O
he	O
gave	O
me	O
a	O
wire	O
,	O
I	O
plucked	O
one	O
buckle	O
out	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
came	O
out	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
ran	O
away	O
when	O
I	O
was	O
catched	O
.	O
The	O
prisoners	O
denied	O
the	O
fact	O
.	O
Moss	O
called	O
Mr.	O
Bridges	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Norris	O
,	O
who	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
good	O
character	O
.	O
Both	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Alsop	O
T	O
.	O
Moss	O
B	O
.	O
488	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Darby	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assuming	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
character	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
,	O
a	O
mariner	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Dragon	O
,	O
with	O
intent	O
to	O
get	O
possession	O
of	O
prize-money	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
on	O
board	O
,	O
July	O
7	O
.	O
*	O
Mr.	O
Robinson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
Mr.	O
James	B-pers
Dixon	I-pers
,	O
who	O
is	O
agent	O
for	O
the	O
ship	O
Dragon	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
7th	O
of	O
July	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
to	O
the	O
King	B-place
's	I-place
Head-tavern	I-place
,	I-place
in	I-place
Fenchurch-street	I-place
,	O
and	O
demanded	O
the	O
prize-money	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Campbel	I-pers
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Who	O
did	O
he	O
demand	O
it	O
of	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
He	O
demanded	O
it	O
of	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
paying	O
it	O
for	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
.	O
I	O
looked	O
on	O
the	O
list	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
John	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
rated	O
an	O
able	O
seaman	O
,	O
the	O
first	O
payment	O
was	O
2	O
l.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
how	O
long	O
he	O
had	O
belonged	O
to	O
that	O
ship	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
a	O
year	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
his	O
captain	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
captain	O
Harvey	O
,	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
any	O
of	O
the	O
lieutenants	O
were	O
stain	O
at	O
the	O
Havanna	O
,	O
and	O
their	O
names	O
;	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
know	O
either	O
of	O
their	O
names	O
;	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
answer	O
any	O
other	O
question	O
that	O
was	O
asked	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
he	O
was	O
come	O
to	O
receive	O
money	O
falsly	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
would	O
send	O
for	O
the	O
constable	O
,	O
and	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
but	O
confessed	O
he	O
was	O
put	O
on	O
to	O
do	O
it	O
by	O
one	O
that	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
ship	O
,	O
name	O
John	B-pers
Rearden	I-pers
.	O
I	O
looked	O
in	O
the	O
prize-list	O
and	O
found	O
that	O
name	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
brought	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
tavern	O
,	O
and	O
bid	O
him	O
ask	O
for	O
the	O
prize-money	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
if	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
asked	O
any	O
questions	O
,	O
what	O
was	O
his	O
captain	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
to	O
say	O
,	O
captain	O
Harvey	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
Rearden	O
was	O
waiting	O
at	O
the	O
tavern	O
door	O
till	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
again	O
;	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
his	O
dress	O
,	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
but	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
any	O
such	O
person	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
two	O
or	O
three	O
hu	O
ndred	O
seamen	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
impossible	O
to	O
find	O
him	O
out	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Dixon	O
came	O
in	O
the	O
mean	O
time	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
I	O
had	O
told	O
him	O
the	O
affair	O
he	O
sent	O
for	O
a	O
constable	O
and	O
he	O
was	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
Mansion-house	O
,	O
there	O
he	O
confessed	O
that	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
Darby	O
Quin	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
was	O
a	O
waiter	O
at	O
a	O
public-house	O
in	O
Berry-street	O
,	O
St.	O
James	O
's	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
this	O
Rearden	O
had	O
used	O
his	O
master	O
's	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
borrowed	O
money	O
of	O
him	O
to	O
the	O
amount	O
of	O
11	O
s.	O
and	O
when	O
he	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
he	O
told	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
would	O
put	O
on	O
his	O
cloaths	O
,	O
and	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
demand	O
the	O
money	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
Campbell	O
that	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
him	O
half	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
money	O
this	O
Rearden	O
was	O
to	O
have	O
.	O
I	O
do	O
believe	O
the	O
boy	O
was	O
imposed	O
upon	O
by	O
Reanden	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
a	O
real	O
stranger	O
to	O
what	O
he	O
was	O
about	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
How	O
old	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
?	O
Robinson	O
.	O
About	O
17	O
years	O
of	O
age	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
lent	O
Rearden	O
12	O
or	O
13	O
s.	O
he	O
told	O
me	O
.	O
when	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
for	O
it	O
,	O
If	O
I	O
would	O
do	O
him	O
one	O
favour	O
he	O
would	O
pay	O
me	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
,	O
to	O
go	O
and	O
demand	O
prize-money	O
in	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Campbell	I-pers
.	O
When	O
I	O
came	O
there	O
the	O
gentleman	O
asked	O
me	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
said	O
captain	O
Harvey	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
what	O
he	O
bid	O
me	O
say	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
knew	O
nothing	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
Rearden	O
lives	O
at	O
my	O
master	O
's	O
still	O
;	O
my	O
master	O
will	O
not	O
take	O
him	O
up	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
owes	O
my	O
master	O
twenty-eight	O
shillings	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
489	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Peter	B-pers
Gatlett	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
15	O
silver	O
spoons	O
,	O
value	O
6	O
l.	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
John	B-pers
Mignot	I-pers
,	O
in	O
the	O
dwelling-house	O
of	O
the	O
said	O
John	O
,	O
Sept.	O
19	O
.	O
++	O
John	B-pers
Mignot	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
King-street	B-place
,	I-place
Seven	I-place
Dials	I-place
.	O
I	O
lost	O
15	O
silver	O
spoons	O
on	O
the	O
19th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
about	O
2	O
o'clock	O
,	O
from	O
my	O
bar	O
,	O
I	O
keep	O
a	O
public	O
house	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
lodged	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
but	O
was	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
house	O
the	O
day	O
I	O
lost	O
them	O
,	O
nor	O
for	O
6	O
weeks	O
before	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Have	O
you	O
got	O
any	O
of	O
your	O
spoons	O
again	O
?	O
Mignot	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
but	O
four	O
of	O
them	O
again	O
,	O
two	O
of	O
them	O
were	O
given	O
me	O
by	O
a	O
constable	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
not	O
know	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
them	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Conyers	I-pers
.	O
I	O
live	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Gunston	O
,	O
a	O
Pawnbroker	O
,	O
at	O
the	O
corner	O
of	O
Derby-Court	O
,	O
in	O
Jermain-street	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
brought	O
me	O
some	O
spoons	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
stopt	O
them	O
,	O
(	O
some	O
silver	O
spoons	O
broke	O
in	O
the	O
handles	O
produced	O
)	O
these	O
are	O
them	O
.	O
(	O
Two	O
of	O
them	O
deposed	O
to	O
by	O
the	O
prosecutor	O
.	O
)	O
Conyers	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
English	O
,	O
he	O
is	O
a	O
Frenchman	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
a	O
piece	O
of	O
paper	O
,	O
letting	O
him	O
know	O
if	O
he	O
could	O
bring	O
any	O
body	O
that	O
could	O
prove	O
them	O
his	O
property	O
he	O
should	O
have	O
them	O
again	O
;	O
he	O
went	O
away	O
,	O
and	O
never	O
came	O
back	O
again	O
.	O
Acquitted	O
.	O
490	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
John	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
that	O
he	O
having	O
in	O
his	O
custody	O
a	O
certain	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
name	O
John	B-pers
Parnell	I-pers
thereunto	O
subscribed	O
,	O
bearing	O
date	O
the	O
6th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
1763	O
,	O
directed	O
to	O
John	B-pers
Puget	I-pers
,	O
merchant	O
,	O
to	O
which	O
he	O
forged	O
an	O
acceptance	O
in	O
the	O
words	O
following	O
:	O
``	O
Pay	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
in	O
six	O
days	O
.	O
J.	O
Puget	O
,	O
''	O
and	O
for	O
publishing	O
the	O
same	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
Lawrence	B-pers
Quin	I-pers
;	O
it	O
was	O
likewise	O
laid	O
to	O
be	O
done	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
defraud	O
the	O
governors	B-pers
and	I-pers
company	I-pers
of	I-pers
the	I-pers
Bank	I-pers
of	I-pers
England	I-pers
,	O
September	O
30	O
.	O
*	O
Charles	B-pers
Jewson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
the	O
principal	O
in	O
the	O
drawing	O
office	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
on	O
the	O
30th	O
of	O
Sept.	O
last	O
this	O
bill	O
(	O
producing	O
a	O
bill	O
of	O
exchange	O
)	O
was	O
brought	O
to	O
me	O
by	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
,	O
on	O
my	O
seeing	O
the	O
bill	O
I	O
immediately	O
perceived	O
it	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
counterfeit	O
,	O
I	O
pretended	O
to	O
look	O
on	O
the	O
file	O
for	O
an	O
order	O
,	O
knowing	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
there	O
could	O
be	O
none	O
;	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
there	O
was	O
no	O
order	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
I	O
thought	O
Mr.	O
Puget	O
had	O
made	O
a	O
mistake	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
forgot	O
to	O
give	O
an	O
order	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
with	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Puget	O
,	O
and	O
found	O
him	O
in	O
his	O
compting-house	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
him	O
I	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
bill	O
which	O
I	O
believed	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
forgery	O
,	O
it	O
not	O
being	O
his	O
hand	O
writing	O
.	O
Stevens	O
was	O
called	O
in	O
,	O
he	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
who	O
he	O
lived	O
with	O
,	O
and	O
how	O
he	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
;	O
it	O
was	O
thought	O
proper	O
to	O
detain	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
till	O
we	O
could	O
be	O
better	O
informed	O
,	O
and	O
in	O
the	O
afternoon	O
Mr.	O
Puget	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Brown	O
,	O
his	O
clerk	O
,	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
went	O
to	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Fielding	I-pers
,	O
and	O
acquainted	O
him	O
with	O
the	O
affair	O
,	O
he	O
immediately	O
issued	O
a	O
warrant	O
to	O
bring	O
the	O
body	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Quin	O
,	O
and	O
also	O
of	O
Broughton	O
if	O
we	O
could	O
,	O
but	O
to	O
be	O
sure	O
to	O
bring	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Broughton	O
was	O
not	O
at	O
home	O
,	O
Quin	O
was	O
brought	O
,	O
and	O
gave	O
an	O
account	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
Broughton	O
,	O
who	O
owed	O
him	O
some	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
lived	O
with	O
him	O
six	O
or	O
seven	O
years	O
off	O
and	O
on	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
acquainted	O
with	O
Mr.	O
Puget	O
's	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Jewson	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
very	O
well	O
acquainted	O
with	O
it	O
;	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Does	O
he	O
keep	O
cash	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
?	O
Jewson	O
.	O
He	O
does	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
Broughton	O
before	O
the	O
Magistrate	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
the	O
bill	O
of	O
Parnell	O
,	O
the	O
drawer	O
of	O
the	O
bill	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
his	O
indorsement	O
upon	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
that	O
he	O
paid	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Quin	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
what	O
he	O
owed	O
him	O
.	O
The	O
bill	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
London	O
,	O
Sept.	O
6	O
,	O
1763	O
.	O
Sir	O
,	O
ten	O
days	O
after	O
``	O
fight	O
please	O
to	O
pay	O
to	O
Mr.	O
John	B-pers
Broughton	I-pers
,	O
``	O
or	O
his	O
order	O
,	O
the	O
sum	O
of	O
49	O
l.	O
sterling	O
,	O
as	O
by	O
``	O
advice	O
from	O
your	O
humble	O
servant	O
,	O
``	O
John	B-pers
Parnell	I-pers
.	O
``	O
To	O
be	O
paid	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
in	O
six	O
days	O
.	O
``	O
J	O
.	O
Puget	O
.	O
''	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
your	O
course	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
where	O
gentlemen	O
keep	O
cash	O
with	O
you	O
?	O
Jewson	O
.	O
We	O
must	O
have	O
an	O
order	O
specified	O
,	O
besides	O
the	O
acceptance	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Whether	O
at	O
a	O
banker	O
's	O
they	O
would	O
have	O
paid	O
upon	O
such	O
acceptance	O
?	O
Jewson	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
irregular	O
;	O
here	O
is	O
no	O
date	O
to	O
the	O
bill	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
Mr.	O
Puget	O
's	O
clerk	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
takes	O
the	O
bill	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
This	O
name	O
,	O
I	O
Puget	O
,	O
is	O
not	O
Mr.	O
Puget	O
's	O
Hand-writing	O
;	O
I	O
have	O
often	O
seen	O
him	O
write	O
.	O
John	B-pers
Stevens	I-pers
.	O
I	O
had	O
this	O
bill	O
of	O
Mr.	O
Quin	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
September	O
,	O
he	O
paid	O
it	O
me	O
in	O
part	O
of	O
payment	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
it	O
endorsed	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Broughton	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
might	O
go	O
and	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
at	O
the	O
Bank	O
when	O
I	O
would	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Broughton	O
after	O
that	O
came	O
along	O
with	O
Mr	O
Quin	O
to	O
our	O
house	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
,	O
I	O
'll	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
you	O
on	O
Thursday	O
;	O
he	O
acknowledged	O
the	O
endorsement	O
on	O
it	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
let	O
us	O
go	O
on	O
the	O
Friday	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
Friday	O
I	O
said	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Broughton	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
ready	O
to	O
go	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
?	O
He	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
should	O
be	O
ready	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
;	O
when	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
not	O
very	O
well	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
gentleman	O
was	O
to	O
call	O
upon	O
him	O
;	O
so	O
I	O
went	O
by	O
myself	O
;	O
I	O
thought	O
the	O
bill	O
was	O
not	O
good	O
,	O
seeing	O
the	O
date	O
was	O
not	O
set	O
properly	O
for	O
the	O
payment	O
.	O
He	O
told	O
me	O
the	O
drawer	O
lived	O
at	O
the	O
Grecian	O
Coffee-house	O
,	O
Temple-Bar	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Jewson	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
order	O
to	O
pay	O
it	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
go	O
along	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Puget	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
;	O
Mr.	O
Puget	O
asked	O
me	O
,	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
it	O
?	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
;	O
then	O
he	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
Grecian	O
Coffee-house	O
to	O
enquire	O
after	O
Mr.	O
Parnell	O
;	O
the	O
person	O
told	O
us	O
there	O
had	O
been	O
such	O
a	O
person	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
was	O
gone	O
to	O
Ireland	O
.	O
They	O
took	O
me	O
back	O
into	O
the	O
city	O
to	O
the	O
Bank	O
,	O
and	O
from	O
thence	O
to	O
Justice	O
Fielding	O
,	O
who	O
examined	O
how	O
I	O
came	O
by	O
the	O
bill	O
;	O
I	O
gave	O
him	O
the	O
same	O
account	O
as	O
before	O
;	O
then	O
we	O
went	O
and	O
brought	O
Mr.	O
Quin	O
before	O
him	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
time	O
did	O
you	O
part	O
with	O
Broughton	O
that	O
morning	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
parted	O
with	O
him	O
between	O
10	O
and	O
11	O
o'clock	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Broughton	O
before	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
I	O
had	O
seen	O
him	O
at	O
Mr.	O
Quin	O
's	O
house	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
as	O
I	O
have	O
gone	O
there	O
about	O
business	O
.	O
Broughton	O
said	O
,	O
Parnell	O
was	O
a	O
relation	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
he	O
say	O
where	O
Parnell	O
liv	O
'd	O
?	O
Stevens	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
.	O
Lawrance	O
Quin	O
.	O
I	O
received	O
this	O
bill	O
of	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
(	O
holding	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
)	O
the	O
minute	O
I	O
got	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
past	O
it	O
to	O
Mr.	O
Stevens	O
as	O
cash	O
;	O
Broughton	O
owed	O
me	O
a	O
great	O
deal	O
more	O
than	O
that	O
.	O
When	O
was	O
this	O
?	O
Quin	O
.	O
This	O
was	O
the	O
28th	O
of	O
last	O
month	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
lodged	O
with	O
me	O
,	O
off	O
and	O
on	O
,	O
6	O
or	O
7	O
years	O
.	O
When	O
this	O
came	O
to	O
be	O
enquired	O
into	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
him	O
till	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
Thames-street	O
,	O
he	O
never	O
came	O
home	O
that	O
night	O
,	O
nor	O
the	O
next	O
night	O
;	O
he	O
was	O
advertised	O
several	O
times	O
;	O
I	O
found	O
him	O
concealed	O
between	O
the	O
bed	O
and	O
the	O
tick	O
.	O
Samuel	B-pers
Copack	I-pers
.	O
I	O
keep	O
the	O
Grecian	O
Coffee-house	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
Mr.	O
Parnell	O
,	O
an	O
Irish	O
gentleman	O
,	O
he	O
frequented	O
my	O
house	O
;	O
he	O
has	O
been	O
gone	O
to	O
Ireland	O
two	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
believe	O
he	O
has	O
not	O
been	O
in	O
England	O
since	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
know	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
?	O
Copack	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
several	O
letters	O
of	O
his	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
this	O
bill	O
.	O
(	O
He	O
takes	O
it	O
in	O
his	O
hand	O
.	O
)	O
Copack	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
this	O
is	O
not	O
like	O
his	O
hand-writing	O
at	O
all	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
have	O
no	O
person	O
to	O
appear	O
for	O
my	O
character	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
491	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Ann	B-pers
Johnson	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
stealing	O
three	O
cotton	O
gowns	O
,	O
value	O
12	O
s.	O
one	O
linnen	O
shift	O
,	O
value	O
3	O
s.	O
seven	O
linnen	O
caps	O
,	O
one	O
muslin	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
two	O
linnen	O
aprons	O
,	O
and	O
one	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
,	O
the	O
property	O
of	O
Comfort	B-pers
Bosely	I-pers
,	O
spinster	O
,	O
Aug.	O
24	O
.	O
||	O
Comfort	O
Bosely	O
.	O
I	O
came	O
out	O
of	O
place	O
on	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
August	O
,	O
and	O
left	O
my	O
cloaths	O
,	O
the	O
things	O
mentioned	O
in	O
the	O
indictment	O
,	O
with	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Church	I-pers
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
missing	O
in	O
about	O
an	O
hour	O
and	O
an	O
half	O
afterwards	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
taken	O
last	O
Saturday	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
my	O
caps	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
,	O
that	O
is	O
all	O
I	O
have	O
got	O
again	O
.	O
She	O
owned	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
a	O
gown	O
and	O
shift	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
but	O
when	O
she	O
came	O
before	O
the	O
Alderman	O
,	O
she	O
denied	O
it	O
again	O
,	O
(	O
the	O
cap	O
produced	O
and	O
deposed	O
to	O
.	O
)	O
Elizabeth	B-pers
Church	I-pers
.	O
The	O
prosecutrix	O
left	O
a	O
bundle	O
with	O
me	O
tied	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
cotton	O
handkerchief	O
;	O
I	O
left	O
the	O
prisoner	O
in	O
my	O
room	O
while	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
market	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
came	O
back	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
the	O
bundle	O
were	O
gone	O
;	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
her	O
till	O
last	O
Saturday	O
,	O
when	O
Sarah	B-pers
Heyd	I-pers
brought	O
her	O
to	O
my	O
lodging	O
.	O
Sarah	B-pers
Heyd	I-pers
I	O
lodge	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
house	O
where	O
Elizabeth	O
Church	O
does	O
.	O
The	O
young	O
woman	O
that	O
the	O
cloaths	O
belong	O
to	O
,	O
went	O
to	O
Billingsgate	O
for	O
some	O
oysters	O
,	O
after	O
that	O
the	O
things	O
were	O
missing	O
.	O
I	O
met	O
with	O
the	O
prisoner	O
last	O
Saturday	O
on	O
Ludgate-hill	O
,	O
and	O
brought	O
her	O
home	O
,	O
with	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
a	O
watchman	O
;	O
I	O
heard	O
her	O
own	O
,	O
she	O
had	O
pawned	O
a	O
dark	O
coloured	O
gown	O
and	O
shift	O
for	O
2	O
s.	O
the	O
cap	O
on	O
her	O
head	O
the	O
young	O
woman	O
swore	O
to	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
bought	O
the	O
cap	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
T	O
.	O
492	O
.	O
(	O
L.	O
)	O
Hugh	B-pers
Maloney	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
assuming	O
the	O
name	O
and	O
character	O
of	O
Elias	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
a	O
seaman	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Warwick	O
,	O
with	O
intention	O
to	O
receive	O
wages	O
due	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
Aug.	O
26	O
.	O
||	O
William	B-pers
Hubord	I-pers
.	O
I	O
am	O
clerk	O
to	O
the	O
treasury	O
of	O
the	O
Navy	O
.	O
There	O
was	O
about	O
ten	O
months	O
wages	O
due	O
to	O
Elias	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
as	O
appears	O
by	O
the	O
pay-books	O
of	O
the	O
Warwick	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
made	O
application	O
for	O
the	O
wages	O
due	O
to	O
Elias	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
Elias	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
he	O
produced	O
a	O
certificate	O
,	O
and	O
answered	O
all	O
the	O
necessary	O
questions	O
usually	O
asked	O
,	O
as	O
,	O
who	O
was	O
mustered	O
before	O
him	O
?	O
and	O
the	O
like	O
.	O
We	O
had	O
received	O
information	O
from	O
Mr.	O
Moxey	O
,	O
that	O
Hugh	B-pers
Maloney	I-pers
intended	O
to	O
be	O
there	O
to	O
receive	O
the	O
wages	O
due	O
to	O
Elias	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
;	O
we	O
did	O
pay	O
him	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
called	O
in	O
Mr.	O
Moxey	O
.	O
then	O
he	O
threw	O
down	O
the	O
money	O
immediately	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
in	O
such	O
a	O
tremble	O
,	O
he	O
could	O
not	O
speak	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
Please	O
to	O
produce	O
the	O
certificate	O
.	O
(	O
It	O
is	O
produced	O
.	O
)	O
Hubord	O
.	O
This	O
I	O
take	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
captain	O
's	O
handwriting	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
produced	O
this	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
read	O
to	O
this	O
purport	O
.	O
``	O
These	O
are	O
to	O
certify	O
the	O
honourable	O
principal	O
``	O
officers	O
and	O
commissioners	O
of	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
``	O
navy	O
,	O
that	O
Elias	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
did	O
belong	O
to	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
``	O
ship	O
the	O
Warwick	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
taken	O
on	O
``	O
the	O
11th	O
of	O
March	O
,	O
1756	O
,	O
after	O
which	O
he	O
was	O
``	O
sent	O
on	O
board	O
a	O
French	O
merchant	O
ship	O
to	O
proceed	O
``	O
in	O
her	O
to	O
France	O
,	O
but	O
was	O
taken	O
by	O
the	O
``	O
St.	O
Andrew	O
privateer	O
belonging	O
to	O
Bristol	O
.	O
``	O
Given	O
under	O
my	O
hand	O
on	O
board	O
his	O
Majesty	O
's	O
``	O
Ship	O
Foudroyant	O
at	O
Spithead	O
.	O
''	O
Signed	O
by	O
the	O
captain	O
.	O
Richard	B-pers
Moxey	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
from	O
the	O
year	O
45	O
,	O
I	O
sail	O
'd	O
with	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
Hampton-Court	O
from	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
that	O
year	O
to	O
the	O
year	O
48	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
his	O
name	O
?	O
Moxey	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Hugh	B-pers
Maloney	I-pers
,	O
he	O
always	O
went	O
by	O
that	O
name	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
never	O
heard	O
him	O
go	O
by	O
any	O
other	O
name	O
till	O
the	O
day	O
he	O
produced	O
this	O
certificate	O
.	O
Some	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
last	O
Aug.	O
he	O
met	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Pay-office-yard	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
me	O
he	O
had	O
wages	O
due	O
from	O
his	O
majesty	O
's	O
ship	O
the	O
Warwick	O
.	O
I	O
asked	O
him	O
where	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
since	O
?	O
how	O
came	O
it	O
you	O
never	O
got	O
your	O
money	O
?	O
he	O
answered	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
in	O
the	O
King	O
's	O
service	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
believed	O
he	O
could	O
get	O
it	O
if	O
I	O
could	O
get	O
the	O
books	O
sent	O
to	O
Broad-street	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
clerk	O
,	O
and	O
desired	O
he	O
would	O
send	O
the	O
Warwick	O
's	O
books	O
for	O
Hugh	B-pers
Maloney	I-pers
;	O
the	O
books	O
were	O
sent	O
,	O
he	O
at	O
this	O
time	O
had	O
got	O
no	O
certificate	O
,	O
they	O
did	O
not	O
pay	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
no	O
more	O
till	O
about	O
the	O
24th	O
of	O
Aug.	O
he	O
then	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
again	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
had	O
been	O
to	O
Portsmouth	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
got	O
a	O
certificate	O
from	O
his	O
captain	O
;	O
I	O
looked	O
into	O
the	O
book	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
his	O
wages	O
were	O
paid	O
ever	O
since	O
the	O
year	O
1758	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Maloney	O
,	O
you	O
are	O
wrong	O
,	O
you	O
come	O
here	O
for	O
me	O
to	O
get	O
the	O
books	O
sent	O
to	O
Broad-street	O
,	O
your	O
wages	O
is	O
paid	O
.	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
my	O
name	O
is	O
not	O
Maloney	O
now	O
.	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
how	O
long	O
has	O
that	O
been	O
?	O
Said	O
he	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
changed	O
my	O
name	O
to	O
Elias	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
and	O
shewed	O
me	O
this	O
certificate	O
;	O
said	O
I	O
,	O
this	O
will	O
not	O
do	O
,	O
your	O
name	O
can	O
not	O
be	O
Hugh	B-pers
Maloney	I-pers
and	O
Elias	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
on	O
board	O
the	O
same	O
ship	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
would	O
I	O
be	O
his	O
friend	O
,	O
and	O
send	O
the	O
books	O
to	O
Broad-street	O
.	O
I	O
told	O
him	O
,	O
no	O
;	O
and	O
so	O
sure	O
as	O
you	O
attempt	O
to	O
receive	O
Elias	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
's	O
wages	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
die	O
for	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
went	O
to	O
the	O
proper	O
clerk	O
,	O
and	O
producing	O
this	O
certificate	O
,	O
got	O
the	O
books	O
sent	O
to	O
Broad-street	O
;	O
I	O
was	O
there	O
a	O
little	O
after	O
8	O
;	O
Maloney	O
came	O
in	O
in	O
the	O
morning	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
me	O
if	O
the	O
Warwick	O
's	O
books	O
were	O
come	O
?	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
and	O
I	O
was	O
afraid	O
too	O
soon	O
for	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
kept	O
his	O
station	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
to	O
get	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
Pay-office	O
;	O
I	O
began	O
to	O
consider	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
letting	O
a	O
man	O
receive	O
wages	O
that	O
he	O
had	O
no	O
right	O
to	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
the	O
Pay-office	O
,	O
and	O
told	O
Sir	O
John	B-pers
Bentley	I-pers
my	O
opinion	O
,	O
and	O
saw	O
Maloney	O
receive	O
the	O
money	O
into	O
his	O
hand	O
;	O
I	O
said	O
,	O
Maloney	O
,	O
what	O
have	O
you	O
done	O
?	O
he	O
then	O
dropped	O
the	O
money	O
,	O
and	O
trembled	O
very	O
much	O
.	O
Here	O
is	O
the	O
Warwick	O
's	O
book	O
,	O
(	O
producing	O
it	O
)	O
here	O
is	O
his	O
name	O
Hugh	B-pers
Maloney	I-pers
in	O
it	O
.	O
James	B-pers
Brown	I-pers
.	O
I	O
served	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Warwick	O
between	O
8	O
and	O
10	O
months	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
her	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
taken	O
in	O
her	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
name	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
His	O
name	O
is	O
Hugh	B-pers
Maloney	I-pers
,	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
no	O
other	O
name	O
on	O
board	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
know	O
Elias	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Warwick	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
is	O
he	O
now	O
?	O
Brown	O
.	O
The	O
last	O
place	O
I	O
saw	O
him	O
was	O
in	O
Antigua	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
West	O
Indies	O
,	O
pretty	O
near	O
seven	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
not	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
since	O
;	O
the	O
prisoner	O
was	O
taken	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
in	O
the	O
Warwick	O
;	O
Elias	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
did	O
belong	O
to	O
the	O
gunner	O
's	O
crew	O
,	O
he	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
forecastle	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Holding	O
.	O
I	O
know	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
,	O
he	O
failed	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
about	O
three	O
years	O
the	O
war	O
before	O
last	O
,	O
his	O
name	O
is	O
Hugh	O
Maloney	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
by	O
no	O
other	O
name	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
along	O
with	O
me	O
with	O
captain	O
Mawson	O
three	O
years	O
;	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
Mr.	O
Moxon	O
was	O
on	O
board	O
the	O
Hampton-court	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
's	O
Defence	O
.	O
I	O
leave	O
it	O
to	O
God	O
and	O
the	O
world	O
.	O
My	O
name	O
is	O
Elias	B-pers
Davis	I-pers
,	O
I	O
was	O
born	O
in	O
Ireland	O
.	O
Guilty	O
.	O
Death	O
.	O
493	O
.	O
(	O
M.	O
)	O
Richard	B-pers
Sinderbury	I-pers
was	O
indicted	O
for	O
the	O
wilful	O
murder	O
of	O
Thomas	B-pers
New	I-pers
;	O
he	O
stood	O
charged	O
with	O
the	O
like	O
murder	O
on	O
the	O
Coroner	O
's	O
inquest	O
,	O
Oct.	O
14	O
.	O
*	O
Adam	B-pers
Robertson	I-pers
.	O
I	O
have	O
known	O
the	O
prisoner	O
at	O
the	O
bar	O
a	O
great	O
many	O
years	O
,	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
any	O
harm	O
by	O
him	O
,	O
only	O
that	O
of	O
getting	O
in	O
liquor	O
,	O
till	O
this	O
happened	O
;	O
that	O
very	O
day	O
that	O
this	O
happened	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
business	O
in	O
Westminster	O
,	O
I	O
live	O
in	O
Bishop's-gate-street	O
,	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
,	O
he	O
was	O
drinking	O
at	O
the	O
Barley-mow	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
called	O
for	O
a	O
pint	O
of	O
beer	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
happened	O
to	O
be	O
drinking	O
in	O
a	O
box	O
with	O
a	O
soldier	O
,	O
I	O
put	O
my	O
pint	O
to	O
their	O
pot	O
,	O
we	O
drank	O
three	O
pots	O
and	O
a	O
pint	O
,	O
we	O
shook	O
hands	O
,	O
and	O
all	O
parted	O
in	O
peace	O
;	O
coming	O
out	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
,	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
Adam	O
,	O
will	O
you	O
go	O
to	O
supper	O
with	O
me	O
?	O
he	O
said	O
,	O
he	O
had	O
three	O
rabbits	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
would	O
smother	O
them	O
with	O
onions	O
.	O
I	O
went	O
with	O
him	O
to	O
his	O
lodgings	O
,	O
and	O
supped	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
his	O
eldest	O
daughter	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
think	O
two	O
more	O
,	O
he	O
put	O
some	O
by	O
for	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
them	O
;	O
after	O
some	O
time	O
his	O
wife	O
came	O
home	O
,	O
and	O
as	O
soon	O
as	O
she	O
came	O
in	O
he	O
went	O
and	O
fetched	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
rabbits	O
,	O
and	O
she	O
eat	O
;	O
sometime	O
after	O
this	O
his	O
wife	O
and	O
he	O
had	O
words	O
together	O
,	O
she	O
struck	O
him	O
several	O
times	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
him	O
very	O
ill	O
;	O
I	O
parted	O
them	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
she	O
got	O
at	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
struck	O
him	O
again	O
several	O
times	O
in	O
the	O
face	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
and	O
sat	O
down	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
,	O
she	O
flew	O
at	O
him	O
again	O
,	O
they	O
were	O
bustling	O
and	O
fighting	O
together	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
,	O
the	O
young	O
fellow	O
,	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
happened	O
to	O
come	O
in	O
,	O
in	O
the	O
God	O
speed	O
;	O
he	O
struck	O
the	O
prisoner	O
once	O
or	O
twice	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
the	O
blows	O
,	O
but	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
the	O
farther	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
house	O
.	O
After	O
he	O
came	O
into	O
the	O
house	O
I	O
sat	O
down	O
,	O
and	O
reasoned	O
the	O
case	O
with	O
him	O
,	O
and	O
asked	O
him	O
if	O
he	O
knew	O
the	O
consequence	O
of	O
striking	O
a	O
man	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
house	O
?	O
he	O
made	O
answer	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
if	O
he	O
does	O
not	O
like	O
this	O
or	O
that	O
I	O
'll	O
give	O
him	O
more	O
to-morrow	O
,	O
or	O
something	O
to	O
that	O
purpose	O
;	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
drank	O
to	O
him	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
never	O
seen	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
life	O
before	O
.	O
The	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
sat	O
between	O
the	O
young	O
man	O
and	O
I	O
,	O
she	O
and	O
he	O
were	O
talking	O
together	O
,	O
the	O
prisoner	O
came	O
in	O
at	O
the	O
door	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
we	O
were	O
talking	O
and	O
drinking	O
,	O
he	O
made	O
a	O
blow	O
at	O
the	O
deceased	O
,	O
and	O
directly	O
he	O
jumped	O
out	O
of	O
his	O
chair	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
he	O
was	O
stabb	O
'd	O
.	O
I	O
jumped	O
up	O
,	O
and	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
my	O
arms	O
,	O
and	O
said	O
,	O
For	O
God	O
or	O
Christ	O
's	O
sake	O
do	O
n't	O
go	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
,	O
and	O
held	O
him	O
fast	O
;	O
he	O
dragged	O
me	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
into	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
down	O
a	O
step	O
or	O
two	O
into	O
the	O
street	O
,	O
and	O
got	O
loose	O
from	O
me	O
,	O
and	O
ran	O
down	O
the	O
street	O
cryi	O
ng	O
he	O
was	O
stabb	O
'd	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
weapon	O
in	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
hand	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
I	O
did	O
not	O
till	O
after	O
the	O
murder	O
was	O
done	O
,	O
I	O
saw	O
it	O
when	O
before	O
the	O
Justice	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Which	O
way	O
did	O
he	O
come	O
to	O
New	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
He	O
came	O
fronting	O
him	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
sitting	O
in	O
a	O
chair	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
space	O
of	O
time	O
might	O
there	O
be	O
between	O
the	O
two	O
blows	O
given	O
in	O
the	O
entry	O
to	O
the	O
prisoner	O
,	O
and	O
this	O
happening	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
I	O
believe	O
it	O
might	O
be	O
four	O
or	O
five	O
minutes	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Where	O
did	O
the	O
prisoner	O
go	O
after	O
them	O
two	O
blows	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
Whether	O
he	O
went	O
out	O
,	O
or	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
As	O
you	O
did	O
not	O
see	O
New	O
strike	O
them	O
two	O
blows	O
,	O
how	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
who	O
gave	O
the	O
blows	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
The	O
deceased	O
gave	O
the	O
blows	O
;	O
I	O
know	O
by	O
the	O
conversation	O
between	O
him	O
and	O
me	O
afterwards	O
;	O
he	O
said	O
he	O
would	O
give	O
him	O
more	O
on	O
the	O
morrow	O
if	O
he	O
did	O
not	O
like	O
that	O
;	O
that	O
was	O
when	O
the	O
prisoner	O
's	O
wife	O
,	O
New	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
were	O
sitting	O
talking	O
together	O
.	O
Prisoner	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
was	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
for	O
five	O
hours	O
.	O
Robertson	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
house	O
while	O
New	O
was	O
there	O
,	O
for	O
the	O
blows	O
that	O
past	O
were	O
in	O
the	O
passage	O
,	O
and	O
after	O
that	O
I	O
never	O
saw	O
him	O
till	O
he	O
came	O
in	O
and	O
did	O
the	O
mischief	O
;	O
Q	O
.	O
What	O
induced	O
the	O
deceased	O
to	O
struggle	O
and	O
get	O
away	O
when	O
you	O
would	O
have	O
kept	O
him	O
in	O
the	O
room	O
after	O
he	O
received	O
the	O
blow	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
not	O
tell	O
.	O
After	O
the	O
prisoner	O
had	O
stabbed	O
him	O
,	O
he	O
went	O
directly	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
room	O
;	O
where	O
he	O
went	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Q	O
.	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
any	O
blood	O
?	O
Robertson	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
some	O
on	O
my	O
shirt	O
.	O
Thomas	B-pers
Freeman	I-pers
.	O
Betwixt	O
8	O
and	O
9	O
o'clock	O
on	O
Friday	O
night	O
last	O
,	O
I	O
had	O
almost	O
done	O
supper	O
,	O
I	O
heard	O
a	O
man	O
by	O
my	O
door	O
cry	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
stabbed	O
,	O
I	O
am	O
stabbed	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
out	O
.	O
They	O
knowing	O
I	O
had	O
been	O
constable	O
,	O
came	O
to	O
me	O
and	O
cry	O
'd	O
,	O
for	O
God	O
's	O
sake	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Sinderbury	O
has	O
killed	O
a	O
man	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
and	O
asked	O
where	O
he	O
was	O
,	O
I	O
was	O
told	O
he	O
was	O
run	O
up	O
stairs	O
,	O
they	O
desired	O
I	O
would	O
not	O
go	O
up	O
,	O
for	O
he	O
says	O
,	O
he	O
will	O
kill	O
the	O
first	O
man	O
that	O
comes	O
to	O
him	O
;	O
I	O
went	O
into	O
his	O
lower	O
room	O
and	O
asked	O
for	O
a	O
stick	O
,	O
I	O
found	O
